March 5
[The culprit who framed Kageyama Reina is a teacher of Kaio High School.]
[The fake video's client is Kaio High's teacher?]
Mind Voice viewers, good morning! This is Hiiragi.
I'm currently looking for the culprit who drove Kageyama Reina to suicide.
That cuplrit is one of Kaio High School's teachers.
Whoaaa!! He has showed up!
Hiiragi Ibuki, a video call!
Guys!  It's the real Ibuki! LOL
He's simply an ikemen. LMAO
Sorry. I'm in love...
That murder teacher has showed up so shamelessly!
Is this some kind of crime show performance? He watches too much dramas. Lol
[Now that he has suddenly showed up, it's getting more interesting!]
[Hiiragi is looking for the teacher who drove the student to suicide?]
[Once he knows the culprit, will it be game over?]
It seems that the culprit is one of the teachers, right?
-  Well, that's...
- It's impossible for a Kaio High School's teacher to be the culprit.
I believe in my colleagues.
Believe in English is "Believe".
[Simple question. Why is Hiiragi doing this barricade thing?]
[Can he just simply asking the police to solve it?]
Where are you going?
I'm already dismissed from the investigation.
Stand up.
I will start my class.
Bow.
Sit down.
From now on,
we will start the game 'Believe it or Not'~!
He has finally gone crazy.
What is that?
Believe it!
Or not!
Is your fake video's client among these people?
Yes, exactly like that!
Hiiragi Ibuki is the suspect of this hostage-taking and barricade incident.
It has entered its 5th day today.
It's still...
- It's really delicious.
- A delicious meal after a long time...
- Okay, go ahead~!
- We're going now!
[Being held hostages by their own homeroom teacher, they must be in a mental breakdown.]
[I think it's not the time to search for the culprit, right...]
[It's also a lie that all the students are still alive, right.]
[If your classmates were killed in front of you, you'd lose your shit.]
[They would definitely be traumatized, right.]
Yeay~! Let's have fun, guys~!
Let's dance!
Isn't Hiiragi contradicting himself by doing this?
[He killed way too many people just to uncover the truth behind the suicide. LOL]
[You can't justify murder no matter what the reason is.]
[Hiiragi Ibuki = A mass murderer confirmed.]
Fuel-dropping.
[This is Hiiragi. None of the students are dead.]
[It's today's newspaper. That means it's real?]
He acts as a bad guy to reveal the hidden truth behind Kageyama Reina...
[The devil teacher is not devil after all. He's just a teacher.]
[Hiiragi Ibuki is perhaps a hero?]
The Hero's part...
...has begun~!
English Subtitle by eveychooey.
3 Nen A Gumi: Ima kara Mina-san wa, Hitojichi Desu.
3rd Grade A Class : From Now on, You Are Hostages.
It's cool.
Right?
This is Garm Phoenix, right?
Right.
I can be revived so many times!
Then, how to defeat you...
The Garm Phoenix suit actor is Fighter Tanaka who had retracted his retirement statement,
and suddenly decided to take the leading role.
That's the story behind it.
March 6
- You're so well-informed.
- What was that again...?
- The protagonist's signature phrase...?
- It's time to go back to your seat!
All right, stand up!
I will start my class today.
Bow.
Sit down.
[We've been deceived by Sensei. Lol]
Who posted this on SNS this morning?
Yuki...
I told you not to post anything on SNS until further instruction is issued.
- But, I got so many followers...
- That's not the problem.
I'm sorry.
Then, let's make it more exciting, shall we?
Did you see Hiiragi Ibuki's post?
We are also flustered...
We can't believe he treats us like criminals.
Then...
- Do you have any clue?
- Of course not.
That's just his trick!
Hiiragi-sensei is calling me!
Camera! Get closer!
Right now, Hiiragi-sen...sei...
Sorry! I'll pick it up right now.
Please get out!
Hiiragi-sensei?
Good morning~!
Can you please let the other teachers hear my voice too?
Okay.
Please speak.
Guys,
You must have been surprised at my sudden announcement the other day, right?
What are you thinking?
- Spreading that kind of rumor!
- It's not a rumor.
One of you is the culprit who asked Bermuzu to make Kageyama Reina's fake video.
You have seen the attached customers list's image too, right?
There's no way we could believe that!
That's right! None of us is the culprit!
I also wanted to think like that...
So, today, I would like to give you a task!
A task?
I want the "hunter", who had asked Berumuzu to make Kageyama Reina's fake video, to confess at 8 pm today.
If that person doesn't confess, I will blow up the class.
- What are you saying?!
-  Our students' lives...
...depend on you, guys.
I'll be waiting for the good news!
Bye!
Hiiragi-sensei!
What do you mean by that?
Just like I said.
I'll blow up the class if the "hunter" doesn't confess.
You will evacuate us first...
...right?
Why aren't you saying anything?
- We're on the same team, aren't we?
- Don't get the wrong idea.
I have no intention of becoming your alliance.
I asked you to cooperate with me by offering you lives, so that I could find the truth. That's all.
Okay, stop using your phones!
It's risky to let you keep your phones after all.
I'm gonna collect your bags and phones now.
I feel somewhat nostalgic!
Okay, this is the last!
You won't kill us, right?
I'm afraid I have to do that if they can't fulfill my request.
Then...
If none of the teachers confesses as the culprit,
...we will die?
- Binggo! As an ex insider, you're truly understand this conversation.
However, I feel sorry for you because all you can do is wait without doing anything.
Then, do you guys want to try persuading your teachers?
Maybe you can touch the culprit's heart by begging desperately for your lives.
Don't be silly.
Listen.
Do not see things only from the surface.
Do not ignore the essence..
Let's think.
Ah! I'll help you!
Ha~
Thank you. Put it there.
Okay.
I'm sure...
...Berumuzu was asked to do it.
Why do you know about that?
I heard about it before...
...from that person.
I'm sorry to bother you again...
- I need to talk to Fumika-san about something.
- I won't allow that.
- Please go.
- Wait a minute!
Why did Fumika-san think...
...it was probably her fault that this barricade incident happened?
- Even if you ask me that...
- Dad!
- Why can't you tell him?
- Just get back inside!
Why...?
Ibuki is doing that for me, right?
- Then, isn't it better to tell the detective...
- Can you just shut up!
Please don't bother us anymore.
What's the matter?
Then,
Starting from now, I'm going to look for the culprit who requested Reina's fake video.
Hey, why are you the moderator, Sakura?
She's back to being a slave?
She volunteered herself.
She's right!
In order to find out the truth about Reina,
I thought I should move first.
It's fine, then.
After listening to your opinions,
we end up with these 5 candidates.
Here!
- I don't think the principal is one of them.
- Well, he could be.
I heard that the principal was complaining about Kageyama before.
He was annoyed by the press that kept coming in and out to visit a star athlete.
Then...
For now, let's call him "Jay White".
- Jay?
- Jay white?
What's that?
The next suspect is Morisaki-sensei.
- Morisaki-sensei was interested in Bookie, so, there's a possibility.
- Really?
I didn't know about it at all.
You don't understand women~
That's what's cute about you, though.
Ha?
If she thought of Kageyama as her rival,
she could be the one who ordered the fake video.
A strong candidate...
Then she is "Juice Robinson".
Juice?
Wait!
You've been labeling them as "Jay White", "Juice Robinson"..?
What's that?
Of course they're the wrestlers of NJPW*.
* New Japan Pro Wrestling.
I thought it would be easier to compare them with the New Japan Cup's candidates.
We don't understand! Just do it normally!
Okay.
Then,
- What about the 3rd candidate : Sakuma-sensei...?
- To put it simply,
He's gross!
- Right.
- Ah~ That's understandable.
He used to smirk at Reina a lot.
"I want to make Kageyama mine and mine only."
He wanted to possess her.
How gross...
Then...
He's a 'circle'*!
* A 'Yes' symbol
The next candidate is Takechi-sensei.
I don't see any relation between Takechi and Reina, though.
No! He was hitting on her quite passionately.
It's about the recommendation!
She was asked if she wanted to get recommended to college.
Well, in the end, she chose a different desired college,
so that story started to spread.
Seo was also getting a recommended by Takechi, right?
Yeah.
Takechi is the type who's just "all talk, no result".
Isn't it natural for him to do that?
Then...
He's an 'X' mark.
The last one : Tsuboi-sensei!
I guess...
- He's the most suspicious one, right?
- Really?
He was the one behind our powerful swimming club.
- Isn't it better to ask the swimming club members?
- Well...
He has a harsh personality indeed.
There were quite a lot of students who were afraid of Tsuboi-sensei and decided to quit.
Btw, Suzune, you were in swimming club too before, right?
Yes.
Until the summer of 2nd grade.
I quit because of him.
I want to throw up just by thinking about it.
That far?
- What's the reason?
- I was caught dating with Ren.
He was spreading out our pictures in front everyone
He said, " I don't need you."
He changed his attitude towards his favorite student because she had a boyfriend?
He's the worst.
I'm sure he was interested in Reina too.
But,
Since Reina didn't like him, he made that fake video...
- There's no proof.
- Right.
Reina was able to meet Sensei's expectation.
You're saying I wasn't able to?
- I didn't mean...
- If you're an underachiever, you have no right to talk big like that!
You don't even know how I felt when I had to quit.
- Wait a minute!
- Wait! Karen! Please calm down.
I'm from class 1C, my name is Minakoshi Suzune.
Nice to meet you.
Isn't she cute?
Not only she's cute, but also the top prize winner in the city center district.
I'm from class 1B, my name is Kageyama.
She's Kageyama Reina?
I heard she's at the national level.
Don't lose focus!
Don't slack off!
Move your whole body more!
Okay
- Improve your next move!
- Okay.
- Do one more lap!
Tsuboi-sensei...
He's so enthusiastic about Minakoshi.
I heard she's also getting closer to Reina's record.
Right.
Sorry!
- You've been waiting?
- I'm already used to it.
Going home late again after practice, right?
Yes.
Because I don't want to lose to Reina.
What's the matter?
My chest has been hurting lately...
Good morning.
Miyakoshi.
Yes.
Starting tomorrow, you don't have to come again.
Last monday,
Why did you ditch practice?
- I didn't ditch it...
- You were with Nakao, right?
No! That's not true.
I went to the hospital...
A flirting girl like you,
even if you come to practice, you will only annoy me!
I don't want to...
...coach you again for the rest of my life!
Yosh! Let's start the practice!
Okay.
Hurry up!
Leave me alone!
If you get caught, you'll be in trouble.
Please...
...don't tell anyone.
Then...
Will you obey my words?
He?
The culprit is you!
Why am I the culprit??
Nobody said you did it, Morisaki-sensei.
But your eyes say otherwise!
That's why the students hate you.
So, after all, the culprit is...
..probably you..?
What the hell was that?
Tsuboi-sensei gets more hate from the students than I do!
Why me??
I heard the rumor! There are a lot of sexual and power harassment!
I get it!
- You're the culprit.
- Don't be silly!
I trained them like that to make them stronger!
Can you say that you did it purely for the students??
Please calm down!
Are you saying that you are somehow the culprit?
Who benefits from this drama??!
I came to take our dinner.
Over there.
Okay.
That's the ladies' room!
Isn't that voyeurism?
It's only the washroom.
Be quiet!
Minakoshi-san and Yuki-san!
What are they doing?
I'm a Class-3A student at Kaio High School, a former swimming club member, Minakoshi Suzune.
The swimming club's adviser, Tsuboi-sensei, had been sexually harassing and abusing his power over me.
As soon as he knew that I was dating this one guy,
he didn't let me practice anymore.
I was forced to quit.
I think he must have done the same thing to Reina, too.
The person behind the fake video,
must be Tsuboi-sensei.
That video,
please upload it on Mind Voice.
Is it really true, though?
I'm sure Tsuboi will never turn himself in.
That's why I'm using the internet to corner him.
If he doesn't admit that he's the culprit, we will be killed!
That's true...
If you post that video, you'll get a lot of followers.
You will get a lot of attention too.
You won't stop her?
Or,
Is Tsuboi-sensei really the culprit?
Sensei, how much do you know about it?
Do you know the person who drove Reina into suicide?
Too many questions!
Can you just narrow it down to 1?
Then...
Is your goal...
...to catch the culprit?
My goal is...
...beyond that.
Beyond that...
What about dinner? Your friends are waiting for you.
I...
...believe in you, Sensei.
Bye.
I'll excuse myself.
It's here!
Hiiragi Ibuki's origin.
He worked at the movie studio?
It was his part time job while still an art school student.
*Special effects
He seemed to be in charge of doing the modeling for Tokusatsu* heroes and monsters' designs, but...
I heard he also started acting as a suit actor that relied so much on physical abilities.
Suit actor?
Anyway, let's get in!
What is a "suit actor"?
Those words are only used in Japan.
Even though we hide our faces,
we're still actors after all.
He is...
... a fighter, Tanaka-san, he's a legend of Tokusatsu* world.
*Special effects
The Tokusatsu movie that Fighter Tanaka and Hiiragi Ibuki co-starred in...
...is this one!
Look!
"IVKI" is written here. right?
You're right.
Was he also a hero?
Of course not.
He was a villain.
That yellow one.
What kind of person was Hiiragi Ibuki?
He was a serious guy.
Both acting and action, he did it very seriously.
He looked like a person who would never commit a crime.
It's like...
Even if the world turned into his enemy,
he would still fight for someone.
He was like a Hero of Justice.
Even after this thing happened,
you still can believe him?
Of course.
He has strong muscles.
When I thought about retiring,
I wanted to hand over the leading role to him in the next project.
It's this, right?
Garm Phoenix.
But, the main actor is certainly you, right?
Yeah...
He has stopped acting.
Why is that?
He's sick.
It's cancer.
So, he gave up being an action actor.
And with Fumika-chan...
He was taking the same path as his teacher girlfriend.
By "Fumika-chan", do you mean...
...Sagara Fumika-san?
Yes.
Do you know her?
Whether I know her or not,
she's our President's daughter after all.
President?
He's the company president of this movie studio.
Sagara Takahiko.
Gunji-san...
These things...
Well.. Do you know whether these were made here or not?
The time has come!
Your number one suspect is Tsuboi-sensei, huh?
By the way, Minakoshi,
I saw your video.
It caused amazing reactions on the internet.
What video?
I'm a Class-3A student at Kaio High School,
a former swimming club member, Minakoshi Suzune.
The swimming club's adviser, Tsuboi-sensei, had been sexually harassing and abusing his power over me.
The person behind the fake video,
must be Tsuboi-sensei.
Once people see this video,
they must think of Tsuboi-sensei as the culprit, right?
Why did you do something like this?
I didn't tell any lies...
I was only stating my opinions!
What's wrong with that?
Whoa...  People are bashing Tsuboi-sensei all over the internet.
It serves him right...
It's connected.
- Are you connected to the internet?
- Yeah. Somehow.
Hiiragi-sensei also wanted to make a video call so suddenly.
Everyone has been on edge since a while ago.
They even fought with each other.
They seem to be calm now, though.
I want to give out my photo album that will be released tomorrow, finally it....
Hey!
What are you doodling...?
What kind of drawing skill is this?
Stop playing with these pins!
You're awful!
It will pierce through the next pages too...
You look very calm...
Of course I do!
That kind of customers list can't be used as an evidence.
Hiiragi-Sensei is calling!
Guys~!
Long time no see~!
It's almost 8 pm!
The person who asked Berumuzu to make Kageyama Reina's fake video, a.k.a "hunter"-san!
Please come forward!
Hiiragi-sensei, I don't know what kind of joke you're pulling now,
But there's no such a person here!
Is that so? What a pity!
Then...
I will blow up the class now!
Wait a minute!
Let's talk about it properly.
Hiiragi!
Stop doing stupid things! Do you think you can get away after doing something like this??!
Tsuboi-sensei!
I think you're the one...
...who can't get away so easily~!
What do you mean?
According to the students' predictions,
Tusboi-sensei seems to be the culprit.
What did you say?
Oi, Minakoshi! Come here!
You think Tsuboi-sensei is the culprit, right?
Try to persuade him yourself!
Sensei...
You're the one who asked Berumuzu to make Reina's fake video, right?
What are you saying?
- I could never do that...!
- Tell me honestly!!
Otherwhise, we will die!!
- I told you it's not me!
- You're lying!
Just like when you pushed me into a corner,
you must have done it to Reina too!
Though it was only that one day...
...I was absent from practice.
Though I only went to the hospital...
Why did you snatch away swimming from me??
I liked swimming...
I worked harder than everyone else...
Even so, why...?
Minakoshi...
You felt annoyed by my relationship with Ren, right?
You kicked me out because you couldn't have me, right??
As for Reina, because you knew she wasn't interested in you, you decided to corner her just like me!
Am I wrong?
Why aren't you saying anything!
You're wrong.
Tsuboi-sensei...
I think...
...you should tell her the truth.
What do you mean...?
...by "The truth"?
What's the truth? Tell me!
It was no doubt...
...that you worked harder than everyone else.
Every single day...
You practiced till late.
In muscle training too,
among the students I trained,
you were the most hard-working one.
But...
That wouldn't do...
What do you mean?
That day,
when you were absent from practice,
your mom contacted me.
We were both...
...listening to your doctor's explanation.
Suzune-san...
...suffers from exercise-induced lethal arrhythmia*.
*Life-threatening abnormal heartbeats that are triggered by exercise.
Lethal?
The arrhythmia was caused by excessive practice.
If she keeps practicing like that, I'm afraid it may cause her to faint and go into cardiac arrest.
So,
From now on, please prevent her from doing heavy exercise.
No way...
Please...
She is going to take part in the next tournament!
Somehow...
Somehow I want her to participate!
I'm sorry but...
If she keeps being an athlete, she may lose her life.
I...
...was asked by your mother to persuade you.
She said even if she told you to stop,
you would still take part in the tournament.
But...
I thought you would do the same even if I was the one who told you.
I couldn't think of...
...any other way than that.
What the hell was that?
Are you saying you did it all for me?
But...
As a result,
you were hurt because of that.
I'm really...
...sorry!
I feel cheated...
Why are you only telling me this now?
That can't be true!
Minakoshi.
After listening to his explanation,
do you still suspect him?
I didn't know!
I didn't know anything about my own health and what Sensei was suffering from!
Even so, you...
...mistakenly resented Tsuboi-sensei,
and took that video.
What should I do...?
With that video...?
What should I do?
This video wasn't posted on the internet.
I stopped Yuki just before she posted it.
[The truth about a Kaio High School's teacher.]
What a pity!
Yuki, bring your phone here right now!
I'm sorry.
He told me not to say anything.
What...?
What a relief!
How is it a relief??
How is it a relief ?
The fact that...
...you tried to spread that video all over the internet doesn't change, does it?
- But...
- Don't say "but"!
If that video spread all over the world,
what would happen to Tsuboi-sensei??
Have you carefully thought about that?
HUH?
Did you think about that?
Because of your careless statements,
You could turn innocent people into someone they're not!
Stigmatize him!
His family!
His friends!
They could have been hurt.
You...
...tried to do something that can never be recovered, RIGHT?
Do you understand??
That's enough!
It couldn't be helped!
It didn't happen in the end, please forgive her already!
- That's right.
- Suzune has showed her regret...
- Wake up!
What do you mean "it couldn't be helped"? Oi.
What do you mean by "regret"???
All of you...
You see things halfheartedly.
PLEASE CHANGE!
What went wrong?
Don't only see things from the surface!
Think carefully!!
What's happening in front of you,
See it properly with your eyes!
Put it in your head!
Carve it in your heart!
If you don't do that, you will keep repeating the same mistake over and over again, right?
If you turn away from the essence, it won't work out!
Right? Minakoshi!
Are you listening? I'm talking to you!
Minakoshi, Oi!
I'm saying that to you!
Have you put it properly in your head? Huh?
Have you properly carved it in your heart? Are you listening?
You guys...
...are not at the age where...
...you can make mistakes based on your emotions anymore.
You're not at the age to be allowed to do that!
Think!
Think! Think!
Answer me!!
That's why,
For your own words!
For your own actions!
Be more responsible for it!
Listen.
Your single foolish word...
...might be able to save someone.
But, on the other hand,
don't forget that someone might get hurt too because of that.
A single word from you...!
...could easily...
...take someone else's life!
Don't forget that!
Do you understand!?
You guys too, don't ever forget that!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I just gave them a good lesson thanks to all of you~!
However,
A promise is a promise..
As a punishment for not confessing to me,
I will blow up the class.
Didn't I tell you?
I won't forgive you for not fulfilling my request.
Hiiragi-sensei!
Please think again.
Until 8 pm, it's... 5!
- Hiiragi! Stop it!
- 4!
3!
- Hiiragi-sensei!
- 2!
STOP IT!
1!
It's such a shame.
No way...
How is it?
How's your feelings towards your murdered students?
HIIIIRRAGIIIII!!!
Just kidding~!
Please take a closer look at the blasted classroom.
Huh? It's class 3B!
The students are safe. Aren't you glad?
But...
What do people all over the world think about you, who had been running away to protect yourself until the students were killed?
[Self-protection is more important than their students' lives.]
Such shitty teachers. LOL
[I think I understood what Hiiragi Ibuki is fighting for.]
What was that?
Surprising us like that.
Sensei is too cruel!
That's not true.
Sensei has...
...given us the hint perfectly.
From now on,
we will start the game 'Believe it or Not'~!
What is that?
Believe me when I'm wearing my glasses.
Don't believe me when I take them off.
Understood?
When Sensei...
...was telling lies,
he wasn't wearing his glasses.
You've been noticing that?
Sakura, did you notice from the beginning?
Yes.
Why? You should have told us!
You should have told us sooner!
I'm sorry.
I thought...
...Sensei wanted you to notice it yourself.
When he said "think carefully",
"Don't only see things from the surface",
"Do not ignore the essence."
Ah! I just remembered!
Garm Phoenix's signature phrase!
Let's think!
Gunji-san!
During the past month, Sagara Takahiko...
...seems to have ordered some sculpted objects, and bought a large amount of explosives.
Just as I thought.
Hiiragi Ibuki and Sagara Takahiko are...
...related.
Yes.
What video is this?
Today is Tuesday, September 25.
[Is this the moment where Kageyama Reina committed suicide?]
[The man wearing a hat is the culprit?]
[Did he possibly kill Kageyama Reina???]
[Is that the "hunter"!?]
All right!
I finally tracked you down, "hunter"-san!
No.
Takechi Yamato-sensei.
Me?
Let's think!