(Episode 11)
I got the address.
The address was my shop.
What does this mean?
Okay. I'll be there right now.
Ga Hyeon!
(Flower)
Excuse me. Was this Ms. So Hye In?
Yes, she passed away.
It looked like there was a gas leak
from her heater.
We found soot on
the mucous membrane of her nose,
so it looks like...
she first passed out from the gas,
then she suffocated her to death.
We'll have to conduct
an autopsy to be sure.
Could this have been arson?
There's nothing I caught
in particular,
but we'll know for sure
after the NFS gives us the result.
Please do give us a call
as soon as the results are in.
Sure, I'll call you.
Do you think this happened
because we found out...
about the flower shop?
It was already addressed
to the flower shop.
Ms. So Hye In could've been
the target from the start.
But she didn't even reset.
So why?
Whoever that ordered it will know.
Did you find out
what the flower baskets mean?
You do know that...
Ms. So Hye In passed away, right?
- Who?
- The pregnant lady you invited.
Hye In, who didn't even reset,
just died...
after she got the message
with those flowers.
What are you talking about?
Will you keep denying it
even after you see this?
The one who sent the flowers
was Ms. Song Ji Hyun.
Ms. Song.
You're here, Mir.
Yes.
We're closed for the day.
I came to give you this.
To be exact, I'm sure
Ms. Song was acting on your order.
I have no idea what's going on.
Why do you keep denying this?
You wrote excerpts from
"Pieces of Destiny" and sent it.
"Pieces of Destiny"?
("Pieces of Destiny")
Ms. Song gave this to me.
We'll talk to her in person.
She suddenly quit yesterday.
This has never happened
in any other reset,
so I was quite flustered.
She said it was
for personal reasons,
so I couldn't pry anymore.
She disappeared...
as soon as we found out.
Is that what has happened?
I can't believe this.
She doesn't know
anything about these resets.
Are you 100 percent sure?
If she knows about Ms. So Hye In,
it means she also knows
what happened before the reset.
There's no way.
It's impossible for her to find out
unless I tell her.
What if you're lying?
Then everything is possible.
Since when were you
acquainted with Ms. Song Ji Hyun?
It has been a long time.
It was...
Mom.
Young.
Banana cha cha
Everyone sing
la, la, la, la, la, cha cha
Banana cha cha
Everyone sing
la, la, la, la, la, hoo
Mom, Mom
Yeah, it's so good
Mom, sing cha cha
Dad, Dad
Banana na
Yeah, buy one for me
Dad, sing cha cha
If it's long, it's a train, cha cha
Ms. Song Ji Hyun?
Is Ms. Song Ji Hyun here?
One second.
- Right here?
- Yes.
I wanted to ask you something.
Were you on your way
to the sanitarium?
Yes, I couldn't seem to
focus on my work.
Were you there yesterday too?
With your wife?
Yes, right.
I was there with her.
Anyway, what was it
that you wanted to say...
At the time of the explosion,
Detective Ji and I were...
in front of that flower shop.
And I saw you...
there.
Why...
were you there?
(Michael Clinic)
I know Ms. Song Ji Hyun very well.
She comes here once every week...
to volunteer.
Then was she especially close...
to someone who's in this clinic?
I'm not sure.
She's probably close to
other volunteers...
that she was trained with.
- One second.
- Okay.
But there weren't
a lot of volunteers...
during the beginning of this year.
What's the exact date?
(January 14, 2019,
signed by Song Ji Hyun)
It was January 14.
In other words,
exactly a week from today,
on January 11, 2020 at 11 a.m.,
you will be going back...
to January 11, 2019 at 11 a.m.
Three days after the reset?
In that case,
what about this person?
Do you know her too?
She used to work here, didn't she?
I think she was a psychiatrist.
Does Detective Ji know this?
No, I wanted to
check with you first.
I didn't want this
to be a misunderstanding.
Did you know that flower shop was...
- owned by Ms. So Hye In?
- No.
I was shocked when you just told me.
Then why were you there?
Mr. Hwang.
Well, do they know...
why a fire broke out
in that flower shop?
Does this fire...
have something to do with you?
I didn't want to
leave my wife in the sanitorium...
when I realized
I don't know when I'll die.
I took her home with me to spend
at least a few days together.
But that's when
everything went wrong.
That'll be 28 dollars.
All right.
- Here you go. Keep the change.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Wait.
Honey!
Excuse me,
but did you see a woman in her 60s?
No.
Hello?
Goodness, you.
How did you come all the way here?
She was in the neighborhood...
we used to live in
back when we were newlyweds.
Our house is gone.
- Let's go home.
- I finally found her.
- Honey. I...
- She told me something.
- Set it on fire.
- She said she set it something...
- on fire.
- We'll be okay.
She said we'd be okay.
I just brushed it off
as another delusion of hers.
Let's go home.
But a fire
actually broke out nearby.
I thought about reporting it.
But I just wasn't sure.
I didn't know
if she really did that...
or thought that way
after seeing those young kids.
If I reported it,
she'd be interrogated.
I wasn't sure whether
she'd be able to endure it.
When I heard that
it was Hye In's flower shop,
I couldn't report it even more.
I couldn't believe
the fate she faced...
just like those of yours
and Yeon Soo.
(Psychiatrist, Kim Soo Yeon)
It's been about three years.
Ever since she quit, we lost touch.
I heard that she moved abroad.
She's in charge of Zian Clinic.
- Didn't you know?
- Are you saying she's in Korea?
Yes.
I didn't think she'd work
as a doctor again.
Sorry? Why not?
She had a delicate heart.
Her best friend committed suicide,
and she couldn't move on.
She blamed herself...
for not being aware
of her friend's state...
when she was a psychiatrist herself.
After a few months,
she decided to quit.
Do you know who that friend was?
I'm not sure.
Do you know her?
She doesn't look familiar.
(Lee Shin, Song Ji Hyun)
I looked up some articles
about Zian Clinic.
("Interview with Mr. Kim Joon Hyuk
of Zian Clinic")
This was released last December.
It's not her.
And look.
It's a transfer of ownership.
(Certified Copy of Register)
She bought it on January 14.
She purchased it
right after the reset.
She needed the clinic...
in order to gain our trust
for the reset.
She lied about knowing Ms. Song
for a long time.
They first contacted each other
on January 11,
the day of the reset.
The date Ms. Song signed up
for Michael Clinic...
was January 14.
She knew about that clinic...
because she worked
at Sejin Hospital.
So everything was a lie.
She planned it all.
- Hey.
- Song Ji Hyun's phone turned on.
This way!
Ms. Song.
Why did you send the bouquets?
- I have no idea what you're...
- Was it Ms. Lee Shin's order?
I don't know anything.
I just delivered the cards
like she told me to.
What do those messages mean?
Why are people dying?
I'm sure you know that much.
Are you planning
to take all the blame?
People are dying.
Five people have died already.
- How many...
- Exactly.
Run away while you still have
the chance.
I don't know why you people
gather at Zian Clinic...
or why you're dying one at a time.
I don't want to know either.
But what I do know...
is that Lee Shin is capable
of anything.
It's as if she knows the future.
She knew everything about me.
I said what you told me to say.
But they'll soon find out
that it was a lie.
They'll find out the real reason
why you quit.
It doesn't matter.
She might even know
that you've found me.
If you want to live,
don't fight her.
Come with us.
If you can prove
that it was her doing...
It's already too late.
The 8:40 p.m. bus headed...
for Cheongdo will depart soon.
(We are closed for the time being.
Zian Clinic)
Mom, are we moving again?
No.
We're just playing hide-and-seek.
Where will we hide?
I'm not sure.
Where should we hide to make it fun?
Ms. Lee Shin...
has a daughter.
Resetting the time means...
the daughter will always be
the same age.
Any mother would want to watch
her kid grow up.
But she chose to reset instead.
And she purchased Zian Clinic...
right after the reset.
Why would she?
It's not like we're special.
Who knows? Maybe it had...
to be us.
The NFS hasn't announced
the result of the accident yet.
We'll have to wait a bit more.
Did you tell him about my wife?
No. You don't need to worry.
How is she doing?
Ever since that day,
her condition has worsened.
She couldn't even
recognize me yesterday.
No matter how many times
I think about this,
I don't think we met by coincidence.
That woman came to me
and brought us together.
Got it?
We should find out...
whether our encounters
were special or ill-fated.
Let's remove them.
What a waste.
(Director of Zian Clinic)
Park Young Gil.
Car accident on January 11.
Choi Kyung Man.
Heart attack on January 25.
"I hope sun's power gives you energy
and moon's power gives you rest."
Seo Yeon Soo. Fell on January 27.
"Let the rainbow of the soul
be in your garden."
Cha Jeung Seok.
Committed suicide on February 22.
"The gleaming golden glory
of the light will be with you."
So Hye In. Explosion on March 13.
"You will become the captain
of your life,"
"challenging your fate."
(Hwang No Sub, Bae Jung Tae)
(Ko Jae Young, Kim Se Rin)
(Shin Ga Hyeon)
(Lee Shin, Song Ji Hyun)
(Seo Yeon Soo)
(Kim Dae Sung)
(Cha Jeung Seok)
(Bae Jung Tae)
(Kim Dae Sung)
(Lee Shin)
(Song Ji Hyun)
(So Hye In)
Wait.
We all went to...
Mr. Choi Kyung Man's funeral.
And you checked Seo Yeon Soo
and Mr. Cha Jeung Seok's death...
yourself, didn't you?
We were on the scene
when Ms. So Hye In died.
(Flower)
Mr. Park Young Gil
who couldn't make it here today...
is dead.
There was someone
whom we couldn't check.
(Park Young Gil,
January 11, car accident)
So you're saying...
your elementary school friend's
alumnus' friend's cousin's...
sister's husband is Park Young Gil?
So just check...
if he's on the death list
from car accidents on January 11.
Exactly. Why do you need to check?
I'll treat you to Korean beef,
grade two pluses.
- Two pluses?
- Yes.
Let's see.
Park Young Gil. Park Young Gil.
Park Young Gil...
He's not on it.
He's nowhere in the death list.
He's not?
Hello?
Who are you?
We were born on the same day,
but I guess we had
different days of death.
I suggested
that we run a business together,
but he ended up dying like this
after he took up a driving job.
I saw that
Mr. Park Young Gil's death...
wasn't registered.
Is there a story?
It's all because of money.
When I went to file his death,
they told me I need to
pay back his debt at once.
I've been wondering...
if I should give up on
his inheritance or pay his debt.
Anyway, why do you need to see him?
By any chance,
do any of these people
ring any bells for you?
I'm not sure.
I think his colleagues
would know better.
We barely got some sleep at home,
and never really saw each other.
I'm not really sure.
Hey.
Did Young Soo say
anything bad about me?
What?
Young Gil died...
because of me.
What do you mean?
Wasn't it a car accident?
It was his day off,
but he had been delivering
in my area with my car.
It was my daughter's recital,
so I asked him to fill in for me.
Then this is...
It's his car.
I've been driving it thinking
he left it behind for me.
Goodbye, then.
Did you know that
Ms. Lee Shin has a kid?
So what?
You knew.
How much do you know?
Do you also know why she invited us?
If you need information,
you need to pay.
We're all about to die.
Why do you want money?
Then maybe I should
stop looking for that guy.
I'm going to get
his facial composite tomorrow,
but should I stop here?
Why do you think...
those people died?
Do you think good people...
suddenly died without any reason?
Are you saying
they paid for their sins?
I never said that.
You must have sinned a lot.
Are you scared that...
you might be next?
Are you?
I like how quickly
you made this decision.
What do you need me to do?
It might be a little difficult,
and you may not understand.
But I will make sure...
I compensate you handsomely.
I promise.
The cooler of her refrigerator
for flowers became overheated.
The circuit breaker got loose,
so it didn't get shut off either.
Your wife misunderstood.
I can finally die...
on a clear conscience.
Thank you, Ga Hyeon.
Thank you, Detective.
If something like this had happened,
you should've told me already.
What if this turned into
an arson case?
He thought this over
many times as well.
He didn't want to
put you in a tight spot,
so he couldn't tell you.
Hey, I'm very sorry.
It's nothing for you to apologize.
Anyway,
did you find out anything?
Not yet.
Goodness.
We're all living in fear
without knowing the reason.
Do you think someone
who knows everything...
thinks this is nothing
but fun entertainment?
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Ms. Shin!
- Hello.
- Seung Min.
What brings you here at this hour?
Well...
You suddenly said
you're taking a hiatus,
so our company is in huge chaos.
My team leader got mad at me
and blamed me...
for not taking good care of you.
Gosh, that's awful of him.
I already said
I had personal reasons.
Is something going on?
I should know as your manager...
to cover for you and help you out.
That's why I'm here.
I already sent a few files,
so you can continue to publish
for a couple months.
Then will you return
within two months?
He asked me to make sure we
won't have to announce your hiatus.
I'll talk to your team leader.
It's not your fault,
so don't be discouraged.
Please excuse me.
Hello?
Ga Hyeon.
You meet your boyfriend every day.
Isn't it okay to skip a day?
This is my first
housewarming party ever.
I pushed it back...
until he had time to come.
I'll celebrate with you
in his place, so stop crying.
Anyway, why did you move?
Wouldn't it be better
to stay with your parents?
I'm mostly alone at home anyway.
And it's reassuring to have
my boyfriend next door.
You should worry about yourself.
Aren't you scared
to be alone in that huge house?
I'm a woman who draws
a knife fight every single day.
And I have good security
because that place is expensive.
You're so cool.
Ga Hyeon, you seem
just like my sister.
You're pretty, nice,
and smart, someone who's
too good to be true.
Well.
I get that pretty often.
It must be pretty tough
because of that.
You always have to be the best.
You always have to
live up to other people's standards.
I looked up your interview,
and you said
you even get volvulus...
when you don't get
the first place for ratings.
You did my background check too?
I'm saying...
I learned to understand my sister
thanks to you.
That even winners of life...
have troubles
losers like us can't imagine.
We're all just people.
If I had known that
before my sister died,
it would've been great.
Something like that.
Cheers.
(Zolid: Sleep inducer)
I'll get a housewarming gift for you
later. Let me know what you need.
Really? May I ask for anything?
Something really expensive?
Sure, something very expensive.
I think this is it.
It's this one. Bye, then.
Go home safely!
Bye-bye!
(Magpie)
Someone is calling you.
Magpie? Hey, why is
Magpie calling you? Why?
- Why is that?
- My gosh.
Hold on a second. Wait.
What's going on with you?
I know you do whatever you want,
but you don't do shortcuts.
Why is the thug from
the detective agency calling you?
- Why is he calling you?
- Why are you beating him up again?
- Gosh, he just got...
- Captain Heo!
Goodness. It's...
- This came for you.
- Thank you.
What's that? What did you get?
(Zian Clinic)
(Detective Ji Hyeong Ju,
Seoul Makang Police Station)
(Kim Se Rin, Royal Studio)
Hello.
Goodness. Thank you.
(Zian Clinic)
(Hwang No Sub)
(Ko Jae Young)
(Shin Ga Hyeon)
(You will be the star
of the guardian and light the dark.)
Yes, we got it too.
You'll stay at the cafe, right?
I'll call you as soon
as we find anything.
("Rest on the Flight into Egypt"
By Rembrandt)
(You will be the star
of the guardian and light the dark.)
Did you find it?
Yes.
What's the point though?
We don't know what this means.
Looking at Hye In's card,
it didn't represent her death.
And the painting didn't
make sense either.
And all the lines are
as abstract as they can be.
Why is this happening to us?
I'm sure this means something.
We're being invited
to play this game.
(Seo Yeon Soo, died from a fall,
Cha Jeung Seok, suicide)
(Chapter 3, Star of the Guardian)
(Volume 27, Song of the Light)
Hold on.
What is it?
Look.
Chapter 3, Volume 27.
March 27.
(You will become the captain of
your life, challenging your fate.)
Chapter 3, Volume 13.
March 13.
That's the date
of Hye In's accident.
(So Hye In, March 13)
Cha Jeung Seok...
(Cha Jeung Seok, February 22)
(The gleaming golden glory
of the light will be with you.)
- Chapter 2, Volume 22.
(Let the rainbow of the soul
be in your garden.)
Chapter 1, Volume 27.
(Seo Yeon Soo, January 27)
(I hope sun's power gives you energy
and moon's power gives you rest.)
(Chapter 1, Volume 25)
Chapter 1, Volume 25.
(Choi Kyung Man, January 25)
It was the date.
The date of their death.
March 27.
It's today.
Then,
will one of us die again?
There are so many stars, right?
Yes.
Young, which constellation
is your favorite?
Leo.
Leo?
Yes.
Se Rin.
My gosh, please pick up.
- Did you reach him?
- He's not answering.
Did something already happen to him?
Keep trying. Call me
as soon as he answers.
- Where are you going?
- I must check on Bae Jung Tae.
Hyeong Ju.
I'll be careful.
Ga Hyeon, don't go outside.
Stay here.
Please stay inside.
Mr. Bae Jung Tae?
Text me Bae Jung Tae's
phone number. Now!
What? Why?
Darn it.
Gosh, what's going on?
Se Rin, where are you?
Ga Hyeon, I think someone
is following me.
Where's your boyfriend?
Did you call the police?
I called both of them just now.
I'm so scared.
Get inside your house right now.
Se Rin.
Se Rin, are you there?
(Kim Se Rin)
Why did you call me out
at this hour? What's going on?
I'll explain it all later.
- Ga Hyeon? Follow me!
- What?
- Do you really want to die?
- Mr. Bae Jung Tae!
Se Rin! Se Rin!
Are you okay?
- Hyeong Ju, check on Ga Hyeon.
- Okay.
Royal Studio, Room 716
in Sinyeong-dong. Hurry!
- Se Rin!
- Bae Jung Tae ran away! Catch him!
Se Rin. Se Rin.
Se Rin. Are you okay?
Stop! Stop!
The suspect is on the run.
You should've stayed still.
Stay still.
What are you? Why are you...
Let's go.
Sun Ho.
Sun Ho! Sun Ho!
Wake up. Sun Ho.
Sun Ho!
Excuse me.
Did that man look familiar to you?
No.
She did mention a stalker.
She was nervous because she felt
like she was being followed.
This is it. Which room is it?
- Room 576.
- Room... There it is.
Goodness.
- Are you okay?
- Hello, sir.
What did the doctor say?
Do you need to go
to a bigger hospital?
What's happened to your leg?
- Did you break your leg?
- No, it's just fractured.
I just need to rest for some time.
My goodness!
When I heard you lost consciousness,
I expected the worst.
Exactly. Do you know how shocked
our Lieutenant Jin was?
What?
"Our Lieutenant Jin"?
Since when
have you been calling her that?
Since when?
Goodness, look at your hand.
- It must hurt.
- I scraped it.
Hyeong Ju.
- Did you catch Bae Jung Tae?
- How's Se Rin?
She was moved to a room just now.
Thankfully,
the wounds aren't serious.
We caught him.
You should've stayed home.
Why did you come outside?
Aren't you scared?
I am.
I'm afraid of dying as well.
But...
do you know
what scares me even more?
It's when people die...
right before my eyes.
I see the people I could've saved...
in my dreams every night.
They ask why...
I'm still alive...
and why I failed to save them.
They ask me that every night.
So...
I thought Se Rin would meet
the same fate.
That's how I feel as well.
Losing a partner once again...
is too terrifying.
Are you talking about me?
Other people may not think that way,
but we're still partners.
We even have our own headquarters.
It's the next day.
Everyone's still alive.
If Sun Ho had died,
I would've killed you myself.
Do you understand?
That's exactly why...
he shouldn't have chased
an innocent man.
You scumbag.
"Innocent"? How can you say that
after what you did to Se Rin?
I've done nothing wrong.
That wench was determined
to set me up.
Ms. Lee Shin ordered you
to kill her, didn't you?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Where is she?
- Hyeong Ju!
What are you doing?
Are you okay? That darn man...
Who appointed that lawyer for him?
Don't you know
that he has the right to have one?
- You're just letting him squirm...
- How will he squirm out of this?
I wouldn't be surprised
if he and his lawyer plan...
to shorten his sentence.
So...
I'll take care of this.
You stay out of this.
He'll say you coerced him.
Don't give him a reason to get out.
You can take this after 10 minutes.
Okay.
What about your meal? Did you eat?
You've been eyeing Bae Jung Tae.
You finally got him.
What's your relationship
with the victim?
She seems to be Ga Hyeon's friend.
How long do you need to stay here?
They need to observe me
for 3 to 4 weeks.
Come on. I asked you
a question first.
Why are you deflecting my question?
You seem fine.
Bye.
Come on, answer my questions
when I ask them.
It's frustrating for me.
The message was the date of death?
That's why I called you.
That means...
I could have really died.
Did you hear
why Bae Jung Tae attacked you?
Or anything about Ms. Lee Shin?
No.
For the past few days,
I did feel
that someone was following me.
But I didn't think I was right.
I had no idea
that it was that ex-convict.
What?
Murderer?
Do all ex-convicts murder people?
People like you
look down on the others.
Seriously.
Se Rin.
Young Woong.
Who are you?
Young Woong!
Do you really want to die?
Mr. Bae Jung Tae!
If it weren't for you,
I really might have died yesterday.
What about your parents?
You still didn't call them?
It's better that they don't know.
If they find out I was attacked,
I might have to move back home.
Do you think Se Rin
could have died yesterday?
If so,
you saved her, Ga Hyeon.
What did Bae Jung Tae say?
He's denying all the charges.
He said he didn't hit her
or do anything wrong.
And that Ms. Lee Shin
didn't order him to do so.
If she didn't order him to do that,
how did we end up getting
those messages?
Do you think the messages
don't mean the date of death?
We've been given a test
that doesn't have answers.
And the person
who gave out the test...
has disappeared.
(Lee Shin,
Ji Hyeong Ju, Shin Ga Hyeon)
Wait. Are you telling me that
we don't even know where she went?
Yes.
Game over.
(Automatic transfer of fund)
- Hyeong Ju.
- You're back.
- Sa Kyung.
- Hello.
- I'm back.
- Captain Heo.
I came back to work after a month!
- Sun Ho.
- Sun Ho, congratulations!
- I missed you.
Why are you curious about that?
I want to go to Russia.
I want to eat sausages in Germany.
- German beer! I love sausages.
- That sounds good, doesn't it?
In 1, 2, 3.
What is it?
Iced coffee. It's hot.
What about you?
Do you want to share it?
You got something over here.
You're so cute.
Drink this. I made it.
It's hot!
In 1, 2, 3.
Nose. Nose. There, nose.
Come here.
How adorable.
Good dog!
("Pieces of Destiny")
(We are closed for the time being.
Zian Clinic)
(7 months later)
Sa Kyung, what are you going
to do with Soon Woo?
- What do you mean?
- If you're not interested in him,
I'll hand him over
to the Traffic Department.
There's a line of women
who want to date Soon Woo.
You should do that. Set him up with
a new post too while you're at it.
My gosh, you're quite an actress.
This is why I had no idea
until I got a wedding invitation.
- What are you talking about?
- It's nothing.
What wedding invitation?
- My gosh. He's so annoying.
- Yes.
Hey, we need to go.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Okay.
- Soon Woo,
why did you leave without me?
I just stepped out for a moment.
Okay.
Thank you for your help, everyone.
- What's this case?
- Name, Jang Jin Ho.
A missing person's report
was filed on him seven months ago.
A few days after the report,
only the fallen vehicle
was discovered at Woonjeong Lake.
There wasn't any blood in the car.
After falling,
he probably tried to escape.
But he got swept away
in the current.
They already came to
a tentative conclusion.
He drifted down pretty far.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- 2, 3.
(Handong Logistics)
Hold on. What's his name?
Jang Jin Ho.
(ID card, Jang Jin Ho)
(Handong Logistics)
Young Gil died because of me.
When was the missing
person's report filed?
March 27.
(Chapter 3, Volume 27.)
(Handong Logistics)
It was after the loading the boxes.
He got in the accident
on the route he always takes.
So we couldn't believe it either.
He could've driven that route
with his eyes closed.
What? Park Young Gil's
replacement died?
Yes. His name is Jang Jin Ho.
The date of the missing person's
report was March 27.
According to our investigation,
it's highly likely that he died...
on the day of his disappearance.
Then, the date on the last card...
was pointing
at Jang Jin Ho's death?
After Park Young Gil died,
Jang Jin Ho
took over his district...
as well as his truck.
So if Park Young Gil was alive,
it's very likely that he might
have faced the same accident.
In the end, the date of death
on the card was correct.
You all remember
the first phone call...
from Ms. Lee Shin, right?
It was the train derailment.
Tomorrow morning at 11:34.
KTX 738 from Busan bound to Seoul
will be derailed.
When a certain date comes,
I go back to the past...
and relive my life again.
I knew the train number
because I had already seen it...
on the news.
She told me she knew it because
she did the reset several times.
Ms. Lee Shin knew
the dates of deaths...
because she already knew
about their deaths.
What are you talking about?
They were all alive.
What if it wasn't before the reset?
But the life before the reset?
What?
What if she observed us, so she knew
what would happen to us...
in advance?
That's right.
All of you...
were...
dead.
(Handong Logistics)
(327th Lottery, Price: 5 dollars)
(365: Repeat the Year)
I don't have any resentment
against you.
I just have a lot of time.
I won't be fooled again.
She told me to choose
either to save him or save myself.
- I'm going to die?
- Open up!
- I don't believe it.
- It's all related to Shin Ga Hyeon.
- Isn't this odd?
- Who wouldn't cherish their lives?
Shouldn't we try to survive?
You must thank me.
I'm doing the work for you.
I wonder why you're
suddenly curious about that.
You must pay the price for it.
Next up is you.