Going back to the past
and repeating your life.
I call this...
Dad!
"reset".
You should hurry home.
I left a gift for you.
A close colleague of mine died.
I chose to reset to save him.
But if I could bring you back,
I'd do anything.
How did you know? How did you...
All you need to know is
that I saved your life today.
Thank you.
- Was it a car accident...
- Maru!
That made you sit in the wheelchair?
- A hit-and-run accident.
- Thank you.
Gosh! I'm back! My friend died.
My friend got into the
same accident that I had.
The same time, the same
place. It was exactly like that time.
Did she get hurt because
I avoided the accident?
If it happened at the same time and place,
the culprit should be the same person too.
The person who ran over me...
was Seo Yeon Soo, not Kim Dae Sung.
Turn yourself in now and
beg for my friend's forgiveness.
Do you have proof?
That hypnosis session?
You invited both of us knowing the truth,
didn't you?
Seo Yeon Soo will come to you soon.
When she does, relay this message.
I won't let her get
away like the last time.
Mr. Park Young Gil who
couldn't make it here today...
is dead.
Why did he pass away all of a sudden?
It was a heart attack.
The deliveryman died not long ago.
Why did another guy die like this?
In the order people got up,
they will be killed.
We've been invited to
play the Death Note Game.
(Episode 5)
(Violent Crimes Investigation Team 1)
Why is no one at work yet?
What?
I thought you were at
the scene of the crime.
What in the world happened?
Okay.
Hey! Why are you late?
I'm in charge here,
but I'm doing all the work.
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I didn't get your call. You
should've left a message.
How dare you give me that attitude?
- Hello.
- Hey. Soon Woo.
- Did you identify the victim?
- We'll have to get her prints.
We couldn't find either
her ID card or her phone.
There's a CCTV camera above those stairs.
It'll be easy once we get the footage.
The patrol divisions are
changing their CCTV cameras,
so all the CCTV cameras
on the north are broken.
Darn it.
The ones at the park and
on the south are still working,
so I'll take a look at them.
Did you find anything unusual?
- Don't you think she just fell?
- No, there wasn't much.
- I'll check once again.
- Hold on.
Okay, you do that.
- We'll go check.
- Let's go.
Hello, sir.
Her name is Seo Yeon
Soo. She was 29 years old.
She resided at Sangho Villa,
Unit 507 in Suin-dong.
Her family signed the autopsy consent form,
and we've requested her call
logs from the phone company.
Did you find anything in
particular from the CCTV footage?
There was someone she
met right before she died.
I thought she tripped and fell...
since there were no other footprints.
This will become more
serious if it is a murder case.
Ga Hyeon.
What was that text about?
Is something wrong?
I met Seo Yeon Soo.
Where? Did she agree to turn herself in?
I'll tell you at the cafe tomorrow.
I need to rest.
The video quality is terrible.
I can't see their faces at all.
And we haven't gotten Seo
Yeon Soo's call logs either.
- We won't be able to track her.
- We'll have to ask around.
Let's focus on identifying
that unknown woman.
Shin Ga Hyeon.
That's her name.
You're going to interrogate her, right?
I'll bring her in.
Wait...
- What was that?
- Maybe he's a clairvoyant.
"Shin Ga Hyeon", was it?
How did he know?
I have something to tell you
about Seo Yeon Soo and me.
Before the reset,
I was a victim of a hit-and-run accident.
And the driver...
was Seo Yeon Soo.
- What?
- No way.
That's chilling.
Did you hear? Ga Hyeon's
hit-and-run driver was...
Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon. Is this you?
- Why do you have this?
- Answer me.
Yes, it's me.
We met last night. We...
Seo Yeon Soo is dead.
- Dead?
- She's dead?
I need to interrogate
you regarding her death.
Please come with me to the police station.
Ga Hyeon?
I can't believe this.
Is she really dead?
Why? Where? How?
Why would you ask me?
Then who else could I ask?
We found her body...
at the Circular Park.
I told you to be patient.
I said I'd find evidence to arrest her.
Are you suspecting me?
You're a key suspect.
Only I know this,
but you have a motive as well.
Hyeong Ju.
Seo Yeon Soo.
Did you kill her?
This reset is quite dynamic.
I'm being suspected of murder...
while trying to find
the hit-and-run driver.
You haven't answered me.
Was it you?
No.
I'd only be able to catch Dae
Sung through Yeon Soo's testimony,
so why would I kill her?
All right. If you just tell the truth,
the interrogation won't take that long.
If you can, don't plead the Fifth.
The detective in
charge isn't a fan of that.
You don't think Ga Hyeon really killed her,
do you?
You all saw her riding the wheelchair.
If I met the culprit who did that to me,
I would've killed them as well.
There's no way she would've done that.
She's just a testifier.
She'll be out of there
after the interrogation.
I really don't know what's going on.
They were all alive
and well before the reset.
But three have died already.
What if we're cursed?
You know, like the demon's curse?
What if we're dying in
return for resetting our lives?
Come on.
Then what about Ms. Lee?
She did this numerous times.
But she's still breathing, right?
I got it.
So this was it.
I knew the rules were simple.
If you're going to blabber nonsense,
just cut it out.
You were wrong about
the standing-up-order story.
When did you take this?
Look.
No way.
(Shin Ga Hyeon)
(Seo Yeon Soo)
I don't think you're a
clairvoyant or anything like that.
How do you two know each other?
You recognized her right
away through the CCTV footage.
You two must be close.
She's the writer of "Hidden Killer".
- What?
- She's that webtoon artist?
The writer was female? That's awesome.
So that's how you knew.
Your fanboying paid off.
But what a shame. You won't
be able to get her autograph.
All right, shall we talk?
You know Ms. Seo Yeon Soo, right?
- Yes.
- How?
What should I say if he asks
how I knew Seo Yeon Soo?
"We reset our lives together."
"Before that,
she was the hit-and-run driver."
"I was going through hypnosis
and chasing after Kim Dae Sung."
He wouldn't buy that.
A few days ago, I had lost my dog.
She found him for me.
(Call Log)
It's true that she contacted you first.
You two had just one call,
and you're very thankful for
her because she found your dog.
You're behaving pretty
violently to someone...
you're grateful for.
Why did you fight with her?
That's not a tough question.
Why did you two fight?
I'll plead the Fifth.
Do you have the result of her autopsy?
Or the result of her postmortem exam?
You don't know the cause of her death yet,
and I've been summoned here
to be questioned as a testifier.
I won't answer anything private.
Did you go straight
home after you parted...
with Ms. Seo Yeon Soo?
No, I was at the park a bit longer.
You two parted ways at 22:35.
Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon, you left the park...
at 23:37.
You were sitting at the
park alone for an hour?
Can someone prove that?
It was late,
so there wasn't anyone passing by.
But can't you just check
the security footage?
Sadly,
that was when the cameras got changed,
so there's no way to prove your innocence.
Ms. Seo Yeon Soo and I
walked the opposite way.
If I had run after her,
the security footage at the park...
would have shown how I followed her.
You're right.
(Guide to the Circular
Park around Banho-ro)
The park you two met at is...
this one.
Like you said, Ms. Seo Yeon Soo went east,
then you went west,
and parted your ways
in the opposite direction.
But if you two kept walking,
you two would have met
again at the exact place...
where she got into the accident,
in front of these stairs.
- Seo Yeon Soo.
- I have nothing more to say.
No.
I didn't run into her again.
And I sat at this bench...
until I left the park.
I didn't kill her.
I need her to testify
to catch Kim Dae Sung.
Why would I kill her?
Why is this here? You deserve the same.
I'll kill you! Seo Yeon Soo! Come out!
Man, reporters.
They released an article already.
("Popular Webtoon Artist S
Under Police Investigation")
Which one?
I know.
Inside sources say it's
the artist of "Hidden Killer".
"Hidden Killer" is finished.
Did she end up murdering
someone while researching?
"Hidden Killer" won't be
made into a movie now.
Darn it.
Yes, Captain Heo. Yes.
Yes, sir. Okay.
Ms. Seo Yeon Soo's fiance is
here to be questioned as a testifier.
Should I get him?
I'll go.
I have the analysis report of
the examination for the scene.
This is what you mentioned before.
We have the estimated time of her death.
It's between 23:00 and 1:00am.
Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon, that means you,
who was at the park at that time...
- could be a culprit...
- No.
I really didn't do it!
Or a witness.
Did you see anything weird...
while you were at the park?
Did you see anyone weird?
Or did you hear someone screaming?
No.
I had too much on my mind,
so I had no time to be
concerned about anything else.
No. I was going to
report it and turn myself in.
But Kim Dae Sung said he'd kill me.
He told me to keep quiet.
I'm a victim who was threatened too.
Kim Dae Sung. Did you question him?
Ms. Seo Yeon Soo's fiance?
Yes, him.
They weren't on good terms,
and she said he even
threatened to kill her.
He threatened to kill her?
Do people usually talk
about something that deep...
with a woman whom she just
met because of a missing dog?
Were you in a wrongful relationship...
with Mr. Kim Dae Sung?
- What?
- Ms. Seo Yeon Soo found out...
about her boyfriend's other woman,
and called you to meet at the park.
Then you two began to quarrel,
and things got heated up...
Kim Dae Sung killed my
friend in a hit-and-run accident!
How can you get a guy
like him involved with me...
Wait.
He killed her in a hit-and-run accident?
On the report we have,
both Ms. Seo and Mr. Kim...
do not have any previous criminal records.
How do you know about an incident
that even the police don't know?
(We are closed temporarily on January 28,
Monday.)
(On patrol, working outside)
You're right. I don't see him leaving.
I'm sure he wasn't here
all through the night.
Hello? This is Daeri Building.
Hurry over to the dermatologist's
office on the seventh floor.
Is anybody here? Hello?
(Skin Care Room)
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim. Are you here?
Mr. Kim Dae Sung?
Mr. Kim. Mr. Kim!
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim!
It really wasn't me.
Why would I kill her? We
were going to marry next month.
I believe Ms. Seo Yeon
Soo wanted to call it off.
Where were you between
11:00pm to 1:00am last night?
You met Ms. Seo Yeon Soo, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
You talked to her on the
phone at 11:00pm last night.
The base station that
captured your phone signal...
had been near that park
where Ms. Seo Yeon Soo died.
I was near that park, then I called her...
to tell her that I can't come
because something came up.
Something came up? Like what?
Going to Naeilro Junkyard?
Go Dong Cheol.
You met him, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
He threatened me and said...
he'll hand over the security footage
unless I pay him, so I met him.
Yeon Soo wouldn't have
died if it wasn't for him.
Do you admit that you're the culprit of...
the hit-and-run accident at Sodam Park?
Mr. Kim Dae Sung.
As of this hour,
you became the suspect of the
hit-and-run accident at Sodam...
instead of the testifier...
of Ms. Seo Yeon Soo's death.
This is a very important case
where Ms. Min Ju Young died,
and we have enough evidence
and proof that you did this.
If I do not arrest you now,
you may try to tamper
the evidence or run away.
I told you.
You should've turned
yourself in to live in peace...
instead of putting up a useless fight.
You're under emergency arrest for...
professional negligence resulting
in injury as well as violating...
Additional Punishment
Law on Specific Crimes.
You may consult an attorney
or choose to remain silent.
You may refuse to say anything
that can be used against you.
But let's not put up a useless fight.
If you're going to be like this,
just come back to our team.
Okay, fine. Just go. Hurry up and go.
Hey, wait.
Did he make a confession?
Yes, but it's not Ms. Seo Yeon Soo's case.
- It's for the hit-and-run accident.
- What?
A hit-and-run case?
Why did you bring in the
Traffic Department into this?
That case is the same as this one.
Ms. Shin also had been saying
Kim caused the hit-and-run accident.
Then have you been investigating
Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon's friend's case?
- Well, I...
- Ji Hyeong Ju!
This wasn't your first time
meeting Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon.
What is she saying?
I went to look around Seo Yeon Soo's place,
and I heard Ms. Shin came
by often and made a scene.
And the patrol division had
to come one of those times,
and I heard you're the one who took her.
Why are you telling
them every single detail...
of the account?
What's going on?
That woman came to me...
and brought us together.
Got it?
Stop.
Stop right there, Seo Yeon Soo!
What's your relationship
with Shin Ga Hyeon?
Why didn't you tell me that you knew her?
You took a day off to investigate
her case and catch the culprit.
Are you her personal assistant?
How can I just stand
around when I could see...
the bad guy right there?
There's a detective who's in charge!
Why did you step in and to
make a huge deal out of this?
- They didn't even have a suspect.
- Exactly.
Even the detective in
charge couldn't find a suspect.
How did Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon find out?
Why did she think Kim did it,
and why did you trust her?
Well, because...
Anyway,
isn't it great that we caught the culprit?
If he was going to side with her,
I'm sure he would've
ignored the security footage.
Thanks.
Ji Hyeong Ju. You're taking
your hands off this case.
- Come out.
- Captain Heo.
- What?
- I...
Captain Heo, I'll let Ji Hyeong Ju go home.
Hey, go home.
Bye!
Captain Heo.
There's a report on Ms.
Seo Yeon Soo's case.
Play it.
I fell asleep on my way
down from the mountain.
Stop right there, Seo Yeon Soo!
Then I heard two women in a fight.
Let's go to the police
station. You can talk there.
Seo Yeon Soo.
I didn't want to cause a misunderstanding,
so I waited there for a
while before I climbed down.
I went back down after about 10 minutes,
but the woman in black clothes
was still sitting on the bench.
It would've been weird to pass her by,
so I waited a while,
and left the park after she did.
Her statement matches the report.
If he left after Shin Ga Hyeon did,
he could be the culprit too.
He wouldn't make
this report if he did this.
Does this mean Ms. Shin
Ga Hyeon has an alibi?
She was just seen on the bench.
We don't know how long she was there.
Hey! What are you doing over there?
Detective Ji,
the webtoon artist is here, right?
- Did she really kill her?
- She's here as a testifier.
Why would you question
a testifier for hours?
People on the internet and
social media are going crazy...
saying the artist of "Hidden
Killer" became an actual killer.
You're Reporter Hwang,
aren't you? The initial reporter.
You upload rumors on social
media and turn that into an article.
That's your specialty.
The way you misspelled a
few words was exactly the same.
This case hasn't been closed yet.
Are you just concerned
about blowing up the case?
It's not like I used her real name...
or made up a case.
If she's found innocent,
- it'll be reported...
- What if I beat you up now...
and apologize? Does
that make everything okay?
- What?
- Try to act like an intellect.
All right?
- Hey!
- We saw something suspicious.
- We're here to make a report.
- What is it?
We saw the artist of "Hidden
Killer" sitting on a bench at the park.
Hey, what if someone is here?
Why would anyone be here at this hour?
What's that?
Who's that woman?
Hey, wait. Isn't she Maru?
- You know, of "Hidden Killer".
- Really?
Wow, that's amazing.
- Let's take her picture.
- Okay.
Okay.
A selfie too.
- We caught Maru.
- Her bare face is pretty too.
- I'm glad we cut our academy.
- I thought she was a ghost.
- So scary.
- Is she here to feel scared?
No wonder she's the
artist of "Hidden Killer".
It's right here on this day, right?
We uploaded it as soon
as we took her picture.
Who said she's a suspect?
It's all over the internet...
that the artist of "Hidden
Killer" is getting investigated.
We weren't sure if it was real,
but we knew as soon as we saw that
witnesses are wanted from that day.
Do we get rewarded for this?
How much do we get?
But did Maru really kill her?
No!
What was that? We
didn't even get any money.
- They're awful.
- Let's go.
This is the map of the Circular Park.
- And the pictures they brought.
- What?
The security footage pictures. Captain Heo.
If she was seen here at 23:15,
it's impossible for her
to travel all the way...
to where Ms. Seo fell,
then get caught on camera at
23:37 as she leaves the park.
It wasn't Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon.
- I have the autopsy report.
- Good.
(Autopsy Report)
(1. Nothing other than scratches.
2. Could have slipped and fell.)
"Cause of death: excessive
bleeding from skull fracture."
"Nothing other than scratches."
The NFS also said she
could have slipped and fell.
That's the conclusion.
What are you doing?
Go tell her the joyful news.
Yes.
Why should I go?
The detective in charge should go.
They found your alibi.
How?
Are you all right?
About what?
How I was questioned for four hours?
How my name is the most
searched word right now?
If that's not it, how my fan betrayed me...
to get rewarded?
I'm fine. I get countless
awful comments every week.
Something like this doesn't get to me.
Kim Dae Sung is...
arrested.
- Really?
- I'm not sure if it's comforting,
but let's call it even...
since I caught Kim Dae Sung.
Thank you.
Do you want me to take you home?
No, it's okay. I can go home by myself.
You should go.
Okay.
- Goodbye.
- Be careful.
So that's how it ended.
Okay. Please keep doing your best.
Hey, do you think...
I've been too harsh on your future wife?
What are you talking about?
Even if so, I'm glad that it
was closed as a falling accident.
Finding a murderer of a murder
case would be a huge headache.
Hey, why don't we get together
with Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon sometime?
- It's my treat. I'll apologize...
- Bye.
Okay. Bye.
I should go home too.
Maru.
They caught the bad guy.
But...
I'm not relieved at all.
I wish...
I could go back.
Detective Ji.
Hello.
What brings you here?
What happened to Ga Hyeon?
Her alibi checked out.
That's a relief.
- What about Yeon Soo?
- She tripped and fell.
Is that why you're here.
That and...
I had something to tell you.
(Violent Crimes Investigation)
What are you looking at so intently?
Hyeong Ju.
I was keeping an eye on him so
he wouldn't cause more trouble.
Let's go.
After you two left,
Jae Young said something strange.
Here.
- No way.
- What? Let me see.
The deliveryman sat on that empty seat.
The guard sat next to him.
Then it was Seo Yeon Soo.
Do you still think I'm spewing nonsense?
Then are you saying...
he's next?
It may have been his turn already.
We haven't been able to reach him.
Then the next person is...
He's just trying to make
sense of what's happening.
Don't think too much of it.
Now that Yeon Soo's dead,
it's hard to ignore what he said.
I can't even focus on work these days.
Can you check...
on Bae Jung Tae for me?
It would help me be at peace.
Please, sir.
Deliveryman, killed.
That old man.
Nice.
And lastly...
Killed.
Nice.
What?
Ko Jae Young just killed everyone.
How are you so good at this new game?
It feels like you've played this before.
Of course, I have.
I've played all the games
out there. Bring it on.
- I'll beat you all.
- I admit that you're good.
But I know you never played this before.
They released this game today.
Gosh, this is boring.
I mean what I said.
Right.
I guess he's played this before.
Why do you look so scared?
Darn it. I died because of you.
Let's play one more round.
Royal Officetel, Unit 716?
Yes.
There's still someone living there.
There are many other places
that you can move in immediately.
They're cheaper and nicer.
Would you like to take a look?
No, thank you.
It has to be that house.
I'll pay a higher commission,
so please call me first
when that place is available.
We don't know when that'll
be. Are you just going to wait?
It'll happen soon.
Please give me a call.
(Real Estate)
(Real-time: "Famous webtoon artist",
"Webtoon artist murder")
I heard her fans confirmed her alibi.
Her work has become even more popular.
Did she become a killer herself?
No wonder her drawings looked so realistic.
Only her initials were posted,
but everyone knows that it's her.
These darn comments...
Why are people like this?
Still,
it's a relief that her alibi checked out.
Ga Hyeon must've been distraught.
Do you think we're really
dying in the order of our seats?
Of course, not.
It's just a coincidence.
I can't confront Ms. Lee either.
I have trouble sleeping these
days because I'm scared.
Let's not worry in advance.
Do you want some more tea?
Yes, please.
(Sunghee Sanatorium,
Specializes in Dementia and Strokes)
"Dementia"?
Hey.
How did you know about
the hit-and-run accident...
at Sodam Park even before
the detective in charge did?
Why would I tell you something
that I didn't even tell Captain Heo?
We're colleagues.
Ahn Gyeong Nam,
Oh Myung Chul, and now, this?
You're full of secrets these days.
Are you really a clairvoyant?
Do you see the culprits' faces?
Stop watching dramas.
What is this?
Its Kim Dae Sung's alibi.
When Seo Yeon Soo died,
he had met this man at Pungjin Hotel.
Naeilro Junkyard? Go Dong Cheol.
He threatened me and said...
he'll hand over the security footage
unless I pay him, so I met him.
What is it?
What?
Yes, he's the worker from the junkyard.
Did Seo Yeon Soo know him as well?
Yeon Soo?
I'm not sure. I don't think they met.
Why do you ask?
Don't trust that woman, Lee Shin, too much.
It's me, Shin Ga Hyeon.
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Wait.
Hello, I'll be helping you from today on.
My name is Koo Seung Min.
Right, I heard.
I wasn't in charge of webtoons,
but I volunteered as your fan.
It's truly an honor.
I hope we get along.
I prepared these for you myself.
And these...
are from your fans.
They're cheering you on.
And I was specifically ordered
to buy these macarons...
by our team manager.
I heard you liked their macarons.
I was told to help you focus...
- on writing...
- I'm sorry.
- But I need to head out.
- Are you going somewhere?
I'll drive you.
That's okay.
You can put all of
them in front of my door.
I'll call you later.
These macarons are organic,
so they'll go bad...
Goodbye!
I couldn't say bye properly.
This is where Seo Yeon Soo died.
You're not even alarmed.
Mr. Hwang visited me.
(Lee Shin)
He said people were anxious...
due to Ms. Seo's death.
What about you?
You had already met her before the reset.
How do you feel?
To me, Ms. Seo Yeon Soo...
was a bit special.
Seo Yeong. Ms. Lee Seo Yeong.
- My client left after a session.
- Are you listening to me?
And she called me and
alluded to ending her life.
I went to her as fast as I could.
Seo Yeong! Seo Yeong!
It wasn't my client.
- It was Ms. Seo Yeon Soo.
- No.
Hold my hand now!
No!
Are you all right?
Let me see.
That's how we met, and I suggested a reset.
I promised her that...
she could turn back everything.
She was special to you,
but why did she tell me
that I shouldn't trust you?
As I promised, we came back in time,
but everything was the same.
And she had the same
misunderstanding as you.
That I had already known about
the connection between you two.
I can see how you'd think so.
Even I can't believe it.
I thought about for days
how it must have felt...
for the both of you.
And I finally found an answer.
It was fate.
You were fated to meet in this way.
Fate?
If that's truly the answer,
it's too easy.
And it's cruel too.
Maru.
I'm sorry to come at this hour.
No, it's okay. Come on in.
Why are they together in this photo?
The worker at the
junkyard was Bae Jung Tae.
What?
Then, Bae Jung Tae and Seo Yeon Soo...
It's possible that they knew
each other before the reset.
My gosh.
Then, Ms. Lee was lying even to the end.
We met this afternoon.
She told me it was a coincidence
Seo Yeon Soo and I met.
She even talked about it being our fate.
I just came back from a
meeting with Ms. Lee as well.
What?
You didn't call ahead.
What brings you here?
Well, you were the one who
told us to feel free to come to you.
That's right. Take a seat.
Okay.
You probably heard what happened to...
Ms. Seo Yeon Soo, right?
Yes. I am very sad about what happened.
Everyone underwent the
reset to live a better life.
I don't know why this keeps happening.
Just like someone's claim,
you don't believe there's
a rule about death, do you?
I came here to ask you for a favor.
Are you in touch with Mr. Bae Jung Tae?
I've been calling him,
but I can't reach him at all.
Why do you want to reach him?
It has to do with an investigation.
I can't tell you the details.
I take it that it's not good news, then.
I understand.
I would like to ask you...
for a favor, Detective Ji.
She knew that I was a detective.
And she knew about the weird
rule Ko Jae Young talked about.
Seo Yeon Soo must have told her.
They knew each other before the reset.
She must've reported...
Seo Yeon Soo wasn't at the funeral.
She wouldn't know about the rule.
The owner of the cafe told
me that he was at Zian Clinic.
Did he tell her about the rule?
I already called him.
He talked about Seo Yeon Soo's death,
but he didn't talk about anything else.
I mean, then who on earth told her?
Here's what's even more strange.
I would like to ask you...
for a favor, Detective Ji.
I need information about the
people who went through the reset.
I only offered them the chance,
but I don't know much about the people...
who went through the reset.
As this all began from my offer,
I think I have the
responsibility to keep them safe.
Will you help me?
She's asking me to dig
information about the people.
What do you think her agenda is?
First of all, we must find Bae Jung Tae.
If we can prove that he knew
Seo Yeon Soo before the reset,
she won't be able to play innocent anymore.
But...
how can we find him?
He already quit the junkyard.
We don't even have his phone number.
Well,
I am a detective and all,
but I cannot officially launch
an investigation on this.
Doing this by myself would be difficult.
So that's why I'm here.
This is Bae Jung Tae's call record.
You know, you're very intelligent.
Since you're a webtoon artist,
you're great at drawing.
So this is...
Will you be my partner?
What?
Hurry!
- Hey.
- Darn it.
Did you think we wouldn't find
you once you quit the junkyard?
Who are you? Who sent you?
You know that we don't reveal our clients.
You must know how this
works. You were one of us.
Get him.
- Come on.
- Hey.
- Darn it. Come on.
- Hey, you jerk!
(Trustworthy police, safe country)
- Yes?
- What did you find out?
Did you get in touch with Bae Jung Tae?
Not yet.
I'm looking into that now.
I see. You must be busy,
but I'm sorry to bother you with this.
No one would take it seriously.
But I'm glad that I have you.
Don't mention it. If I hear anything,
I'll call you right away.
Okay.
What happened?
The detective couldn't reach him yet.
Did something really happen to him?
I'm so nervous my
heart is about to give out.
You don't think all of us will end up dead,
right?
You're finally taking
what I said seriously.
I figured out the pattern.
We must create a hack if
it means we can survive.
What? A hack? What do you mean by that?
We must make our own weapon.
We can't just sit here and be killed.
What should we do?
We must find the answer now.
I'm sure the answer
must be within the rule.
Hey, wake up.
Hey.
Darn it.
Hey. Wake up.
Hey.
What's going on?
I'll hand him over once
you settle the balance.
What?
What are you doing? Get him!
(Daeshin Tech)
- Get him!
- Go after him.
- You jerk.
- My gosh.
Get him.
- Go around.
- Did you get him?
My gosh. He's driving me crazy. Darn it.
(Trustworthy police, safe country)
Thank you.
What about Sun Ho?
He had to do something.
He said he'd eat later.
Did you get the autograph from her?
What autograph? I didn't get anything.
Seriously? You were anxious
about getting her autograph.
You didn't even get an autograph?
No way. I don't believe this.
Is it that you don't have games
or that artist is so cold-hearted?
It's not that. It sounds like...
he won't be satisfied with
just an autograph now.
What else do you want then?
There you go again. Stop making stuff up.
You should use your passion
and your intense gaze...
during interrogation. Okay?
Hey, should I lock you up in
the box and interrogate you?
Besides, Sun Ho is already onto
you. He said something is off with you.
Why did he say that?
Why are you asking me? You're
the suspicious one. You should know.
(Corporal Ji Hyeong Ju)
His ID is...
(KICS Verification)
His passcode...
Is it 1234?
(KICS Verification, Passcode)
That simple-minded punk.
(Violent Crimes Investigation Team 1)
- Sun Ho.
- Where are you?
I'm on my way now.
You didn't even eat. What's going on?
I'm thinking if I should
kill you or spare you.
- Why?
- Come with me.
(Background Check)
Bae Jung Tae. What is this about?
I saw it when I was on KICS at your desk.
Fraud, assault,
and gambling. He works for loan sharks too.
His rap sheet is a mile long.
What are you up to? You
didn't even tell me about him.
I came across his file when I
was checking Kim Dae Sung's alibi.
I see. The guy from Pungjin
Hotel is Bae Jung Tae?
- Yes.
- Even I didn't know...
who this guy was. And
I'm in charge of this case.
How did you find out so quickly?
Come on,
Sun Ho. He looks like he had a record.
He popped up when I compared his face...
to the facial recognition system.
Gosh, something is definitely up with you.
This isn't your case.
Why are you working
so hard all of a sudden?
You nag me when I work hard.
And you nag me when I don't
work hard. What should I do?
It's not that. You're clearly
hiding something now.
There shouldn't be any
secrets between us. Right?
Both of us should know
what the other one is up to,
so we can either protect each other
or work together to solve the case.
Who's the man that came to see you?
- Who?
- I saw you two whispering...
and going to a corner like a
couple of suspicious punks.
I see. He works at a stock firm.
I lost some money with stocks.
He came to the station to
apologize. My goodness.
Stocks?
You have no money.
- Darn it.
- You...
I have money, Sun Ho.
You're hurting my pride. Seriously.
I'm not in the mood to play. Let go.
Sun Ho,
I got a call. I need to go answer this.
I'm leaving.
Yes.
That punk.
(Base stations for Bae
Jung Tae's burner phone)
(Paseon-dong, Howoon-dong)
(Burner phone 1, burner phone 2)
(Burner phone 3, burner phone 4)
(14 pings, 16 pings)
(Yimyeon-dong, Eulmi-dong, Howoon-dong)
(Banho-dong, sinyeong-dong, bukhae-dong)
My gosh, no way.
How did you pull this off?
You could take the test to become a cop.
You're better than our rookie.
You really should be nice to your rookie.
This was exhausting.
The area with the most pings...
is probably where Bae Jung Tae lives.
Luckily, there's a cluster of factories.
So the residential area is...
only between these two alleys.
Sir.
Have you seen this man around here?
I don't know.
I don't know! Darn it.
This man? I know him.
- You do?
- Yes.
Go straight down. Was his house number 41?
Mr. Bae Jung Tae.
What is this?
Choi Kyung Man.
Seo Yeon Soo.
Mr. Hwang.
Ko Jae Young.
Se Rin.
Why are there... Why on earth...
(Decline with a Text Message)
Clean it up.
Hello?
Ms. Lee?
(Bae Jung Tae)
(Power off)
The person you have reached is unavailable.
You'll be connected to the voicemail box.
(Lee Shin)
(010-710-2744, unsaved number)
(Mobile, 010-352-4775)
The numbers are different.
(Shin Ga Hyeon)
(365: Repeat the Year)
I'm Bae Jung Tae.
- How did he die?
- You must be very shocked.
It's "Hidden Killer". Don't
people die in the webtoon?
It's not suicide.
Since you underwent
the reset several times,
you must know what it is.
It's not just the two of them.
You knew each other before the reset,
right?
If someone is after us...
Kill me when you have the chance.
Has she been stalking us all this time?
No way. It must be a coincidence.
It's dangerous.
Should I commit murder?