(Episode 7)
Goodness.
(Shin Ga Hyeon)
Hyeong Ju.
- Sun Ho.
- My gosh.
Why did you get caught?
Why... Why are you here?
- The... The gun.
- Yes, the gun.
I thought you were Jo Doo Pal.
- Jo Doo Pal?
- He's on the wanted list,
and the factory he works at is
around here.
Why won't you check your text?
If you weren't here for him,
why were you running around...
exactly like how Jo Doo Pal runs?
Well, it's...
Is everything okay?
Ga Hyeon. Ga Hyeon?
(Recent calls)
Was that Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon?
Sun Ho, I'll call you later.
Wait. You'll look extra suspicious
if you leave like this.
So why were you here?
I wanted to help Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon
researching for her webtoon.
She's at a dangerous place,
so I have to be there for her.
I see.
- Is it love?
- No way.
- Then what is it?
- Soon Woo will catch Jo Doo Pal,
so don't worry about it.
Hey, where are you? Where are you?
I arrested Jo Doo Pal.
Operation complete.
This was Nam Soon Woo, over.
What was that?
Hey. Hey!
Bae Jung Tae, he's the biggest jerk.
He said he'll marry me.
But he took my money and ran away.
Goodness, you're
a perfectly fine young woman,
but you have an awful taste in men.
Hey, I'll help you
get your money back.
You should stop crying.
There, there.
Who are you?
Goodness, it wasn't me.
I didn't make her cry. Right?
He's looking for Bae Jung Tae too.
I see.
Are you two cops?
I'm not a cop. I'm a detective.
Why were you
looking for Bae Jung Tae?
We have rules for our business.
The police also have rules.
Goodness, I'm sure my client
has a reason to look for him.
We get half the amount if we find
him, everything if we catch him.
The client already promised
to give us a huge sum,
so we're just doing our job.
Who's your client?
We don't work for the person.
We only work for money.
Is that so?
That's why you're working so hard.
You're trespassing,
and you damaged the property.
Are you all right?
It looks like she could write...
a short novel
about what happened to her.
Okay?
Goodness, I really don't know.
I don't know.
Give me your phone.
Hurry.
I got your number.
Once you find out
who your client is...
or if you find Bae Jung Tae,
call me right away, okay?
Fine.
Darn it. I can't believe
how unlucky I am today.
What was he up to?
But this isn't everything.
Someone called him, so I picked up.
- Clean it up.
- It was Ms. Lee Shin's voice.
She hung up when she heard my voice.
When I called her back,
the phone was turned off.
Are you saying Ms. Lee Shin
made him do these things?
Who knows? But what we do know is...
that she had been in contact
with Bae Jung Tae all along,
when we didn't even know her number.
She's not here right now.
She left the country
to attend a seminar.
She left the country?
Do you expect me to believe that?
I have no reason
to tell you anything else.
Please leave.
Wait...
Hey!
You should leave now.
If you don't, I'll call security.
Bae Jung Tae?
He may have used an alias.
Go Dong Cheol.
Oh, him? He's well known
in the gambling world.
His nickname is Go Getter
since he always doubles up...
even when he doesn't have
any money to gamble.
Where does he usually gamble?
It's always different
since people meet up and gamble...
after knowing each other online.
If he shows up,
- should I invite him to play?
- Yes.
But what sins have you committed
that you're so eager to help?
Come on, now. I'm innocent.
Anyway, lie low.
- Call me if you get in touch.
- I will.
Is she not home?
Ma'am.
Seung Min.
Ma'am, hello.
I didn't know you'd be here.
You postponed yesterday's meeting
to today.
You're 15 minutes late already.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry. Let's go inside.
Don't be. I can wait
an entire day for you.
I thought the bell was broken.
("Hidden Killer Season 2" Storyline)
You've finished the endings
for every episode and the season.
This will last at least six months.
How did you finish this
in a single day?
I just wrote down
whatever came to mind.
It still needs some touch-ups.
Not at all.
I think you can just draw them.
Oh, right. I thought you needed
a new assistant,
so I came up
with a few candidates. Here.
No, thank you.
I prefer being alone for now.
The detective who helped you
was dispatched to the countryside,
so we need to find someone else.
I think you'll need some help
from your assistant.
I know a detective who can help.
I've thoroughly looked through them
and came up with...
I'll hire an assistant later.
Is it because of what happened
to Ju Young?
I shouldn't have said that.
I'll tell our team leader so.
Soon Woo, these are
your first handcuffs.
- Thank you.
- Take good care of them.
How did you know that
he'd arrest Jo Doo Pal?
Can you now see who arrests whom?
Jo Doo Pal has been arrested.
Hyeong Ju,
these are my first handcuffs.
I miss you.
He's been here for six months.
It's time that he arrested someone.
Captain Heo, shouldn't he receive
a special promotion...
for arresting Jo Doo Pal?
- Special promotion?
Right.
- He caught him.
- That's right.
It was his first,
and he was just a figurehead.
Special promotion, as if.
Work harder.
- Yes, sir.
- All right. Let me see that.
They were lying low
in Daepo-dong.
But now they are causing
a headache in our jurisdiction.
I'm sure there are more places
that Jo Doo Pal is in charge of.
Investigate, go on a stakeout...
Do whatever it takes
to locate those places.
- Got it? Let's nip it in the bud.
- Yes, sir.
Good luck on the reporting, sir.
How was the date?
You went on a date?
I was just helping her
with her work.
- Work?
- Work.
- Webtoon.
Ms. Shin.
I sense romance.
Aren't you going to interrogate
Jo Doo Pal?
I'm sorry. I'll do well.
He was embarrassed
and took it out on Soon Woo.
I read the beginning part
of "Hidden Killer".
This is Ji Hwan, the righteous one.
He's the problem-solver, right?
Pay for the webtoon.
Pay?
Your love for her is amazing.
Could you check
a phone number for me?
- Whose phone number?
- I'm not sure.
(Seoul Makang Police Station)
Hello.
I'm going to send you a photo.
Could you check immediately?
Sure.
Mr. Bae Jung Tae had this photo.
Why would he?
I think "when" is
the more important question.
(November 4, 2018,
2nd floor auditorium)
This photo is older than the time
we reset our lives,
so how did he get this?
You two knew each other already,
didn't you?
The reason why you visited me
last time...
wasn't because you were afraid
Mr. Bae would get killed, right?
How do you two know each other?
The stocks I had suddenly crashed,
so I stole some company funds.
Why isn't he here yet?
- There he is.
- There you are.
Hurry up and sit down.
- Goodness.
- Wait!
Darn it.
Why, thank you.
- I'd like 5,000 dollars more.
- Your ID card, please.
Your business card.
"Hello Securities"?
We're in the same field.
Here.
I wanted to make some money,
so I gambled.
I won again.
I ended up taking out
a private loan.
I think that's where he spotted me.
Aren't you freezing?
If you had kept your promise,
this wouldn't have happened.
- Look at this.
- Look at it.
Are you already done reading?
- Goodness.
- Stamp your fingerprint.
- Let's do it.
- No!
- Come on, now.
Let's see if we can use
any of your organs.
How did you know I'd be here?
It's hard to forget this face.
Sorry?
But then again,
I couldn't recognize you at first.
You looked too shabby.
I heard you paid Ms. Baek
right after the reset.
Your kidney and your eyes
put together...
aren't worth that much.
You're really something.
Come on. We're reset buddies.
Let's help each other out.
I've looked into you,
and it looked like
I could help you out.
He threatened to tell my company
about my gambling.
I had no choice
but to give him some money.
There must've been many ways
for him to get money.
So why did he threaten you?
It seemed like he gambled
all the money he got...
through horse racing betting.
Every time he ran out of money,
he came to me...
as if I was an ATM machine.
I see. It must've been tough.
By the way,
did Mr. Bae ever talk about
Ms. Lee Shin?
No. Why?
It's nothing.
(Hello Investment and Securities)
Cha Jeung Seok!
- I'm fine.
- You have more than enough money.
How dare you tell those thugs
about me...
just because you didn't want
to give me some petty money?
- Let me go, please.
- So this is how you'll play?
Fine, then.
- Cha Jeung Seok.
- I'm fine.
Bring it on!
You scumbag. Let me go!
Look at him.
All right. Here. Take this.
What do you want me to do
with this money?
Are you telling me to buy
a popsicle and get lost?
Hey.
It's me, Bae Jung Tae.
I noticed that your wife
and your daughter moved.
Richmond Street, was it?
Canada's too far for me.
Should I tell your boss
what you've done?
I'll see you there
in 10 minutes.
That punk.
You should've said that sooner.
Move aside. Don't touch them.
Go on.
It's freezing.
How did you know I was here?
Mr. Kim Dae Sung.
You knew about him, didn't you?
I already confirmed his alibi
with the detectives.
It looks like you already know
that I'm a detective too.
You knew that Ms. Seo Yeon Soo
and Kim Dae Sung...
were a couple, right?
Were you acquainted with
Seo Yeon Soo before the reset?
Did you scrap Kim Dae Sung's car
back then as well?
I did scrap his car twice,
but I didn't know
who Seo Yeon Soo was.
Did you come here to ask me that?
You can be charged with threatening
even if you didn't take money.
I'll bet the rest of my career
as a detective...
that you have a recording
of your phone call...
with Kim Dae Sung on your phone.
I know a thing or two
about the law too.
You need to bring a warrant
before I can show you...
Are you insane?
Who is this crazy jerk?
Stop right there!
Hey... Darn it.
Hey!
When will he come back?
Well then.
Let's talk again next time.
Give me a call
if you remember anything.
Goodbye.
Why are you back alone?
I thought you went to arrest him.
He'll find a way to escape
even if I arrest him.
Then why did we come here?
I only followed you because
you said you're on a stakeout.
Listen to it. It'll be good.
- Who is this crazy jerk?
- What?
Don't let me catch you.
You were right, Ga Hyeon.
The number that called
Bae Jung Tae was...
opened under Ms. Lee Shin's name.
That's why...
you'll cover for me.
Okay, I get it.
But this isn't even a gun.
- With these?
- Exactly in 15 minutes.
I trust you with this, Ga Hyeon.
Wait.
I know a thing or two
about the law too.
You need to bring a warrant
before I can show you...
Who is this crazy jerk?
Wait, isn't it illegal
to tap his phone like this?
It can't be used as evidence.
I got to do all kinds of things
after resetting my life.
We'll be able to find out
the orders Ms. Lee Shin has been...
giving to Bae Jung Tae,
and why she has been...
running our background checks.
She might have noticed
that it was my voice.
Do you think
she'll contact him again?
We should hope so.
- Doctor Lee is waiting for you.
- Okay.
Great to see you again.
- Me too. How's everything going?
- Yes.
Perfect. Come on in.
- Yes?
(Ko Jae Young)
(Choi Kyung Man, died on January 25,
Seo Yeon Soo, died on January 27)
(Hanteo Apartment's guard)
(Choi Kyung Man, died on January 25,
Seo Yeon Soo, died on January 27)
Lottery?
Goodness.
He didn't want to waste a penny,
so he has never even bought
a scratchcard before.
He wouldn't buy any lottery.
He said it was his wish
to buy his son a house...
if he wins the lottery.
Goodness.
He did buy him a house, I guess.
He helped out a little
with his death benefit.
He didn't even
get to see his son's wedding.
He lived such a tough life,
then passed away.
He wanted to live to see
his grandchildren,
so he quit smoking and drinking
a year ago.
I can't believe
how he passed away...
after a glass of drink.
Thank you for coming by.
I guess my old man was...
in good terms
with residents of that apartment.
It's cold outside.
You should go back in.
Okay. Goodbye.
Yes, thank you.
Hyeong Ju, can you check...
if Mr. Choi Kyung Man had...
a lottery ticket on him
at the time of his death?
Why do you need to know that?
(Hanteo Apartment's guard,
Fiance: Kim Dae Sung)
Mr. Choi Kyung Man definitely
bought a lottery on this day.
I confirmed that the first place
bought the ticket there.
But his wife didn't know
anything about the lottery ticket.
It was missing
on the articles he had.
Bae Jung Tae took these pictures.
Bae Jung Tae needed money,
and he knew Mr. Choi Kyung Man
will be buying a winning ticket.
Are you saying Bae Jung Tae...
killed Mr. Choi Kyung Man?
Take a look at this.
This arrived two days
before Mr. Choi Kyung Man's death.
So?
Do you know where I saw...
the same exact basket?
Will you stop?
She moved out this morning.
I can't deal with this much noise
day after day.
Do you think this is a coincidence?
But you can receive a flower basket
from just anybody.
Kim Dae Sung could have
sent it to her.
According to Mr. Choi's wife,
he also said he wasn't sure
who gave him those flowers.
What if...
someone is after us,
and that person has been
sending the flower baskets?
But Mr. Choi Kyung Man
died of a heart attack,
and Seo Yeon Soo's case was
concluded as an accidental fall.
It doesn't make any sense to think
that someone is after us.
What brings you here
without a notice?
It's not like we ever called.
Why? Is anyone here?
No, right?
Make it spicier than usual.
He's really good at
making tteokbokki.
I love tteokbokki too.
- All right.
- What?
Hey.
Wow, this is so good.
This is Soon Woo's party for using
his handcuffs for the first time.
Isn't this way too simple?
Way back in my days,
when Hyeong Ju used
his handcuffs for the first time.
I gave him this house.
- This house?
- Not just that. You gave me a car.
- Really?
- He rented out his old house...
and sold him his old car.
- I see.
- I got at least 500 dollars less...
compared to
the market price at that time.
It has been running fine
without any trouble for seven years.
It didn't cause me any trouble,
but the brakes didn't work,
so I almost died a few times.
But 500 dollars is quite a lot.
Isn't it?
What? Why?
I'm wondering
if we are truly partners.
Stop it. This is good enough.
Mr. Park paid for this.
Then Mr. Ji cooked.
What about you?
- Exactly. What did you do?
- You're awful.
You can't help it.
People say fate
brings your partner to you.
- Grab a drink.
- You're unlucky.
Try making a toast with them.
Go ahead.
Do it.
He's really unlucky.
I heard he came back again.
What in the world
have you been doing, Cha?
How did some thug like that
get a hold of your weakness?
I won't let this happen again.
Your performance has been
the lowest recently.
Are you going to let
your reputation drop that low too?
Pay him out...
or report him to the police
and get him locked up.
You need to come up with
a way to deal with this for good!
I'll deal with this for good.
(Letter of Resignation)
Hey, Cha!
You have two months at most
in that position.
Don't work too hard.
And try to contain your anger too.
Hey! Cha! You!
Hey, you!
Goodness, Mr. Cha.
What brings you here at this hour?
I quit my job.
I fought with my abusive boss,
then quit my job first...
before I ended up
with defaulting bonds.
Then we should celebrate.
Isn't that so?
- All right, cheers!
- Cheers!
Congratulations!
I'm probably the only guy
who celebrates after he quits.
When will you leave the country?
I'll start getting ready.
I'll only think about my family
once I move to Canada.
I could deal with getting fired
and becoming penniless,
but I couldn't take getting divorced
and never seeing my daughter again.
The older you get,
the more important your family is.
Be good to your family
while they're around and young.
How's your wife?
She still recognizes me.
But she'll soon ask,
"Who are you, old man?"
Wait, is she...
She's at a sanatorium.
It would be great
if things would always be like this.
You all have a sweet family.
I've been preparing for the college
entrance exam for two years...
and became the odd one out.
Ko Jae Young,
why did you decide to reset?
To get my revenge.
There's this guy
I really want to kill.
I lost to this weak guy
in a video game competition.
I know all of his moves,
so this time, I'll destroy him.
Are you a professional gamer?
That's why you kept saying
everything is a game...
and that you need to
keep people alive or dead.
By any chance,
do you know what this flower is?
Let me see.
Goodness, these are very pretty.
Anyway, what are these flowers?
I'm not really sure.
These are too dry.
You can't even do an image search.
Why do you ask?
I want to use it for my work.
For "Hidden Killer"?
Isn't that webtoon
about killing people?
Yes, well. Right.
Ms. Shin, take a look at this.
My daughter drew that.
What do you think?
Is she talented?
Yes, it looks very cute.
Right? Isn't she promising?
Hey, that's so cute.
My daughter sent it to me
for my birthday.
I might forget to bring
my wallet and phone,
but I always carry that around
with me like a talisman.
It feels like
my daughter is protecting me.
Goodness! Here's another guy
who's a fool for his daughter!
- Thank you.
- You're very good with alcohol.
Don't say that.
Since you paid for everything today,
I'll make sure I buy a huge meal
for everyone before I leave.
How about this Saturday?
Sounds great.
All I have is time.
I can make it too.
What about Detective Ji?
I'll... I'll call him.
Okay! Then it's
eleven o'clock on Saturday.
Let's meet here again.
On that day,
I'll treat all of you...
with a luxurious full-course dining!
- Make sure you come!
- Okay.
All right.
Goodbye, then.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- Goodbye.
Was it just a coincidence?
Was I overreacting?
The characters for "Hidden Killer"
weren't this difficult to create.
Isn't that so, Maru?
You're so cute.
It's something I've always done.
It's not that hard.
Are you back?
Let's meet up.
Yes, okay.
- Yes?
- It's not the phone with a USIM,
so I didn't hear who it was
or where they're meeting.
What about Bae Jung Tae?
Is he still at home?
Yes, he is.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
I missed Bae Jung Tae.
I found something over here.
You got here pretty fast
like a bullet.
The photos were pretty risque
this time, weren't they?
You extorted enough money out of me.
How much more do you want,
you scumbag?
That's not something
I'd like to hear...
from a guy who secretly met up with
his mistress on his family vacation.
If I were extorting money out of you
because you gambled,
it wouldn't feel right
for me either.
Should I sent these photos...
to your wife via international mail?
You know, I'm trying
very hard not to explode on you.
So you have money to pay the thugs
and to put a price on my head,
but when I'm trying
to keep your family together,
how could you call me a scumbag?
The thugs keep...
their promises
better than a scumbag.
Hey.
It's been a while.
There's no point talking
to jerks like you.
Where's the original copy?
Don't you know the world we live in?
Don't you know the cloud?
"Cloud"?
Don't just stand there. Get him.
Hey, Jung Tae.
Doesn't this scene
look familiar to you?
Doesn't it? You punk.
Hey, getting rid of
a scumbag like you...
doesn't even cost that much.
Don't you know I can do anything...
as long as I have money
in this capitalist society?
- Jerk.
- My gosh.
Kill me when you have the chance.
Otherwise, I'll kill you
with my own hands.
Hey, you might not have anything
in this brain of yours.
But you should think, you know.
Calculate which one of us...
has a higher chance of dying?
You jerk. Scumbag.
Hey, get him out.
Don't come. No.
If he dies,
you won't get
the rest of the money.
Get that scumbag!
That darned scumbag. Gosh.
You must catch him!
So...
the client who hired those thugs...
was Mr. Cha Jeung Seok.
He pretended to be a victim,
but he was secretly chasing
Bae Jung Tae.
Do you think Ms. Lee Shin knew
about their relationship?
Is she still not back?
No.
Mr. Cha Jeung Seok, are you there?
Mr. Cha Jeung Seok?
Do you think he'll come?
- I'm not sure.
- No way!
- Hello.
- Are you here alone?
I've been calling Mr. Cha Jeung Seok
since yesterday,
but he hasn't picked up.
He has already settled the balance.
I came here because he told me to.
But is he not here?
What's going on?
Wait. Mr. Bae Jung Tae took these?
Has he been stalking us?
It can't be. Then does that mean...
(I'll Carry You: You always sit
in the same seat. Enjoy your meal.)
What? Wait.
But why would he?
It must be the master's plan.
Master?
Ms. Lee Shin's photo isn't in there.
He's been watching
all the people who have reset,
but Ms. Lee Shin isn't one of them.
There's something going on
between those two.
It's true...
that they've been in touch.
Then we shouldn't be talking
about this here.
We should visit her.
I did, but she's abroad
due to a seminar.
I've checked, and she did leave.
About Jeung Seok's not picking up,
do you think it has anything to do
with Jung Tae?
What do you think?
It's possible.
Or it could be the opposite.
- What?
- Opposite?
Mr. Cha Jeung Seok
and Mr. Bae Jung Tae...
knew each other
even before the reset.
- What?
- But why?
He's such a goodhearted man.
Hey, getting rid of
a scumbag like you...
doesn't even cost that much.
Don't you know I can do anything...
as long as I have money
in this capitalist society?
- Jerk.
- My gosh.
Kill me when you have the chance.
Otherwise, I'll kill you
with my own hands.
How could that well-mannered man
say such things?
What is this?
You knew about everything
and recorded their conversation.
That's because Bae Jung Tae
was the key suspect.
But I actually found out
a new side of Mr. Cha Jeung Seok.
He's like the villain of a PvP game.
What was that?
Hey, Soon Woo.
Where? Got it.
I need to go.
Let me know once
you reach Mr. Cha Jeung Seok.
About Jeung Seok's not picking up,
do you think it has anything to do
with Jung Tae?
It's possible.
Or it could be the opposite.
Mr. Bae Jung Tae.
I know this makes no sense.
I know I sound crazy.
But I think Mr. Cha Jeung Seok
is in danger.
Hyeong Ju, are you there?
Yes.
I got in touch with them.
They said it'll take 3 to 4 days.
- All right.
- We found his ID card.
Thank you.
(Cha Jeung Seok)
What's wrong? Do you know him?
Yes.
He's that stock firm employee.
The one who visited you last time?
Do you know anything?
Sir, this is the last message
he sent.
Honey, thank you for everything.
And I'm sorry.
Take good care of our daughter.
I hope you'll be happy
in your next life...
and not meet someone like me.
He even had a daughter.
Did you get in touch
with his family?
I got in touch with his wife
in Canada. She's flying in.
She seemed quite calm.
They had been living apart
for over five years.
She had asked him for a divorce.
It's true that they weren't close.
But he was planning
to move to Canada.
That's why he quit his work.
That's not what Soon Woo said.
The private equity fund that
he was in charge of had many issues.
When I was there,
the investors were causing a scene.
The company believes he quit
after realizing...
the details about
the distressed-debt.
- That's not why.
- Then what is it?
Do you know something?
He didn't commit suicide.
Given the circumstances,
it wasn't an accident.
Are you saying he was murdered?
The owner of a store nearby
testified...
that Cha Jeung Seok purchased
charcoal briquettes from him.
And we found no traces
of other people in his car.
The message he had sent to his wife
sounds like a suicide note as well.
His black box and the CCTV cameras
showed nothing in particular...
after his arrival at the scene.
Let's put this case on hold
until we get the autopsy results.
If you want to reinvestigate
this case,
bring me proof that this is murder.
Don't you know I can do anything...
as long as I have money
in this capitalist society?
You little jerk.
Kill me when you have the chance.
Otherwise, I'll kill you
with my own hands.
- What is this?
- It's Cha Jeung Seok...
and Bae Jung Tae.
- So?
- Sun Ho.
Cha Jeung Seok
would've never killed himself.
I'm sure there's something going on
between him and Bae Jung Tae.
We need to investigate him first.
I see.
Where did you get this?
Did you wiretap Bae Jung Tae?
If this was illegal,
you won't get away...
with just being disciplined.
- You'll be brought to court.
- Sun Ho...
I don't know why you're so obsessed
with Bae Jung Tae.
But even if this wasn't illegal,
you know very well
that it doesn't prove...
that he didn't commit suicide.
- Of course, I do.
- You better not mention this...
to Captain Heo.
You'll get in trouble.
I'm going to pretend
like I didn't hear anything.
Ga Hyeon.
Is it really Mr. Cha Jeung Seok?
How did he die?
He committed suicide.
That can't be.
By the way,
You said he could be in danger.
What made you think that?
It's not just the two of them now.
This was also in front
of Mr. Cha Jeung Seok's house.
All three of them received
a bouquet of flowers.
No, not you too. You're scaring me.
Is it like a warning
the Master is sending us?
Come on, stop that!
I can't even believe...
that he committed suicide.
That can't be.
I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
Besides, sending and receiving
bouquets of flowers is quite common.
If only the dead received them,
it's pretty rare.
Could it be that the bouquets
of flowers are cursed?
Like the Demon's doll.
That is not...
the only strange thing.
Mr. Choi Kyung Man...
definitely bought
a lottery ticket.
But that disappeared
without a trace.
There was something off
about Ms. Seo Yeon Soo as well.
Right before the estimated time
of her death,
she was on the phone
according to the record.
But her phone wasn't found
at the scene.
Right.
What about Mr. Cha's music box?
(Choi Kyung Man)
Everyone must be utterly shocked.
I'll go back soon.
Do you think Ms. Lee Shin is the one
who sent the bouquets of flowers
It could be Bae Jung Tae.
He spied on them,
so he must know their addresses.
Where on earth did he go?
I think his cell phone
is still at his house.
Yes.
Hyeong Ju, Hammer is spotted.
- Where?
- In Jangpo-dong.
Please report to the scene
with Lieutenant Park.
We'll back you up
with the task force.
Okay. I'll be there soon.
I need to go somewhere.
Okay.
Maru. I'm back.
Have you been well?
I told you to just leave, man.
Come on.
Don't even think about joining...
the big table
with that chicken feed.
- Bring more money next time.
- Go.
Seriously.
- Don't move.
- My gosh.
- Hey, take him.
- Good work.
- He's huge.
- Good job.
Let's get some soju.
Sun Ho, something important
came up. I'm leaving. Bye.
- Sa Kyung.
- I can't.
- Soon Woo.
- I'm sorry, sir.
They are too cruel.
What was that?
- You...
- Mr. Cha Jeung Seok.
Did you kill him?
He's dead? That jerk is dead?
I know everything.
That you were spying on us,
the nature of your relationship
with him,
and you're on Ms. Lee Shin's side.
I know everything.
If you know everything,
you shouldn't come here alone.
Do you think I came here alone?
To a place like this?
- Get him.
- Get the other side.
- Stay down.
- Arrest him.
Are you the one
who made the report?
- Get him.
- Yes, I am.
- Call my lawyer!
- Stop it.
- I want my lawyer.
- How can you say that?
- You can't do that!
- Hey, you over there.
- I can't believe this!
- Let go of me!
- Be quiet!
- What are you doing?
- Quiet down!
- You're unbelievable.
(Investigation Room 1)
Ga Hyeon.
Hey, Hyeong Ju.
Are you all right?
How could you go to such
a dangerous place by yourself?
I wasn't alone. The first thing
I did was call the police.
They arrived right on time.
How did you know I was here?
I have my own informant.
But you handled everything
even before I got here.
You're amazing.
By the way, it's about
Mr. Cha Jeung Seok's death.
It looked like Bae Jung Tae
really had no idea.
I've never seen a criminal
confess to his crime right away.
Let's go. I have more questions
other than that.
Okay.
Let him go?
He was arrested at the scene.
Why would you let him go?
Besides, he has gambling priors too.
He said he had just arrived
at the scene.
He couldn't even join
because the stake was too high.
Although he had been arrested
for illegal gambling before,
someone with a good status
was willing to vouch for him.
I released him...
because investigating him without
detainment wouldn't be a problem.
Someone vouched for him?
That jerk wouldn't have anyone...
(Fund manager
at Hello Investment and Securities)
(New message, Ms. Lee Shin)
(Corporal Ji Hyeong Ju)
This is Lee Shin.
Please meet me at Zian Clinic
at 2 p.m. tomorrow.
I am sorry that I wasn't available
for the past several days.
I was abroad.
Mr. Cha Jeung Seok passed away.
Yes. I read the text messages...
you sent me.
You probably already
knew even without my texts.
Someone would have reported to you
simultaneously.
You ordered
Bae Jung Tae to spy on us.
We already know that.
That's right.
I ordered him to do so.
Why?
I've undergone
the reset several times,
but this was my first time...
going through the reset
with other people.
I thought that I was sharing
a piece of luck with you.
But right after the reset,
Park Young Gil died.
And one of you told me
that you regretted doing the reset.
So I was confused too.
That's when he came to me.
Come in.
You know,
since you've done this
several times,
you must have a few good tips
on making money.
Whether it's horse racing,
stocks, or lottery,
just tell me one.
Fine.
In exchange,
I have a favor to ask you.
I want to know about the people
who went through the reset.
You want to spy on them?
- Why?
- If he didn't go through with this,
Park Young Gil
would have been alive.
It is definitely a butterfly effect
from the reset.
And this may happen to other people
who did the reset.
I must know
what will happen to them.
And that's how I found out
Mr. Ji Hyeong Ju was a detective.
So I asked for your help separately.
I called Mr. Bae Jung Tae
to stop him.
And you were the one
who answered it, Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon.
Why did you help him get released?
Weren't you behind that?
Yes.
What? You helped him get out too?
As we went through the reset
together, I was willing to help.
And he didn't commit
any illegal activities.
I also wanted him to join us
at this meeting.
Even so,
making an ex-convict dig up
information about us...
- wasn't prudent, don't you agree?
- An ex-convict?
Usually, when there's a detective,
there's an ex-convict.
Then, are you really a murderer?
- What?
- You killed Jeung Seok, didn't you?
You killed him and covered it up
as a suicide, right?
Right?
Should I really commit murder?
What's this?
This was to be delivered
to the meeting room.
(It's you this time.)
"It's you this time."
(365: Repeat the Year)
I don't know anything about this.
Why do you keep playing innocent?
I'm sure this person knows
about the reset.
The message. What do you mean?
Why do people keep dying?
You must at least know the answer.
Keep playing detective.
Hyeong Ju, you were sussing me out
because you don't believe me, right?
Hero. I have a hero.
I thought about turning myself in.
It means one of us will die
in a couple of days.
The reason why
Ms. Lee went through the reset.
That means she's
in as much danger as we are.
Isn't this why?