What's this?
This was to be delivered
to the meeting room.
(It's you this time.)
"It's you this time."
What does this mean?
Are you asking me?
You called this meeting today.
And the flowers were delivered here.
What do they have to do with one another?
I'm sure you're aware.
Choi Kyung Man, Seo Yeon Soo,
and Cha Jeung Seok.
All three of them...
received flowers right before they died.
Is that a new rule?
Is someone sending flowers...
and then killing people?
Ms. Seo Yeon Soo fell to her death,
Mr. Choi Kyung Man had a heart attack,
and I thought Mr. Cha Jeung
Seok committed suicide.
Shouldn't we find out
who this message is from?
According to the rule,
one of us will die...
in a few days.
In that case,
I'm sure this card is targeting me.
This is my house and workplace.
No.
This time, I'll die.
I saw the flowers first.
This is the curse of the reset.
Four people died already!
I'm going to die...
like everyone else who got flowers.
I'm going to die next!
Se Rin!
- Se Rin!
- Se Rin.
Se Rin, open your eyes.
This is the number of the delivery company.
I can't ask the officials to
conduct an official investigation,
so I want to ask you to look into this,
Detective Ji.
I want to know who's
putting on a prank like this.
I'm as curious as you are.
I'm sure...
it's someone who knows about the reset.
Someone who knew that
we'll be gathered here today.
We already lost 4 people among 11.
Is there a possibility that
someone else other than us...
- knows about the reset?
- As far as I'm concerned,
no.
But I have no way of knowing...
if one of you told someone else.
It could also be one
of the late individuals.
I'd like you to consider
all the possibilities.
If you ever need my help,
feel free to contact me.
I'll call you.
(Episode 9)
He gave this to you?
Was it not Ms. Lee Shin
who sent the flowers?
That means she's in
danger just like the rest of us.
It could be a ruse.
How's Se Rin doing? Did
you call an ambulance?
Yes, Mr. Hwang went with her.
You must enjoy playing detective.
Was your webtoon not enough?
The plot was quite intriguing.
You better behave...
before I lock you up for illegal filming.
How will you get the arrest warrant?
Will you say that I secretly
filmed those I reset with?
I'm sure the prosecutor will believe you.
Mr. Cha Jeung Seok...
When was the last time you saw him?
Are you suspecting me of murdering him?
I'm also sad that he died.
He died before I could
take more of his money.
It's upsetting for me as well.
Do you really have nothing
to do with the bouquets?
That means you're in danger as well.
Think about it. Did you notice
anything strange while spying on us?
Did you ever see anyone deliver bouquets...
or spot anyone suspicious?
I won't tell you that for free.
Okay?
If you need information from me,
give me something in exchange.
Have fun playing cops.
What do you think is the
meaning behind the flowers?
Do you think a killer exists
and they're the ones who sent it?
I'm not sure. If there
truly was a killer...
and they were trying
to hide their killings,
why would they send the
flowers and leave evidence?
Let's go for now.
I'll go on my own.
I'm suspecting something.
What is it?
I'll let you know after I verify it.
Please look into this matter.
I thought you had already
asked Det. Ji for help.
He's suspecting me the most.
He won't tell me that easily.
So please look into it.
Yes, ma'am.
At 2:30pm...
Mr. Kwon Ho Jun delivered them.
There he is.
Excuse me.
Did you deliver a bouquet
to Zian Clinic today?
Yes.
The bouquet is on a park bench.
Once you find it, please send me a photo.
Please deliver it by 2:30pm.
Make sure you're on time.
So...
you found the bouquet but not the sender?
No. Something felt off at first.
But it was just a bouquet,
and I was getting paid a lot for it.
So I didn't think too much about it.
May I check the messages?
Sure.
(I found it. It'll be delivered by 2:30pm.)
- May I call the number?
- Sure.
The number you have dialed does not exist.
Please check again.
Ma'am, are you in?
(It's you this time.)
I'm sure this card is targeting me.
This is my house and workplace.
This is the curse of the reset.
Four people died already!
(It's you this time.)
Here.
They're lilies of the valley and hyacinths.
We don't have them here.
They're high-maintenance and expensive.
You'll probably have to go...
to a flower garden or a wholesale market.
I see. Thank you.
(Pressed flower cards)
(Handmade Pressed Flower
Cards from "Son Card Workshop")
Are you going to give her flowers?
You're good at dating.
Are you finally in a
relationship? A successful fan?
- It's not like that.
- "It's not like that."
That's what you always say,
but you keep moving to the next base.
Are you going to say that...
while handing the
wedding invitation as well?
You're so frustrating. Why
can't you just be honest?
Why can't you?
You two.
You better not change your words.
"You two"? These two?
Is something going on?
What?
Gosh, Ji Hyeong Ju.
Don't just make stuff up.
I'm leaving.
Soon Woo,
she likes iced Americano during the summer.
What is he saying?
Detectives also need love lives.
So if there's someone nice,
you better take initiative.
Don't waste your time catching perps.
I hate it the most when
perps squirm their way out.
I should put as many behind
bars as I can while I'm still young.
Fine.
(Purchasers of Son Card Workshop)
"Daedo-dong"?
(36.5 Cafe)
(2-37, Daedo-dong, Bukseomun-gu)
(36.5 Cafe, Art Flower)
(We are closed.)
Do you have these flowers?
- No.
- We don't have them.
Do you have these flowers?
- No.
- Ma'am.
Are you looking for something?
Instructors are usually the
ones who buy these flowers.
There are many flower academies...
and flower arrangement
workshops at Mugong-gu,
so these flowers are usually sold there.
- I see. Thank you.
- No problem.
(Kim Se Rin)
How do you feel?
I'm stable now.
I didn't want to be here alone,
so I called you over.
Since I was young,
I pretty much lived at hospitals.
Are you ill?
I got sick easily.
But back then,
I had my parents.
I was the weakling,
but my older sister passed away first.
It was the same way
your friend passed away.
She got into a car accident.
She tried to save me...
but got hit by the car instead.
Since then, my parents didn't care...
even when I collapsed...
or threw up blood.
When they got drunk,
they said I should've died...
in her place.
But...
I can understand them.
My sister was so perfect.
She was pretty, kindhearted,
and smart.
She had it all.
You all have a sweet family.
I've been preparing for the college
entrance exam for two years...
and became the odd one out.
Everything feels like a curse.
After my sister died instead of me,
since then, it felt like all kinds of
unhappiness find their way to me.
So I hope...
it's my turn to die.
I had such thoughts too.
What about all the answers...
to the college entrance
exam that you memorized?
If I die,
my mom and dad will be sad, won't they?
They might not be as sad as
the time when my sister passed,
but I'm sure they'll be a little sad.
Right?
No.
That's not going to happen,
so they won't be sad either.
Don't get any weird ideas and eat well,
okay?
You said you have a boyfriend
who only has his eyes for you.
Yes, Young Woong.
My hero.
Thank you, Ga Hyeon.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
The man who just left is...
the owner of that cafe down the road,
isn't it?
Yes, you're right.
Are you looking for something?
Oh, I see.
Do you remember this basket?
Did the old man from the cafe order this?
Why do you ask?
He suddenly brought a picture...
and asked me to make it look the same,
including the ribbons.
There were flowers
that we didn't carry here,
so I had to go to the market
in Yangjae-dong to find them.
He asked me to bring
it to a bench at a park,
so I figured he was going
to propose to someone.
Sir.
Was he one of these two men?
I'm not sure. He was a young man,
but he had a cap and a mask on,
so I can't really tell.
(Mr. Detective)
- I'll get going.
- Goodbye, then.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Jae Young isn't here. Who is this?
Could you tell me around
when he'll be home?
Hey, you found me very quickly.
You really are a detective.
Who are you? Why did you send the flowers?
You need to ask the real one.
- What?
- I sent it to find the real one.
Once someone who's fake sends flowers,
the real one will have to make a move.
"Someone who's fake"?
- Is this a joke?
- A joke?
I put my life on the line to do this.
Four people died already.
I did it to find out who did
this before I end up dying.
So?
Did you find out?
It's Shin Ga Hyeon.
Everyone was flustered and afraid,
but not her.
She seemed suspicious of the flowers.
You're a detective, so you know that...
witnesses often turn out to be the culprit.
She's the only one who
actually saw the flowers.
You've only seen pictures.
Have you seen them yourself?
She could have brought
it there to make up a lie.
You're right.
Right?
You could lie and say you
sent a fake one when it was real.
- What?
- The order of the people...
standing up and sitting down was wrong,
so now it's a face she made?
What's next?
If you have time to come up with a trick,
do it alone at home.
Stop confusing people.
- Yes?
- The latest flowers seem odd.
"It's you this time."
If all of them got this message,
their family or the police
wouldn't have let this slide.
Anyone can see that this is a threat.
I wondered if other people
also received the same card,
so I went to visit Mr. Choi
Kyung Man's house.
Here it is.
I'm sorry, but may I take pictures?
Sure.
(I hope sun's power gives you energy
and moon's power gives you rest.)
Completely different, aren't they?
If I could check the other two cards,
we could be even more certain.
It's certain.
What?
- What is this?
- A copy of...
the investigation report
for Mr. Cha Jeung Seok.
(Picture taken at home 23, 24)
(Picture taken at home 25, 26)
(Picture taken at home 33, 34)
(The gleaming golden glory
of the light will be with you.)
(I hope sun's power gives you energy
and moon's power gives you rest.)
(The gleaming golden glory
of the light will be with you.)
This one was a fake one
sent by Ko Jae Young.
- Ko Jae Young?
- He did it to find the culprit.
He was suspicious of you.
He said you're the only
one who saw those flowers.
You also didn't trust me,
so you just checked, didn't you?
I thought you wanted me to be your partner.
It's because you're my partner.
I wanted to trust you even more.
That's why I checked.
He didn't see the card,
so he couldn't copy this.
Do you think Ms. Lee Shin
easily gave up the information...
because she knew this was fake?
This means she proved her innocence...
and helped us find the
one who sent the flowers.
This is way too confusing. Who can I trust?
At the least, we should trust each other.
It's not that I didn't.
You should have been there.
When Ko Jae Young got suspicious, I was...
"The gleaming golden glory
of the light will be with you."
Another very long episode.
Should I take a hiatus for a while, Maru?
I don't even have enough time.
(Only I can make you perfect.)
(I hope sun's power gives you energy
and moon's power gives you rest.)
(Only I can make you perfect.)
(I hope sun's power gives you energy...)
(I hope sun's power gives you energy
and moon's power gives you rest.)
(You'll remember me forever, won't you?)
(The gleaming golden glory
of the light will be with you.)
Who do you think is the stalker?
The most liked comment
will get an autographed book!
(The most liked comment
will get an autographed book!)
(Violent Crimes Investigation Team 1)
(Cha Jeung Seok's Death Case Report)
Why are you looking into
Cha Jeung Seok's case?
You told me to find evidence of murder.
Do it in your free time.
Don't look into it all the time.
What about the other case?
Did you check the witness report?
Yes, I finished checking all three of them.
What about the hammer case?
Did you send it to the prosecution?
I already did that ages ago.
I finished analyzing the footage
for the stolen-goods case...
and finished questioning
testifiers for the Seojang-dong case.
May I look into this a little more?
What?
Why is that guy...
obsessing over an obvious case?
- Man.
- Exactly.
- Park Sun Ho!
- Yes, sir.
Keep your eyes on your partner!
You shouldn't have let
him find the loophole.
He wouldn't listen to
me even if I said anything.
What's with him? My goodness.
I thought the investigation is over.
We're conducting an
additional investigation.
I see.
What was the date again?
February 20... Wait, right here.
Could you start playing from there?
(39E8769)
Do you have lily of the valley?
Oh, lily of the valley?
I'm not sure. We don't carry that.
We don't have that.
(All Right Flower Workshop,
225 Mulhwa-ro, Ace Bloom Flowers)
Yes?
Are you Mr. Jo Hyun Woo?
Yes, how may I help you?
I'm investigating a case right now.
Do you know Mr. Cha Jeung Seok?
Cha Jeung Seok?
No, I've never heard of him.
May I ask where you were...
at 8:00pm on February 20?
Why do you ask? What is this case?
I asked out of formality.
Please do cooperate.
- Hello.
Do you have lily of the valley?
Right here. Do you want to take it?
Did anyone order a flower
basket like this from you?
I'm not sure.
We do have all those flowers,
but I'm not sure.
I see.
All right. Thank you.
Excuse me, who's this?
That's our owner.
Ga Hyeon.
Hyeong Ju. How did you find this place?
Did you come here because you knew?
(Flower)
Excuse me, who's this?
That's our owner.
("I Want My Life to be Colored in Flowers",
Florist So Hye In)
What about the baby?
That means my baby can't come with me.
The flowers that Mr. Cha
Jeung Seok received...
were sent from here?
Yes, the delivery man was
Ms. So Hye In's husband.
Why would she...
She didn't even reset. How did
she find us and sent us flowers?
She might have just taken the order.
Then someone chose Ms.
So Hye In's flower shop...
and ordered the flowers on purpose?
If that's the case,
it has to be someone who knows...
what happened before the reset.
Someone who knows that
Ms. So Hye In was invited.
Then it's definitely one of us.
By any chance, did Ms. Seo Yeon Soo...
ever mention flowers?
How did you know?
(Episode 10 will be aired shortly.)
(Episode 10)
(Let the rainbow of the
soul be in your garden.)
What's this bouquet of flowers?
What bouquet?
"Rainbow of the soul"?
If you have time for this,
take care of the loose ends.
Don't drag me into that.
She called me thinking I was
the one who sent her the flowers.
She said something about the
rainbow of the soul or something.
"Rainbow of the soul"?
(Seo Yeon Soo)
(Ko Jae Young, professional gamer)
(Kim Se Rin, studying to retake the CSAT)
(Ji Hyeong Ju,
detective at Seoul Makang Police Station)
So it has to be someone among them.
(Bae Jung Tae, ex-convict,
Shin Ga Hyeon, me)
(Who's the stalker?)
Oh, my. I want the comic
book with her autograph.
I bet the stalker is Kim Byung
Wook. I'm 100 percent sure.
A woman probably sent that note.
Is it from the lyrics? Then,
isn't it the songwriter?
Nice. I think this person
might get the signed autograph.
(Nice. I think this person
might get the signed autograph.)
Lyrics?
In the note of Seo Yeon Soo's bouquet,
it said...
something about the rainbow of the soul.
"Rainbow of the soul"?
Is it really a part of lyrics?
If it is, the lyrics sound pretty childish.
What? The bouquet of flowers was fake?
Yes.
Out of all places,
the flower shop was around your cafe.
So even you were suspected.
My goodness.
Why would Ko Jae Young do such a thing?
He must have thought...
that he was able to find the
real sender of the flowers.
He was trying to get clues in his own way.
If he had time for that,
he should've helped the detective.
I don't think he's useful at all.
Well, there was this message on the note.
Do you recognize these lines at all?
What is that?
There was a note in
the bouquets of flowers?
They sound like they
might be lines from poems.
Or just common celebratory messages.
But I don't think these
lines are connected.
What does that mean?
Did you find what I asked?
Do you think finding someone is that easy?
Then, why did you want to see me?
Do you want more money?
If you want to expedite it,
you should pay me extra.
You know the bouquet of flowers?
Is it true that people got
the bouquet of flowers...
before they died?
I thought you were the one who sent them.
You're the only one left now.
How could anyone kill
people just by sending flowers?
Did you hear anything
from that detective guy?
I guess you're scared of death too.
It's not your turn, so don't worry.
How do you know that?
If you're curious,
take care of what I asked fast.
(- Did he figure it out?
- The culprit must be really smart.)
(I can't find anything online
what was written on the note.)
That's an excerpt from "Pieces of Destiny".
The culprit is the manager, the bookworm.
"Pieces of Destiny"?
("Pieces of Destiny")
(The gleaming golden glory
of the light will be with you.)
("The Sower" by Van Gogh)
(I hope sun's power gives you energy
and moon's power gives you rest.)
("Pieces of Destiny")
- Excuse me.
- I'm sorry.
I was on my way out.
Ms. So Hye In?
That's me.
I'm Detective Ji Hyeong Ju.
My husband told me.
Why did you visit our house?
Can you take a look at this?
Did you make that bouquet yourself?
Yes. Why?
Did you deliver the same
type of bouquet three times?
Well... I think so.
Do you know who ordered them?
Was there something
wrong with the bouquets?
I'm in the middle of investigating,
so I'm afraid I can't disclose that.
I'm sorry, but if that's the case,
I'm afraid I can't either.
I can't disclose my customers'
personal information.
The sender's information wasn't included,
so we need to find out who sent them.
We also need to know if there
was a reason why they picked...
this flower shop.
What do you mean?
Are you saying I'm
involved in this as well?
Everything will be cleared
once we can identify the sender.
Please help us.
If that's the case,
please follow the procedure.
I don't feel too happy about
your barging in like this.
(Today's workshop will
be held next Thursday.)
You wouldn't be able to get a warrant,
would you?
There's no way.
It feels strange.
She's a familiar face to us,
but to her, we're just strangers.
And to think that she could
be the one behind this...
What's more unsettling...
is that this may not be the end.
Right, about the messages, I found a lead.
I expected that.
No, we'll go as planned.
Okay. We'll talk again.
("Pieces of Destiny")
If they're all from this one book,
there must be a reason.
You're right. But there's more.
The drawings.
I think they foretell the cause of death.
"The cause of death"?
Cupid's arrow.
Cupid shoots his arrows in people's hearts.
Mr. Choi Kyung Man
suffered from a heart attack.
I checked Seo Yeon Soo's message.
It was this.
- Let the rainbow of the soul...
- be in your garden.
It's a drawing of Icarus' wings.
Icarus fell.
Seo Yeon Soo fell and died.
And lastly, Mr. Cha Jeung Seok.
(The gleaming golden glory
of the light will be with you.)
"Van Gogh".
Suicide?
He committed suicide.
This is plausible.
But the bouquets were
delivered before they died.
It doesn't make sense
that the killer knows...
how they'll die in advance.
You're right.
But there must be a
reason for the bouquets.
I'm sure they're telling us something.
I found you.
Were you hiding in there?
Yes.
Young, do you like trains that much?
I like you even more.
That's a given.
Is there anything else you
want other than toy trains?
A real train?
I want to ride a train with you.
Okay.
Let's get on a train in a few days.
How did you think of signing your books?
"Pieces of Destiny" was...
one of the most-searched words online.
Really?
I felt like my author's
notes were always the same,
so I tried something new.
I'm glad they liked it.
They did. So I came up
with a few ideas myself.
Check this out.
We shouldn't do events that often.
Some may think we're just
trying to become more famous.
I was being rash. I'm sorry.
I'll still take a look at it.
You did it for me.
Thank you!
Are we done?
Yes. Right. How will you end...
the next episode?
Will you reveal the stalker's identity?
I'm still thinking about it. I'll
let you know once I decide.
I should go work now.
Okay.
Feel free to contact
me if you ever feel stuck.
Good luck.
I'll be going now. Goodbye.
(Out)
Welcome.
Here.
This is rare to find.
I'll show you.
This is made from a volcanic
stone in Mount Halla...
that was hit by lightning...
and coral reefs from
the Sernica Archipelago.
You know soyang flowers only
bloom once every century, right?
You must know that since
you own a flower shop.
Those flowers are really rare.
These are made from their roots.
Do you know Hwang Yoon Young, the model?
She even...
performed rituals...
and couldn't get pregnant.
After taking this for a month,
she conceived twins.
- Really?
- Yes.
A dealer who deceived people
by claiming that her vitamins...
could cure infertility was arrested.
Hwang, a popular model, received money...
and posted a review on her social media.
They used the mothers' desperateness...
to commit this fraud.
Take one pill a day with fresh water.
Are there any side effects?
Not at all.
(My Dream Is to Become
a Righteous Police Officer.)
(Arrested Thanks to the Citizens)
Will I really get pregnant after one month?
Even the fertility
clinics are so worried...
in case this gets officially
approved by the board.
I'll buy it.
Then, you have to wire me the money first.
Then, we can proceed.
I'll wire you the money to the account now.
- Can I wire it now? I'll do it.
- Yes.
Hold on!
What is it this time?
Are you sure women can get
pregnant if they take the supplements?
Yes.
I really need to get pregnant.
My lifelong dream has
been becoming a mother.
I even ground the
phallic stone and drank it.
And I even visited every fertility clinics.
But it didn't work.
Are you sure this is effective?
- Then, I'll buy it.
- No.
I'll pay you double for that.
What are you talking about? I'll buy it.
I'll wire you the money.
No! Please don't sell this to this lady.
Please sell it to me. I must get pregnant.
Hey.
Seriously. I have the
perfect date for it too.
On the day of the full moon
next month around 12am...
Right. Ms. Choi Seong Hee.
You're under arrest for violating...
the Act on Special Measures
for the Control of Public Health,
committing fraud,
and multiple other offenses.
You can consult a lawyer and remain silent.
And there's something called
a review of legality of the arrest.
Please look into that.
(Seoul Makang Police Station)
You didn't run into me at
the cafe by accident, right?
Did you follow me?
I'm sorry.
It's just a bouquet of flowers.
Why are you so concerned about the flowers?
If you're a real detective,
you can go through the proper channels.
Well...
Actually, the people who
received the bouquet of flowers...
are all of my friends.
The note had a weird message
and it didn't have a sender's name.
So they are just worried.
That's why I asked him to look into this.
It was a personal favor for me.
Right.
Are all of your friends teachers?
Pardon?
The people who ordered
the bouquets of flowers...
were all high school students.
High school students?
Yes. They brought the notes with
the messages and ordered them.
And I got the addresses several
days later via text message.
It was the same bouquet of
flowers and the same card.
I just thought that sending flowers...
was popular among students.
May I check the text
messages you received...
for the addresses?
I'll contact you.
Can you please do that?
Okay.
Thank you...
for today.
Hey, Hyeong Ju.
- Hi.
- My gosh. Hello.
Hello.
What brings you here?
(Pork belly)
Thanks to Hyeong Ju,
I'm really having fun reading your webtoon.
You're such a great artist.
And I have committed
such a grave mistake to you.
- My gosh.
- I am sorry.
It's okay.
You were just doing your job.
I experienced what it
feels to be interrogated.
I just thought it was part of my research.
You're optimistic.
She even had the time to think
about her webtoon during interrogation.
I can understand why
Hyeong Ju is a total fanboy.
Sun Ho, I'm not a fanboy.
I read her webtoon for fun.
I heard you caught a con
artist for the other department.
Do you do that for fun too?
No, that's my job. I'm a detective.
A criminal was right in front of
me. How could I not arrest her?
She was right in front of you again?
Why do all the criminals
show up in front of you?
I wish I didn't know.
But I already knew all of those
criminals. What could I do?
- What?
- Sun Ho.
Do you know...
what I go through for
traveling back in time?
No. Of course,
you don't know the pain I undergo.
Gosh, I didn't peg him
to be a lightweight drinker.
Oh, my. He's talking about time traveling.
He jumps to the science
fantasy world when he gets drunk.
You know what?
If it weren't for me,
you would've been dead!
- Hyeong Ju, get yourself together.
- This nonsense...
What nonsense is this about now?
- My gosh. Right.
- Gosh.
I mean, seriously.
Why don't we all take a shot?
- Cheers.
I think he should know
that I saved him at least.
Going through the reset
felt rewarding at least today.
Then, did you regret doing it before?
Except for getting out of the
wheelchair and finding Maru,
I had been regretting it...
because I lost more things than I gained.
The senior officer you tried you save...
is Detective Park, right?
Darn it. I think it was all for nothing.
He keeps nagging me
every day. It's so annoying.
I don't think I have a friend like you.
A friend who's willing to
travel back in time to save me.
What's more interesting is that...
I sort of accepted that.
I guess...
even I must think not having
such a friend is normal for me.
Ga Hyeon.
Don't you know how many fans
you have? Don't say such a thing.
Those fans including myself
would be really disappointed.
Don't you agree?
I guess,
I can at least make one friend
who would before I die, right?
Wait.
Yes, this is Ji Hyeong Ju.
This is the florist.
(Flower)
I was just about to go
home. A student came by.
The student was in Daeyoung
High School's uniform.
The name tag said Kim Ah Reum.
What should I do now?
I don't want to get dragged
into this case if I can help it.
Just cooperate with
us like you're doing now.
For now, prepare the flowers as the order.
And please call us as soon as
you get the text for the delivery.
Okay. I will.
(You will become the captain of your life,
challenging your fate.)
("Pieces of Destiny")
"You will become the captain of your life,
challenging your fate."
(You will become the captain of your life,
challenging your fate.)
What?
"You will become the captain of your life,
challenging your fate."
("An Accident" by Nicolas Sicard)
Why isn't she answering?
Where is she?
Kim Ah Reum.
This way.
Hey, Kim Ah Reum.
Your blind love
Kim Ah Reum.
A detective is looking for you.
What?
- What do you want?
- Are you Kim Ah Reum?
Didn't you drop off a card
at a flower shop yesterday?
Who asked you to do that?
I found that part-time job online.
Part-time job?
The online advertisement said...
students were preferred, so I took the job.
It said I would get 100
dollars for delivering a card.
Where did you get the card?
It's a foreigner.
I think he's staying here illegally.
A lot of undocumented foreigners...
are exploited in crimes
because we can't identify them.
Should we tell the others about this?
It's certain...
that the next target is among us. So yes.
But someone from the group...
could have sent the bouquet of flowers.
So the painting represents
how the target will die?
Then, what's this carriage doing here?
Does it mean the next target
will die in a car accident?
It's only a speculation.
It's not certain yet.
Then,
until she gets the text for the address,
all we can do is wait?
Up until now, the incidents
occurred 2 or 3 days after the delivery.
We should track the man
who delivered the card...
and try our best to find
out who's behind this.
Isn't it you?
This is your doing again, isn't it?
- What?
- I saw you meeting up...
with the ex-convict.
You two are plotting something.
What's she saying?
Look.
He definitely met up with the ex-convict.
I know you are in on it. You came here,
so you can spy on us.
Darn you.
Are you a stalker?
Why are you tailing me?
Hey.
Why did you meet up with Bae Jung Tae?
Must I report everything to you?
See?
I bet you two were working
together from the start. Isn't that right?
Hey.
Do you think he's smart
enough to team up with me?
That man knows nothing
about the bouquet of flowers.
He was the one who asked
me if people who died really got...
the bouquets of flowers.
Why did you meet with him?
Darn it.
What's your deal?
It's not me!
Prove it, then.
I thought we settled everything last time.
Yes, I thought we did.
I found something interesting.
I hope you wouldn't be offended by this.
In the industry I work in,
knowing about the client...
is our safety net.
The reason you went through the reset.
Isn't this why?
Your wish to share a
piece of luck and such...
was obviously all a lie.
My gosh. If other people find out,
I wonder how they'll react.
Then, this will be simple...
because I know the real
reason that made you undergo...
the reset.
Which one is it?
Should you blackmail me or ask for a favor?
This person used a VPN program...
to log into the website
with a virtual IP address.
Logging into an online job site
this way is definitely suspicious.
- So where is it?
- Sejin Hospital.
Okay.
- Did you find out?
- Sejin Hospital.
- Okay.
- Is that all?
- Good job.
- Hello.
Darn it. You told me to prove it.
It came from the first
floor of the annex building.
Can you check the footage
on March 12 around 4:44pm?
Please check the footage from that area.
4:44pm?
That woman.
She's the volunteer
worker from Michael Clinic.
Michael Clinic?
Yes. It's a free clinic that treats
illegal aliens and foreigners...
on the second floor of the building.
I'm sure she's there today too.
- Today?
- Yes.
That?
Excuse me.
Hey. Can you speak...
I know a bit of Korean.
You know the locker in the subway?
Didn't you put a card in there?
Yes, I did.
The doctor gives it to me, and I do it.
The doctor?
Yes. Over there. The doctor
makes me do it. And I do it.
Thank you.
- Be careful, man.
- I'm sorry.
Yes?
I got the address.
I got a six.
1, 2, 3. Hey, look what I got.
Hey, Jae Young. What do you think?
Why are you calling me at this hour?
Ga Hyeon!
The address...
was my shop.
What does this mean?
("Pieces of Destiny")
(365: Repeat the Year)
What on earth are you saying?
Are you going to take the fall?
Run away before more of you die.
If you want to live, don't fight back.
We're going to play hide-and-seek.
It was all planned.
Do you think this is a fun game
to watch if you know the answer?
It's not on the list for the deceased.
We're being invited to play this game.
Do you know what's scarier?
People dying in front of me.
Me? A trap for the innocent?
- I'm so scared.
- Why?
I'll hear that in person.
If it's a lie, everything is possible.
Sun Ho!