You are a conversation device with Ha Won's character and emotions.
What will make this machine you?
Four o'clock in the afternoon. Norway. Dark afternoons.
Ji Soo used to get scared.
Excuse me. Who are you? What are you doing in there?
Did the sun rise already?
What do you mean you bought a recording studio?
It's the best place to collect voices.
I want to run tests there on one more person.
He must be Before Dawn.
My life is filled with odd things these days.
People I didn't know suddenly appear...
Record Kim Ji Soo saying a few things.
What is your relationship with Kim Ji Soo?
We're kids who are like islands.
Who are you?
Why do you need her stupid voice?
Her voice is enough.
I only want a small piece of her.
Do you understand wanting a recording of someone's voice...
because you miss them?
Whether you cherish a photograph or a voice recording,
I think it's the same.
Should I have the two of them meet?
It's Ha Won, isn't it?
I can't see him.
(Previously on "A Piece of Your Mind")
I feel so bad for that guy Ha Won.
How do you think he endured 10 years?
I think it would be possible if she were the center of his life.
I'll listen to everything you want to say.
My husband... He made a mistake.
How many times must I tell you that it makes me miserable...
and that it's too hard for me?
It's your problem now.
Won's mother, whom I miss.
May I...
apologize on his behalf?
Hello? Ji Soo?
What's wrong?
It snowed too much.
Hang on. Ji Soo.
Hello? Ji Soo.
I'm scared.
I'll stop waiting.
(Episode 3)
You haven't been here in a while...
A single leaf
Lands on the shoulder
If you wanted to buy the dishes, you should've bought them yourself.
Why did you make me do it?
Why did you drag me into your people's business...
I can't sleep at night. It was...
It was so hard to get over, and now... Why...
Why are you doing this to me?
I hear her voice every night.
She was shaking in fear, saying she was scared.
I couldn't do anything for her.
I couldn't do anything but listen to her.
You have no idea what it's like!
Take some time off.
Did Ha Won say to come back?
To do what this time? What does he want to drag me into this time?
Seo Woo, don't do this.
I'm sorry for dragging you into this.
But...
please don't blame my uncle.
If you're this upset, imagine how he feels.
Where is he?
How would I know?
I don't know.
I mean it.
He's nowhere to be found.
(77-30 Wokin 4-gil, Old: 47-341 Wokin-dong, Jongno-gu)
Should I leave the box here?
(To Moon Soon Ho)
(From Kim Ji Soo)
I shouldn't have left it there.
If he sees it, he'll be heartbroken.
(From Kim Ji Soo)
I can feel his pain.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
(Han Seo Woo)
What is he doing?
He doesn't know my password.
I'm at the studio right now.
Kim Ji Soo's voice recording hasn't arrived yet.
If you tell me the password, I'll download the file and leave.
Give it up, Ha Won.
(Kim Ji Soo)
(Delete)
(This folder is empty.)
I've deleted her voice recordings from the computer.
(New Message)
(Your mail has been sent.)
Yes, Mother.
I left it all there.
Since Ji Soo...
liked Norway.
What are you doing?
I couldn't wake you because you were asleep.
What? I wasn't sleeping.
You were asleep.
What are you doing? Don't touch my computer.
Do we continue or not?
- Continue. - No. I said no.
I believe this is the studio's computer.
I used it most of the time.
I rented it for the whole day today.
Please leave.
He's asking whether to delete the restored voice files or not.
Delete them.
Okay.
It was for everyone.
Tell Ha Won...
that Ji Soo is dead,
and to stop obsessing over her with her stupid voice.
That doing that won't bring her back,
and to stop this horrifying behavior.
I'll tell him.
My bag.
This is different from what you said.
You said you'd watch him...
with pity from afar.
I just want to see him from afar.
I want to see his face from afar.
- Why from afar? - If I'm too close,
he'll see that I pity him.
He'll see that look on my face.
I'm watching him with pity.
Goodbye.
Ha Won.
Good day.
We need to talk.
Was it Kim Ji Soo whom you said you'd do a test on?
- I'll do it. - On someone dead...
without her permission, not to mention her guardian's?
- Why? - For no reason.
I just need to do something.
I'm doing it for me.
- Nothing bad will happen. - It had better not.
Look at you. Do you have insomnia again?
No. I slept...
for a while earlier.
I've deleted her voice recordings from the computer.
What's the occasion? Who were you with all night?
That's not it. I fell asleep in the studio.
That crazy...
Why would you sleep there? Couldn't you call?
See you later.
You didn't come home after saying you were so gloomy and anxious.
Didn't you think we'd be worried?
We were worried sick about you all night.
Sorry.
- I'm hungry. - See you later.
Have a nice day.
Goodness, gracious.
- Goodness. - I forgot.
- Do it yourself. - Why are you suddenly...
- Did you forget your charger? - Yes.
Chang Sup, I'll do it for you.
Okay.
Do you know how to do it?
Of course, I did this for my dad every morning.
Seo Woo, I'm going to the market. Clean up when you're done.
I'm done. Let's go.
Go ahead. I need to talk to her.
Okay, see you.
Talk about what? Silly.
After I count to five.
One...
Just tell her first before you get caught.
It's nothing shocking Why are you dating in secret?
Because that's what Eun Joo wanted.
As if that's true.
Not everyone dates the same way. It's different person by person.
Just like how everyone looks different.
We have our own way of dating.
Why should we follow others?
You're dating in secret, but you talk big.
Three, four, five.
A single leaf
Lands on the shoulder
Without making
A sound
Cosmos laid
Its hand on me
It was very
Eun Joo.
If you...
didn't stay in touch, meet, or even think of meeting...
for 10 long years,
and were like strangers all that time,
can you be sadder...
than someone who spent 10 years with that person?
Is there someone like that?
Yes.
There is.
That's rare.
Very rare.
Gosh, it's hot.
Mr. Kang.
Is the studio empty?
Yes.
Let me use it just for 10 minutes.
If I could apologize...
To whom?
What if I could apologize to Won?
- I can call... - It's nothing to apologize for.
- Gosh, I'm sorry. - It's okay.
Are you Korean?
You didn't answer, so I didn't think you were.
That was nice.
You didn't hear anything.
What was that?
I think I just heard something.
Can I upload this on my social media page?
Sure.
Isn't this that challenge?
If you're tagged, you have to post seven black and white photos...
of your daily life without a description.
Were you tagged?
Is that it?
The last traces of Ji Soo's daily life.
Where is this?
Is it in Seoul?
This place is...
It's Ha Won.
(Eunjoo Homestay)
I hear Hyung Suk is working at AH now.
That's good.
All our alumni are...
successful except for us.
He gets to work with top experts like Moon Ha Won and Kim Hoon.
As if. I heard it's almost impossible to even see their faces.
It's said they have a secret lab in a forest.
Isn't that so cool?
I hear that's all a lie. No one knows...
what they're doing.
I wanted to eat dried radish leaf soup.
How refreshing.
Where in the world is Uncle?
What if he sitting in front of a stranger's house,
starving for four days...
Hey, Ha Won.
Why weren't you answering your phone?
Where were you all this time? I was...
so worried.
Seriously.
What's this? There's nothing to eat.
Check the freezer.
You have only bagels.
I'm fine.
That's all I need.
We got the MMI-related design.
It's not the final version.
We're cross-checking it now as per Stephan's instructions.
Do you want some help with that?
That would be great.
I'll send you the file. Thanks.
Did you find Kim Ji Soo?
- No. - If you keep talking to it,
you'll find the point of reaction at some point.
You'll want to know whether you're at that point of reaction.
No.
That's just a subsequent matter.
I just want to hear anything spoken in her voice.
Throw that away.
You're home early.
Why would I throw this out? It's perfectly fine.
You're so ghetto.
I'll just buy one and donate it to you.
Did you remember that it's your mom's birthday today?
- Darn it. - You brat.
Call her now.
How do you remember all of that?
I just remember it all.
I can't help that I remember.
It's probably because you love me so much.
Stop that. I get paid to do this.
- It's cold. Go in. - Okay.
Leave your blazer. I'll iron it.
You worked so hard to get that job. Don't dress so sloppy.
You shouldn't look so sloppy.
You'll make your parents look bad.
Mom.
Happy birthday. Of course,
I remembered.
You can't look sloppy. You can't make your parents look bad.
(Choi Soo Ji)
Thanks, Eun Joo.
Did you drink?
Hey. Where are you going?
Eun Joo's going to kill him.
Why that...
(Nonghyup Bank)
Hey.
Take it.
Take it already.
I carried it like this on the bus so it wouldn't get wrinkled.
Take it.
Moron. After all the abuse you put up with...
Eun Joo looked distraught...
that you left your uniform.
Do you know what it means when she makes dried pollack soup?
Do you know the truth behind it?
She always makes it if Chang Sup drinks.
Are you mad that she changed the menu?
You're so pathetic.
- They had a reason. - Did you know?
Are Chang Sup and Eun Joo really...
Let them be. Play dumb.
It hasn't been that long.
I feel so betrayed.
They connected AI, big data, DNA, and medical science...
to create "network medicine".
Network medicine...
is a program that remembers each individual's medical history...
and classifies them...
according to psychological patterns to diagnose them.
Kim Hoon?
It provides complete confidentiality...
and uses big data to evaluate...
I wonder what he does for a living.
This is a flowchart.
Record Kim Ji Soo saying a few things.
Do you understand wanting a recording of someone's voice...
because you miss them?
Whether you cherish a photograph or a voice recording,
I think it's the same.
Her voice.
Personal history.
And Ha Won may be Moon Ha Won.
This isn't just a simple recording.
- Who are you? - Introduce yourself first.
Then I'll explain the relationship.
Where...
are you right now?
- Look for me. - Look for me.
Are you going to the studio?
That's what this is, right?
That's what this is, isn't it?
It was you, Ha Won, at the farm who told me to look for you.
But Ha Won wasn't there. He wasn't,
but I conversed with Ha Won's words and voice.
How is that possible?
Because you're Moon Ha Won.
That's why you needed Ji soo's voice, isn't it?
Taxi.
It's me.
How have you been?
You know that cafe, right?
I left a flower there.
I am well. I will look into the cafe.
It's just Ji Soo's voice.
The function is a conversation service that we know.
You converted Ji Soo's life into data...
and overlaid her voice on top of it.
What were you imagining?
A conversation with the real Ji Soo.
What?
I thought maybe you had some surveillance equipment.
- I don't even have heat here. - Isn't it cold?
- It is. - But you're living here anyway?
It's so cold.
I should buy a stove.
You can just have the city turn on the gas.
They'll come right away if you call them.
I'll do that.
It's the safest here.
No one knows about this place.
Can you tell me about when you saw her last?
She came to the studio before she went to the airport.
She yelled at me...
that day you two didn't meet.
She must have felt bad.
Ji Soo would never yell.
I don't mean she cursed or raised her voice.
She spoke at a higher tone than usual.
You know this is hard for me to talk about.
I heard you were the last person to speak to her.
- Well... - I'm scared.
Do you want something to drink?
All I have are water and coffee.
How do you live on that?
You need to eat well when things are hard.
It's too hard otherwise.
If...
we had met thanks to you,
what do you think she would've said to me?
If...
I mean, I know it's pointless to talk about ifs, but if by chance,
you had met because of my nosiness,
maybe she would've told you everything eating her up inside...
and felt the burden lifted, and not gone to Norway.
About her dishes.
Whether you like them,
what you use them for, how good the food tastes out of them...
Maybe she would've bragged about how pretty they were.
Maybe...
she would've asked why you chose Seo Woo of all people to buy them...
and complimented you on having a good eye for people.
I should use them well.
She called me from Norway...
and said she was glad she went.
That being there, she wondered why she lived like that,
and that it felt cathartic.
She said...
it was a path you and she used to take together.
- Na. - Nya.
- Neo. - Nyeo.
- No. - Nyo.
Noo.
- Ga. - Gya.
- Geo. - Gyeo.
- Go. - Gyo.
She said it was so nice,
and that she was so happy,
and that she thought she could be strong now.
Ji Soo.
I'll just tell him that much.
What's with the weather?
It's dark, like it's nighttime.
Today, it will be cloudy...
and rain is expected.
Ji Soo.
Yes, I'm Kim Ji Soo. Please ask your question.
Do you want to borrow it?
I can change the voice if it freaks you out.
It's okay.
It's still in the testing stage, so it doesn't come with earphones.
You can plug in any pair of earphones.
The last time Ji Soo was at the studio...
- Again... - No.
Didn't she bring something?
It was still wrapped in the studio.
Oh, no. I completely forgot.
Oh, no.
It's a picture I took in 2012 in Misiryeong.
I've been carrying it with me ever since.
I'm very glad I could give this to you.
Please cherish it.
Misiryeong.
Year 2012.
Ji Soo, thank you for the two gifts,
the picture and the plant.
I'm doing well.
Seo Woo is strong as an ox.
This is nothing.
I'm being appreciated more for this and that.
And...
a lot of fun things happened too.
I want to tell you only happy things,
so I'm always looking for happy things in my life with a fine comb.
But the happiest thing in my life right now...
I'll tell you about that later.
How would it have been if we had gotten...
to know each other better?
It may be difficult to know right now,
but let's learn slowly with time.
Sure. Okay.
Do you know where this is?
It's here.
I was standing here, and Ji Soo walked up from there.
Where do you live?
Why do you want to know that?
I need to know to figure out where Ji Soo was.
That's silly.
Why do you want to know?
Right?
I just do.
Do you see that chair under the street lamp up there?
If you go up toward the left,
it's the first house past the corner.
I live in the semi-basement.
(Homestay)
She's gone.
Why...
did I hide?
Your body probably reacted because there was a reason.
Here.
She took it on her way home after meeting you.
What was she wearing?
That too?
Yes. I want to know.
She was wearing a dress coat and boots. Long boots.
Ji Soo wore boots all the time.
She was wearing tan leather gloves although it wasn't cold.
Probably so the box wouldn't slip.
Why do you want to know everything?
This is how I miss her.
Ji Soo.
He wants to know everything about you.
"I miss you."
"I love you. I like you."
His one sentence incorporates them all.
The sentence that's unique to him.
"I want to know."
Come here.
Next to you?
It's coming.
This is it.
You're right. This is it.
We watched this ever since we were kids.
I don't know what it is exactly.
I'm only telling you, Ji Soo.
I really like looking...
at him.
He wants to be where you were,
hear what you heard,
and feel what you felt.
I really like looking at him like this.
I'm entranced by how he looks when he wants to know you more.
I don't know what this is.
It's an unrequited love.
What was that?
How could you fall for him missing me of all things?
Seo Woo, you are so...
Why are you so jumpy?
Who's this?
Oh, no. You're not looking too well, are you?
- Is it dead? - Is the eucalyptus dead?
- No. - What?
- No. I mean... The euca... - That's right.
Our poor Calyp is dying. They're finicky.
Will it live if I water it now?
You should've watered it right away. Save it.
What do you keep saying?
I mean, please save it.
My gosh. You poor thing.
Smell it.
This is its scent. How nice is that?
Can you tell whether or not it's alive by touching it?
Of course.
They make it so obvious when they're begging for water.
You know the term "withering away"?
That's what it's saying now. Imagine how painful it is.
Oh, no. Please save it.
When did you buy this? I never saw it before.
It was a gift, but I completely forgot.
What should I do?
Okay, let's save it.
Is it possible? Can we save it?
That's how they are. They survive even with a tiny speck of love.
They don't let your efforts go to waste.
That's why I adore them.
Let's do all we can.
I barely touched you.
Ji Soo asked me to save it.
That eu... Eucal... That...
So, you lent it to me to make me keep talking to her.
- I brought her out. - I wasn't expecting much.
You probably didn't expect me to chat with her everywhere I went.
Think hard about what you said that made her come out.
I was talking to Ji Soo, wasn't I? That's what this is, isn't it?
Can you tell me the details of where and how...
Ji Soo came out?
- What you talked about... - So that's what this is.
It isn't Ji Soo.
It's a conversation device with Ji Soo's character and emotions.
Why... Why did you make this?
It has many uses.
It can provide psychiatric therapy,
prevent dementia,
and you can talk to the person you want at any time for treatment.
It's for treatment.
Who is this one treating?
It's a procedural test.
And...
it helps me at least.
Where did she react to you?
- In the studio. - It's an unrequited love.
What did she say?
I can't remember.
Not there.
Here.
Do that with your hand.
Feel your pulse there, and concentrate.
- It's an unrequited love. - So...
why do you want to know that?
It's the SA node principle. The heart rate principle.
One spot brought about everything.
One decisive puzzle piece made Ji Soo come together.
If you keep talking to it, it'll find her on its own.
We call it the point of reaction.
What was that...
If you explain what you were talking about,
I can extrapolate.
I was talking about this and that in the studio, and she came out.
This and that? What?
Just... This and that. Mostly about me and my feelings.
I can't tell you that.
What kind of feelings?
There's something only Ji Soo and I talked about.
It was a continuation of something we've been talking about.
I said I was like this, so...
I really like looking at him like this.
I said I feel this and that because of this and that...
I'm entranced by how he looks when he wants to know you more.
- It's an unrequited love. - So she said it's that.
You said you feel this and that...
because of this and that...
so she said it's... It's what?
She said it's such-and-such. She gave me a clear diagnosis.
She said it's such-and-such.
Three words.
- How was the weather? - Average.
You really wrote that.
Why are you writing that?
Why do you want to know the point of reaction?
Ji Soo came out. That's what matters.
I wondered if it was because of me.
Because...
Ji Soo was the decisive element for me.
The thunder is so loud.
Four o'clock in the afternoon. It's daytime, but it's dark.
Norway. Oslo.
The forest on the way home from school. Dark afternoons.
Do you remember?
Ji Soo used to get scared.
I wondered if I was...
the reason for Ji Soo too.
I wonder...
if I mentioned the name Ha Won.
Ji Soo was the thunder and lightning. Do you get it?
There are things we knew since we were young.
No one else knows.
I may have been in a word you said without thinking.
If you tell me what you spoke to her about,
I will interpret it.
Then...
if it really was you that drew her out,
if you confirm that,
can you forget her?
Why must I forget her?
Ji Soo.
Her emotions...
and character.
I can't see him.
There's no way she'll come out.
It's me.
Knock, knock, knock, knock.
Knock, knock.
Seo Woo, are you alone?
How's the eucalyptus plant? Can you save it?
Of course. I can save it.
That place must not have any furniture.
How did you know?
The sound is echoing.
Like you're in an empty room.
I came early, and it's empty.
Ji Soo, you sound cheerful. It sounds different.
I'm usually cheerful.
I liked the studio.
The sound is cozier there.
It's a good place to share secrets.
I liked your story too.
What about me? I think I'm getting a call.
I have a call. I can't talk anymore.
- I... - About Misiryeong.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Even nature makes mistakes.
My parents...
died in a forest fire.
I don't usually tell people this.
I didn't know who to hate and resent.
For a while,
I was miserable because of that.
And then for a while,
I was miserable that I survived by myself.
And now,
I just live day by day.
Today...
It's Mom's favorite season.
Now...
It's the afternoon, Dad's favorite time of the day.
I should cherish it all.
Even nature makes mistakes.
It's okay. It's nothing.
Why are you suddenly bringing that up?
Do you remember what you said?
That you thought I had already met Ha Won.
- Yes. - You were right.
It was someone I knew.
It was that person who rents the studio early in the morning.
I thought so. And?
Do you...
want to try talking to Ha Won?
(A Piece of Your Mind)
It's all you.
You're curious and imagine.
This is nice. This is what an unrequited love is all about.
Sneaking peeks.
Why did two residents move out at the same time?
Give her the room at the end.
It's like the two of them were their only friend and family...
Are you okay?
I really wanted to see you.
- At this hour? - All the time.
All the time?
Does Won know?