I guess Won doesn't know...
that you like him.
You said you liked seeing him.
To be more precise, it's unrequited love.
Do you not feel that way anymore?
Well...
I like him.
I really like looking at him.
The way he cherishes you,
the way he misses you,
the way a person gives his all for another person...
I like it all.
Won doesn't know how you feel, does he?
No.
I don't want him to know.
You had no idea how much he cherished you either.
I hope...
he won't know either.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
Why are you following me?
It's late. I'll take you home.
- I... - Don't.
- What? - Don't do anything.
I didn't do anything.
Look. I'm okay, so don't worry about what Ji Soo said...
- I'll pretend I don't know. - No.
Don't do that either. Don't do anything.
What did you mean by you like looking at me?
- I'm leaving. - I'll go with you.
I won't do anything.
Can I really do nothing?
Isn't there anything I can do for you?
If I say there is, will you do it?
Tell me.
It'll be tough.
Try me.
You must be in a good mood.
You were at Ji Soo's point of reaction.
That's why you're in a good mood.
You're right. Goodnight.
Darn it. I'm so embarrassed.
Ji Soo.
Is this not a good place?
Should we go to the studio?
You seem to be comfortable there.
We're at the studio now.
So you can hear too.
Is it too dark?
Why are you comfortable here?
You said you were more comfortable at the studio.
Ji Soo.
Let's take it slowly. Slowly.
I heard you recited it like an incantation...
whenever you were scared walking home alone...
after I left Norway.
I can do it alone, Won.
Get used to it slowly. Slowly.
Sure.
Let's take it slowly.
Did you talk to her?
No. She won't talk to me.
I'll continue to know nothing.
Our studio may end up only renting out our mics.
How nice would it have been to film that in our studio?
The hourly rate was insane.
Jin Moo brings you a lot of work.
What's the use?
They always bring a sound engineer.
Your talents are being wasted.
I guess it's hard to make it in this field too.
It's hard everywhere.
What if you don't get to debut until you're 60?
I'm fine with what I do now.
I'm happy just being kept on.
Liar.
Still, I'm sure you'll debut before you turn 60.
Gosh.
Hey. Leave that and go.
I'll put them away first.
I'll do it. I forgot I was expecting a guest.
Okay.
Okay. I'll take that.
Thanks for today.
It's okay.
Gosh.
Hey. Open the door for me.
Okay.
Gosh.
You're so mean.
How could you just say that?
Crushes are always in secret.
No one tells the person they have a crush on them.
What do you mean?
You said everything in front of Ha Won.
Were you with Won?
You said you were home.
What were you doing together at home at night?
That girl is Han Seo Woo.
Leave a little later so you don't run into her.
No good will come of meeting each other.
- Avoid her. - That's a bit much.
Han Seo Woo knows too much about Kim Ji Soo...
whom you're so curious about.
And she's most curious about you right now.
The two of your frantic curiosity...
will only lead to Kim Ji Soo.
What's the use in talking? It's best not to know anything.
Don't even bring up her name.
Ji Soo this. Ji Soo that. You talk about her the most.
Me?
The address here is 47-431 Wokin-dong.
This house is like Ha Won's office.
He discusses important issues here.
It's the address for the package.
That's why he wanted to receive it here.
- I guess. - I see.
I know I sold the dishes,
but why did I do that?
She doesn't know why?
(Prescription)
If you keep talking to it, it'll find her on its own.
Wouldn't it be nice to record songs with the windows open here?
I really liked the performances...
recorded in places like houses and churches too.
The acoustics are nice here.
When you go to a nice church, you can hear the piano more clearly.
It's like that here.
I should try recording something here.
If you do, let me hear it.
Of course.
Use your work as an excuse to be here with Won.
Oh, come on.
There are no curtains here, are there?
- No. - How far does the sunlight reach?
Enough to cover the entire living room.
Sunlight is precious in Oslo. The afternoons are short.
I saw pictures of Korea, and there were curtains in every room.
Won and I used to wonder...
why they blocked out the precious sunlight.
Sunlight is precious to me too.
- I live in a semi-basement. - I see.
Have you ever visited Ha Won's house?
Of course, not.
I wonder what his place looks like.
- Should I check it out for you? - That's such a transparent excuse.
Just show me around this place.
He won't invite me over anyway.
Here comes the evidence that this place is his office.
It's business for Ha Won, but you have ulterior motives.
- I've gotten comfortable. - What?
I've become quite comfortable talking with you, Ji Soo.
Let's look for furniture that would be nice here.
Just the bare minimum.
Won doesn't keep anything around that he doesn't need.
Do that for me.
Will you do me a favor in return?
What is it?
There's something strange.
Ji Soo doesn't know why she sold her dishes.
Why did she?
I don't know.
Do you live here?
I sent you an e-mail.
That place is too empty. Make sure you buy them.
- These are Ji Soo's style. - She picked them with me.
Make sure to buy them.
She'll only do what I ask if you do.
She worries about you all the time.
There's nothing to worry about me.
I'm worried about Han Seo Woo who lives here.
The doors are about to break down.
It looks like it would be cold and damp.
You're staring at me way too obviously.
I'm so offended.
I did something important, but I won't tell you.
- What is it? - What do I get in return?
You say that all the time.
Just tell me. I don't care how difficult it is.
I'll tell you, so you have to do it no matter what.
I wake up every night at 2am and 4am.
I'll call you whenever I do.
It's very difficult, isn't it?
I'm always awake at those times.
- Call me. - Really?
Ji Soo agreed to talk to you.
Tomorrow evening.
Are you touched?
I did good, didn't I?
- What are you doing? - I'm looking at you with pity.
I'm watching him with pity.
Seo Woo.
Thank you.
(2:04am)
(Before Dawn)
(Han Seo Woo)
Room service.
- Shall I extend your stay? - No.
Aren't you going to work again?
I'm going to enjoy touring around our hotels for the rest of my life,
using all the hotel vouchers that I got as an employee.
You've never used any.
You must have quite a lot of them.
I'll let you rest.
Where is Seo Woo?
She had breakfast and left.
What are you wearing?
What's wrong with it?
It's just us two in the house.
Let's not get too comfortable around each other.
I said not to waste the soup!
I wear this all the time.
Hand me the list quickly.
Let's hurry things.
Min Jung?
Are you here early to see me?
Shall we go to my office together?
No, I'll finish this first.
Are you going on a trip or something?
Doctor, my appointment is at 1:30pm.
- Right. - It's 1:15pm right now.
I'll see you at my appointment.
Gosh.
It's been forever since I took a trip.
Why are we living like this, eating gimbap and sandwiches?
Doctor.
Oh, okay.
Right, why don't you do a test?
It hasn't been commercialized yet,
but it's about having a conversation with a device...
that portrays your personality and emotions.
Are you interested?
I'll see you at 1:30pm.
Okay, okay.
My gosh.
I bought this a little while ago, so it's still warm.
Eat this too. I'll see you at my office.
Gosh, my back.
My back hurts because I'm always stuck in my office.
It's good for menopause...
to move every part of your body like this.
I'll see you in 10 minutes then.
It's just tuna. I don't want it.
Do you have a place to stay?
Did you come all the way here to ask me that?
You keep screening my calls.
Just enjoy your relationship.
And don't mind me.
You're so chill.
I'll get going.
Goodness. Seriously.
Why do you look so down?
I'm getting all achy...
now that I have less work.
Why do you have less work? Chang Sup eats the most.
You guys ate a lot too.
I was so good to you, and you ate so much.
Now that's more like you, raising your voice like that.
So...
stop acting out, and come back.
I have a few gift certificates left at the salon.
You can use them.
It's a gift for you.
What time are you going to talk today?
I'll be in charge of the hardware and sensor signals.
And Do Hyun will be in charge of the processor and output.
I'll do the software training.
How much test data do we have so far?
She won't answer me.
I'll help you.
- Where are you going? - We're taking a break.
I need to step out.
Ji Soo.
Exactly what time today?
Okay.
It's 6pm today. Good luck.
Did she leave?
At 6pm tonight.
Finally.
- Good work. - Good work.
Finally what, at 6pm?
Is it near the studio?
Hand out our business cards if you can.
Let's work hard at promoting our studio.
Oh, no. We didn't choose a location.
Sit down, guys.
Oh, hello.
In Wook is here. Let's join them.
We offer discounts for practices.
- Why aren't you giving me one? - Of course, I will.
Here.
I heard your wife was traveling. Is she not back yet?
No. She doesn't seem to want to come back.
What is a woman thinking when she takes a trip alone?
What about a man?
This is not about a difference between men and women.
They could go on a trip alone if they have a reason.
They might need some time to think,
or maybe to meet someone.
Meet whom?
Soon Ho, please stop.
He's already sensitive because of the recording.
I hear you're taking In Wook out. How could you do that?
Who said that? No one told me.
No, it's been called off.
Try to reschedule the recording.
His slump won't last long.
Excuse me.
You left behind something important.
Did I do something wrong?
You're being rude to my face.
Just tell me what exactly made you mad.
Is it because I said she may be meeting someone?
Why are you getting strange ideas? I meant a friend.
A female friend.
She could've gone there to meet...
Your wife...
is cool.
What did I say?
Do you see me?
I don't.
Oh, I see you. Here.
I see you.
That way.
Ji Soo. We didn't set a location.
Near the studio.
The overpass?
I know where.
You'll talk to him only once?
That's so mean.
Okay. Just once.
Okay.
You have to talk to Ha Won...
later, okay?
Even if it's just once.
I'll let you rest now.
You heard, right? She'll talk to you only once.
What will you talk about if it's only once?
That must be hard.
There's something I want to hear,
and something I want to tell her.
See you.
(5:59pm)
Ji Soo.
I became miserable, but I didn't call him.
I won't. I will never.
I know, but...
I understand, but...
please come out.
Ji Soo.
"Ji Soo."
Are you going to say my name all day long?
What's wrong?
Why aren't you talking?
Well...
It's just this once. I'll talk to you once.
What do you want to talk about?
I thought a lot about what I should talk about, but...
I wondered...
what we'd talk about...
if we had just one chance to talk.
- Did you do that on purpose? - Yes.
"What would Ha Won say to me if he had only one chance?"
But look at you. You can't say anything.
"Ji Soo, Ji Soo."
You kept saying my name, so I was listening.
Do you see the church with the blue roof?
- Yes. - Three trees above the building.
Autumn Study Dorm.
What about the high school on the left?
I don't remember.
Where's Seo Woo?
Find her for me.
And?
- Find her first. - Why?
Why else? It's all for her.
She says she's happy just looking at you. How does that make you feel?
- I'm not sure. - Since when is Ha Won "not sure"?
It felt weird for me.
But then again,
Seo Woo and you seem to suit each other for some reason.
There's someone who suits Ji Soo.
Are you done? Already?
Ji Soo told me to do this.
This is extremely uncomfortable.
There were a lot of pretty things there.
- Show me the stuff... - What should I do?
behind where Seo Woo was standing.
The top shelf in front of Seo Woo.
That's a diffuser that I like. Buy one.
I can't afford it.
- I don't need it. - It's for me.
That candle has a nice scent.
I don't need a candle.
Sorry, Seo Woo.
Let's go.
What's that behind you? The thing that's sparkling.
Stickers.
Not this. This one is prettier.
Are we on the overpass?
Yes.
I like being here.
I feel like I'm looking at the same thing as you.
Are you standing side by side?
Are you close?
I have no choice since we're sharing earphones.
Seo Woo, you must be looking at Ha Won's side profile.
Pretty much.
And Ha Won is looking at Seo Woo's side profile.
No.
She's looking at me, so I see her straight on.
It's my side profile now.
The last I saw of Ha Won was also his side profile.
The cafe.
You ran away when you saw him inside.
Let's say that's true.
What does that mean?
When did you see me again?
The sun is setting, right?
Show me what you see right now.
So this is it.
This is how it looks when the sun sets here.
I wanted to see it.
I thought it would be nice to watch the sunset from there.
I remembered how you told me to go somewhere high up, Seo Woo.
And it caught my eye.
It would be nice to watch the sunset from there.
That's my final memory.
There's nothing...
after that.
She doesn't know anything after that.
She doesn't know why she sold her dishes,
or that she went to Norway.
She doesn't know any of that.
She'll find out on her own.
No. Never. She can never find out.
She can't find out what happens to her.
Stop it.
Stop the conversations.
The more we talk, the more she finds out.
And if we're unlucky, she'll find out everything.
Why did she sell her dishes?
To do something, anything.
She sold her dishes and went to Norway...
probably because she was miserable.
And you know why.
Am I right?
Why...
was Ji Soo hurting?
She didn't want to tell you.
Don't try to find out.
She'll find out everything! Don't do it!
If Ji Soo isn't here, neither is the reason for her misery.
There's nothing here. She's gone.
That's what it means to be gone.
She isn't gone just because I can't see her.
She's here...
to me.
That's a delusion that only idiots have.
So is an unrequited love.
Seo Woo.
I mean...
Stop it.
You spoiled brats. I'm doing my best.
I'm coaxing those hypersensitive jerks.
I'll do it this time for sure. I...
This way.
(2:09am)
(2:10am)
(Before Dawn)
I don't know if this will make any sense,
but the two things I heard most were...
to forget Ji Soo...
and to quit.
But...
I don't know what that means.
What must I do to forget and quit?
She was there even when she was gone,
and she was there even when I couldn't see her.
How could I explain that?
I don't know how to explain it,
so I never tell anyone.
I'm just saying.
It's different from your unrequited love.
Yes, it's different.
I do it for myself.
To make myself happy.
It's completely different from you.
You can't stand not knowing something, can you?
Ji Soo said...
her husband made a mistake.
That's why...
it was too hard to bear, so she didn't leave home.
She wanted to do something, so she sold her dishes.
That's all that I know.
To be exact, this is the entire reason...
Ji Soo was so miserable...
with her life.
That's why I'm telling you.
Don't try to find out more.
She didn't tell you,
so you shouldn't know.
In Wook, what...
If you're going to go behind my back,
at least do it right.
We were... Why didn't you tell him?
You said you told him.
I did not.
You should've told him. You're so mean.
What are you talking about, Mr. Song?
You said let's do it without Mr. Kang.
What brings you here?
The studio.
Okay. I'll open it for you.
Is it locked?
Give me a minute.
Are you at work?
I think the door is locked from the inside.
What time is it?
I'm...
I'm really sorry,
but can you go somewhere...
for just 30 minutes?
I need to go save someone's life.
I'll come right back and let you in.
I'll text you the code as soon as I get there.
I'm sorry.
Don't try to find out more.
She didn't tell you,
so you shouldn't know.
Oh my gosh. Oh no.
I can usually handle my alcohol.
I'm quitting drinking. I won't drink anymore.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Thanks.
If you had texted me the code,
I could've let Mr. Kang in and then come over.
- Who? - Mr. Kang's waiting.
Hold on.
He texted me yesterday.
I even replied.
But I remember none of it.
My hard work was worth it. Right?
- The code. - Oh no.
Okay. I sent it.
See?
Why... Why am I here?
- Isn't this your place? - I don't have a place in Seoul.
Look at the mess.
Is this the bedroom, living room, or kitchen?
I'm going now. Mr. Kang is really mad.
I'll call a cab.
Wait for me.
There's someone here.
- Who? - The cab's here.
That's my uncle.
It's okay. Ask him...
to leave nicely, and he will.
He's easy-going.
Or I can take care of it once I get there.
Give me five minutes. I'll be right there.
Okay.
Why was he working all night long?
Why else?
He was fixated on someone's misery.
Uncle, please go out.
Mr. Kang's there. Let him in.
He's too sensitive to say anything first.
You do it. Now.
What are you waiting for? Get in.
I left my phone.
Hurry up.
Ji Soo.
Guess where I am right now.
Stop the music.
You said you never saw Ha Won's place, right?
I did.
What did I see in there?
I saw you everywhere.
But...
this isn't right.
I hear you're taking In Wook out. How could you do that?
Who said that? No one told me.
I heard your wife was traveling. Is she not back yet?
Did she go to meet her first love or something?
- If I could apologize... - To whom?
What if I could apologize to Won?
You don't keep in touch with him.
2209-0696.
Excuse me. May I use your phone?
I'm sorry, but we don't have one.
I'm sorry, but...
can you call this number...
and check whether it's a man or a woman?
Me?
Just check whether it's a man or a woman.
If a man picks up,
please ask if he's Ha Won.
Never mind.
Sir! You forgot...
Stop it already.
Just...
let me be sad. I'm begging you.
Maybe she'll come back if she's miserable.
Maybe she'll call if she's hurting.
Possibilities. A sliver of hope.
Stop it.
Stop your neverending unrequited love.
That's right. You said you didn't know...
what it means to stop and why you should, right?
My unrequited love...
has at least one percent chance.
Who says I have one percent?
You're alive.
You don't even have one percent.
So stop it.
I'm sorry, but...
I know I should be sorry, but...
So I'll stop too.
I'm stopping because I have only one percent. You...
You should've stopped a while ago.
Where did she disappear to?
I hear you're miserable.
I'm doing well.
I'm sufficiently miserable and sufficiently happy.
She'll find out everything! Don't do it!
If Ji Soo isn't here, neither is the reason for her misery.
There's nothing here. She's gone.
That's what it means to be gone.
My unrequited love has at least one percent chance.
You're alive.
Are you alone?
Yes.
There's something I wanted to do for you.
What?
I want to hug you.
But it's...
You're so random.
I want to hug you...
and pat you on the back.
Scream.
What's gotten into you?
Scream loudly.
Do it.
More.
That's it.
When you said you'd talk to me just once,
there was something I wanted to hear from you...
and something I wanted to tell you.
I thought a lot about what I should say.
And?
I'll say what I wanted to tell you.
When I say this,
it feels like I'm hugging you.
What is it?
What I used to say...
whenever you were hurting...
or depressed.
Ji Soo.
Ji Soo?
Rest...
in peace.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
What kind of music do you want to listen to?
I guess you missed Before Dawn a lot. Me.
The last room is vacant, right?
We have to be careful about who we take in.
I wonder how Seo Woo's one percent will grow.
I'll raise him to be strong.
Who do you think you are?
In Wook. You need to stop treating people this way.
Are you stupid?
How can a person not cry?
Don't you have anything to say to Before Dawn?
Thank you,
Ha Won.