10 boxes each of essentials and medical kits?
Yes.
Make it quick.
I'm busy. I need to go catch someone.
No. This jerk threw a fit saying he needs the studio, but flaked.
He won't answer his phone either. I have to find him.
Fruit. Okay. Is that all?
Okay.
When are you coming home, Grandma?
Do you like it there that much? Do you like it more than me?
How could you?
She's too old to be doing this.
You should tell her to come home. She listens to you.
I'm so worried.
Okay. I'll try talking to her.
Don't worry.
Why do you sound so dejected?
I'll email you the list of stuff Grandma says she needs.
It's so noisy there. Where are you?
Outside.
Outside where?
You know where you are, right?
Don't space out and end up somewhere strange.
Soon Ho.
Why is it so hard?
You never say things are hard.
Seo Woo. Where were you?
I didn't see you.
Anyway, Kang In Wook isn't here.
- I'll call him. - He won't pick up.
That jerk.
Maybe he has plans.
No. That jerk just left.
He couldn't wait a few minutes.
I'm going to catch him.
May I go home?
Sure.
Something's up, isn't it?
Are you at the studio?
Yes.
I came out for a bit.
Why?
I got the best sleep there recently.
What's wrong with your apartment?
Fine.
Seriously. He doesn't need an apartment.
I should take it.
Weren't you leaving?
I'll open the studio and then go.
Okay. Bye.
Kang In Wook. I'm so annoyed.
I ran out without even washing my face.
Stop it.
Stop your neverending unrequited love.
That's right. You said you didn't know...
what it means to stop and why you should, right?
My unrequited love...
has at least one percent chance.
Who says I have one percent?
You're alive.
You don't even have one percent.
So stop it.
I'm sorry, but...
So I'll stop too.
I'm stopping because I have only one percent. You...
You should've stopped a while ago.
Did you turn on the music?
The music there is supposedly good for falling asleep.
Sleep well.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
(Episode 6)
Did you come out to greet me?
You had dinner, right?
Yes. You must have known I had a rough day.
This is nice.
- You had a rough day again? - Yes.
A new roomie is moving in today.
Since when were we "roomies"?
Everyone but you two are roomies.
I don't want to care about them.
A "roomie" sounds distant.
Here he is.
Are you Bae Jin Soo?
Hello. I'm Bae Jin Soo.
You're wearing a puffer in April.
Is this everything?
The performance... I'm sure that was you.
I was in our med school orchestra.
Is this everything?
It will be delivered tomorrow.
I see.
Gosh, your lab coat is so dirty.
Take it off as soon as you come in. I'll wash it for you.
A doctor's lab coat should be clean.
I'm just a student.
Suna in Senegal became a swimmer.
She used to be so weak. I'm proud of her.
I guess you're down about something,
seeing how you called me and are reading letters.
You got me.
Read anything at a time like that.
It will all be helpful to you guys.
That is why I've had them addressed to you,
but Soon Ho never reads any of them.
She must never get sad.
That's a good thing.
When are you coming back? Soon Ho is worried about you.
I'll be back when the time comes.
Tell her that I'll be there before the weather gets hot.
I can't bear the hot weather here either.
I'm excited already.
(4am)
(4:02am)
A single leaf
Lands on the shoulder
Well...
I was curious.
About what?
Kim Ji Soo.
Moon Ha Won's fixed point.
The coordinate center that remains no matter how distorted it gets.
The desperation that raises his technical skills to the extreme.
Could it be this person?
If then,
every research would've started with Kim Ji Soo.
Kim Ji Soo's device has been tested.
A hint about the next stage might be in here.
Delete it. Delete everything in front of me.
Right...
now.
(Deleting)
It's done.
- I just don't understand. - Of course.
It must be so frustrating...
because you can't understand even with your smart brain.
You don't have to stay.
There. Go there.
The R2 Team.
Right, you know. Go to that team.
They'll love it if you go there.
No. I won't go anywhere without Moon Ha Won and Kim Hoon.
Who is Kim Ji Soo? Who is she?
I'm not even interested.
Don't be.
Jin Hwan, this punk, has good deduction skills.
He's a smart punk.
The fixed point will never change.
But it has to satisfy Lefschetz's conditions.
And it reacts only...
when certain conditions of sections and places are met.
Lean back.
The capillaries in your eyes are about to burst.
Do you have insomnia again?
You need to sleep.
Jin Soo, do you eat breakfast?
Jin Soo.
You must be tired.
Why are you sleeping in your lab coat? It'll get all wrinkled.
Take it off.
- Goodness. - What are you...
I'll take it off of him. Seriously.
- My gosh! - What...
- Let's do it together. - Gosh.
Gosh, Jin Soo. Oh no.
Goodness, what's wrong with you?
Look how dirty this is. I need to wash it again.
Mr. Choi, where's Mr. Kang?
I've known In Wook for a long time.
It was his first chance to record an album with a major label.
But then he was struck with a slump and a sense of betrayal.
He isn't in his right mind now.
He can do it alone.
What...
I mean, your answer is too creative.
You want to record yourself when your skills are at its highest.
Not when it's at the lowest.
Then he can set a goal and improve his skills.
It's easier said than done.
All right, let's do that. Will you?
Everything survives as long as its roots aren't dead.
Where's Mr. Kang?
In the studio.
Goodness, really?
- Hello, Mr. Kang. - Turn off the light.
Don't you have something to say to me?
- What? - Gosh.
I mean, yesterday. You demanded that I open the studio...
out of the blue.
I ran over like a crazy person.
How long was I supposed to wait then?
- Couldn't you wait 10 minutes? - I waited for 20 minutes.
That's the same thing.
You should've left a text if you weren't going to wait.
Turn off the light and get out.
I'm getting to my point now.
Moon Studio is the best for overcoming a slump.
You know that?
You can record yourself alone and release an album.
What's the problem?
My studio will give you full support...
including Han Seo Woo.
You just need to make up your mind.
You have my business card, right?
- I gave you my business card. - I said, no!
Good. Yell. You finally seem human.
Call me.
I found Kang In Wook and gave him a sales pitch too.
- Did you check the timetable? - No.
Did you sleep at your place in Seoul?
Do I have a place in Seoul?
Where you passed out after getting plastered.
That's not my place.
Wait, I should just live there.
Someone already lives there.
I can make it mine.
What about the person who lives there? You shouldn't do that.
It's only a small family issue. Did you check the timetable?
I'm on my way to look at it.
Don't go. It's for a voice recording.
- That... - Yes.
It's like Kim Ji Soo. You don't want to do it, do you?
Let's just check the time and hand it over to someone else.
- We just lend them the studio. - I'll do it.
(12-9 Sejong-ro, Jongno-gu, Seoul)
Hello.
Can I take photos to post on my social media page?
I was given this address.
Give me the room at the end if I decide to move in.
Excuse me, your face.
You're still in it.
From simple consonants and vowels to sentences.
Do I just read it?
Yes, if you want to stop in the middle,
just say stop. It will all be recorded.
I hear it lets me have conversations with myself.
Is there really a machine like that?
Have you seen it?
I'm not allowed to say anything about recordings.
- I signed an NDA. - You have.
Wait. Give me those.
- You don't have to wear these. - I want to.
It looks cool.
Hello. Hello.
Start reading when I give you a sign.
"A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N,"
- "O, P, Q, R..." - Excuse me.
Let's do that again. A little slower this time.
A, B,
C, D,
- I'm sorry, a little faster. - E...
A, B, C...
"I thought it was the end for me as well as this winter,"
"so I went to Namhae without any plans."
"It was already spring there."
"Sea bass, trout, and blue crabs were in season."
Wait a second.
Do you want to take a break?
I need to post something.
It has to be at 1pm.
Okay.
I'm done.
Let's resume.
Hold on. Where was it?
Gosh, it's hard to read.
- Where's the trash can? - Give it to me.
Okay. Sorry.
I can't do this again.
My mouth is so dry now.
The room at the end is vacant, right?
Leave it vacant.
Well, okay.
She remembers me.
Heikin's book was somewhere around here.
Where is it?
In Shik, here.
Thank you.
Before Dawn,
the name of the voice recording is Kim Min Jung.
(Where are you, Before Dawn?)
Where are you, Before Dawn?
It's me. Before Dawn.
So you missed Before Dawn.
I meant the man from back then.
Exactly. The man from back then.
Me.
You must crave coffee since you just woke up.
- What do you want? - I wasn't sleeping.
I was thinking.
I see.
It's okay to have coffee with Before Dawn, right?
Why are you glaring at Before Dawn?
- Did you cry? - No.
- You look like you did. - I don't cry.
How can someone not cry?
I don't.
Oh, right. Hoon poured mustard in my cold noodles one day.
I cried while eating it.
I don't remember crying otherwise.
It's hot.
I'm here early, so I'll leave after I drink this.
I'll leave. I'm done with my work.
It's hot.
Are you going to quit?
Is that necessary?
Yes.
I want to show an example of what it means to quit.
I was going to do it to make myself happy,
but whatever.
I'm just going to quit.
That guy Ha Won is really something.
I told you he's meticulous.
No, not meticulous. That's not it.
Why quit when it's to make yourself happy?
Ha Won is Ha Won.
Leave your one percent as is. Let it be free.
Don't kill it yourself.
Ha Won will do as you said,
so you don't need to show him an example.
Just so you know.
This is your time slot,
so clean up after you're done.
Don't touch my stuff without permission.
My bag...
Do I keep the door open?
Close it.
It's dark. I thought you'd be scared.
Where's Chang Sup?
He has a family matter and is spending the night there.
That's unusual.
Come home late tomorrow.
Why?
He has the day off tomorrow.
Why are you so dense?
Oh, okay.
Enjoy your sweet time alone.
Why don't you move upstairs? We have a vacant room.
I'll give you a discount.
Not yet.
Eun Joo.
Is one percent...
potential or false hope?
If you think, "I have a whole percent,"
it's potential.
If you think, "I only have one percent," it's false hope.
What is it about?
My crush.
Just do it by yourself as you have been.
I'm going to throw it out there.
I'll throw my one percent out there,
and watch how it survives, whether it survives,
or whether it crawls and falls flat on its face.
I'll use tough love.
Are you saying you'll do it or not?
(Mr. Kang)
Sweetie.
Sweetie. Mr. Kang says he'll work on the album with you.
I proposed that.
Me.
Mr. Kang, this is Han Seo Woo.
I heard from Ms. Moon.
I'll do my best. I'll see you this afternoon.
(I'll do my best. I'll see you this afternoon.)
Why did Ji Soo have Han Seo Woo's number?
Why Han Seo Woo?
(Choi Soo Ji)
What's up?
It was nice when you got free breakfast every morning, right?
How have you been?
Why are you asking? You don't care.
I asked to be polite.
- Why are you eating breakfast? - I pulled an all-nighter.
Are things going well with Eun Joo?
Like you care.
Forget it then.
What's wrong?
Seeing you suffer after leaving because of me...
- breaks my heart. - What?
Be honest. You liked me, right?
That's why you got mad and moved out.
You're delusional.
A lot of women at work like me too.
I'm one of those guys that get more attractive with age.
This chest is a perfect fit for suits.
Having my status change overnight...
made me reflect back on whether I made the right choice.
Why you...
- I said I'd kill you... - Hey.
Underwear, socks, shirt...
I rented the room at the end.
I wanted to move in today.
Rent?
I never rented it out.
Hey, you. That guy took my deposit.
That Chang Sup guy. How dare you try to con me?
Didn't you get the deposit?
What?
I did it.
I deposited it into your account.
Check it.
She said she doesn't eat breakfast.
Why did you take in a tenant?
I was helping. Why are you whining?
I need to screen the people first.
Since when did you care about their personalities?
I worked so hard!
Darn it.
What...
Darn it!
Hello.
Were you...
the one that called...
- Let's go. - Okay.
I said I wanted the room at the end of the hall.
When?
I said over and over again that I wanted the room at the end.
But...
When? How many times?
I told that girl at the studio!
Given what it is, just leave.
Someone is already in the room at the end, so leave.
I'll return the deposit.
I won't go.
I won't budge until you give me the room at the end.
I told the girl at the studio that I wanted this room.
The girl at the studio, so Seo woo.
Let me check first.
Why aren't you picking up?
Pick up. Pick up, Seo Woo...
Seo Woo. Seo Woo, you'd better pick up!
Pick up!
Hello.
Let's talk comfortably today.
Let's record a few songs as practice.
I hope I do a good job. It's my first time, so...
Mr. Kang, who is he?
He's my engineer.
Ms. Moon told me you'd be working with me.
If you'd explain...
I never said I'd work with you.
Close the door behind you.
- Where are you going? - I'm going home early.
You can't go.
He brought another engineer.
What?
What does she mean?
Come here.
He said he'd work with you.
- He must have changed his mind. - In a few hours?
I know how he used to be.
He wasn't like that. It's the slump.
Does a slump mean you can be mean to people?
Don't yield to his flippant behavior.
- Come with me. - I'm fine.
I mean it. Are you okay?
Are you stupid?
If you call this "yielding",
you can't do anything.
Misunderstandings and mistakes happen.
I'm fine.
I feel wronged. So why am I not even angry?
Darn it.
Don't be mad.
Soon Ho, don't lose your temper if you want to stay in Seoul.
Darn it.
- She ran away? - Yes.
Seo Woo ran away, and... I'm so furious.
The nice ones are always the first to leave.
Where did she go?
I don't know. She walked away calmly...
I'm so annoyed. I'm livid right now.
Seo Woo defended Kang In Wook so much.
She explained that there were many musicians...
who are gifted even if they aren't famous, and...
I hate how Kang In Wook stabs people in the back.
That Kang whatever was wrong.
What infuriates me more is that I'm just taking it.
Why are you just taking it?
Right?
I can't stand that jerk.
Mr. Kang In Wook.
You clearly said you'd work with Seo Woo,
and that you'd try.
I heard you clearly.
Seo Woo...
must have been offended.
I had my reasons.
You repeatedly disrespect others.
Let me explain.
Explain to yourself.
You're paying by the hour to rent this place,
so explain to yourself or pound on the piano.
I need some powerful healing.
What's wrong with him? He always leaves it open.
(New deadline)
Are you going to Oslo?
Should I?
You should've done everything you could to hide it.
It would've been nothing if I didn't know.
The more it killed you, the more you should've hidden it.
- You should've done everything... - Why can't you understand me?
I didn't do it on purpose.
It was a mistake.
Just say it's okay.
If you would, I'll be able to live.
Are you free?
It won't take long.
Do you want to drink? Or eat?
Ms. Moon is with Mr. Kang.
Soon Ho's inside?
Why are they together?
They're probably arguing.
She called me, huffing and puffing.
She can't stand it when people break their promise.
She is a bit sensitive.
She's beyond sensitive.
That's why she shunned the world and lived on a farm...
for about nine years.
I mean...
You got dumped as soon as you came?
You hadn't seen her in years, so you came, and she dumped you?
Of all the...
I'm tearing up.
What's that girl Ji Soo's deal?
What a dramatic way to be stabbed in the back.
I never liked someone I just met this much before.
How are we so alike?
Birds of a feather.
She and her first love had promised to get married,
but he fell for Soon Ho's best friend.
She took me to a restaurant to cheer me up,
and just bawled.
That's when she left Seoul and went to a farm.
She became a gardener.
Soon Ho...
is very frail.
Where can we go?
Are you very hungry?
I was worried.
Okay. I'll listen to your story now.
If you have nothing to say, I'll start.
Keep coming as scheduled for this week.
As Seo Woo said, it may be a misunderstanding and a mistake.
You can make a new reservation at a new studio with a new heart.
You must care a lot about Seo Woo.
- Are you close? - I'm not close to anyone.
I don't really care for people.
You come into this world alone, and you leave alone.
I want to be as lonely as possible.
Then why are you so thoughtful of Seo Woo?
Mr. Kang. When people look after someone else,
you can't look at it as them liking them or being close.
This is purely about your promise.
You broke your promise,
Seo Woo was hurt,
and I was annoyed.
Did you first meet Seo Woo after you came to the studio?
That's right.
As soon as I came, she did a difficult favor for me.
I was buying dishes online, but I didn't want to use my name.
She did it for me.
It may seem like nothing,
but it could raise suspicions.
"Why doesn't she order them herself?"
"Does she have bad credit?"
I would've been suspicious.
That's part of the reason for your slump too.
You suspect and doubt everyone.
Whom did you buy the dishes from?
Well...
It was online. How would I know?
True. All you need are the address and contact information.
There's no need to meet.
Obviously.
I'll record with Seo Woo next time.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding.
Are you using the dishes?
I'm not using them.
I was asked through someone else.
Life is so disgustingly entangled.
Why do you keep laughing?
I was just dumbfounded.
We're out of sandwiches.
How about instant noodles?
- Here? - Yes.
Instant noodles taste so good at a cafe.
(Closed, See you next time)
Should I testify about how you waited?
I guess she isn't coming today either.
She'll come eventually.
Once she does, I'll testify as to how much you waited.
No.
I was waiting for someone else.
Someone I know too.
Did you see her since?
No.
Everyone who waits at our cafe met the other person eventually.
Every cafe has a story.
I feel bad when I see a customer who was stood up.
Then the next day, they come together.
I'm sure you'll see her.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said anything.
It's okay.
He should've cried long ago.
You stood right there...
with a woman before, right?
That woman...
came first and looked up at the ceiling by herself,
so I remember.
That's her.
The person he waited for.
She came.
Seo Woo.
Would you please tell Won not to wait at the cafe?
Are you really the person who said he never ever cries?
I guess I cry too. I only found out today.
Plus, didn't you come because you were worried about me?
This isn't why I came.
I'm so encouraged.
Why was it cathartic for me when you're the one who cried?
- Let's go. - Where?
Taxi.
I guess you feel awkward.
Why are you waving at an empty street?
It's nice to see you, Ha Won.
Can I be Ha Won now?
Don't you have anything to say to Before Dawn?
I don't think he'll be back.
So this is my last time with Before Dawn.
I can't tell him not to leave.
Will you turn around?
Just say it.
Because you're Before Dawn?
Before Dawn. Goodbye.
Thank you for everything.
I'm done.
Taxi.
Kim Ji Soo. Let me hear you scream.
DJ, play something upbeat.
Where's the music?
Kim Ji Soo.
Did he change it?
You think I can't find you if you hide, right?
Genie.
Siri.
- The device? - No. Listen to it.
This was...
from when I first met you.
I remember.
I was looking down, but some guy was looking around,
so I raised the volume so he could hear it better.
Oh my gosh. Was that you?
So you remember when you first saw me.
Clear as day.
I heard the song, so I looked up,
went to the studio, and you were there.
I told you...
a relationship will last long if you remember when you first met.
I must have made a huge impression. Right?
Of course.
The first meeting that I remember...
was when you were in the studio.
It's different.
What happens if we remember different moments?
Wait and see what happens.
Do you feel better?
I said that to cheer you up.
I forgot that I was upset once I saw you cry.
I think the door's open.
Stop.
We're not done talking.
This is dangerous.
Hold on.
It's nicer than it looks from the outside. And it's warm.
I live here because it's not bad.
Eun Joo wouldn't let me stay just anywhere.
What about the device?
I got rid of it.
Saying, "I got rid of it," sounds so...
Before,
it was clear what Ji Soo was giving me.
If I was having a hard time, I was happy if I thought about her.
If I felt empty inside, I'd think about her...
and I was able to console myself.
Ji Soo kept me in place.
But now, if I think about her,
it's too hard.
You're right. It's time to stop.
But saying you'll stop something is so vague.
But everything has a way...
when you look inside.
I'm determined,
so I'll figure out what and how...
to stop.
That's me.
Your turn.
You said...
you liked looking at me.
To be honest, I didn't know what that meant.
For many years, I put no value in physically seeing someone,
and I believed feelings continued even if you didn't see each other.
But I get it now.
I get what it means to like looking at someone.
It was nice looking at it...
when things were tough.
What do you mean?
And...
You didn't quit, right?
Again. There's no subject.
One percent is a lot. You shouldn't quit.
One percent it everything.
I really want to see how your one percent...
grows.
Seo Woo.
- Seo Woo. - Give me a minute.
Jin Soo has been lost at the station for half an hour.
I'm going to pick him up, so you should go up.
Why are you down here? You know we're busy.
Eun Joo's doing everything. Hurry.
That's right.
We always have a big dinner when we get a new tenant.
I forgot.
Eun Joo will kill me if I skip it.
One more thing.
I think it'll be best to find out everything while you're determined.
There is one more thing Ji Soo wanted...
to tell you.
She went to the spot where you were supposed to meet.
Seo Woo.
Add some soy sauce to the japchae. It's bland.
Okay.
The alleys are a bit confusing,
but there's a butcher on the street leading to our house.
- A butcher? - Yes.
The chicken next door to them is really good.
Butcher. Chicken.
If only I had turned around...
Ji Soo.
Quitting you...
is putting an end...
to my endless regret.
Here.
Welcome.
Take how much you want to eat.
All I've had was a roll of gimbap.
Thank you.
- Eat up. - Her japchae...
is the best.
Soo Ji used to love japchae.
Who's Soo Ji?
- Well... - No one important.
Why are you bringing her up?
Are you two close?
The thing is...
Well... We're dating. Yes.
- Don't mind us. - Okay.
- It's delicious. - Thanks.
I need to make a call. I left my phone downstairs.
Hurry back.
I never quit.
But it's not like I want or expect anything...
from you, so...
I'll take care of myself, so... Ha Won,
make sure to find out.
You can do it.
I found out...
what and how to stop.
I did find out, but...
I need you to do something for me.
You just...
have to go back and forth...
so I can see you.
The thing you said you liked looking at...
You don't mean...
I can't say exactly what this feeling is.
But...
I need you.
Can you stay?
Please stay.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
I want to play it for you.
I'll have to show you what I can do.
You'll be floored.
I always get...
so nervous this time of year.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
I feel like I'm being exposed.
- I left something behind. - What, your heart?
My bike.
It's pretty! It's totally my style.
The worst already happened.
At least one person should live.
One percent. And one person.
The one asking you to stay should follow you around.