You can't see him?
No, never.
I only want a small piece of her.
It was nothing.
I haven't met him before,
but he burrowed into my heart.
(Kim Ji Soo)
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry.
You two were old friends, so...
Friends...
What do you know?
I just...
Did Ha Won ask you?
I don't know him. I really don't know him.
I just...
wanted to do something for you.
Do you know what the last thing he said to me was?
"Call me when you become miserable."
I became miserable,
but I didn't call him.
I won't. I will never. Do you know why?
Because...
(Episode 2)
(77-30 Wokin 4-gil)
(Before Dawn, They didn't meet)
Before Dawn. They didn't meet.
I think it's for the best, actually.
I shouldn't have done anything.
How did they...
(External Input)
This is the final boarding call for Lee Han Sol...
booked on flight to...
Excuse me.
Please proceed to gate 10...
on the third floor immediately.
Hello?
Where are you again?
I'm in...
Wokin-dong, Jongno-gu.
It's Ha Won.
Is this the place?
Yes.
What is this place?
When we were on the phone,
its address captured my attention.
Doesn't it feel so warm?
It's a typical Korean house.
How long were you in Seoul?
I wasn't.
Where are you coming from?
- College. - From the States?
You wanted to see me, so I left in the middle of a lecture.
I guess you have something important to tell me.
Let's take some time to breathe before then.
I'm okay now.
Let's still do it. Otherwise, your mom will give me a scolding.
I said I'm okay.
I know a park here. Let's go.
Your mom always said...
that you shouldn't live in Seoul...
because you'd get rashes all over your body.
That you should live around trees.
That was just briefly when I was a kid. I'm fine now.
Tell me. What did you want to tell me?
Not yet.
You and I always wondered...
what Korea was like.
We could only imagine it before, but we're here together now.
Let's take it slow.
Do you have enough time?
Yes.
- Should we go to that place? - Is there a place you want to go?
Where you wanted to go.
Me?
A single leaf Lands on the shoulder
Without making a sound
Cosmos laid its hand on me
It was very light
"Sunset in Misiryeong", right?
It's beautiful.
Won, look.
We always pictured this place together.
I'm so glad I came here with you.
I think I can say it now.
I'm getting married.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
So she ran away?
She didn't exactly run away.
That's the same thing. I mean, was that really necessary?
She changed her mind and dumped him.
It's ridiculous.
Did Ji Soo dump him?
I'll plant a lot of herbs here...
and make tea with the leaves...
- for our customers. - There's no way you'd tell me.
After breaking up with Kim Ji Soo, he told me to...
I was flabbergasted.
My grandma was a diplomat.
She felt guilty that she couldn't do anything for the Koreans...
who suffered injustice abroad.
It's different now though.
Anyway, Ha Won ended up alone...
for a similar reason, and my grandma brought him here.
That's how he became my uncle.
- I told you about him before. - Yes, that he's so competent.
When I first saw him...
Oh, he and I are the same age.
I call him as Won or Uncle.
Sometimes, that guy or hey. It all indicates him.
Specifically, we're going to keep...
addressing CMOS architecture.
The technology that allows low power circuits...
to form in these components.
When you put a low power...
through a circuit...
He was in a lecture in the States...
when he got a call from Ji Soo, and he hopped on the next flight.
He has been living in Seoul ever since.
Where in the world is it?
(47-435 Wokin-dong, Jongno-gu)
Uncle?
Soon Ho.
I witnessed the virtue and vice of his tenacious crush.
Oh, that's the shipping address.
What am I saying?
Gosh, why am I crying over this?
Where did you live?
That is restricted.
What does your address have to do with the research?
Where were you with Kim Ji Soo?
Oslo. Seoul.
Gangneung.
When did you go to Gangneung with her?
We broke up there,
and I lived there alone for a few months the following year.
- What year was it exactly? - 2013.
2013?
That's when you were developing the tracking device.
Hey, where you lived is restricted,
but when I asked you where you were with Kim Ji Soo,
you told me everything.
I can get all the information...
if I ask indirectly relating it to Kim Ji Soo.
I guess it has something to do with the point of reaction.
Try changing the password.
Any other problems?
It's fine as long as it isn't your device.
Share it with the hospital...
after training it with virtual patients and improving its accuracy.
But you need real patients to test it on...
to improve its accuracy.
So you must...
discard this.
Let's put an end to our unofficial test here.
- What? - What?
I mean, it chatted with me...
and answered all my silly questions.
Thinking you'll throw it out,
I feel kind of bad.
What?
Since it's for treatment.
For treatment?
What do you think?
I like it.
Try mixing it.
Pardon?
Me? I'm still...
You need experience to improve.
You have a good ear, so I have high hopes for you.
Thank you.
It feels strange that all of us are here.
If I join too, we'll have our original team again.
What did the studio tell you?
Did they make it clear yet?
Not yet.
We're recording a live play this week.
And?
Come if you want to watch.
The place is small but nice for capturing sounds.
It'll be helpful to you.
I see.
(Before Dawn, They didn't meet)
Is Before Dawn not coming anymore?
Excuse me.
Did she say she was miserable?
She was miserable, but she didn't say it.
That means she's miserable.
I'm done meddling with their relationship now.
Order a drink if you want. I don't drink.
I'm okay too.
I feel so bad for that guy Ha Won.
I don't feel bad for him at all.
He's so like me.
In what way?
He believes it exists when it actually doesn't.
I'm great at it, you know.
I always run toward it, dream about it,
read too much into it,
and pour my heart and soul and my time into it.
But for more than 10 years, he...
Who has unrequited love these days?
They're competitive even about love.
They argue about who loves the other more.
They measure and weigh love although it's unmeasurable.
But he says a small piece of her is enough.
I guess he told you all sorts of things in hiding.
How do you think he endured 10 years?
I wonder.
Wouldn't it be possible if she was precious to him?
I think it would be possible if she were the center of his life.
You know how a single word can let some people go on living.
A single word.
There is something that I think would keep me going...
for about three years if someone would say it to me.
Something no one ever says to me.
"Stay."
The real estate agent called me several times...
to sell the semi-basement unit.
I'd sell it off right away if it weren't for you.
"Seo Woo."
"Stay."
I'll get going.
Okay, bye.
- Now, the cello. - Okay.
"Seo Woo."
"Stay."
I wonder what Ha Won's next assignment will be.
I doubt there will be any.
Really? Did she say that?
(Eatery)
I hear you're miserable.
You haven't called in years,
and the first thing you say...
I told you to call me.
I could tell you were unhappy even from behind.
Why did you run so hard? You don't even run that well.
It's been a while.
I'm not miserable.
Then why did you run away?
Because you showed up out of the blue.
Then how else was I supposed to show up?
Won, I can't really talk right now.
- Let's talk later... - Later when?
Let's talk again in 20 minutes.
(Ha Won)
My fiance knows you.
He seems to be bothered by you.
Who is he that he knows me?
He has been with me ever since you left.
So you knew him in Norway?
Who could...
Can you not try to find out?
Please.
Do you love him?
Well,
I feel like I grow when I'm with him.
We get each other musically...
So...
do you love him?
Yes.
Please respect my decision.
Of course, I do.
But...
you get married.
I'll keep loving you as I always have.
The fact that I love you...
won't affect your life in any way.
I'll never intrude on your life, so don't worry.
Please respect my decision too.
I have faith you'll be well.
You have to be.
But...
call me when you become miserable.
(Ji Soo)
Sure. The voice recording, the shipping address...
It was all you.
Why?
To refresh...
your recollection.
To call me when you become miserable.
I wanted to do it once every 10 years,
and you got me from the start.
You and your "being miserable".
I can't say I'm perfectly happy,
but I can't say I'm miserable either.
I'm sufficiently miserable and sufficiently happy.
You're making no sense.
I'm doing well.
- Ji Soo. - I won't run away next time.
Okay?
Ji Soo.
"Ji Soo."
It's been so long...
Hey. I'm doing just fine.
Don't worry.
I was going to ask you first before throwing it out.
Why would you throw it out?
Let's try leaving it out when it rains.
Rain rejuvenates them at times.
They grow crazy well when they get rainwater.
What if someone steals it?
Isn't it better if someone steals it...
and saves it than it dying?
- Hello. - Do you deliver?
Of course.
I guess he doesn't remember me.
Do you want something in particular?
- I'd like something small. - Look over there.
Take your time.
Hello, I'm Han Seo Woo.
Hello, Seo Woo.
Is it Seo Woo?
Hello.
I recognized you as soon as you walked in.
- Don't you remember me? - Hello?
Yes?
Mr. Choi checked the cello sonata recording...
and approved it,
so I emailed you the file.
I mixed it,
but Mr. Choi said it was good.
Would you please listen to it?
It's the first I've ever mixed.
- Congratulations. I'll check it. - Congratulations on what?
I'll ask her once you're off the phone.
Seo Woo, someone says she'll call you.
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
You hung up already? I feel bad.
Han Seo Woo. Han...
Seo Woo. I hear congratulations are in order.
What do you mean, how do I know?
I told you. It's a small world.
Will you come here if you're not busy?
The address is...
I wanted to clarify something.
Can I keep working at the studio?
Even when we don't have recordings scheduled.
Most studios have someone like that.
I don't know.
Please tell me,
so that I know whether or not to let the studio grow on me.
I guess everything is personal to you.
Of course. Every single thing, every corner, is mine when I work.
Okay. Then it makes sense that you want to know.
Give me a minute.
Hey.
Tell her to stay.
Okay.
Stay.
Excuse me?
He says to stay.
Keep staying at the studio.
Is that Ha Won too?
Your entire world is filled with Ha Won, isn't it?
I was important to him.
No one can be important to him on a personal level.
Let's go.
(Ji Soo)
Hey.
I was doing the laundry, so I couldn't pick up.
What's up?
Ji Soo even does laundry now?
I'm so speechless, I can't help but laugh.
You called for no reason, didn't you?
That's right.
You came.
(Ji Soo)
(Sindongmun)
You sent me a new message?
It suddenly...
got dark and started to rain, right?
- Yes. - That's my message too.
The sun rising, and setting,
the wind blowing, and it raining. All of it.
Everything you saw, heard, and gazed upon... Everything.
It's my message to be happy wherever you are.
It's from Kang In Wook.
Is today the only day we can record it here?
- Yes. Probably. - How much time do we have?
One hour. It's hard to rent this place.
Record that for me now.
Seo Woo!
Seo Woo. Can you find just the piano?
Yes.
Look for me.
Was that not a person's voice?
Stay here.
In Wook.
If I could apologize...
To whom?
Are you going to Oslo?
Should I?
If you're going to apologize to just scenery, do it here.
What if...
I could apologize to Won?
You don't keep in touch with him.
I know his email address.
- I can call... - It's nothing to apologize for.
How many times must I tell you that it makes me miserable...
and that it's too hard for me?
Ji Soo. This isn't a problem as long as you're okay with it.
It's not worth making us...
like this.
It's your problem now.
I saw you come in.
Do you know this place?
This is my favorite cafe. Isn't it nice?
You looked like you were watching someone.
I was people-watching.
I like doing that.
Alone?
Maybe someone will come.
I'm so clueless.
I'll go to another table.
Actually, I have happy news.
The studio said to keep coming.
Congratulations. I won't be going there anymore.
Did you finish?
From now on, I'm going to enjoy coffee and music in the mornings,
rather than cleaning.
As you should.
You see over there?
That's where Ha Won missed Ji Soo.
And I almost found Ha Won.
Is there something you want to ask that person Ha Won?
No.
I just want to see him from afar.
From afar?
I want to see his face from afar.
Why from afar?
If I'm too close, he'll see that I pity him.
He'll see that look on my face.
I want to see what he looks like from afar.
"So that's what someone who does something like that looks like."
I'll just look at his face. I wouldn't ask him anything.
I hope you work a very long time at the place that asked you to stay.
Thank you.
Work here.
You said you were waiting for someone.
I don't think the person is coming.
I'm sure they will. I'll...
There are plenty of other places nearby where I can work.
Why am I sad to hear I won't see him again?
Won,
do you want to go to Norway?
When?
Tomorrow is good too.
Why?
I need your help.
There's something I need you to do there.
What is it?
You just have to say one thing.
What's that?
I'll say it now.
Well...
It's okay. Tell me.
Tell me, and I'll help you.
I shouldn't have said anything. Sorry.
- I'll call you again... - Let's go tomorrow.
I'll help you, and then you can tell me.
Okay. Let's meet at the cafe.
I know.
Where you ran away.
See you there tomorrow morning...
It's nothing to apologize for.
How many times must I tell you that it makes me miserable...
and that it's too hard for me?
Never mind. No.
I'll call you tonight after I think it over some more.
What are you thinking about?
It may be too hard for you...
See you tomorrow.
Are you here for the cafe?
Yes.
Would you like to wait inside?
Thank you.
Leave.
I'll stay behind and find out why.
I'm sorry again about the other day.
Please call or text me when you have time.
(I'm sorry again about the other day.)
(I'm nearby.)
I'm nearby.
Over here.
It can be a gift or a nuisance.
- What is it? - A plant.
Keep it if you can grow it.
If not, just water it a little for a few days.
It's quite finicky.
I'm super good with plants.
Then it's a gift. It's all yours.
What were you doing nearby?
I had something to decide.
I'm going to go alone.
I'm scared, but I'm going to go.
It concerns me that you're scared.
I'll be fine.
I gained courage the moment I told you.
Tell me more.
I'll listen to everything you want to say.
I received a gift and everything. Say anything you want.
It's okay if it's about things that upset you.
Before...
I met my husband,
he did something...
He made a mistake.
Now that I found out about it,
it's too hard for me to bear.
My whole world turned upside down in an instant.
This...
This pain...
is all new to me.
This...
is too...
You didn't go to the mountain, did you?
I said to go somewhere high up.
It's therapeutic to look down on the world.
You can scream as loudly as you can.
Do you want to scream in there?
It's soundproofed, so it's the best at relieving stress.
There's something particular that you want to hear,
and not these silly things, right?
That one thing that you feel would make it all go away.
"It's okay."
"It's nothing."
Everyone makes mistakes.
Even nature makes mistakes.
My parents...
died in a forest fire.
I don't usually tell people this.
Even nature makes mistakes.
It's okay. It's nothing.
Just a minute.
(Dear Before Dawn. Please clean before you leave.)
"Nightlike afternoon."
Even objects fall flat on their faces.
It's just me and the machines. How strange is that?
What is this?
This?
I think Before Dawn wrote this.
I wonder what he does for a living.
This is a flowchart.
Dawn?
I call him "Before Dawn"...
because he rents this space for four hours early in the morning.
You know, I ran into him yesterday...
at the cafe we go to all the time.
He said he won't be coming anymore.
He asked out of the blue if I was miserable,
so I wondered why.
So this is how he knew.
You said you never saw Ha Won, right?
Yes. I saw him from behind from far away. That's all.
I think you will see him.
You may have already.
What?
I'm glad.
Is something wrong?
I can't concentrate.
I can't reschedule anymore.
One more song and we're done.
Why did you go?
Why?
- Please take your time. - Thank you.
This isn't good.
Nice. That was good.
I guess she isn't coming today either.
She'll come eventually.
Once she does, I'll testify as to how much you waited.
Make sure to collect for it all.
You have to. You promised.
I will.
The moon is huge tonight. It looks like it's coming toward us.
Make a wish.
She'll come.
Hello?
It's...
blinding here.
It's so nice.
Now that I'm here, I wonder why I lived like that.
All my anxiety lifted.
Where are you?
I'm on the path I used to walk all the time with Won.
In Norway?
How did I forget this place?
Did you always have such a cheerful voice?
Your voice sounds completely different.
I'm glad you went.
I can handle it all.
I'm a tough girl.
I'm so glad I came alone.
Seo Woo.
Would you please tell Won not to wait at the cafe?
I just came.
He's very simpleminded, so I feel like he'll keep waiting.
I told you, I don't know who he is.
It's so easy.
It's a quiz.
I'll call you in a bit. Solve the quiz, okay?
I'll give you a hint.
You've already met him.
I'll call you later.
But...
Who's Ha Won?
Wouldn't it be possible if she was precious to him?
I think it would be possible if she were the center of his life.
No way.
I became miserable, but I didn't call him.
Did she say she was miserable?
"Stay."
He says to stay. Keep staying at the studio.
I hope you work a very long time at the place that asked you to stay.
Was that you too?
Ms. Moon.
I told you, I quit the piano a long time ago.
You were the only one who didn't know that your favorite pupil...
just didn't have the skills.
Won lives in Seoul, but his skin is fine.
He's very healthy.
Won's mother, whom I love...
and miss so very much.
May I...
apologize on his behalf?
(Kim Ji Soo)
Is he really Before Dawn? Is Ha Won Before Dawn?
Hello?
I...
Ji Soo?
Seo Woo. Did it go through?
I was scared.
What's wrong?
It snowed too much.
My old town isn't far from here.
Can you walk out to a big street?
I can't budge right now.
It'll be better once it stops snowing.
Are you listening to music?
It's nice.
I'm scared,
but it's beautiful.
I used to come here with Won all the time.
Did you call a rescue team?
They must have that there too.
They're on their way.
Then hang up. Save your battery.
That's probably wise...
Ga.
Gya.
Geo.
Gyeo.
Ga.
- Ga. - Gya.
- Geo. - Gyeo.
- Go. - Gyo.
- Goo. - Gyoo.
- Geu. - Gi.
- Na. - Nya.
- Neo. - Nyeo.
- No. - Nyo.
- Noo. - Nyoo.
Neu.
Ga.
Gya.
A single leaf Lands on the shoulder
Without making a sound
Cosmos laid its hand on me
It was very light
A single leaf
Lands on the shoulder
Without
Making a sound
Stop looking out the window.
Look at the ceiling.
It's soothing.
Okay, Ji Soo.
I'll...
stop waiting.
Hang on.
Wait. Ha Won.
Maybe someone will come.
Ha Won.
Hang on.
Ji Soo.
Hello? Ji Soo.
I'm scared.
(Kim Ji Soo)
(A Piece of Your Mind)
"Look for me."
Please tell Ha Won...
that doing that won't bring Ji Soo back.
I left it all there. You liked Norway.
Why weren't you answering your phone?
Ha Won! I'm worried about Ha Won!
What were you imagining?
Conversing with the real Ji Soo.
Do you want to borrow it?
He is curious about everything when it comes to you.
This is how I miss someone.
The person you saw and spoke to...
last.