(You'll end up killing
the one you love.)
(The path of humans.
The path of beasts 2.)
(Episode 15)
(National Forensic Service)
(Jang Hye Mi. Walk my dog, Manson.)
Sit.
Good boy.
Go inside.
Manson is a ferocious dog.
How did you make it behave so well?
Dogs have good intuition
so they know whom to fight.
They feel the energy wave...
and use their sense of smell.
After that, a ferocious dog will...
- choose its owner.
- You like this tea, don't you?
("Wuthering Heights"
by Emily Brontë)
Revenge.
Upon his return,
Heathcliff destroyed everything...
and led everyone to destruction.
Destroying is a way
of possessing love.
Watching the woman he loves die
because of himself...
what would've Heathcliff felt like?
I don't know.
Wouldn't he have cried?
What would it feel like to kill
someone you love?
Well, I wouldn't know that.
Do you think it would be sad?
What do you think you'd feel
if it were you?
If it were for me,
I wouldn't kill someone by being
caught in someone's trap.
I could kill the one...
who trapped me.
Do you think the one who is
trapped...
can realize that he is trapped?
He could set a trap too...
and make it more painful.
What if the game does not come
to where the trap is?
He could lure it.
He could arouse the instinct
of the game madly.
I wonder what choice...
the game would make.
Would it be driven like a beast...
to where the hunter wants it?
Or would it be able...
to deny its instinct like
a human being?
I guess you're interested
in things of this nature.
I like writing about those games.
Humans are the most human
when they are brutal.
Help me!
Before the case took place,
a sign that says "off-limits" was
definitely here.
But on the day Chun Jong Woo fell
in the water, the sign wasn't there.
The distance from the villa
for the party...
to the lake is 300 m away.
The lake is connected
to the mountains.
What about the CCTV?
There are no cameras near
the lake and the villa.
They are set up...
at a barley rice restaurant along
the walkway,
at another restaurant that resembles
a mountain cabin,
and at a convenience store.
But the incident took place here,
so why would you want to know
about the CCTV and the walkway?
The culprit would've planned it out.
They always do.
He would've thought about a week,
three days, and the day before it.
Even the few hours before
on the day of the incident.
He would've visited the site
beforehand and plotted a scenario.
Check the CCTV in the walkway,
and hand everything over
to the video analysis room...
No.
To my assistant.
There aren't many CCTV
in a rural area like this.
I'll see to that, sir.
But even if it were
attempted murder,
it's not like someone's reported it.
And it has to do
with Chief Prosecutor Chun's family.
If he finds out you've cracked
this open like this,
he won't leave you alone.
Detective Joo, are you standing
behind Chief Prosecutor Chun?
Pardon?
Well, I know that you're standing...
behind Chief Prosecutor Chun.
As for me,
I'm not the type to stand behind
someone.
The history between
Chief Prosecutor Chun and I...
go way back, 30 years ago.
He's being sulky.
Are you sulking?
I saw him first when he was 13.
He had a great interest
in Gong Ji Chul.
So I gave him a book as a gift.
Ma'am, could I briefly see you
today?
I know you're busy.
Tell me where to go.
- Where are you?
- It's near the villa at Sangpyung.
(Mom)
Yes, Mom.
I'm coming now.
Mr. Lee, didn't you say
you can't swim?
You said you were scared of water
after falling into it as a child.
- Yes.
- I see.
Then come and stand here.
In front of me.
I apologize, ma'am. I slipped.
Right. You can go.
It would've been fun for you.
- when you stared at him drown.
- Was this it?
Is this why you called me?
No way.
Your voice is still so calm
in situations like this.
You have a voice that will hit
people's heart right in the center.
I'm sure this is one of your tastes.
Try to put a bigger smile.
I called you here to let you know
that I will never abandon you.
You're not just
the superior one percent.
You are so perfect even...
in the details
that it's breathtaking.
Mom.
Normal moms usually say that
they won't abandon their kids.
I'd be disappointed if you wanted
a normal mom.
Go first, I'll follow soon.
You never came when I waited.
Didn't someone else
always come for me...
instead of you?
That someone else is also me.
I sent them personally for you.
You should go first this time.
I'll follow.
I haven't been to a theme park
in so long.
Sa Bin's jealous that I went alone.
(W studio apartment)
A blue car.
Who are you looking for?
Why are you doing this
in a dumb way?
- I'm busy.
- Don't be like that.
You have a part-timer
at the cashier.
Let me see a bit more.
Stop. Stop right there.
Rewind a bit.
Stop right there.
R. M. Bike.
Prosecutor, I have it.
Jong Bum's bike was caught
on camera.
Yes. The RM bike logo was...
on the body and the wheels. Yes.
The license plate is
Seoul Seocho Da 6037.
The bike caught on camera just
passed right by me.
- Is it Jong Bum for sure?
- He has his helmet on...
so I'm not sure.
But it's the same bike
I tailed last time.
The footage from the
convenience store was taken...
at 2:30 p.m. on the day of the case.
There was a female student
at the back of his bike.
- A female student?
- Yes.
Her uniform is from
Sanjong High School nearby.
I'll drop by and find out more.
I'd like to talk about
Chun Jong Bum today.
By the way, is she okay?
The person you saved at the lake.
I was surprised. I didn't know
you could be so heroic.
I thought you were
a rational person.
But jumping in to save some other
women in front of your fiance?
- If you're worried about Sang Ah...
- It's just a curiosity.
You don't bat an eye...
when a man you framed
killed himself in prison.
But how could you be
so philanthropic at that moment?
- Framed?
- I picked it up somewhere.
Someone's after you because
of his brother's innocent death.
Who would that be?
I thought you knew.
I think it was Seo Tae Ha.
And his brother's name is
Seo Sung Ha.
Seo Tae Ha.
And his brother Seo Sung Ha.
Seo Sung Ha wasn't framed.
That pedophile snooped
around the daycare center...
every time he got out of jail.
Even if he was a pedophile,
no prosecutor should frame someone
for something he hasn't done.
I'm sorry, but I came here...
to hear what Jong Bum is copying
from Gong Ji Chul.
I hear they are both a part
of your major.
I guess you're not going after...
the real killer of Hwa Young's case
because of Jong Bum.
You think after Jong Bum read
my book,
he copied the Yellow umbrella case.
But why do you disregard Gong
Ji Chul from your suspect list?
Gong Ji Chul?
My book is fictional.
It has facts hidden in lies,
like hide-and-seek.
Do you think the last page is
fictional or real?
You keep dodging my questions.
I'll be going now.
I don't have time to play
games with you.
Wait.
("You may have just met
Gong Ji Chul.")
There's a guard...
who saw Ji Chul walk out alive
from the morgue.
Sir, I checked the prison where
Gong Ji Chul was executed.
May 31st, 1988. There were
three executioners for Ji Chul.
Gu Won Jin, Hwang Jung Eui,
and Jung Sung Hoon.
The first two are already deceased.
But Jeong Sung Hoon is still alive.
Where does he live?
Seolin-dong 36-2, Sangheun-gu,
Yongin-si, Gyunggi-do.
Jung Sung Eun is at
Dasarang Nursing Hospital.
(Seolin-dong 36-2, Sangheun-gu,
Yongin-si, Gyunggi-do.)
Make sure you walk
my dad twice today.
They shouldn't be too long.
Just 30 minutes each.
He likes flowers.
I went to a tulip festival with him
when I was young.
Please don't let him see anyone
besides me and my uncles.
What is he up to?
He keeps writing
something down these days.
I think it's to remember
whenever his mind comes back.
Could you tell him I love him?
Let's pretend that confession
didn't happen.
I have a fiancee.
My wedding invitation will
be out soon.
I'll send you one if you'd like one.
I must be crazy.
("How to end one-sided love")
How did you...
You must come here often.
What book are you reading?
Are you planning to stay here
on this sunny day?
Yes, I like it here.
I need to master
someone's mind today.
You're not buying this, are you?
Hey. What's he doing?
We have somewhere to go. Let's go.
I told you I don't want to go.
What's wrong with you?
- I'll go get us drinks.
- I want a pineapple drink.
You wanted to come with me
to an arcade?
Actually, I wanted to ride
a roller coaster with you.
How are we going to ride
a roller coaster here?
Wait a minute.
This is a scary one, is it?
You know what,
I've never been
on any rides in my life.
You can hold on to me
if you get scared.
We're going.
This feels real.
I was surprised.
This feels like my heart stays still
and only my body is falling.
But let's do this again.
This is freaking the best ever.
Freaking best?
(Caregiver)
You're not picking up.
I got a call
that my son got hurt.
I need to go out for a bit.
(Dasarang Nursing Hospital)
Where is the room
for patient Jung Sung Eun?
Visits other than family have been
prohibited by his daughter.
I'm the daughter's friend.
What is the daughter's name?
Her name was...
Ma'am!
Jung Sung Eun has disappeared.
I surely saw him at the concert.
I told you to keep an eye on him.
I told you he would go out
whenever he had the chance.
Where is the caregiver?
Where did he go?
You look for Jung Sung Eun.
You call the guardian. Hurry up.
Geez.
Hello?
This is Dasarang Nursing Hospital.
Are you his guardian?
Yes, Ms. Jung Sa Bin.
Your father has disappeared.
Yes.
I think you should come
to the hospital right now.
I'll be there right away.
I think I have to go now.
- What's going on?
- It's my dad.
I'm sorry. I'll call you.
Just wait for a while, kitty.
I'm on my way to rescue you.
All right.
No, don't move.
You're going to fall. Stay still.
Wait a minute, kitty.
Don't ever let go, okay?
What a surprise.
I won't let go...
of your hand.
Ever.
(Dasarang Nursing Hospital)
Oh, no. It's all because of me.
It all happened
while I went out for a little while.
Have you tried the closed jail?
He always went there
whenever he disappeared.
I've already been there,
but he wasn't there.
I'll go there one more time.
Sa Bin.
Even my friends are looking for him.
We'll be able to find him soon.
Wait, was it your boyfriend?
My boyfriend?
If you tell anyone that I'm alive,
you'll die for sure.
He's coming.
You have to run away from him.
Please run away.
Please run.
Run for your life.
Jung Sung Eun.
Jung Sa Bin.
(If you stay beside Kim Su Hyuk,
you and your father will die.)
Dad!
Why is my dad with you?
Let's go to the hospital first.
(Episode 16)
(Dasarang Nursing Hospital)
What brings you here?
Get in the car if you're
on your way home.
I can take the bus.
The town bus ended for today.
I can take a cab.
Robbery cases in a taxi happened
twice this month nearby.
Kidnapping someone by taxi
then raping took place last week.
Why don't you just get in?
What brought you to the hospital
today?
Was prison officer
Jung Sung Eun your father?
Did you come to look for my dad?
Why?
Is he too hungry to talk?
You should move him
to another hospital.
That hospital will accept
any visitor...
even if you requested
no visitors except for the family.
- Sorry?
- Ms. Jung Sa Bin.
Judo, Taekwondo, and Hapkido.
Did you train in any martial art?
Well, there isn't any.
I warned you.
Don't interfere
in someone else's business.
What were you thinking rushing at
a gangster with a knife, unarmed?
And...
don't you know jumping into the
water to save someone is suicidal?
You jumped in too.
Also,
you should keep those kinds
of concerns for your girlfriend.
Don't ever save me whether I fall
in the water or not.
There are many others who could
save me, other than you.
I'm merely a passerby to you.
You know the passerby in a movie?
It's something like that.
Is there anything you want to add?
What brings you here?
Do you live here, Sa Bin?
I have a regular customer here
for my part-time errand.
We cross each other too many times.
You live alone on the floor
above my uncle's...
and you have a part-time job
in the building I live in.
We also met at the bookstore.
Don't you think that would make
him a stalker?
I think a stalker is better
than dating two people.
At least he'd focus on one woman.
Go home safely, Prosecutor Kim.
Why don't we grab something to eat?
I was paid for my part-time job,
so I'm buying.
Stores should be closed by now.
The convenience store is open.
Let's go.
I was worried when you left before.
Pomegranate...
is supposed to be good
for the heart.
Try it.
Is something healthy
what I need right now?
Sense of loss.
I've run an errand that involved
listening to someone's secret.
I'll listen to yours and forget
all about it.
Think of me as a wall...
and talk to me.
A wall?
All right. From now on,
can you promise not to make
any reaction at all?
I hope it's because of this man.
A heart has...
nerves and memory cells too.
But...
the death-row convict...
should be 42 years old now.
He would not have felt the way I do.
I feel uneasy...
but...
it's like this part is breaking
meanwhile.
What could this be explained by?
What memory does this heart have?
This...
is not fake like virtual reality.
I'm hurting so much here.
Sometimes I can't even breathe.
How could this man...
be so vivid?
I could still feel...
his hands holding mine
in the water.
It was so painful...
and painful...
that I hope my heart stops beating.
It shouldn't be your heart
that should stop beating.
Don't look...
at that man anymore.
It'll be okay if don't look at him.
I'll help you do that.
People change.
Why do you love people
who are prone to change?
How about you?
Won't you change?
- I won't.
- You won't?
No, I won't.
You're human too.
Aren't you?
I only love the ones I choose.
I'm not human.
I've never seen a human being.
You can win over it.
Fight the monster in you.
I'll help you...
to fight it.
He's the only one
I should get rid of.
It can't be.
That's an excellent performance
every time I hear.
You found your way here.
I heard you were released,
but wasn't that enough for you?
She has no relation to me,
so take her name down from now.
- A woman?
- You jerk.
He does not deal with women.
Is that so?
Is that why you crashed into my car
with your truck back then?
I was sorry about that.
Who's that woman?
Is it your fiancee?
That's my privacy.
That makes me more curious.
You came all the way here
for a girl you don't care about?
You want to mess with women again,
don't you?
I only deal with beasts.
Your brother Seo Sung Ha,
a pedophile.
Do you expect your brother to be
normal while you live like this?
Revenge is what humans do,
not beasts like you.
That's what qualifies revenge.
That scumbag.
Stick by and keep on eye
on a woman at the NFS.
At the NFS?
Su Hyuk, you know we have to see
our wedding presents today, right?
There are 13 days left
until our wedding.
Do you know you still haven't
proposed properly yet?
I would have done it
if you wanted me to.
- Do it for me now then.
- Now?
I'm happy just looking at you.
I'll be happy to have been
your husband when I die...
and I'll live on reminiscing this
moment if you die.
Su Hyuk.
Oh, sorry.
I'm at the NFS.
I'm following Sa Bin like
you told me to.
But why is Seo Tae Ha here?
I'm sorry. I have to go somewhere.
What? Why?
I'll call you later.
Kim Su Hyuk.
This will be fun.
Can't we at least say hello?
I thought we had nothing to
do with each other.
Didn't you say that?
Hey, Sa Bin.
Did you meet Prosecutor Kim?
He was looking for you.
Me? When?
Around ten minutes ago.
I thought something was about to
happen between you two.
His face was deadly serious.
This is 911, how can we help you?
I have something to ask you.
If you ride the ambulance from the
NFS junction, where do you go to?
You go to Jisung for IM and
Inju University ER for surgery.
Do you have an emergency patient
with you?
Thank you.
Hey, what are you doing here?
How did you get in here?
I'm glad you look okay.
You're glad?
Are you crazy?
Where do you think you're sitting?
I have something to ask you.
Why would you kill someone
for someone else?
- What?
- I'm here to ask you that.
Blind hatred.
Beat it before I stab you.
I guess I was expecting too much.
Hey.
Do you know what family is?
I was a knife fodder since I was 15.
Do you know what that is?
You stand in front of fights,
so you can be a human shield.
If you survive the stabbing?
You go back out to
get stabbed again.
I lived to die.
And Tae Ha took me in as a family.
Do you know what he taught me?
You live to live.
If that's family, I think
I understand.
A murder to protect your family.
But, why can't you kill
someone today?
- I thought he was your family.
- What?
Do you know how many John Doe
remains come up in Korea?
A hundred? A thousand?
Or more?
Then how many do you think
your boss has killed?
Like Kim Su Hyuk did
to Byun Sung Hoon.
If he makes your boss
a serial killer.
What are you?
I owe something to Kim Su Hyuk.
Just like you.
Sorry, I'm late.
Take a seat.
I like everything about you,
except you take things too far.
Byung Sung Hoon or Lim Hwa Young...
just go as much as I tell you to.
It's Chun Jong Bum.
This photo was taken...
at 2:30 p.m. on April 7th.
The party started at six...
but why would Jong Bum
be there at that time?
The student at the back
of his motorcycle.
She fell in the same spot that
Jong Woo fell in.
Jong Bum saved her
on top of the bridge...
and took her to the hospital.
So what?
The off-limit sign was there
until the party started...
but it disappeared at the moment
that Jong Woo fell in the water.
Is it a coincidence?
What are you trying to say?
Jong Bum will try to kill
Jong Woo again.
He won't give up...
until he kills Jong Woo.
What...
are you trying to prove?
The real Jong Bum.
You know what that is, don't you?
The person I met at the
end of both cases was...
Chun Jong Bum.
If I do know, does it make
a difference?
Why can't you let go of Jong Bum?
Is it because he's my son?
You...
only need to think of one thing.
What you will gain and lose
by going after my son.
Decide right now.
Either rip the photo in front of me
and put the USB drive here or...
leave now.
Put Chun Jong Bum on the
suspect list of Lim's case...
and start from square one.
How did my dad do today?
Did he look for me?
I was going to tell you.
He was thinking straight today...
and was writing a lot of notes.
He was like that when I was young.
He used to open his note
while sitting on the sofa...
and kept writing notes
again and again.
April 9, 2020.
A lady came to visit me.
The ninth was...
She said someone was trying
to kill my daughter.
She played the violin.
She had a sharp voice.
Her glare was frightening.
It's him, Gong Ji Chul.
I need someone to help my daughter.
Sa Bin, remember two kinds of eyes.
The eyes
that are trying to kill you...
and those who are trying
to save you.
(Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk)
Why is she acting that way?
Go talk to her.
You should leave her alone...
in times like that.
Sa Bin was like that
when she was 14.
She gulped down soft drinks...
the whole night.
But she can't even drink that well.
You don't know anything.
It's not that she can't drink.
Sa Bin takes after me
and she drinks like a fish.
How can you say that?
If Kim Su Hyuk is beside you,
you and your father will die.
Prosecutor Kim,
I know I'm crossing the line...
and I also know
I shouldn't be doing this.
But don't get hurt, please.
Don't hurt yourself.
What was that?
Have you been drinking?
Who sent that note?
Who is trying to kill me...
and my father and even you?
Who in the world is
trying to kill you?
How much have you been drinking?
Let me talk to your friend.
- Are you by yourself?
- You looked down...
on me because I don't know
any judo, taekwondo, and hapkido.
Fighting is not done by technique...
but by your heart.
I'm not scared of knives...
or even guns.
I only put my eyes to the person...
that I need to protect.
Where are you right now?
Read the signs you can see.
(NFS Jung Sa Bin)
The number you are calling is
unavailable.
(Gu Hyul Ki)
Where is Jung Sa Bin now?
It looks like snow.
(Born Again)
Aren't you bad luck? Someone always
gets hurt when you're together.
Am I not the one you wanted to kill?
- A motive can't be given by others.
- I can't control myself.
It's the first time I want to kill
someone for someone I like.
Is it a coincidence
that the diary is gone?
The one with the tattoo is
the suspect.
I guess we'll see
who'll protect you in the end.
I found someone
I want to protect now.
Let's call this marriage off.
It's because I love you,
Jung Sa Bin.