(Year 2000)
(Episode 13)
Dad
isn't Park Do Seong the killer
of the milk-delivery girl?
You'll give him a life sentence,
won't you?
Didn't you say you wanted to be
a judge like me, son?
Yes.
This is dripped for 12 hours...
to become coffee.
A judge has to be slow to make
a decision.
"Is the defendant really
a criminal?"
"Does the punishment suit
the defendant?"
"Would it be unfair to his
or her life in any way?"
This is not the business of beasts,
but humans.
What if Park Do Seong kills someone
else after he's released?
I saw the way he looked at me
at the trial.
(The damage and pain caused by
the defendant are irrevocable.)
(The defendant is sentenced
to four years in prison.)
Dad.
At 2 a.m. this morning,
the culprit of
the milk-delivery murder case...
Mr. Park visited the house
of Mr. Choi, age 78...
who lives at Sillim-dong
right after his release.
Mr. Park killed Mr. Choi,
a 78-year-old who gave...
eyewitness testimony four years ago,
and Lee, his granddaughter,
by bludgeoning,
then set fire at Mr. Choi's house.
His granddaughter Lee was
a three-month-old baby,
and Mr. Park testified he killed
her because she was crying too loud,
which provoked outrage
from the public.
Moreover, Mr. Park was decided
as unfit...
due to his personality disorder
and alcohol dependence...
and sentenced to four years
in prison.
There is public uproar against...
Judge Kim Hyeong Suk, the judge
in charge.
Being unfit is when someone is
unable to distinguish objects...
or is unable to make
his or her own decision.
Park had been receiving hospital
treatment for alcoholism...
for three months
before he'd committed the crime...
and was decided as unfit.
This was not the business of humans,
but beasts.
Dad should not have given him
a chance...
to that beast.
(The path of humans.
The path of beasts.)
How could you still smile like that?
I'm alive now...
and I can't forgive him.
("Resurrection" by Tolstoy)
A polaroid photo?
You take immunosuppressant,
but don't care about weak immunity.
The cut is festering.
It's swollen and has heat.
You didn't take antibiotics,
did you?
Well, I don't think this is
something...
a professor should hear
from her student in medical school.
You're good at noticing the damage
of someone else.
But you don't seem to be good
at noticing your own.
The cut might become a scar.
You have to disinfect it at least
once a week.
Apply this three times a day.
Eat this twice a day.
Don't forget to take it.
It's a snowy field.
Why are there only two men in it?
I found paintings of the old
testament by James Tissot memorable.
- It's Cain and Abel.
- I see.
I guess you get inspiration
from the bible as well.
I was just curious growing up.
My grandfather used to be a pastor,
and I would annoy him by asking
so many questions.
Why did the lord abandon Cain...
and pick Abel?
Cain became the first murderer
of the humankind.
How scared would he have been?
He would've regretted it
after committing murder.
His father did not abandon him,
and he would've realized
that he loved his brother too,
- at the moment he killed him.
- You are concerned...
about the murderer, not the victim?
Regret is a painful emotion.
Sometimes the feeling of longing,
sorry, and sadness...
surge up at the same time.
Regret is an emotion...
that a person can feel...
only for the one he or she loves.
I wanted to know everything...
about this woman.
Could I have the sushi roll I tried
last time?
Of course, you can...
since you're Sa Bin's student.
You can sit right there.
I'll make one for you quickly.
I read an article that Professor
Jung implanted the heart...
- of a death-row convict.
- Well,
there was this death-row convict
called Kim Sa Yeon...
who killed his wife and kid.
But Kim Sa Yeon hanged himself
in jail.
Sa Bin's father saved this man
several times.
That's how he came to decide
to donate his heart to Sa Bin.
Before Kim Sa Yeon donated
his heart,
he met Sa Bin once.
And he's said to have cried
so much...
as he regretted it. Amen.
The blood in your hands
after you kill your family...
can never be washed away.
Well, I think you'd know that
better than anyone, don't you?
You went around looking
everywhere...
for your wife who had an affair,
holding your raw fish knife.
You jerk!
Is that how you cut an apple?
Give it to me.
That's why I boiled
Sa Bin's milk bottle,
changed her diapers,
and worked hard.
That's not a big deal.
When Sa Bin went to school...
I helped sort out traffic at school
wearing green clothes...
and attended career counseling.
You jerk,
you act as a religious leader
among a group of women.
Did you throw the bull
with your sly mouth?
A sly mouth?
Right, I'd sell a nation as well as
my soul.
What is there I can't sell?
I need money so Sa Bin's dad...
could stay at a comfortable
long-term care hospital.
And what about Sa Bin?
I can't sleep when I think about
when her heart might fail her.
But what could I do?
Do you have money?
You don't have a dime.
I have money. How much do you want?
20 dollars?
I couldn't even pay your monthly
wage. You have no money.
(Body heat)
(Human remains in museums)
(Donggang mummy)
My friend is a talented graphic
designer who restores the remains.
(Follow this user)
(New post is uploaded.)
It's weekend and the bone maniac is
going to the NFS after lunch.
When are you planning to hang
out with me?
What are you looking for?
I was hoping it wasn't true.
But my diary...
is really not here.
Your diary? The 14th item on your
list of outdated items?
I've looked everywhere from
university to my dad's shop.
Is your credit card in there?
No one would have taken that
cheap thing.
Just relax. Someone will
find it for you.
I feel like
I'm being dissected alive...
when I picture someone reading it.
Oh, my.
- Hello?
- Can I look at corpses today?
Corpses?
You said I could have
three visits to NFS.
- I think today's good.
- Today?
I do have one night autopsy
of remains from Busan...
but it's at 11 p.m. Are you
okay with this?
Of course. See you later Sa Bin.
Why are you calling me so casually?
I'll be working in NFS in five
years. Can't I call you that now?
I'll bring the late night snacks
you like.
Blood type, AB. Favorite
season, spring.
Treasured items, sand glass and
compass.
Used a 2G phone until last year.
Favorite fruit, unfortunately,
grapefruits.
Relieves stress by eating
classic snacks.
Favorite spot, Dongmyo.
Impossible bucket list, riding
a roller coaster.
Favorite sound, the scribbling of
a fountain pen.
Favorite song, "In a Dream."
Favorite type of men...
Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk?
Su Hyuk, why are you looking at
me like that?
Why? Do you not like it?
No.
What about an anadem
instead of a tiara?
An anadem?
I think it will fit you very well.
How do you about corn cockle
or white tulips?
Bring me something that
reminds me of winter.
Something like boat orchids,
like Christmas.
No, a simple anadem.
- With purple wildflowers.
- Wildflower?
Are you saying wildflowers
fit me?
You know about the gala for legal
personnel next week, right?
Yes, I heard it from the chief.
Go home with your mom today.
I have to drop by the office.
But it's a Saturday.
I leave her in your hands.
Does that look like someone
who is about to be married?
I don't care. He's mine now.
I'll make sure to get his love
for the rest of my life.
Love?
If you're the only one giving it out
that's called an obsession.
It's your life. Do whatever
you want.
Mom, are you jealous of me?
You've never met a man who
would make you like this.
I won't stop you going crazy.
Make sure you return
to your place.
Sir, we've caught the perpetrator
of the Lim Hwa Young case.
Do you know Heo Do Jin?
The one who got arrested
for assaulting a grandma?
He had a woman's fingernail mark...
on his left wrist.
We found his skin DNA under
Hwa Young's fingernails.
Fingernail. Do Jin's DNA.
Someone who threatened strangers
set up the yellow umbrella in a tub?
Who is it? The idiot that
arrested Do Jin?
Do you know the vampire of
the Gwanik station?
He won the MMA tournament held by
the chief commissioner.
(Gu Hyul Ki)
Good grief!
Did you arrest Do Jin? I didn't
order that. Why did you act out?
I arrested him after Chief Chun
told me it was your orders.
He told me you'll be cautious
because you're under inspection.
Don't act unless you hear the orders
directly from me from now on.
I'll be in NFS after 11 p.m. So
bring me the fabricated proof there.
Sir.
Seo Tae Ha is out.
I think you need to lay low.
He's the one who needs to lay low.
He's in my field now.
I'll make sure to let Su Hyuk know
your thoughts deep in his guts.
Don't hate your enemy. That clouds
your judgment.
Just go greet him for today.
Tell him he can die at any moment
in any place.
- Let him know just that.
- Yes, sir.
Hello?
Su Hyuk, how have you been
all these years?
I'm tired.
- Where are you?
- I'm almost there.
You know I can't get in without
the ID card, right?
- How about you?
- I'm...
Is that Prosecutor Su Hyuk?
I'll be right back.
I'll go over there. Where are you?
I'm in the basement parking lot.
Oh, no! Prosecutor!
Hello? Sa Bin?
You did a good job sharpening
the knife.
Close your mouth and open
your eyes.
Do you not see what will happen
to you?
Kim Su Hyuk!
Who are you?
Mind your own business
and move aside.
Until when will you block my way?
Hey you!
Your looks could kill people.
You should think you're lucky.
If it wasn't for me,
he would've torn you into pieces.
Why do you live in
such a dangerous life?
Did you see his eyes?
He came here today to kill you.
Why do you make them
hate you so much?
He's not the only one who hates you.
You have enemies all around you.
Do you think you're the only one
in danger?
Your family is put in danger too.
Don't you have anyone
you wish to protect?
You should fight people with the law
if you're a prosecutor.
You think you're a gangster
or a blackbelt holder.
How will you fight them by yourself?
I'm not a gangster,
but I am a blackbelt holder.
Why do you care
whether I get hurt or not?
I don't want the person I like
to get hurt.
I like you.
And because I like you,
you shouldn't get hurt.
Are you making a confession
right now?
You're right. I am.
I realized it
when you got hurt earlier.
I didn't need...
any experiments at all.
Let's pretend that confession
didn't happen.
It's my freedom to like you.
I have a fiancee.
A fiancee?
My wedding invitation will
be out soon.
I'll send you one if you'd like one.
I mean...
he could've just said he didn't
like me than say those words.
Then...
why did he light my path
on my way home?
Why did he risk his life to save me
during that car accident?
Does this make sense?
He's getting married.
It's false evidence.
You don't let other people
drive your car.
What's wrong with his face?
Did he gets dumped or what?
(Joy)
(Easy Cardiology)
He killed a female classmate
in a fall?
He even painted...
(Seo Yeon University Message Board)
My brother's a sophomore of medical
school at Seoyeon University.
I witnessed a murder committed
by my brother eight years ago.
Congratulations on becoming a star
in the University of Seoyeon.
I have a fiancee.
I know. I get it.
But why won't that man
get out of my head?
It's Professor Jung.
Professor.
A murderer? Does that make sense?
- What's happening?
- Gosh.
What happened to your eye, ma'am?
Did you get an eye infection?
No, it isn't.
We've got super nerve-wrecking news.
There's a murderer
in our medical school.
- Pardon?
- It's all over social media.
Oh, right.
You don't have an account.
It's here.
My brother's a sophomore of medical
school at Seoyeon University.
I witnessed a murder committed
by my brother eight years ago.
He pushed off his female classmate
in a deserted building.
He was painting the dying classmate.
My brother is very good at painting.
I can't forget what I saw that day.
My brother had a lunatic look
on his face.
The reason I'm writing this is...
because of the fear that I might
be killed by my brother someday.
My brother knows I saw
what happened that day.
Hey.
If it's a sophomore
from medical school,
he would've been 15 years old
8 years ago.
He killed a person at 15 years old.
Doesn't that overlap
with Chun Jong Bum's rumors?
That can't be.
But does he paint?
What are you doing here?
Jong Bum, you must've
waited long yesterday.
I'm sorry I didn't call.
I'm sure you couldn't
because your phone is here.
That's right.
Where did you find this?
I guess you don't look for things
you lose.
Pardon?
What happened to your face?
This...
I'll let you know
if you buy me a meal.
Sure. You must've not yet eaten.
All right, let's go.
I'm suddenly hungry.
Do you want to go together?
- No.
- We need to go.
- Goodbye.
Let's go.
You can ask me anything
you're curious about now.
It's nothing. Let's go have lunch.
(Episode 14)
You used to read books
about psychopaths.
What are those books now?
It's about the genes of Cain.
The genes of psychopaths, MAOK.
According to statistics, 1 in 1,000
people is born with these genes.
Cain, did he have the genes
of a psychopath too?
Who are you talking with?
Right, let's say he had the genes
of a psychopath.
Let's say those genes were
manifested when he was 15.
Let's say he lived with the stigma
as a youth offender.
But his little brother made him
drink detergent.
And what's next?
What would happen next?
You're not in your right mind.
What is this?
Why are you hooked by Cain and Abel
when you don't even go to church?
(Mom)
I returned to Korea yesterday, son.
You know we have a charity gala
in the legal circle tomorrow?
I guess...
you don't want to attend the gala.
- If...
- I'll be there, Mom.
I'm coming.
All right.
I'll wear that.
See you tomorrow, Mom.
(Charity Concert by
the Law Organization, KRC)
Jong Bum?
Why is the door open?
The number you have dialed is
currently unavailable...
He's not picking up.
(Charity Concert by
the Law Organization, KRC)
Mom said you should attend
the charity party...
at the weekend.
Why do you think the lord abandoned
Cain and picked Abel?
Cain became the first murderer
of the humankind.
- Please take me to Sangpyung City.
- Yes, ma'am.
The number you have dialed is
currently unavailable...
To make her wealthy husband
a lawmaker, she verbally abused...
employees, beat them, and took clips
of sexual favors.
There's so much I can dig into
this issue.
Would you be okay with that?
Is Jong Bum doing okay?
That's why I plan to...
keep my son-in-law
by my husband's side from now on.
Your son-in-law?
Didn't Prosecutor Kim tell you yet?
I like how he is a man
of few words.
- Oh, you're the writer.
- Oh, yes.
- You really are. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Could you give me an autograph?
- Yes, I will.
Were you...
going to send me
an wedding invitation at least?
I was figuring out
when I could tell you.
I'm sorry, Chief Prosecutor.
Don't you think that you could be...
digging your own grave?
Why would a man like you clean up
after that dubious family?
I know how to draw a line
between public and private matters.
(Detective Joo In Do)
I got it.
I don't think you're here
to give support.
Are there dead bodies here too?
Hello, Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk?
Could I go inside?
- Did something happen?
- Well, it's...
that there's something I need
to check.
You have so much to check,
don't' you?
Chun Jong Bum.
Did you really come here?
You're alone even here.
You can't fit in anywhere.
You'll be alone for the rest of your
life, why not jump in and die?
Why?
Do you not want to die?
Then kill me.
Should I?
Save me. Someone! Save me!
Help me!
- Save me!
- No!
Help!
Save me!
Sa Bin, wake up. Sa Bin!
Sa Bin, wake up!
Death, it feels weird.
It doesn't feel strange.
- Hyung Bin.
- Ha Eun.
Why can't I die?
I miss him.
I miss him so much.
My heart beats...
whenever I see this man.
It always does.
Are you sure you're okay?
Are you okay?
I'm so relieved.
Move.
Why is he like this?
- Hang in there.
- What happened?
Jong Woo!
Are you okay?
Are you sure you're okay?
Is the boy alive?
He is.
You almost died though.
Why are you so reckless?
She saved him.
- I can't believe this happened.
- How did this happen?
Sa Bin, wake up.
Sa Bin!
Are you awake?
Wait here. I'll call the doctor.
We tested him, but other than
the flesh wound, nothing's wrong.
But the water in his lungs could
cause problems later...
so he should stay here for a day.
Okay.
I called professor Cha on my
way here. Did you hear?
Yes, we'll help you
with the admission process.
Jong Bum saved you.
Say thank you.
Jong Bum.
You know I can't swim.
Why did you call me there?
You knew the bridge was broken,
didn't you?
Jong Bum.
You murderer!
Lower your voice, you're in
a hospital.
Is that what's important to you?
Jong Bum tried to kill me!
I told you to be quiet.
Is this true?
Now you try to kill my son?
I covered you for Lim Hwa Young.
Did you ever think
that it wasn't me?
What?
Did you ever think that I wasn't...
the one who killed Hwa Young?
Then bring me the killer yourself.
I'll talk to him.
He's my son.
I have nothing to say.
Did you try to kill Jong Woo?
Yes.
Let me ask you again.
Did you try to kill my son?
You said you didn't care
if I killed.
I said I was okay with murder.
I didn't say you can touch
what's mine.
Mom.
Speak.
Jong Woo gets sick a lot.
If I was sick that often...
what would you have done with me?
What?
If I was normal like Jong Woo...
you would've abandoned me.
(Vacant)
(I think I'll find you first.
I was there too.)
I saw you too. I knew all along...
about your signature.
Someone told me to give this to you.
(I can kill that lady for you
if you wish.)
- I need to clarify something.
- Let's talk another time.
No, let's talk now.
No matter how much
you wanted to kill your brother,
not everyone kills
their own brother.
Are you trying to prove
that you're different from me?
- Pardon?
- I'd like to ask you something too.
Why did you...
- save Jong Woo?
- Because it shouldn't happen.
- It shouldn't?
- You...
shouldn't become a murderer.
I’m already a murderer.
I told you
I wasn't interested in your past.
My past? I'm a murderer...
today and in the future.
I may have failed today,
but I'm going to kill Jong Woo
in the end.
You didn't kill him.
It's a relief you didn't kill him.
If I had been a little late,
you would've become...
completely different...
from who you are right now.
I'm happy I wasn't late...
and that I was able to stop you...
from making a regret.
You can win this.
Fight the monster in you.
I'll make you win.
Did you hear it?
My performance was the worst.
I told you to correct your habit
of pulling the strings.
Do you want to marry a woman
who has a bad habit like this?
You can fix that. I can bear it.
Let's go.
- Why are you being like this?
- Why did you rescue her?
There were two people
drowning in water.
Why was it her?
That was the second time.
I only rescued the person
that needed to be rescued first.
- She has heart disease.
- Do you know how your eyes look...
when looking at her?
You've never looked at me that way.
You've never looked
at any other woman like that.
You're still illogical like a child.
The promise I made
to marry you is...
also a promise I made myself.
I've never broken a promise
I made myself.
Whether it's cold or hot,
this is the logic of my emotions.
Do you remember, Su Hyuk?
We first met
at the Philip Jang Theater.
What was the reason
you accepted my date request?
- Was it because I was pretty?
- It was a long time ago. Let's go.
Tell me. What was the reason?
- I liked what you said.
- What were they?
Don't you think Philip Jang is
really sexy?
His heart and my heart were
connected.
Philip Jang's real name is
Jang Ki Pyo.
He's been addicted to drugs
since 17 and committed rape.
He changed his identity abroad.
Artists usually have a monster
within them.
I want to sleep not with his body
but his soul...
this very night.
I don't want to embrace your body...
but your soul instead.
It was then.
When you said you wanted to sleep
with his soul and not his body,
I wanted to meet you again.
I was curious about what kind
of lady would talk like that.
You're right. I am.
I realized it
when you got hurt earlier.
I didn't need any experiments
at all.
I see it.
I like you.
Because I like you,
you shouldn't get hurt.
I realized it
when you got hurt earlier.
I didn't need...
any experiments at all.
(You'll end up killing
the one you love.)
(Born Again)
Why do you exclude Gong Ji Chul
from the list of suspects?
It has been recorded on the camera.
Do you think the last page is
a fiction or a fact?
I was told there was someone
who's trying to kill my daughter.
Are you here to see my father?
Why is that?
Remember two kinds of eyes
between those that are trying...
to kill you and those
who are trying to save you.
If you die, I can live
by longing for this moment.
I only love the ones I choose.