(All characters, organizations, places, entities, and events...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
What's wrong with them?
Cheers.
(Episode 6)
Once, I caught someone...
doing something perverted.
I checked his transportation card history,
and he had taken the first train from Cheonan at 5am.
They're so diligent.
Yes. But he claims he came to see a friend.
Who meets a friend at 7am?
And two guys at that.
I may be diligent,
but I'd never get up to catch a 5am train to meet a friend.
Soo Ho and Officer Lee are close,
but they don't even make eye contact in the morning.
That's true.
Last time, I went all the way to Incheon and caught this punk,
and he...
It got cut again.
I rolled down like 10 steps,
so it's to be expected.
Another time, I followed him to Incheon and arrested him,
and I realized he was wearing our handcuff.
So I asked him while I was arresting him,
and he had gotten loose and run away.
Didn't it hurt?
What?
Hye Jin told me.
Oh, well...
I wanted to try fighting him.
We both did martial arts. I wanted to see if he was better.
He seemed to need a sparring partner too. So I...
What? What are you doing?
Open up.
It won't heal if you don't treat it.
I got a cut here too.
Okay. I see. You got a cut there too.
Darn it. He hit me for real.
It hurt so much.
Sorry.
Seriously. You're such a crybaby, Chief.
Pro fighters are different.
Don't do that again.
Here comes the first train.
The train to Seongsu is now approaching.
If you party all night long in Hongdae on Club Day...
and take the first train, you disappear.
You're a natural-born detective.
Let's get on.
Let's see whether or not we disappear.
- Okay. - The doors are opening.
Take a nap if you're tired.
I'll wake you when we're there...
I'm Chief Inspector Ko Ji Seok with the Subway Police.
May I see your bag?
That punk isn't just a petty thief.
What...
That jerk.
Please stand clear of the closing doors.
(Ewha Womans University Station)
Newbie.
Chief, why did you leave me...
Listen.
- Yes? - There's a petty thief...
with a knife on that train.
- What? - He's dangerous,
so follow my orders exactly.
Okay.
At the left end of the seats across from you,
there's a woman with short hair in a black dress, sleeping.
She's his victim, so tell her you're an officer...
and exit at the next stop with her.
What about the thief?
Leave him.
I have my handcuffs.
Is he wearing a black cap and...
Newbie!
Get off with the victim.
I can catch a petty thief.
He isn't just a petty thief.
I told you why I came here, right?
Because the most I get are petty thieves with nail clippers.
That's true.
That's your conviction, not mine.
That's not it.
Weapon possession increases the sentence,
so subway thieves do not carry knives.
And he didn't touch her gold jewelry.
Because most people use credit cards, the petty thieves...
go after jewelry first before wallets.
Something is off about him.
I'm on the next train, so get off at the next stop.
I promise to catch him again.
Okay.
I'll get off with the victim then.
Stand clear of the closing doors.
(Ahyeon)
Chief!
I even took off my heels. It was so hard holding myself back.
Aren't you proud of me?
Good job, Newbie. You're all grown up.
We'll call you as soon as we recover your wallet.
- Thank you. - Get home safely.
Get home safely.
Officer Lee.
See if he was caught on camera at Hongik University Station.
Yes, sir.
If we catch him, we can take the lead this quarter.
Hello, Chief Gong.
I'm sorry, but may I see complaints regarding petty thieves...
on the first train at Hongik University Station?
Why? That's my station.
I saw a weird one.
He had a weapon, and took the victim's wallet and not jewelry.
He's short, wore a cap with an eagle...
Oh, him. He's so quick. I lost him once too.
But yes, he is weird.
He always targets the first train after Hongdae Club Day.
He only robs people on the first train after Club Day?
Probably because there are so many drunk people.
If you lost him once,
you must have checked his transportation card.
Do you know his identity?
If I did, I would've caught him already.
He always uses a single-ride card, so we found nothing.
I see.
Then may I meet the victims...
whose wallets he stole?
There are many victims, so we'll find a clue once we meet them all.
Why is Chief Gong actually helping us?
He said he saw us dancing...
last night.
He felt like he was too mean.
So you don't remember anything about the thief, right?
No. I completely blacked out.
Were you wearing any gold jewelry or anything valuable that day?
I was since I went clubbing.
And yet, he only took your wallet.
For all three, he left the valuables and only took their wallets.
Why?
We need to find a lead.
Here.
Hong Ye Ra.
Don't waste your time, and go home.
No one has lived there for a while.
- Hello. - Sure.
I'm Chief Inspector Ko Ji Seok of the Subway Police.
So you're cops.
You look different from the ones who came last time.
Were the police here?
Yes.
Would you please tell us what you know?
This lady... What did they say? So...
she does an Internet broadcast. She's super famous here.
But they said she suddenly disappeared during a broadcast.
So detectives came by and asked me all sorts of things.
She disappeared while doing a broadcast?
Yes.
Is this her?
Yes, that's right. Yes.
Based on the list of victims,
Avocado had her wallet stolen on the 26th.
The last day she posted on her vlog.
She went missing the day her wallet was stolen.
Maybe that petty thief had something to do with Avocado's disappearance.
I'm not sure. It's too soon to say.
You said so yourself,
that he isn't just a petty thief.
And Chief Gong said...
he only goes after people on the first train after Club Day.
Maybe he has something to do with the ghost story.
We should investigate Avocado's missing person case.
Not those eyes again. Watch it.
No... I'm saying we should investigate Avocado's case...
so we could catch the petty thief.
We should bring up our arrest numbers...
so you won't get any disciplinary...
I told you an adult shouldn't fib, right?
If I knew you'd be like this, I should've arrested that thief.
"I promise to catch him again."
I trusted your words.
I'm not saying I won't catch him.
All right. Fine.
You're always threatening your boss.
Metropolitan Detective Division is investigating this case,
so I'll ask if they can share the information they have.
But can we get some rest first?
We've been up for 30 hours.
Metropolitan Detective Division...
Yes, sir. Salute.
You always salute, then rebel against me.
Chief, wait for me.
- Aren't you sleepy? - Me? I'm fine.
(Avocado TV)
My makeup smudged all over.
I'm so thirsty.
The criminal was caught on camera here.
What?
You see the dim reflection on the window, don't you?
I thought it was Avocado's shadow.
Look at it from the angle of the light shining through.
It's not Avocado.
Take it to the video analyst to get a detailed analysis.
The window in her home is about 1m above the floor,
so get an estimate for his height by taking that into account.
How do you know how high the window is from the floor?
Isn't it a given?
Her house is the crime scene.
Of course, we should know everything about the scene.
- Go and get it. - Okay. I'll be back.
We have two months left.
(Bring down the Grasshoppers, D-75)
Making more arrests isn't the priority.
I'm going to get fired.
About our investigation on the Grasshoppers...
Are you sure we checked all the costume companies?
Yes.
(List of Costume Businesses)
- Your delivery is here. - That way.
It's here.
It's not like someone can make their own Podori costume.
How did they get their hands on it?
All right, let's eat.
- How much is it? - It's 15 dollars.
15 dollars.
Enjoy.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Did you see that? That was withdrawal symptoms.
Oh, gosh! Hang in there, Boss.
- Soon... - Your delivery is here.
(Subway Pickpockets, the Grasshoppers)
Shall we see how far Chief Inspector Ko got?
"Checking costume businesses"?
That makes me a little nervous.
Be quiet, Baldie.
Bong Man. I...
even made myself an autograph because I thought...
I'd get big after this job.
But I was trending on the Internet just for 10 minutes.
Thanks to that murderer, people forgot about us.
My pride was badly damaged.
When you go to retrieve the dishes,
put this document back. Okay?
The possibility of making a secret deal...
with a costume business...
Officer Lee, did you take the file on the Grasshoppers?
No.
That's strange.
- Soo Ho. - Yes?
I have to go somewhere, so can you look for it for me?
- Okay. - Great. Thank you.
I'll get going.
- Bye. - See you later.
I haven't been able to go home, let alone change my socks.
This job is so ridiculous.
She's so young, but she's always bossing us around.
- Exactly. - She thinks she's the best.
I worked at least 10 more years in the field than her.
She only became a lieutenant because of her mom.
You're wrong.
She got her job because she's capable.
She's the Commissioner's daughter,
and the youngest lieutenant at the Metro Detective Division.
Are you jealous?
If you are, then just say you are.
It'll make you look less pathetic.
(Estimated time of the crime, August 4, 2pm)
Ma Ri.
What brings you here?
You shouldn't drink coffee at night. Have some tea.
Thank you.
So? Why are you curious about Avocado's case?
I found a suspicious man while investigating.
I wonder if he might be related to Avocado's missing person case.
Who is the suspicious man?
A petty thief.
He stole Avocado's wallet...
on the first train from Hongik University Station.
That's the day...
Avocado disappeared.
On the first train from Hongik University Station?
Lieutenant Ha!
You were right. He's on the clip.
I need to try going in there.
Who is that? It looks like he's tailing Newbie.
(Konkuk University Station)
Ryung...
My neck...
My neck hurts so much.
I can't breathe.
What's the matter, Jin?
Jin?
Jin!
The one who took Jin...
also tried to kill me.
(Safe Room: Guns and Ammunition Must be Stored in Safe Room)
(Gun Locker)
I'll find him no matter what.
They brought up the resolution...
and zoomed in. Look.
We calculated his height by using the window's location,
- and he's about 160cm tall. - It's that petty thief.
What?
He was about 160cm, and he had this mark on his hat.
I'm certain. Even this morning,
he pick-pocketed on the first train from Hongik University Station.
I could've arrested him.
He pickpockets women on the first train...
from Hongik University Station,
then goes to the woman's house.
He must've stolen wallets of more than just a couple of women.
It's highly likely that there are more victims.
The ghost story about the first train...
needs to be investigated.
(Gyeongseo-dong Missing Vlogger Case)
(Investigating family and acquaintances)
I'll go study the petty thief's victim list again.
Hey.
You have a partner. Call her and ask her to find out.
Actually, I have to go back because of her.
She's alone right now,
and it's scary when the shutters are down.
Then...
do the suspect's composite sketch before you go.
Call the sketch artist.
It's 2am right now.
Just ask him to see you again...
Go and get the sketch artist right now.
Yes, ma'am.
Sit.
But I think I better go.
Newbie is by herself. I'm worried.
"Worried"?
Let's work on the composite early tomorrow morning.
I'll call you.
What is this?
Did the power go out?
Who are you?
Newbie!
I have to catch him.
Newbie.
Newbie!
Chief.
Newbie.
What are you doing down here? Are you hurt?
Why did the power go out?
I'm sorry.
Are you sure...
you didn't get hurt?
Did something...
happen?
By the way, Newbie.
Are you hiding something from me?
Pardon?
You look a little anxious.
Also, someone was tailing you last time.
No one was tailing me.
I checked,
and he was just a pervert.
I'm just startled, that's all. I'm scared of the dark.
I'm glad it's nothing serious.
Just a second.
I thought you were fearless.
Sleep tight.
If you get scared, you can wake me up.
I'll leave this open.
Chief.
I think I need to get stronger.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you kill me?
Why?
(Employee Lounge, Authorized Personnel Only)
They fixed it quick.
Hi.
- Hello. Did you sleep well? - Hey.
Good morning.
- Did you eat? - Yes.
Goodness.
- Chief. - Did you get some sleep?
I'd like...
- a new partner. - A partner...
Me?
You want to swap me out?
Yes.
What's this all about?
Did you two fight again last night?
Who wants to be my partner?
Do you want to be my partner?
Partner, I'm going to order an expandable baton.
Should we look together?
- Of course. We're partners. - You're so mean.
I'm not an infectious disease or anything.
Nice. I like silver.
- Silver? - That's right.
Should I go with pink?
There's no pink.
Is it...
because I left you all alone...
in the dark last night?
I didn't know the power would go out. I already apologized.
- Why are you... - That's not why.
Then?
Because...
I don't think we're a good fit.
Come with me.
Chief.
When were we ever a good fit?
I said from the get-go...
that we weren't a good fit and that it wouldn't work.
From the first time we met.
We met with you handcuffing me.
I'm sorry about...
But you insisted on joining us.
I really didn't want to say this,
but the past month that I worked with you...
was more exhausting than my past two years combined.
Exactly.
It's better if we switch. It would be less exhausting.
Are you kidding me? Seriously?
We're finally starting to work well together.
I worked so hard to get this far.
Exactly. I'm saying stop working so hard now.
Who can put up with you other than me in the Subway Police?
Were you "putting up" with me?
- That's not what I mean. - You should've said you hated me!
I never said...
It's not that I hate you.
Seriously.
You said...
I was your seatbelt and stuff before.
How could your feelings change so quickly? And overnight too!
They're talking about switching partners, right?
They're not breaking up, right?
I'm not sure.
Let's not be emotional.
Let's take some time to cool off.
Until we solve the Avocado case.
Avocado.
What did Metro say?
There's a connection between Avocado and the petty thief.
He was caught on her vlog.
Really?
Metro is taking him and Avocado,
and we'll meet the other victims he robbed...
- Let's go. - Wait.
Wait for me.
Is it jammed?
- Yes, I think so. - See you later.
See you later.
What's going on?
Where did you find it?
So that's where I dropped my wallet.
Okay. Just a minute.
I'll go there to pick up my wallet.
Thank you.
May I help you?
Did you find your wallet?
Yes.
We're detectives with the Subway Police.
You had reported that you lost your wallet.
I thought someone had stolen it.
I had expensive concert tickets in my wallet,
which was why I reported it,
but I guess it wasn't a pickpocket.
Please cancel my report.
Why did you think it was a pickpocket?
Since I scanned my card when I got on the train.
But...
when I checked when I got off, my wallet wasn't there.
I guess I dropped it somewhere...
since he said the tickets and money are all there.
I see.
Goodbye.
It's late. Let's go to the next one.
Okay.
Park Yoo Mi.
Is anyone home?
It looks like she hasn't been home in a while.
I guess you didn't know.
No, no. She reported her wallet stolen, so we came to talk to her,
but we couldn't reach her.
Okay.
Park Yoo Mi's mother...
thinks she still lives here.
So her family doesn't know where she is either.
Hi, Soo Ho.
- Did you meet the victim? - No. She isn't home.
Her friends say...
they haven't been able to reach her since they went clubbing.
I see. It's the same as here.
Get all the surveillance videos from near her place.
Okay. Bye.
That means two more women went missing on top of Avocado.
The ghost story is real.
What happened?
What? Why?
What?
- We'll find a clue inside. - That's breaking and entering.
Newbie. Snap out of it.
Snap out of it.
Stop it.
I thought you finally grew up.
I'm doing this because I grew up.
I should do what I must at all costs.
Are you rebelling because you don't want to be my partner?
But...
That's not it. Darn it.
Officer Lee and Soo Ho, check the surveillance cameras.
If the victims are alive, they'll be on them somewhere.
Newbie and I'll check their credit card uses after their disappearance.
Okay.
Hello, this is the Subway Police. I'd like to see...
Park Yoo Mi's credit card transaction list.
Please fax it to me. Thank you.
(Credit Card Transaction Details)
Check this.
I'll check these.
What's this?
This woman is fine.
She's buying something at a convenience store.
Then she used her credit card herself.
The other victims are going around perfectly fine too.
They were caught by every camera.
- Then all the victims... - Are alive.
I know we should be happy, but...
what were we doing all this time?
The ghost story is not real.
Well...
That is a relief.
- But... - Lieutenant.
We found Avocado.
I checked the surveillance cameras near where her card was used,
and I think she's staying at a studio apartment.
I knew it.
What a waste of time.
Isn't it great she's alive?
Call the studio and ask her why she moved,
and close the case.
We started this investigation thinking they went missing,
but none of them did.
But none of them are going home.
They're not minors. Must the police investigate why they don't go home?
The convenience store Park Yoo Mi goes to isn't far from here.
- Can't we just go and... - And what will you say?
"We called after you reported your wallet stolen,"
"but you wouldn't answer your phone and weren't home,"
"so we checked your credit card transactions..."
"and the convenience store you frequent..."
"and were staking out in secret. We didn't expect to see you."
Is that what we should do? Because of one wallet?
- That's a stalker, not a cop. - Yes.
It's weird that both of them won't go home.
Something may have happened like with Avocado.
Even with Avocado,
we don't know exactly what happened.
I still need to check.
This isn't ours to investigate.
They say you can't change people.
Your bad habit is coming back!
That's what I'd like to say.
You keep backing down while investigating.
It must really be an illness.
What? Why...
Is this the Narcotics Unit? This is Ko Ji Seok, Subway Police.
I'd like to report a narcotics case.
Call the lady...
and tell her we can't investigate.
About the Kim Won Tae case.
Let's drop it.
Is that why she doesn't want to be my partner?
What is it?
Fine.
It's late. Let's go tomorrow.
Let's go.
Have a good day.
That stings.
Let me see.
Goodness.
I'm fine.
That stings.
Here.
Hello.
Park Yoo Mi, right?
He only stole my wallet.
There was nothing else.
Is that really true?
Yes.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Hi, Ma Ri. Yes.
Okay, I'll check.
Replay the surveillance video of Avocado.
Okay.
(Seoun Metropolitan Police Agency)
Park and come in. I'll go in first.
Okay.
- Ji Seok. - Hey, Woo Hyuk.
When do you suddenly lose all respect for a supervisor?
Are you asking me about your ex-girlfriend?
Why? Did Ryung say she doesn't like you?
Yes.
She doesn't want to be my partner.
Not wanting to be your partner is different...
from disliking you.
How is that different? It's the same.
You seem to be overreacting.
Take it purely professionally. Professionally.
Of course, I take it professionally.
How else would I take it?
Detective Kim.
- Do you have a minute? - Sure.
Are you really okay? Are you not hurt?
I'm not asking for your concern.
I told you in case it would help with the investigation.
So you're positive the guy who came that night...
is the Subway Ghost, right?
That's right.
Who else would roam around the station at that hour?
I know it's hard to believe,
and you don't have to believe me.
Just run an analysis on this for me.
I found it in the tunnel, but there's no case number...
and I can't request an analysis.
It's a bit clean for something found in the tunnel.
I thought that was suspicious too.
I'll let you know as soon as I get the results.
And when we investigate suspects on our end,
I'll make sure to check if any of them has a shoulder tick.
Thank you.
And let me ask you for one more favor.
Please don't tell Lieutenant Ha. She won't be interested, anyway.
If she finds out I've been going into the tunnel,
it'll put Chief Ko in trouble too.
How come you don't want to be Ji Seok's partner anymore?
Because I don't want to ruin this.
You like him, don't you?
It's not that.
I keep on wanting to rely on him when I'm with him.
I'll get going.
Then, do you want me to help you?
How did you know Avocado was a victim of sexual assault?
After we talked, I noticed the signs of a rape victim.
She'd flinch if a strange man passed by.
- What about you? - She'd wipe things incessantly,
like the coffee ring on the table and dust on her sleeves.
She feels like her body was spoiled,
so she showed compulsive symptoms.
Yes. She can't look at stains because it reminds her of herself.
That's why...
I didn't know.
How would an officer like you know that?
First of all, all of the women had bob cuts.
That means he has a particular taste.
Out of them, only the women who live alone were attacked.
That's why he stole their wallets.
He already saw that they're his taste.
He needed the addresses on their IDs so he could check if they lived...
in multiplex studio apartments which are easy to break into.
That explains why he didn't steal their jewelry.
He targeted women who went clubbing all night because...
He probably thought they deserved it.
He must've said what he thought out loud.
That would make the victims get timid...
and blame themselves, leading them to hide even more.
If you party all night in Hongdae and take the first train,
you disappear.
The rumor already had all the answers.
It would've been difficult to live in the house...
where the crime was committed.
Since they partially blamed themselves to be guilty,
it would've been hard to tell others.
That's how they disappeared.
Does Officer Yoo not know...
that we used to be partners?
We were partners when I was in Major Crimes.
No wonder you two work well together.
What?
Okay, then how about you? Are you two good together?
Why did I even ask? You need to think the same...
and be on the same level to be partners.
Woo Hyuk.
One person only makes trouble, and the other one resolves it.
What should we call such a relationship?
The one resolving it...
must really like the troublemaker.
What?
There's no other reason to keep someone...
who always makes trouble.
The first train ghost story...
can be categorized as a serial rape case.
Get all the documents and forward them to Major Crimes,
then have them contact the victims to get their statements...
before they report it.
Wouldn't that be forwarding the case to them?
We started it, so why...
We have other things to do,
such as the subway serial murders.
People disappeared between the platform and the turnstiles,
then they were found as corpses under the train's seats.
- You know it, don't you? - Lieutenant Ha.
Everyone knows that case.
You left it as a cold case for two years.
- What? - Newbie.
What do you mean, she "left" it?
Let her be.
You must have a problem with our case.
Say it. I'll listen to it right here.
I don't have a problem.
But, I'll be...
meeting all the victims for this case.
She's just so passionate.
Sure. If you're ignorant, you should at least be passionate.
Go. Go and meet them.
Madam Commissioner.
What are you doing?
We're investigating the first train case like you...
Exactly. Why aren't you investigating?
Lieutenant Ha.
What does the Metro Detective Division do?
When the subject of investigation influences a wide area...
The serial rape case happened all over Seoun.
Isn't this your case?
That's why the Major Crimes team in charge...
can just collect the statements for us to review.
The hardest part of a rape case...
is getting the victim's statement!
Forwarding it to someone else means you won't investigate it!
Madam Commissioner.
Us police only have two months left.
If we don't catch the serial murderer,
you have to step down. It's what you promised.
Lieutenant Ha!
It doesn't matter if we have 2 months or 1 day.
As long as we're in this uniform,
we can't look away from a rape case!
On top of that, you're in the Metro Detective Division!
Even a mere officer is willing to do it.
You're the officer who shot the gun, right?
Yes, ma'am.
I was worried you might be too rugged,
but you're gentle at heart.
What? Are you unhappy?
- Do you want to catch Grasshoppers? - No, ma'am.
Metro Detective Division will lead the case.
Work with Subway Police to solve this case right away!
We only have two months to catch the serial murderer and Grasshopper.
Maybe I was trying too hard to look cool.
I'll keep to my principles even if I die tomorrow.
Let's switch partners.
We're a joint investigation team now.
If we want to share the information each team investigated,
I think it would make sense to switch partners.
Officer Yoo, you should be my partner.
- Me? - Hey.
- I'd like that. - Woo Hyuk, watch it.
(Catch the Ghost)
- Hold tight. - Okay!
Speed all the way.
The serial rape case was going to be covered up.
I don't want to remember it.
You're blaming me too, aren't you?
I came because I want to help.
Ji Seok doesn't know yet, does he?
Why you joined the Subway Police...
Newbie, just keep being my partner.
Let's break up again when we get sick of each other.
This turned out for the better.
It's for the better.