Blood...
Bella...
Bella?
Dad.
What do I do?
We've been having ramyeon for days now.
And you're calling this a meal?
Then are we supposed to drive out
each time?
[ Just eat! ]
[ We don't have anything in the kitchen. ]
Hey, aren't you tired of eating that?
[ Why are you picking on her? ]
Darn it.
We were eating!
Why are you taking that?
Hey!
Something good is going to happen.
Stop eating.
We need space for the good stuff.
Thank you for the meal!
Unbelievable.
It's good.
Eat.
What are you going to do now?
What?
You said you'll sell the place
and move to Seoul.
I don't know.
What about Seol-a?
We'll find her mother and send her back.
Right.
But don't you think it's weird?
The mom must have a reason
why she left her with you.
It's too mean to just send her away.
Do I look like a charity to you?
I've never seen her
and she's not even related to me.
So why should I keep her?
I don't know.
Dad.
Bella is...
Be quiet.
- Take care of it.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Just get in.
The security team will take care of it.
How can we just leave like this?
Bella is gone!
We need to report it to the police
and call 911!
She's dead.
She's dead, okay?
She fell into the river in this weather.
Do you really expect her to be alive?
But still, how can we leave like this?
- We need to at least try...
- Are you trying
to destroy me?
Do you want the whole world to know that
the daughter of the head
of Donghan International killed
the world-class designer, Bella?
The company will quietly
take care of this.
You came here alone.
Don't say anything.
Where did she go? Gosh.
Gosh, where is she?
Seung-mo!
- Yes?
- I can't find Seol-a anywhere.
What happened to her?
Let's go out and look.
Gosh.
Seol-a!
Hello. Did you see Seol-a, by any chance?
- Seol-a?
- Yes.
Seol-a? I saw her a while ago.
Where did I see here, again?
- You're getting dementia.
- What?
We just saw her go to the mountains.
The mountains?
[ Why? ]
Weren't you with her?
Yes. Thank you!
Thank you.
Gosh, what is she thinking?
Stop that.
Why is that kid such a brat?
- I said, stop that!
- Stop what?
Darn it.
I'm going back,
so you look for her on your own.
Hey! Why, you...
Hey!
I get that you're going through a lot,
but this is too much!
Seol-a is only seven.
Do you think she feels good
about this situation?
Darn it.
Do whatever you want.
Seol-a!
[ Hello. ]
You're here.
It's a good thing you came.
[ When the town is going through
something like this,  ]
we need the youngsters to help out.
- Where are you going?
- To hunt down the boar.
- "The boar"?
[ - Yes. ]
Mr. Yang got attacked by a boar
while picking mushrooms
and hasn't been able to walk for a month.
[ The boars are so wicked these days. ]
- You won't believe it!
- We need to kill them all!
Seung-mo, there are boars up there.
What are we going to do?
- Chef Moon!
- Chef Moon, where are you going?
Young man!
What will you do with your bare hands?
The boars won't be an easy match!
That's not it. Seol-a ran away
and the ladies said
she went into the mountains.
- What?
- Chef Moon's kid?
Yes.
[ What are you all doing here? ]
Goodness, they think their kid
went into the mountains.
- What?
- So that's why he ran like that.
Let's follow on before something happens.
- Yes.
- Why would we go?
- This is crazy!
- It's dangerous!
Kid!
Seol-a!
Gosh.
Kid!
Seol-a!
It's going to get dark soon.
Where did she go?
Kid!
What are you doing out here?
It's dangerous.
A kid like you
shouldn't be out here alone.
You wanted me to go.
I was just happy to see my father.
But you don't like me and want me out.
What are you talking about?
Do you really want me to yell at you?
- Over there.
- What are you doing?
Over there.
What is it?
[ Seol-a. ]
Are you okay?
Hey.
Hey!
- Seol-a!
- It's getting cold.
- Why? What's wrong?
- What's that noise?
- There's something over there!
- What is it?
[ - It's a boar!
- Stop holding me like that! ]
It's not a boar.
It's Seol-a! Goodness!
Seol-a!
Goodness, did you hide behind me
because you thought it was a boar?
Goodness gracious,
we've found you, Seol-a!
Did you run out of fear?
Seol-a, why did you go up
the mountains so late at night?
Are you okay? Are you thirsty?
Do you need water?
- No?
- Seol-a.
Where's Seung-mo? Your dad?
- In the mountains. A woman.
- Yes?
My dad was in a mess
and there was blood everywhere.
Blood? Oh my goodness!
Who? Where did this happen?
All the way over there!
- Over there? Where?
- Over there?
- Goodness! What's happening?
- Gosh, Chef Moon!
Let's go.
Just walk. You can't even run.
- Chef Moon!
- My goodness.
Take it slow.
Who is this lady?
Take this, please.
I am a man with great strength,
but I hurt my back
at the county's athletic meet.
I may be smart, but I'm not fit at all.
You know it.
I have dislocations all the time.
That's why I can't put my arms behind.
Do you want me to support her?
- No, it's her butt. What should I do?
- Just get out!
- Goodness, isn't this blood?
- What?
- There's blood!
- Gosh, what is going on?
Flip it around. My goodness.
What is going on?
Gosh.
Goodness.
What's taking the ambulance so long?
By the way, did that lady
get hit by a boar?
I don't know.
Let me catch my breath.
The county office should've caught
all the boars in advance.
Look, a person is injured.
No wonder civil servants are condemned.
I should write a petition
to the Blue House.
To the Blue House? Look at you.
Why do you always blame the county office
for everything?
What did we do wrong?
Why do you have to make
a fuss about everything?
We have a witness!
A witness we carried
all the way from the woods.
Come on, Chef Moon. Am I right or wrong?
Right, go ahead and speak.
I said I don't know.
Everyone, just stop.
A person is lying down with an injury.
Look at all that blood.
I hope she's not in a critical condition.
What should we do?
Wait.
[ This is when ]
a civil servant should step in
and do his duty.
- Okay.
- What?
Go check on her.
[ Taking a closer look... ]
Yes?
She's pretty.
- She's pretty?
- Yes.
- Ouch!
[ - Gosh, why isn't the ambulance coming?
- How could you say that? ]
- Gosh.
- Ouch!
- You're pathetic.
- What did I do wrong?
[ Tell me, what did I do wrong? ]
- Gosh, they're so loud.
[ - She's pretty! ]
[ - Stop it!
- What? "She's pretty"? ]
[ Seol-a. ]
You should've gone inside.
Is that lady okay?
Yes.
Don't worry and go inside the home.
The adults will take care of it.
Oh, you must be hungry.
Wait a second.
- Nibble on this. Let's go inside the home.
- Okay.
Just a second.
Yes?
[ Yes, I'm the one who made the call. ]
[ Where are you? ]
[ Come through the west entrance
of Seoha Village. ]
[ Okay. ]
- Let go!
- Stop it!
- Why are you being so worked up about it?
- Get out.
That was totally inappropriate to say.
I'm so embarrassed.
- Who cares?
- How could you joke around?
- I was carrying on with my duties.
- You're so pathetic.
- Could you just shut it, you old woman?
- You're pretty too!
I know I'm pretty. So what?
Everyone knows I'm pretty.
What are you doing?
You didn't ask for my permission.
You can't eat someone else's chocolate
without permission.
Honey, what are you doing?
Well, Da-hoon gave me this chocolate,
but she took it away from me.
That's wrong.
[ What are you talking about? ]
The ambulance is coming soon.
[ - I see. ]
- Seol-a. You can't be there.
Come over here to me.
[ What's going on? What is that? ]
[ What is she? ]
[ - It's a zombie!
- Protect us, Buddha. ]
What are you doing? Let her go.
I'm hungry.
[ Come here. ]
Gosh.
Wait, that's...
Hey, what is this?
This is goji juice.
- Goji?
[ - What? "Goji"? ]
What's that?
It's just some kind of juice.
Then she's not covered in blood?
[ It's juice? ]
- Really?
- Yes.
[ Goodness, what a relief. ]
Thank the lords and deities
all around the world!
What a relief it is indeed.
Why is it a relief?
Is it a relief because she's pretty?
[ - Yes. ]
- Can you quiet down?
I'm so out of my mind.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
By the way,
who are you all?
- Well... I'm...
- Right.
You fainted in the woods
and he carried you all the way here.
- He saved your life.
- Cut it.
Wait.
Haven't we met before?
What?
Are you dropping pickup lines right now?
No, it's not like that.
[ Goodness, old habits never die. ]
- Shame on you!
Chef Moon, I'm disappointed in you.
It's not the right time.
Get out.
Hey, Miss. Are you okay?
Who are you and where are you from?
- Me?
- Yes, you.
I'm...
Who am I?
[ What's your name? ]
Do you remember your name?
- No.
- You don't?
"No"? Is she from overseas?
[ - Will you shut it?
- Why? ]
Where do you live?
I don't know.
[ Do you have any parents,  ]
siblings, relatives, or friends?
I don't know. I can't remember.
She sure did lose it.
- Lose what?
- She's speaking casually to us.
She lost her manners for sure.
[ Goodness, that's not important! ]
I'm certain. I saw her before.
[ Haven't we met before? ]
[ What? Amnesia? ]
[ Yes. Other than that,  ]
she only has light scratches and bruises.
Simple treatments will do.
Is this some kind of drama or what?
How could something so bizarre happen?
It can happen.
There are cases when patients suffer
from brief memory loss after an accident.
Most of them do gain their memory back.
But there are rare cases in which
that doesn't happen.
What will happen to her?
We'll have to see.
- Okay.
What's going to happen now?
Do we have to take care of her?
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
Can't you remember anything?
- I'm hungry.
- Gosh.
Don't worry.
We have our light in the dark.
Right. We have Soon-mi!
Oh right, Officer Jo.
We have her for moments like these.
Trust me and follow.
- So reliable!
- Are you sure about this?
[ Who's Soon-mi? ]
[ It's his daughter.
I wonder what she's doing. ]
- Let's go.
[ - It's all going to work out! ]
[ - Nothing.
- What? ]
What are you talking about?
Is she a ghost?
[ A spy or what? ]
[ Why are you getting mad at me? ]
The computer doesn't recognize her.
What can I do?
Look, here.
Her thumbprint isn't registered?
No.
What are we going to do?
Unidentified patients must be kept
in the designated hospital for 48 hours.
Who is standing surety for her?
- What?
- Surety?
Surety?
[ Surety... ]
[ Safe Nonyang, Happy Residents ]
- What do we do now?
- She's nobody.
I guess we should either stand surety
for her or keep her in the village.
What are you talking about? Surety?
We can't stand surety for a stranger.
You see,
you must never stand surety for anyone.
Not even for your parents.
[ - Right. ]
- And to be honest,
the one who brought her should take
responsibility to the end. Am I wrong?
[ She's right. ]
I'm leaving soon.
I'm not staying here.
The one who takes out the trash is
supposed to be in charge of it.
Don't you know
the polluter pays principle?
You caused this,
- so you are responsible for it.
- Right.
I agree with him.
Officer Jo is my daughter.
That's why she's doing us a favor
and let us keep her in the village.
She doesn't have any memories. Until when?
She might get her memories back soon.
What if she doesn't?
Well, that's none of our business.
Come on. Don't be ridiculous.
Gosh, this is annoying.
Let's take her to the village first and...
What do you mean by we take her?
- You take her.
- Me?
No way.
That doesn't make sense.
Mr. Hwang, you're the chief
of the village. Why don't you take her?
[ What? ]
I'm the Subsection Chief of
the county office
and she's the head of the village
and the women's society!
I'm swamped
with all the government affairs!
We can't take care of her. Am I wrong?
He's right. Don't be crazy.
Now, we have only one person left.
One must be responsible for what they did.
[ - He's right. ]
- Right.
[ Let's just take her with us. ]
I'm sure her memories will come back soon.
Why should I...
This is driving me crazy.
Darn it.
Wait. The kid.
Where's the kid?
Don't do this.
I can't go like this.
What should I...
[ Menu ]
What the... What is it?
[ Chinese restaurant ]
Hey! Kid!
What are you doing here?
You didn't say anything to me.
I didn't want to come,
but the lady is so strong.
- Excuse me.
- Leave her alone.
She has been whining that she's hungry.
We must feed her some food.
He's right. Let's grab some food.
Seol-a, come on in with us.
We have been starving too.
Let's get some food.
- Okay.
- I feel like jjajangmyeon. Let's eat.
[ - Okay. ]
All right.
- Hello.
[ - Welcome. ]
- One jjajangmyeon please.
- Okay.
Seriously.
I definitely have seen her somewhere.
You keep saying weird things.
Where could you have possibly seen her?
I can't remember.
[ It must be an epidemic. ]
Losing memories.
You're single.
If you like her, just tell her...
That's not what it is.
[ Easy. You might get an upset stomach. ]
Does she have a beggar
inside her stomach or what?
"A beggar"?
I think she's staying here illegally.
Like a poor homeless on the street?
A poor homeless?
[ No way. ]
Hey, I remember where I saw her.
- Come on. Don't be...
- Be quiet.
Follow me.
[ What is it? ]
Hey.
I'm sure that woman was...
What?
An Australian beggar.
An Australian beggar?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I saw her when I went on a business trip
to Australia.
Really?
What is an Australian beggar doing here?
How would I know?
It's not a good thing to talk about,
so let's keep this just between us.
Okay.
Let's go.
[ Nakwon Restaurant ]
[ Let's see. ]
[ Who are you calling at this late hour? ]
Stay out of women's business.
Hey, it's me.
Well, I called you for a reason.
You must carry this to the grave.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Today, some Australian beggar
came to our village.
What?
No. Australia.
Austria. A beggar from Austria.
[ It's Australia. ]
The country is Australia.
Hello? Yes. It's Australia...
A beggar came from that country.
I'm telling you.
You must not tell anyone, okay? Okay, bye.
Hey, Mrs. Byung-chun.
I'm going to tell you a top secret.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Today, some Australian beggar
came to our village.
Her fashion is totally different.
It must be because she's from Australia.
No. It looked fake.
Hello? A beggar came from Australia.
No, she's not pretty.
I'm much prettier than her.
It's a secret. Okay?
Hey, Yoon-ja.
You must keep this to yourself.
It's a top secret.
Seriously? An Australian beggar?
You must not tell anyone
about what I just told you.
Hey, that's enough.
That way, you won't be able
to tell the whole nation about it.
Why don't you just make an announcement?
Tell everyone that an Australian beggar
came to our town.
Goodness. Why are you speaking so loudly?
I didn't lie.
It's what Chef Moon said.
You don't know anything.
Sure. Sure. Goodness.
Hang on a second. Now...
Just stop it already.
I need to tell Hyeok's mother about it.
Oh, hey. It's me.
[ An Australian beggar. ]
This way.
[ This way. ]
Come in. This way.
Welcome.
[ Chef Moon. ]
Where is the westerner?
- Who?
- I heard...
an Australian beggar came to our village.
How did you...
It's not me.
It's a secret.
We are going to keep it secret.
Thanks to Ms. Pi,
I get to see something interesting.
Where is the foreign beggar?
We dropped her off on the way.
What? We came here for nothing then?
It's late. You should go home now.
Who is the woman that went into the house?
Right. She seemed new.
I understand.
I'm sure it's hard for a single man
to raise a child.
- Who raises whom?
- Your daughter.
She's not my daughter.
Then who is that woman?
What are you thinking?
- That's not what it is!
- My goodness.
- Jeez.
[ - Goodness. ]
That freak has got a temper.
What's so bad about being curious? Right?
He's one cranky man.
Please don't be mad.
He's just tired today.
Then tell us.
- What?
- Over there.
- Who is she?
- Tell us.
She's a relative of his.
A distant relative.
A relative, I see.
- I will get going.
- Okay.
Okay, bye.
See? She's just his relative.
Do you believe that?
How did Ms. Pi know about her?
Are you acting?
You are the only one whom I told about it.
And I didn't tell anyone.
- So who could it be?
- It's not me.
Forget it.
I didn't realize it before,
but that lady stinks.
Goodness.
[ Who am I? ]
[ Why can't I remember anything? ]
I will put the clothes here.
Right. There is no underwear.
Forget it.
[ The first red sea-bream shows up! ]
[ We caught it! ]
Darn it.
Seriously,
are these the only clothes you've got?
Be happy with what you've got.
They're my clothes.
Of course they don't fit you.
What? They fit you?
You should rather be thankful
than complaining about the clothes.
Just put on what you got.
If you don't like them, just be naked.
What? Be naked?
- What a pervert...
- Pervert?
You're unbelievable.
And why do you talk down to me?
You don't know me.
It's just comfortable that way.
If you don't like it,
you can talk down to me too.
How old are you?
Hey, she doesn't remember her name.
There's no way she remembers her age.
[ Now stop, both of you. ]
I'm sure you're confused
because you lost your memories.
Why don't you go take some rest?
Okay.
I figured she didn't have panties,
so I gave her my new teddy bear panties.
It's kind of me, right?
Yes.
Yours?
Your teddy bear panties?
Is that what she was talking about?
[ The shock from the accident
caused a severe bruise on her head,  ]
[ but it's not too serious. ]
Let her take a complete rest.
It will help her recover fast.
Let's see it for now.
Okay, Doctor.
All right.
Stop pretending to sleep.
Dad, what do I do?
I will take care of everything.
So don't say anything unnecessary.
Just keep quiet.
I...
I killed Bella.
Is it a wild animal?
Goodness! What are you doing?
I'm hungry.
Darn it.
Am I a maid or what?
You guys are unbelievable.
It looks so tasty.
There it comes.
- Thank you for the food!
Let's eat.
That was a great meal.
Chef Moon is the best.
- You're the best!
Now, please get us some morning coffee.
I want an espresso.
I want some hot chocolate.
[ Seriously,  ]
are you kidding me?
From now on, earn your food. Okay?
- You.
- Yes?
Clean up the table and wash the dishes.
And you. Go clean the backyard.
And you.
Follow her.
What are you doing? Do it right now!
- Okay.
But it's already clean.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know.
Isn't this your job, Old Lady?
That has been bothering me
since yesterday.
Why do you call me Old Lady?
I don't look like an old lady.
Then how should I call you?
How old are you?
I'm seven.
Call me sister.
Sister.
You have got to be kidding me.
Okay, Sister.
Well done. Good girl.
Let's go.
That petty punk.
He's a good cook, but he's so arrogant.
I might get a housewife's eczema.
Seriously.
I wonder where a cafe is.
[ Seoha Rice Mill ]
A rice mill?
[ A teahouse? ]
Is it a rice mill or a teahouse?
It looks weird.
[ Seoha Teahouse ]
Have a seat.
I didn't know there was a place like this.
Wait, you're not a local here.
Your accent is...
I'm from Seoul.
You know the old house in the corner.
Then you should be able to tell
how good our coffee is.
[ Our coffee is the original Brazilian... ]
Arabica style.
Pardon?
"I wonder what's the deal with the woman"
"with such a modern and sophisticated
look, which is rare around here."
That's what you were thinking,
weren't you?
What?
Oh, dear.
Are you curious about me?
Just because you are curious,
- do I have to tell you?
- Yes.
No. Sorry.
I used to be a successful model
when I was in Seoul.
And I'm not the type of person
who brags about those things.
Oh, a model.
[ So you're a model. ]
How would I ever show off that I'm a model
who has done photoshoots in Seoul?
- That's not polite of me.
- Not at all.
That's very charming of you.
I wasn't just a famous model,
but a rising star, even starring in ads.
You think I'm the type
that would show off about it?
I can tell you're a star
even without you telling me all this.
Anyway,
if you're here to have some coffee,
can you pay for 10 cups in advance?
For 10 cups?
I only take cash.
Cash!
It's 3.5 dollars per coffee?
I'll give you 35 dollars.
I only have 32 dollars.
That's fine.
Thank you.
[ Update on the Pungcheonok Lawsuit File ]
[ Lawsuit regarding
trademark rights on Pungcheonok ]
Hello, everyone.
Sorry I took so long in calling
for a meeting.
Please understand that I had to look over
all departments' works beforehand.
Before we begin, Mr. Jung,
may I ask you a question?
Yes, please do.
Why do we have so many lawsuits going on?
These lawsuits are
from little issues
that we have with people
while establishing
our new franchise brand.
There's no need to worry about them.
We've already won the lawsuit
on the trademark rights
on Pungcheonok, too.
There's no need to worry, really.
Is that right?
This is something I've learned
in my long time living abroad.
Foreigners think very highly of Korea
because we're so developed.
So I assumed that Donghan was managed
in a very developed way as well.
I was quite disappointed
after reading over my report.
Very disappointed, actually.
It looks like we've been picking fights,
not managing our company.
How we're expanding our business
is also very backward.
In Korea, that's called bullying,
abusing our power
by stealing others' brands.
I will never accept such a way
of expansion,
not during my time here
as the Managing Director.
Yes, sir.
Yes, Gwang-su.
Jun-su did what?
All right.
Where's Chairman Han?
He's not here yet.
Come and have a drink.
You seem busy.
It's been a while since I saw you.
Do you know why he called me?
I don't know.
Maybe he'll announce his successor.
I'm just kidding. It's funny.
This is my first time
seeing you so bad at hiding your thoughts.
I'm in no mood for joking around.
Why do you look so serious?
Is it because of Jun-su?
- Hello, sir.
- You're here.
Have a seat.
I thought it'd be nice if we got together
and had some nice fish stew.
Hello, there.
You went fishing with Jun-su?
- You're mean.
[ - Why? ]
Well,
you've never gone fishing with Chul-yong,
who has served you for over 20 years.
And you went with Jun-su in a heartbeat.
- Chul-yong must be disheartened.
- Well...
He doesn't like fishing.
He likes golfing more.
No need to torture him by going fishing,
don't you think?
Yes, sir.
Did you catch a lot?
Did you?
Jun-su is quite good.
[ He caught a really big one today. ]
[ Really? ]
What aren't you good at, son?
Grandfather taught me everything.
He told me to appease, not force.
[ It's all thanks to him. ]
Did you learn to talk like that
at Harvard?
You adorable kid.
[ This is what I prepared. ]
This is an avant-garde piece
that reflects the fear of uncertainty
we face as the new millennium
is approaching.
[ Donghan International
Principal Designer Contest ]
[ Judges ]
[ - Director!
- Director! ]
Please answer our question!
- Can you explain to us?
- Please stay away.
What's the relationship between you two?
[ News reporters' greed has at last brought
a tragic accident. ]
[ Managing Director Kang Min-suk
of Donghan International ]
[ and Ms. Yoo, a model and a designer,  ]
[ were in a car chase,
fleeing from the reporters,  ]
[ - and crashed into a 25-tonne truck. ]
- What?
[ The two were severely injured ]
[ and were transferred to a hospital,
but passed. ]
[ Application for Divorce ]
[ Seoul Family Court ]
Chul-yong, you can't do this.
How will Hyun-a and I live?
Honey!
Honey.
- They really got married.
- I guess they did.
[ Sure, money is great,
but this is so wrong. ]
[ - Right?
- He's the worst. ]
[ Is that true? Shame on him. ]
[ Indeed. ]
[ Announcement Board ]
[ Notice of New Positions ]
[ Lim Chul-yong will be promoted to
Managing Director of Donghan Food. ]
You always have something you want
when you buy me jewelry.
- What is it?
- What do you mean?
It's just that our wedding anniversary is
coming soon.
Is that what it is?
I thought you were giving me jewelry
because of Jun-su.
What do you mean?
Never mind.
Can I take a look at this?
Honey,
choose wisely...
for your father and for Donghan.
If you become the successor,
then it becomes my husband's company.
If Jun-su becomes the successor,
then it becomes my son's company.
Whoever becomes the successor,
I plan on respecting my father's choice.
I have no courage.
I'm thankful for my father
for entertaining me with all of this.
I don't care who becomes the successor,
but I'll surely have to think
about who has been treating me better.
I don't see anything I like here.
Hyun-a, is it?
Your daughter.
What is she up to?
She hasn't really gone crazy, has she?
I've just heard rumors that she has.
Let's get going.
Why now?
Why?
It's all because of that woman, Bella.
Had she just accepted my offer,
my company and my daughter
would've been fine.
That woman!
[ Look at that! ]
[ - No.
- Hold on. ]
I think this red one
would suit her better.
Her complexion is pale,
so the red one would suit her.
Sure, let's see.
Goodness!
[ You look so good in everything. ]
Maybe it's because you're so pretty.
I told you, I'm the one
who knows about style.
[ Stop bundling her up! ]
She won't be able to walk!
Style, my foot.
It's cold. She needs to dress warmly.
Yes, nice and cozy. How adorable.
Here. Give this to Seol-a.
[ Don't go around ]
wearing Chef Moon's ugly pants.
Dress like this from now on.
It's good that we've got
a lot of clothes we don't wear.
Done.
Even getting out of all these clothes is
so much work.
This is for you.
Really? It's mine?
Yes.
How am I going to wear these?
What's up with all the clothes?
Neighbors donated them to me.
Where have you been?
Nowhere.
Don't you want some coffee?
Coffee? I'm fine.
Why?
I went to a cafe nearby yesterday.
There, I met an angel
who awakened the artist's soul in me.
"Soul"? "Angel"?
I'm actually
an artist.
An artist?
What? A painter?
Yes, a painter.
Artist.
It's a little embarrassing
to say this myself,
but in my teens, I was called a genius.
I swept the awards
from all contests nationwide.
In university, I was so close
to winning an award
at the national contest.
But one day,
I lost all my artistic inspiration.
Persimmon? Dried ones are my favorite!
I'm craving some now
that we're talking about it.
Me too.
Hey!
Go on.
I met my muse for the first time
in 10 years.
When I saw her, my fingertips tingled.
I had this strong desire
to just start painting her,
but unfortunately, I have no money
for coffee.
[ I'm losing my muse ]
just because I have no money for coffee!
Just go and talk to her.
Talking to her doesn't cost anything.
"I thought I could paint you
if I did this."
"Because you're my muse!"
People are coming
to see the house tomorrow,
so we have to clean the house today.
- Coming to see the house?
- Cleaning?
Dad, why are they coming to see our house?
Because we're all moving to Seoul.
But I like it here.
Right. Maybe I'll remember something
when I go to Seoul.
Seung-mo, I promise to make the house
squeaky clean.
But can you lend me 10 dollars first?
- 10 dollars?
- Yes.
I'll see how well you do.
Seol-a! Your dad is giving us 10 dollars
if we clean well!
I'm not her dad!
Hey! He was talking to me, not you!
Goodness.
Look through the site thoroughly
and check with the police
and all hospitals.
Order them to check all people
who have died around there
and check if any of that is her.
- Yes, sir.
- Don't get the company security to do it.
The other guys before
did a really great job.
Yes, sir.
May I ask who she is?
You know that with secrets,
the more you know,
the more harmful it gets.
Yes, sir.
[ Private Agency ]
[ We can do anything for you. ]
Look around the whole accident area
and find me this woman's corpse.
What do we do when we find it?
Make it as if
[ she never existed. ]
You'll arrange a meeting
with Mr. Lim for me, right?
He's so annoying.
Hey!
Coffee.
May I get some coffee, please?
What... What are you doing?
What are you doing?
What are you eating?
What are you talking about?
Why is he here out so late?
What do you mean?
- I was just...
[ - Are you stalking me? ]
Are you spying on me?
Why would I spy on you?
- You pervert.
- What?
What was that?
Is she insane? Not an amnesiac?
Gosh.
[ Seoul High Court ]
[ Verdict ]
[ Seung-mo,  ]
actually,
there's a problem at our restaurant.
Come on. I told you not to tell him that.
He's leaving for a big event.
Hospitals nearby and the police said
that there are
no unidentified bodies found.
She's probably down there.
I've asked the locals in the area
and they said
that finding a body here is impossible,
even when people drown while playing
in the water in summer.
Is that right?
What's that?
- Isn't that a shoe?
- Sorry?
Go and bring it.
Darn it.
Hey. Go.
Go. Hurry.
[ Managing Director Lim Chul-yong ]
The body couldn't be found?
Mr. Jin's friend
from when he was the police is
stationed at the Nonyang Police Station,
so he looked into the matter.
And there hasn't been
any unidentified body found
in the area recently.
And coming down the cliff,
the water is deep and flows fast.
Even when people drown there,
finding the body is nearly impossible.
I see.
Tell him
to take care of Hyun-a's accident.
Yes, sir.
You want it to be
as if the accident has never happened?
Yes, sir.
I'll get back to you when we're done.
- Let's go and eat.
- Yes, sir.
[ She's my cousin from Seoul
and she's rich. ]
She needs a weekend cottage,
so I brought her here.
[ You should be thankful. ]
Nobody would want to buy a house
in the middle of nowhere like this.
She's so rich,
she'll just sign the deal right away.
Just sell it.
Cousin!
Let me tell you how special this house is.
It's the most historical house in
Seoha Village.
You should be honored.
That's just another way
of saying that it's old.
An old house requires a lot of work.
Seems like they didn't do a good job
with renovating the house.
[ What? ]
What's this?
Why is the kitchen so unnecessarily big?
Seems like I'll have to rebuild
the whole house.
That's going to cost a lot.
I'd have to renovate the entire house.
[ - Really?
- Yes. ]
Nobody can stop you when you own it.
[ Fix it as you wish. ]
Sorry, but please leave.
What?
I thought you said
you have to sell the house quickly.
Please leave.
Chef Moon.
I'm not selling the house. Leave.
What is this?
It took me hours to get here from Seoul.
You said that there's a good property.
- Are you messing with me?
- No.
What is this nonsense?
[ - Hear me out.
- Whatever. ]
[ You're so annoying. ]
You told me that you were selling it!
[ Wait for me! ]
- Why aren't you selling it?
- Why?
Why aren't you selling it?
Seung-mo, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
[ - I'm heading to Seoul. ]
Seoul?
Take me with you.
I'm not going for fun.
I have something to take care of.
I need to run an errand, too.
I need to get cash from the ATM!
Nonsense. Just go to the town center!
I need to buy clothes, too!
Dad, you're abandoning me, aren't you?
[ Dad! ]
I told you, I'm not your dad!
Seol-a!
[ Bella in an accident ]
[ Bella is Taking on a New Challenge ]
[ Bella Leaves Louis ]
[ Who Is Designer Bella? ]
[ Bella ]
Dad.
Did you find her?
What happened to Bella?
Hyun-a.
You killed Bella.
- I'll go and have a look.
- No, it's fine. I'll go.
But...
I can revive her if you want me to.
What?
[ Patient Lim Hyun-a ]
No.
From now on,
you are Bella.
I'm hungry.
What an...
eccentric woman she is.
Very eccentric, indeed.
"Eccentric"?
Are you talking about me?
Why are you here?
Goodness.
I've never seen you before. Who are you?
I'm just here to use the bathroom.
Sorry.
Fine, fine!
[ I'll get out! ]
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
She's alive.
[ She's eccentric, just like her name. ]
[ I guess you didn't learn manners
at school. ]
[ You have zero manners at all. ]
Are you kidding?
It looks so perfect on me.
I know you want to buy it for me.
[ What do you think? ]
Awesome!
If you can't remember,
then at least put yourself together!
How dare you talk like that?
What are you doing? Get out!
[ Why are you guys fighting? ]
Is she off to somewhere?
Goodness.
[ I keep thinking of her. ]
[ Make an order to find her
and kill her without anyone knowing. ]
What are you saying?
Let me introduce to you, the new Bella.