[ Episode 1 ]
[ - Hi, Bella. ]
- Hey, Ms. Jang.
"Madam Jang". I told you to call me that.
How could you address me like that?
I'm not some waitress
from the countryside.
Ms. Jang and Madam Jang
are the same thing.
[ Anyway, where are you now? ]
- Me? I'm at my studio.
[ - What? ]
Do you know what time it is?
Why are you still at your studio?
Oh, no!
Hey, if you miss your flight,
you're going to miss your world tour.
It takes over a day for you to get here.
It's in Australia. Australia!
Okay. I got it. I was just about to leave.
[ What about the outfit for the finale? ]
Not yet. I'll finish it over there.
What?
How could you
not have finished it already?
[ Bella, are you trying
to make me lose it? ]
[ You do this every time... ]
There you go.
All right. Look at that.
[ Chef Moon Obscure Only in Korea ]
[ Young Korean Chef Moon Seung-mo ]
[ Chef Moon Seung-mo ]
[ Award, Chef Moon Seung-mo ]
[ President Moon Jae-in ]
[ Pungcheonok ]
[ Pungcheonok, Chef Moon Seung-mo ]
Mom, I'm back! Give me some food!
Mom!
You brat.
That's how you greet you mom after months?
My gosh. Mom, you're still going strong.
You know what? She started cooking this
since dawn because you're coming.
Here.
Do you want some suyuk?
This is why my cholesterol level is high.
That spoiled brat.
Just a few slices, then. A few slices!
You're leaving again?
Where to, this time?
Australia. There's a Korean food event
on the Gold Coast.
Hey, can you stop going abroad?
There's no space for another article.
[ - Don't hang it then.
- You little brat. ]
You visited all eight provinces in Korea,
so you can learn about
traditional cuisine.
Now, you're going abroad all the time!
It's about time that we retire, you punk!
People live up to 100 years nowadays.
It's too early to retire.
No way. If you retire, you'll age quickly.
Your beauty is still ever so striking.
My gosh, you and your words.
Seung-mo, actually,
there's a problem at our restaurant.
Come on.
I told you not to tell him that.
He's leaving for a big event.
Unbelievable.
I must tell him in person,
so this is the right time.
Goodness.
I'm not sure what this is about, but stop.
I'll be there only for a week this time.
Let's talk once I return.
Should we discuss it on a trip?
I'll handle all of your problems.
Really?
Hey, how about this for our trip?
- Doesn't this look great?
- What a cool place.
Where is this place?
She bought an old house
in her hometown, Nonyang.
If you take over the restaurant
and get married,
we'll move and live in that house.
We've been fixing up the place
on our days off.
Move down there after 20 years.
What's the rush?
20 years? You spoiled punk.
I can't let this be.
Before you go, let's settle on this.
Get married this year.
Or go and bring me a grandchild.
I'll raise the kid. Okay?
Write that up and sign it today.
Come on.
We didn't open the restaurant yet.
Hey, kid. Where're your parents? Your mom?
What about your dad?
What?
So irresponsible! How could this happen?
She's really not my kid!
As if! She says you're her dad!
Dad, that's not true!
My gosh, what are we going to do now?
All right, fine. You irresponsible punk.
It's all right!
I could have totally taken her in.
Your mother is very open-minded, you know?
What on earth are you saying?
Is that how I raised you?
How could you abandon your wife and child?
She's not my child! She is not mine!
This is driving me crazy!
Hey, do you even know me?
Don't scare her like that.
Kid, what was your name again?
It's Seol-a. Kim Seol-a.
- Kim?
See? She's a Kim. She's not a Moon!
My grandpa told me!
He said that man was my dad.
He definitely told me that man was my dad!
Oh, no. It's all right. Don't cry.
It's all right.
- Her grandpa must've raised her.
- Her grandpa?
When did you go to Chungcheong Province?
Chungcheong Province?
Don't fall for that too, Dad.
Why would I go there?
I swear! She's not my kid. You come here.
Hey, you'd better not lie about this.
Am I your dad?
My gosh.
I must go now to catch my flight.
Find her real parents before I return.
She's not mine. I'll be back, Mom.
- Hey, you!
- She's really not mine!
Where are you going?
- Hey. That...
- Seung-mo!
Hey.
It's ridiculous. I can't do this anymore.
We go through all this trouble every show.
Technology can help us in so many ways!
Why are you cooped up in your studio
and why do you fix everything by hand?
Working with my hands inspires me.
What choice do I have?
She's such a high-maintenance designer.
My goodness.
What? What is this?
You said inspirations come to you there.
But why haven't you finished this outfit?
Because you keep nagging me,
all of my inspirations ran away.
By the way, this is my last show
with that old geezer, Louis.
Is he coming to tomorrow's show?
You bet. It's the last show of the tour.
Besides, he wants to renew the contract.
That old geezer is stubborn.
I won't renew the contract no matter what.
Don't fall for his tricks.
Okay, I got it. You're so picky.
Did you eat?
No.
Don't tell me you didn't eat anything.
Let's get you treated for anorexia.
You need more than water to survive.
It's not water.
It's goji juice. It's super healthy.
You'll die if you keep that up.
If you don't eat solid food, you'll die.
People don't die that easily.
Where are you going? Finish the outfit.
I'll go out and get inspired.
Don't nag me. Just give me some time.
My gosh, Bella. Bella! Hey, this outfit...
[ Holiday Must-do ]
[ Korean BBQ Buffet Restaurant ]
[ China town ]
[ You can't even kill that yourself? ]
[ Come on, it's not your first time. ]
First, go after the head. Okay?
Strike it hard,
[ so it loses consciousness. ]
And cover the eyes with a towel.
Why do you think? It'll flounder to live.
[ Listen up. Press on it with your weight. ]
[ Go from the head to the body. ]
Slant your knife toward the body.
That's right. The heart.
Stabbing it in one go is important. Okay?
No! Be careful! The suitcase! Watch out!
Watch out!
Are you...
Darn it.
What's she doing? She said she was okay.
Hey! You!
- Gosh. Hey.
- What's going on?
- Hey.
- Mr. Choi.
Do something!
Mr. Choi.
[ She got the wrong idea about me. ]
[ - My gosh!
- Goodness. What should we do? ]
Hey, that woman.
Mom.
Grandpa.
She's Korean?
[ I can affirm that. ]
This isn't funny.
We have everything here
including the knives.
You always bring yours.
A perfect chance for a misunderstanding.
You know that I need my knives to cook.
I brought things that weren't on the list.
Bay salt from Sinan. Mushroom powder.
And dried vegetables.
Of course, I know what they are.
[ But people over here don't know them. ]
[ Goodness. ]
He's having a blast
when his phone call almost got me killed.
- Who is it?
- He's just a friend.
A pathetic man who went to draw the ocean,
but he's only fishing.
He's an artist who makes me angry.
I cook Korean food, not Japanese.
Why did he ask me about filleting a fish?
What did she say?
She's just malnourished.
Malnourished?
I think she's staying here illegally.
Like a poor homeless on the street?
A poor homeless?
No way.
Look at her belongings.
I've seen a lot of people like her.
After studying abroad,
their standards are high.
But things aren't going well.
They can't return because of their pride.
And when they start doing drugs like her,
[ it's a fast track to this. ]
All right. We should get going now.
She's not answering her phone again.
How could she be so self-centered?
I've been calling her nonstop.
What?
[ Madam Jang ]
Come on.
Unbelievable.
- About that lady back there.
- What?
- The homeless lady.
- Yes.
Isn't she a bit too...
"A bit too"?
A bit too cautious about others?
Who does she think I am?
Do I look like that kind of person?
I'm kidding.
Anyway, since I helped you out today,
you need to help me
when I'm back in Seoul.
Of course. But are you coming back?
Well, I did get an offer,
but I'm still debating on it.
You're debating on it?
Talented people get noticed everywhere.
I've been all over the world
opening pop-up restaurants,
and I haven't seen anyone
get things prepared as well as you.
- Anyway, congratulations.
- It's all thanks to you, chef.
[ Gold Coast University Hospital ]
Fine.
She always showed up
right before the show, anyway.
It's huge.
What's that?
That tree?
[ There are so many pelicans. ]
They already know that
this will be a famous restaurant.
- Are we almost at the fish market?
- Yes. It's just down there.
What are you going to make with this?
I'll have to think about it.
There.
[ Invitation,
From October 15 to October 23 ]
Darn it!
Chef. They love your food.
I hope that impressed her.
This is crazy.
Oh my goodness.
[ Gold Coast Skypoint ]
[ Louis Bella World Tour Fashion Show 2019 ]
[ Staff only ]
[ Okay! Go on, guys! ]
[ He is not ready yet. ]
Where is she?
[ Okay. We hope that... ]
Seriously. You're dead meat.
Hey! Come this way!
You! Are you crazy?
Do you have to do this at every show?
Where in the world were you?
Do you have to come like this
and frighten me?
Stop the nagging
and give me my finale dress.
Gosh, you little...
- Take it.
[ - Ladies and gentlemen,  ]
I need to go, so hurry up.
Hurry up, okay?
Bella! The finale dress!
Here.
Hurry.
Good job.
- Mr. Choi?
- Yes?
Designer brands are fighting
to work with Bella.
All interest is on her next move.
Honey!
[ Come here! ]
Okay!
What is it?
You let Seung-mo take this again,
didn't you?
Just a tiny little bit.
Tiny, my foot! It's almost empty!
Gosh, what am I going to do with you?
It's not like I let him
take the whole pot.
We can just make some more.
And will you be doing that?
I'm going to have to make it.
Anyway, what are we going to do with her?
Seung-mo insisted she's not his.
It has to be true, right?
We'll find out when he gets back
and checks properly.
What do you mean, "check properly"?
Like a paternity test?
- Welcome!
- I guess we have customers.
We're here to inspect the power.
Where is your switchboard?
- Gosh, thank you for coming.
- Sure.
If you go to the back,
there's a switchboard by the window.
All right.
It must be a fuss to go around
and check them all.
This building is old,
so you should have it checked often.
By the way, would you like some tea?
We need to get going, anyway.
No, it will only be a minute.
Thank you for trusting me
with the core of the group,
International.
Sit down.
If you're going to thank anyone,
it should be your wife.
Are you okay with it, honey?
I like watching operas
in the classy VIP seats.
Sir, I think that the vacancy
for the head of Donghan Food
should be given to...
He should be arriving anytime soon.
[ There you are. ]
Jun-su?
You didn't tell us you'd be coming.
I didn't call you on purpose
so that I can surprise you.
Let's see.
You've become even younger, mother.
You're as beautiful as ever.
Is that how you're going to pay
for upsetting me?
[ - Have you been well?
- Of course. ]
It's good to see you, Jun-su.
You should've given us a call.
We would've gone to pick you up
at the airport.
Have you been well, Mr. Lim?
[ Come on, now. Let's sit down. ]
We should stop the chit-chat.
About Donghan food.
I've decided to let Jun-su run it.
Jun-su! Really?
- Yes.
- That's good to hear, Jun-su.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
Come to think of it,
you said that your daughter
[ also attends a prestigious fashion school
in Europe, didn't you? ]
[ No, that's not it.
She must have graduated by now. ]
Yes, sir. She graduated
and is gaining work experience,
so she's working for a designer brand.
Such a competent individual
would be a good partner with you
at International.
Yes, sir.
Hyun-a, open the door.
How long are you going to keep this up?
You need to see a counselor or something!
Hyun-a!
What's this?
Honey! Wake up!
- What's wrong?
- Fire!
- What?
- Wake up! Hurry!
- Fire!
- Where?
- Honey! Hurry!
- What?
- What's going on?
- This way!
- Hurry!
- Where are you going?
Hurry up!
- Gosh!
- This way!
Oh, no!
Goodness!
Goodness! Oh, no!
What's going on?
- How could this be?
- Wait. The soy sauce.
Ssi-ganjang!
- Ssi-ganjang!
- Where are you going?
Where are you going? No!
Grandma!
Grandpa!
[ Gosh, what do we do? ]
Who is this? I'm busy.
Hello?
Is this the place?
I think so.
Let's head inside.
Here you go.
You couldn't stomach any food
by the best chefs in town,
but you liked the mung bean porridge?
Had it not been the porridge,
my last show would've been a disaster.
I wonder what made it so good.
Was it made with gold or something?
I have no idea. Let's order first.
Okay.
How is it?
I think this is the place. It's good.
Try some too, Madam Jang.
Really? Is it really good?
Should we ask for some mung bean porridge?
- It's not on the menu.
- We can ask.
- Why are you doing this?
- Why not?
It's a good chance to meet him
and I'll make him our designated chef.
Eat up.
[ Is that the man? ]
He doesn't look like a chef.
- Be quiet.
- It's fine.
Are both of you Korean?
You're Korean, too? Nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Manager Choi Gun-woo.
I see. Where's the chef?
I'm sorry.
Our head chef had to return
to Korea recently.
Is that right?
That's too bad.
- Do you two know each other?
- Yes.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
[ Save us, merciful Buddha. ]
[ May his soul rest in peace. ]
[ May her soul rest in peace. ]
[ Save us, merciful Buddha. ]
[ May his soul rest in peace. ]
[ May her soul rest in peace. ]
[ Save us, merciful Buddha. ]
[ May his soul rest in peace. ]
[ Announcement of New Team Members ]
[ Lim Chul-yong ]
[ New Managing Director of Donghan Food,
Kang Jun-su ]
Come in.
How could you do this?
Sir, I...
It was the chairman's decision.
But you know how hard I worked
to assist you all this time.
There's no need to feel rushed.
You know...
what kind of things I've done for you
when you asked me to.
I still have trouble sleeping at night.
The Pungcheonok incident...
A lot of natural disasters happen
in Korea.
There are storms, then there are fires.
Let's just say that a bothersome person
happened to die in a flood this summer.
Should we feel guilty about it?
Let's see.
That guy.
Seol-a, let's get out.
I thought it was an older person.
Right. He looks young.
Maybe he's the chef. The son.
I hear the family is in grief right now.
Apparently, everyone died in a fire.
You need to be careful of fires.
[ Fires are the worst. ]
[ You be careful, too. ]
Don't burn your house down.
You shouldn't be the one to talk to.
We should say hi since they're new.
- I'll go first.
- All right.
- Hello!
- Hi.
Hello there.
- You must be heartbroken.
- Sorry?
We were just excited
that there's a newcomer,
but what happened is so tragic.
You look exhausted, it must've been a lot
for you to take in.
That's not me. That's my friend.
Right? I thought so.
- I heard that the new guy is handsome.
- What?
I see.
I hear he's not married.
I'm not married.
Not you, I meant your friend.
Yes, he's single.
Then who's this child?
I'm Seol-a.
Your name is Seol-a?
Who's your father?
Well,
I don't know how to tell you.
[ Hang them well. ]
Yes, ma'am.
Seung-mo loves it when I stir-fry these.
[ That's right! ]
You get one per day.
The rest is Seung-mo's.
Don't you dare to eat more than that.
They look great.
[ Did you put everything? ]
- Put that in the sink for me.
- Okay.
[ - Good job.
- This is perfect. ]
Beautiful, isn't it?
Keep pushing.
Come on, you can do much better than that.
[ I'm trying my best. ]
[ That won't clean anything. ]
[ Stop nagging, will you? ]
How are you so weak when you eat so much?
[ You're right, I do eat a lot. ]
We built this house too big.
[ Exactly. ]
It's hard to clean this big house.
[ You said you were tired. ]
[ You said you wanted to rest. ]
[ You said you'd just rest here. ]
My arms are falling off.
Be careful.
You could've helped me out
instead of lying around like that.
I'm doing this for your parents.
Right. Let's see.
Seol-a, put your bag in that room
and get ready for bed. It's getting late.
[ You need to wash up and go to bed. ]
Okay.
Get up.
What are you going to do now?
I don't know.
I can't think.
I don't know what to do.
If you're busy, take the kid
and go back first.
Why would I take the kid?
And how can I, your best friend,
just leave you to be like this alone?
Right, it's not like you have
anywhere to go.
What are you talking about? Unbelievable.
How can you say that to your best friend?
I just think it's time for me to move out
and it'd be nice if I live with you.
And...
Hyo-myoung,
your daughter, Yu-jin,
is all grown-up now.
I'm doing all right, right?
[ I'll be fine, right? ]
My heart is going to explode.
Hyo-myoung, you were the best model
and now it's time for you to make
your debut as the best designer.
Be confident.
All right. At least I know
that you'll become the principal designer.
Promise to take care of me
if I don't get in.
Fine. You don't need to worry about that.
- You promised.
- Of course.
Ms. Yoo Hyo-myoung?
It's your turn now. Get going.
Thank you so much,
Sun-young.
- I'm going.
- Good luck!
That's me.
[ Principal Designer Contest ]
Bella, I'm heading out to meet
with Chairman Louis.
Did she forget something?
Yes, Madam Jang?
Sorry?
Yes, Bella?
We were just talking about you.
He's asking
who you'll collaborate with next.
Where are you?
- I'm on a plane.
[ - A plane? ]
Something urgent came up in Korea.
What are you talking about? Bella?
It's a long story. I'll tell you...
I'll tell you about it all when I land.
[ Ms. Yoo Yu-jin, right?
I'm Lawyer Lee Kyung-hoon. ]
[ I'm contacting you
regarding the Yoo family graves ]
[ at the hill in Seoha Village. ]
[ I'm contacting you
as the new landlord is ]
[ moving your mother's grave ]
[ if we don't hear from you in three days. ]
Mom...
This is an avant-garde piece
that reflects the fear of uncertainty
we face as the new millennium
is approaching.
Beautiful.
We will now announce
the next principal designer
of Donghan International.
The next principal designer is
Designer Yoo Hyo-myoung.
[ Principal Designer ]
There she is!
Please answer our question!
- Can you explain to us?
- Please stay away.
- Please answer our question.
- What do you have to say?
Mom!
[ - How old are you?
- You're very young. ]
[ - Is she really your mother?
- What's your mother's name? ]
[ - Can you answer our questions?
- Who are you? ]
Come in.
Hello.
The office seems brighter
with a young man in it.
Congratulations once again.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Junior Managing Director Jung will be
of great help.
- Introduce yourselves.
- I'm Jung Gwang-su.
Nice to meet you.
I look forward to working with you.
He looks like he lacks life experience.
He's Chairman Han's grandson.
He's no easy opponent.
You may never become the chairman
if you let yourself loose.
So, Managing Director Kang was
appointed now because...
The sly man is throwing a bait.
He's testing to see
who'll beat his grandson.
While the kid is busy getting
a hang of things,
we'll need to set our foot
with what we've prepared.
"What we've prepared"?
She should be arriving soon.
In my opinion...
Why don't you nullify
the existing contract
and sign a new contract
with a better offer?
Absolutely not.
I can't move anywhere.
Sorry?
I don't care how much money it'll take.
Compensate for their loss
and purchase the property again.
Let me ask something out of curiosity.
The land involved in this lawsuit is
nothing more than
a small hill in a small town
without much value.
Why do you insist
that you keep this land?
You can see my mother's hometown
from here.
I see.
Who purchased the hill?
It's someone from Donghan International.
What did you say?
[ Open the door. ]
Hyun-a!
Your beloved Designer Bella is in Korea.
Don't you want to meet her?
I have a meeting with her tomorrow.
Are you still going to stay in your room?
Bella?
[ Managing Director Lim Chul-yong ]
[ of Donghan International
purchased the land. ]
[ Then ]
[ - is it the company buying the land?
- Yes. ]
[ It'd be best if you two meet and talk. ]
[ He's a simple man ]
[ that you can talk things out with. ]
[ Sure, then. ]
How much did it cost you to buy the land?
I'll give you the money.
No,
I'll double it.
We purchased the land
to expand our manufacturing and storage.
It'd be malpractice if I make the call
based on my personal thoughts.
I'll triple the money.
Wouldn't that be a profitable deal?
That's not the only way to make a profit.
Yu-jin,
no,
Bella Yoo.
Who are you?
Don't be too surprised.
I'm the only one who knows.
For now, at least.
I'll be straightforward with you.
I know your contract with Louis is over.
Sign with Donghan.
Why should I?
Why not?
After all,
I know
all of Bella's secrets.
Yoo Hyo-myoung.
Your mother's death was unfortunate.
She was a beautiful model
and an excellent designer.
How did you find out?
A close friend of hers was
a department head here at Donghan.
Jang Sun-young,
Belle Ombre's current business partner.
You should be a detective instead.
A good manager needs
good information sources.
I'll take it as a compliment.
But...
I have no interest in working with you.
I think it was wise of you
to not show yourself in public.
People forget their past so easily,
but never forget famous people's scandals.
Wouldn't it be so tragic...
if people began talking
about your mother's death again?
I've made sure that nobody can come in.
This is our work. Take a look around.
What do you think?
I'll see you at court.
It'd be better for my mind to sue you
than to work with a company like this.
Lawyer Lee, I'm heading
to Nonyang right now.
Please get the people ready.
I've been wanting to meet you for so long.
You stopped in front of my work
back there.
I wanted to show you my other works
and hear what you think of them.
Who are you?
Don't you see the cars behind you?
I have to get going.
I have no time for such a talk.
Bella,
I'm actually Lim Hyun-a,
Lim Chul-yong's daughter.
What a ridiculous family you are.
I'm also an Antwerp alumna.
I've never met you in real life,
but I've been so intrigued by your work
that I've seen all of your shows.
What are you going to do now?
What?
You said you'll sell the place
and move to Seoul.
I don't know.
What about Seol-a?
We'll find her mother and send her back.
Right.
But don't you think it's weird?
The mom must have a reason
why she left her with you.
It's too mean to just send her away.
Do I look like a charity to you?
I've never seen her
and she's not even related to me.
So why should I keep her?
I don't know.
[ You'll be arriving ]
[ - at your destination soon. ]
- We're almost there.
So tell me,
what do you think
of my designs?
I was impressed at first,
but I can see it clearly
now that I've looked into them.
They're not original. They're plagiarized.
Plagiarized?
What are you talking about?
And you made things worse
to cover up the plagiarism.
You're mistaken.
I've put in so much work...
Mistaken?
When I was graduating from Antwerp,
I got a call from the school, saying that
my dress that was going to be
chosen as the best graduate work
had been stolen.
Was that you who stole the dress?
No.
No!
What are you doing?
Are you insane? Stop the car!
What do you think you're doing?
Seung-mo!
- Yes?
- I can't find Seol-a anywhere.
What happened to her?
Let's go out and look.
Gosh.
Kid!
Seol-a!
Gosh.
Kid!
Seol-a!
What are you doing out here?
It's dangerous.
A kid like you
shouldn't be out here alone.
You wanted me to go.
I was just happy to see my father.
But you don't like me and want me out.
What are you talking about?
Do you really want me to yell at you?
- Over there.
- What are you doing?
Over there.
What is it?
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
My goodness!
[ - Memory loss?
- When shocked in an accident,  ]
[ people sometimes temporarily lose
their memories. ]
- I've seen you somewhere.
- I'm starving.
[ Chef Moon, you're the best! ]
[ You're the best! ]
I'm not here to feed you all.
It's delicious.
[ Why can't I remember anything? ]
[ Seung-mo, what are you doing? ]
[ Were you peeking? ]
[ What are you talking about? ]
- You pervert!
- Pervert?
[ What an eccentric woman she is. ]