(Episode 31)
Hey, isn't that Yeo Ha Jin?
Where?
No way.
She's in the US right now.
Oh, you're right.
Do you think
she won't come back to Korea?
I doubt she'll come back.
I heard she's really popular there.
I heard she'll be filming
"Kill the Venus 3" too.
Really? She's so big.
Here's your coffee.
I ordered chocolate.
I canceled it for you.
Do you think I can drink chocolate
before I die?
You can probably have some
when you're about 60.
That's earlier than I thought.
The sunlight is great in Korea.
Is it different from the US?
Of course. It even smells different.
The lack of sugar is
making you way too sensitive.
How is it for you
to be back in Korea?
It's great.
Goodness, my babies.
You two were here already.
- You're here.
- Hey.
Wait, is coffee enough for you?
Aren't you hungry?
We're fine. We already had lunch.
I'm almost finished
getting your home ready.
You can come back home.
What about your niece?
She must've been flustered that
she suddenly had to empty the house.
Exactly.
We could've stayed at a hotel.
Goodness, you'll be
way more comfortable at home.
Thanks to you, she was
practically living there for free...
in return for
taking care of your house.
I gave her some money
to go travel for a few days.
She's completely excited right now.
I'm glad.
So the meeting with the director
will be held tomorrow, right?
He wanted to
book the meeting for today,
but I asked him to postpone it
because you have to...
take a rest today.
Do you absolutely love the scenario?
I do.
But I'll decide
after I meet the director.
Okay.
This is urgent for them, not us.
Slowly.
Let's take our time and think.
Ms. Park, do you have to keep adding
English to your vocabulary?
I have to keep trying to get better.
Ha Jin is now a star worldwide,
and I should be able to speak...
proper English
as the CEO of her agency.
Exactly.
You need to speak it properly.
It was just a joke.
"Joke", no. Joke.
Joke.
Exactly.
(Ju Ri and Woo Hyun's Happy Place)
Nothing has changed.
They loved the decoration,
so they left it as it is.
The second floor is
almost the same too.
You can clear your mind
and get a good rest today.
I will.
We have to go back to the office
right away. Is that okay?
It's all right. I'll get some rest.
We'd rather stay with you,
but we have mountains of work
after staying away for so long.
We're very busy.
Don't get too strained.
You need to look after your health.
Yes, I'll do that.
- Get a good rest, then.
- Goodbye.
I'll get something delicious
on my way home.
Do you want anything?
No. Go work,
eat dinner, and go on a date too.
You haven't called Mr. Jo yet,
have you?
No.
He'll be thrilled to see you.
I want to be alone,
so you need to go.
Okay.
Text me if you want anything.
Don't go out alone.
Okay.
(Dear my Ha Kyung.
My dear Ha Kyung! How was your day?)
I miss my Ha Kyung.
I wonder what she's doing right now.
Hello?
Hey, Ha Kyung!
Why isn't this
an international call?
What do you think?
I'm in Korea right now.
Really?
Where are you? I'll be there.
Are you at home?
I'll be there in 10 minutes.
Ha Kyung...
- Bye-bye.
Jo Il Kwon!
What was that just now?
What?
What's wrong?
Don't you know?
Who was that guy just now?
Who is he that you gave him a hug?
He's someone from the agency
in the US, and he gave me a ride.
And that wasn't even a hug.
I was just saying goodbye.
That's not just saying goodbye.
If you said goodbye to him again,
things will get even more heated up.
Everyone does that in the US.
Will you keep getting angry
over nothing?
Are you saying you hugged
any old guy you met over there?
What?
Why are you so uptight today?
What about you?
You must feel very free...
after staying in the US for a while.
You seem very open.
We finally met after a long time.
Will you keep making me tired?
"Tired"?
If you're tired,
go home and get some rest.
Why did you come all the way here?
Fine! I should do that!
What?
I'm leaving!
Fine! Goodbye, then.
Okay!
How could she really leave?
Ha Kyung, are you still angry?
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
I like you too much,
so that's why
I must've been jealous.
Can we meet and talk it out?
I miss you, Ha Kyung.
(Jo Il Kwon)
You need to feel more desperate.
Goodness, after you became
a prominent actress overseas,
everyone is dying to see you.
- Goodness, hello.
- Hello.
It's so nice to see you, Ha Jin.
Hello.
I finally get to meet you.
Do you know
how long we waited to see you?
The director is in the meeting room.
You two can have
a great conversation.
Okay.
- I'll be back.
- Go ahead.
I heard her scenes...
in "Kill the Venus 2"
increased by double.
It's not exactly double, per se.
Actually, Ha Jin only signed
the contract for the first movie,
but after the movie premiered,
the director went out of his way to
persuade her to do the second one.
Ha Jin will end up
becoming a huge world star.
- That's her class right now, right?
- Yes.
She once went to
a famous brunch place,
and Justin Bieber...
Wait, that Justin Bieber?
Yes, he recognized her and said hi.
Oh, my.
I think they're still in touch.
He only said hi,
thinking we were his fans
since we were staring at him.
Do you like him?
Of course.
I'm sorry about last time.
You came all the way
to the filming site...
but couldn't see me.
It seems like my trip
to the States paid off.
Aren't you back in Korea
because you felt bad?
You're right.
Did you read the revised scenario?
Yes. I read it.
I had more lines than before,
but the male lead
seemed less interesting.
I liked your original one better.
I see.
Speaking of, I'd like to ask you
a question.
What is it?
You do know that
I was involved in a scandal...
before leaving for
the States, right?
They could bring it up again.
Will you be okay with that?
Oh, that?
If you think you may back out,
please let me know right now.
I've gone through such incidents
quite often.
It's best not to waste
each other's time.
Do you remember...
when I told you that I had written
this scenario with you in mind?
That was long before...
you had left for the States.
Even after what happened,
I never thought twice...
about casting you.
What do you say?
Was that a good enough answer?
Yes, it was.
I'm exhausted.
Why am I so tired?
That's because
you've been bluffing all day.
Your English hasn't improved,
but your bluffing has.
I wasn't bluffing.
I just slightly sugarcoated
the facts.
You should've heard her.
She was bluffing so much
in front of the CEO.
Really?
How was the talk with the director?
It went great.
He's so nice, and the scenario
is exactly what I expected.
It's soft but has a decisive topic.
Did you tell him
you'd think about it?
Yes, he said that was fine.
So what do you want to do?
I'm not sure yet.
I'm greatly interested in the movie,
but there are many things
to consider.
What do you think?
To be honest, it hasn't been
that long...
since you've succeeded
in the States.
Perhaps, it's too early
to come back.
If you're not planning to work
in Korea again, then it's fine.
But if not,
I think this is your opportunity.
We'll support you no matter what,
so take your time.
She's right.
You've been working relentlessly.
You should take some good rest
and think about it.
Okay. I'll do that.
Thanks.
I asked Anchor Lee to add
more comments...
since we had too much free time.
He's not here yet, is he?
No, I think he's getting ready.
Ask him how long it'll take.
Yes, sir.
Hold on.
Tell him that I'm not rushing him.
Do explain that
I'm just simply anxious.
Okay.
Did you just smirk?
It seems like you're walking
on eggshells around him.
Of course, I should.
He's the face of our news channel.
Is the team manager
asking for the revised manuscript?
He wanted you to know
that he's not rushing you.
Here. Can you print me a copy
as well?
Okay.
Hi.
Yes, this is it.
I feel so much at peace.
Are you going to come here...
every time I'm preparing
for the news?
I want to enjoy this happiness
for the next month.
Is everything fine?
Do you want a softer chair?
Do you want anything to drink?
How about that honey drink?
I'm fine, so you may leave.
All right, I got it.
You're not worried
about the interview, are you?
This is your first interview
after returning.
I'm not sure. You've invited
a very special guest.
I think I saw him in the green room.
You should visit him.
That's okay.
He'll feel uncomfortable.
It's better that we don't meet.
Hasn't it been ages
since you've last met?
You're right.
It's been two years.
3, 2, 1.
Anchor!
Many people have been interested
and supportive of him...
for what he's been doing abroad.
He's with us today as a guest.
It's nice to meet you,
Doctor Yoo Tae Eun.
Hello.
I'm Doctor Yoo Tae Eun,
a psychiatrist.
You've been counseling those
who have received trauma...
due to violence in countries...
that are at war for free.
How long has it been
since you were last in Korea?
Due to the environment I was in,
time flew by so quickly.
But when I checked my passport
this time,
I realized that
it had been two years.
That's not a short amount of time.
What do you think?
Have things changed around here?
At first, I thought so.
But after some time,
I could spot the things
that hadn't changed.
For example, you're still
the news anchor.
You're right.
I heard you came back
for a reason.
You're holding an exhibition?
Yes, I'm displaying the drawings
made by the children...
I had counseled
during drawing therapy.
The profit will be used
to educate children...
in countries that are at war.
Since he's such a righteous doctor,
Jeong Hoon won't criticize him.
So what if he does?
No matter what he does,
you love him so much.
Most of them
are victims of violence.
- Is it that obvious?
- Extremely.
Because of that,
they become traumatized.
Why are you
in such a hurry to leave?
I'm meeting a reporter
early tomorrow morning...
regarding the exhibition.
It's too late for you to treat me
to something nice anyway.
You can treat me next time.
You seem to be busier here.
Then you shouldn't have invited me
as a guest.
Just now, I received two calls.
I think I'm born to appear on TV.
Aren't charity events supposed
to make you humbler?
You've changed.
It's only natural.
It's been two years.
It's actually strange
that you haven't.
Really?
Goodness.
Are you still waiting for her?
Ha Jin.
Why don't you just call her first?
Actually, I saw her yesterday.
You did? Where?
It was a coincidence.
I saw her while driving.
Then you should've stopped her.
Should I have?
If it's fate, then we'll meet again.
Gosh, you're so pitiful.
I'll clear my schedule
for this weekend, so call me.
I'll treat you to a meal.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- I'll call you.
- Sure.
Many people have been interested
and supportive of him...
for what he's been doing abroad.
He's with us today as a guest.
- What are you doing?
- It's nice to meet you...
- Hey.
- Hello.
I'm so sleepy. I'm going to bed.
You were awake until I came in.
I'm going to bed now.
What's that sound? What is it?
Let me see.
Move.
- Move.
- It's nothing.
Move!
You were watching the news.
Yes. Doctor Yoo was on the news.
Is that so?
But that's Anchor Lee.
You're right.
I'm not sleepy.
You're not either, right?
Judging by what you're doing,
I think I'm right.
You are. That's why
I was watching Doctor Yoo.
I'm going out for a bit. Wait here.
Where are you going?
Answer me.
Just keep watching.
Let's talk about charity.
You're counseling those
in countries that are at war.
This is something new.
What is all this?
Let's have a drink.
We're having wine?
- Tada.
- It's makgeolli.
This is a cure for insomnia.
Gosh, it's been ages.
There's makgeolli, kimchi pancakes,
and cartilage.
Eat as much as you want.
What's gotten into you?
You're free tomorrow.
You'll be running.
I should've known better.
Fine, then.
- Cheers!
This is so good.
It hits the spot.
It's the taste of Korea.
It's so good!
Staying with you at home
feels surreal.
Why is that surreal?
When we were in the States,
my time in Korea seemed
like a dream,
but now that I'm in Korea, my time
in the States feels like a dream.
It's been a long time
I've been away,
but it feels like I'm circling
around the same spot.
Is it because of Anchor Lee?
Why you can't decide on this movie
and are still thinking about it?
It's not just about him.
I'm just scared.
And I'm not sure if it's okay
for me to come back to Korea.
Forget about other reasons.
If you still like him
after all this time has passed,
you should just get back with him.
Don't regret it.
- Yes, Ha Kyung.
- Where are you?
I came out to shop.
To shop?
Jamie is hooked on Korean
historical drama these days,
so Jamie told me to bring back
some traditional fans.
Then, you should have asked me
to go with you.
What if people recognize you
when you're all by yourself?
But no one knows
that I'm in Korea.
And if I cover up my face,
I'll look more suspicious.
But still.
You should have put on a hat.
Gosh, okay.
If something happens,
call me right away. I'll be there.
Don't worry.
I'll call you on my way home.
Okay.
My gosh, where can I get the fans?
I'm hungry.
What should we eat?
Hold on. Wait.
Aren't you Ms. Yeo Ha Jin?
No.
Do I look like her?
I get that quite often.
Yes. You totally look like her.
Right?
You're really not her?
She's in the States right now.
Right.
But thank you for telling me
that I look like a pretty actress.
She's an awesome actress.
- I see. Right.
- Yes.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Bye.
- She looks nothing like Ha Jin.
- Isn't that her?
Come here. Let's go.
Ha Jin.
How are you here?
Well,
I needed to buy something.
Have you been well?
Yes. I have been well.
What about you, Anchor Lee?
Did you come back to Korea for good?
No.
I need to go back to the States.
I see.
Isn't that Yeo Ha Jin?
- She is. Let's take a photo.
- I can't believe it.
I'll get going.
The number you have dialed
has been suspended...
for the time being as requested.
The number you have dialed
has been suspended...
I'm sorry.
I was in a hurry.
It's all right.
I can call my insurance company.
- Are you hurt?
- No, I am okay.
To cover all four corners, why don't
we pull over and discuss this?
I have a customer inside.
I might have to let
my customer go first.
- Okay, let's do that.
- Okay.
Are you okay?
Anchor Lee.
We meet again.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay.
What about you?
I'm okay too.
Out of all taxis,
I was in an accident
with a taxi you were in.
Right.
So that's our destiny.
We're destined to fall in love.
They run into each other three times
on the same day in the same place,
then they miss each other by a hair.
Then they get into
a ridiculous accident on a street.
Don't you think there are
way too many coincidences?
That's why they're meant to be.
They're destined to meet each other
and fall in love.
The way we met tells us
we're destined to be together.
Isn't that right?
Where were you going?
Let me drop you off.
I think it will be harder
for you to run away now.
We got here too fast.
I took my time on purpose
to get to your place.
Thank you for the ride.
I didn't know you were staying here.
Someone else was living here,
so I thought you sold the place.
Ms. Park's niece and her husband
have been staying here.
But they let me have the place
for the time being.
I see.
You're sure
that you're not hurt, right?
If you're hurt, please call me.
I still have the same number.
I will.
I'll go in now. Bye.
Wait.
I wanted to tell you something,
but I couldn't.
You asked...
if I have been well.
I tried my best,
but I couldn't do that.
I missed you
and wanted to see you too much.
On the last day I saw you,
even if you turn me down many times,
I shouldn't have broken up with you.
I should've begged you and said
we have to overcome this together...
to be happy.
I regretted everything
from the moment you left.
I regretted it too.
I'm so sorry that I left you here...
all alone.
(Final Episode)
I saw it! I saw it!
I saw everything!
See what?
I saw you and Anchor Lee
in each other's arms!
What's going on?
Are you two an item again?
- Yes.
- I'm so glad.
Don't ever break up with him again.
You've done well,
so you can have this.
I'm never going to
break up with him.
You need to step it up, though.
Try not to break up with him.
Your relationship might end first.
I have something to say.
I need to see you after work.
I'll be at your office.
This was such a great opportunity
to talk to you face to face,
not through a video call,
but we lost days...
because of my stupidity.
It's okay. I can see why
you misunderstood that.
But I'm so glad
I can talk to you like this.
Let's grab a seat.
Things were really tough for me
while I was in the US.
I wanted to see you, but I couldn't,
and it was difficult to reach you
with the time difference.
Really?
We had been apart for too long,
so the anxiety
began to make me feel troubled.
To be honest,
you're popular at the TV station.
You don't have to worry about
something like that.
You're the only one for me.
I understand why you got angry too.
You must feel nervous as well.
You're right about that.
I gave this a thought.
I don't know
when I'll be back from the US,
and you don't seem to get chosen
as a correspondent.
Wait, what are you talking about?
You aren't asking me
to break up with you, are you?
We can't keep dating like this.
Ha Kyung.
Here.
(Let's live together.)
Only death awaits you
if you turn me down.
Of course, I'll say yes.
Thank you.
Let's live together forever.
I'll kill you
if your feelings change.
Should we move in together
starting today?
I can't do that today.
Why not? Then tomorrow?
- No.
- Why not? Then when?
No idea.
So when?
Ji Won.
Tae Eun.
Why are you out here?
My mom kept telling me
to go out and check.
Goodness, she gets worried
way too easily.
Hey, you're here.
Was there a lot of traffic?
No, I left early,
so it was all right.
I didn't think
Father would be here too.
I thought you two
wouldn't want to meet...
unless I set you up like this.
Sit down.
Honey, what are you doing?
Tae Eun is here. Say hi to him.
It's not like
he did anything special.
Take a seat.
Mother, take a seat.
Ji Won, you too.
Okay.
Mother, how are you doing?
I heard you pulled your back
trying to carry something heavy.
I've gotten much better
after I went to the hospital.
I'm fine now.
But still, be careful.
Don't carry anything too heavy.
Make Ji Won do it.
I help her out a lot.
All right.
But you look much better now
than the last time...
you sent me a picture.
- Really?
- Yes.
I think I gained a bit of weight...
thanks to the side dishes
you sent me.
Her side dishes aren't that good.
That's an overstatement.
No way, it was really good.
Fine, I guess that can happen...
if you live abroad for too long.
Goodness, you.
Ouch.
Have you been well, Father?
Mother told me about you
from time to time.
Let's order first.
It seemed like
they've been waiting for us.
Right, okay.
- Okay, let's do that.
- Let's see.
- What should we eat?
- The most expensive dish.
- This looks good.
- You can choose something.
- That looks good too.
- This one and...
Father.
You could've called me in instead of
coming out if you're done.
Let's go back in.
Do you still blame me?
I heard you quit
your teaching job...
and only stayed in your study
after that happened.
Mother had been
really worried about you.
I feel sorry in a certain aspect,
but I don't regret it.
I did it for your sake too.
Let's not talk about that.
It's all in the past anyway.
So are you doing this
to protest against me?
- Pardon?
- Why don't you...
come home?
Why do you keep traveling around?
Is it because of me?
It's not like that.
I really enjoy doing this.
And it's rewarding to be there...
to help the people that are in need.
I really feel alive.
Goodness, I worked hard
to turn you into a doctor,
but you feel rewarded
by doing something that petty?
I feel much happier now
than when I ran my clinic.
But of course,
I'm sure you won't like it.
You'll have to live
doing what you're destined to do.
Anyway, don't go anywhere
that's too dangerous.
Let's go inside.
Father.
You should come and see
the exhibition with Mother.
I'll keep some tickets for you.
Maybe.
("News Live": Jo Il Kwon)
Jeong Hoon, don't you think
you're way too inconsiderate?
Why are you saying that to me
as soon as I walk in?
I heard you're dating Ha Jin again.
Do I have to report
something like that to you?
Ha Kyung will find out
everything you've been doing.
Come on.
You don't have to go that far.
I'll give you my full support...
for your relationship
to come to fruition.
I'll manage my own relationship.
Just focus on Ha Kyung.
Go work.
You better brace yourself.
A long-distance relationship
isn't as easy as you think.
You should go on as many dates
as possible before she leaves.
Isn't she leaving next Monday?
I'm sorry. I had to finish
watching the news.
That's okay.
Is there anything you'd like to do?
Or anywhere you'd like to go?
I do, but it's too late today.
Really?
I shouldn't have said yes
to returning to the news.
I have no time to waste
if we're going to make up...
for all the lost dates.
When will you be coming back?
I think it'll take a month.
There are several things
I need to take care of.
That's fine. I even waited for you
for two years.
Promise me we'll go on many dates
before you leave.
I do. Let's go.
What are you thinking about?
"People will start talking again."
"Some people
may still criticize us."
Things like these.
They haven't forgotten about it.
I don't think they ever will.
Are you afraid?
No.
What I feared the most...
was not being able
to hold your hand anymore.
The same goes for me.
That's why I have nothing to fear.
As long as you're okay.
I've always been okay.
As long as you were.
Then we're good.
I finally know my top priority.
Is that me?
It's us.
- Us?
- Yes.
Aren't you exhausted?
Not one bit.
I'm going to listen to your voice
a bit more before going to bed.
Oh, right. I have a dilemma.
What is it?
I have to make
an important decision.
I need to choose...
between a Korean movie
and "Kill the Venus 3".
They're both great opportunities,
so I'm in a big dilemma.
Which one do you think
I should take?
I'm not sure.
If I were to be selfish,
I'd like you to stay here...
instead of going back.
But that's wrong.
If that's what you want,
then I'll do that.
You see, I don't know much
about movies.
Give me some time,
and I'll think about it.
Sure.
(Yang Jin Woo)
("Director Yang Knows How to Make
Blockbuster, Cinematic Movies")
Of all the things you've made,
this coffee takes the cake.
I'm going to crave this every day.
Just let me know.
I'll buy it for you anytime.
I have a lot of money.
You picked the right one.
Oh, right.
Have you thought about it?
I'm terribly torn between the two.
I've looked into it.
Director Yang's movies...
were generally liked
by the audience.
Many of them complimented
his characters.
They especially complimented...
on how charming
the female leads are.
As for "Kill the Venus",
it's true that it's a blockbuster.
It'll help you become
more globally famous.
Hold on.
You actually looked into all this?
Yes, during my spare time.
You said it was important.
I had to be thorough.
I didn't want to think about it.
I asked you, hoping that...
you'd tell me to just stay here.
I feel bad that you put
so much effort into this.
Of course, I'd want that.
But you like your job.
You feel happy when acting.
So don't put me first.
Think about what's best for you.
Have I told you before...
that I extremely love you?
I love you even more.
I don't want to.
Why not? You look too...
- You look too boring.
- It's suffocating.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Whatever.
Hold on. You really don't listen.
Come here.
Stand there.
Why are you going this far?
Let me dress like how I always do.
Still, this is your first day...
as the team manager
for the 9 p.m. news.
You should look like one.
Should we eat something tasty
after work?
This isn't a big deal.
I want beef.
All right.
You're now
a part of the 9 p.m. news.
Buying beef is nothing.
- But we're going dutch.
- No, thanks.
Come on, now.
By the way, you really look nice.
Really? Do I look okay?
Yes. You look so handsome.
Hey, are you crazy? Hurry up.
You're late for the meeting.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you sure you're free right now?
I am. I already did all the work
in advance...
so I could be with you.
It's been a long time
since I've come here.
Don't we have so many memories
of this place?
Are you free for lunch tomorrow?
Yes.
Why? Are we going somewhere nice?
It's not that.
There's someone who really wants
to meet you.
Who is it?
What? Look who's here.
Ha Jin, it's been a long time.
Hello.
Have you heard? I'm the team manager
of the 9 p.m. news.
Really? Congratulations.
That's a promotion, right?
Yes, it is.
You and I have climbed up the ladder
in the past couple of years.
You're a world-class star,
and I'm the team manager
of the main news.
Jeong Hoon's the only one
who's still the same.
You're right.
By the way, would you be interested
in doing an interview?
For "News Live"?
No, for the 9 p.m. news.
"News Live" is no longer
what it used to be.
You can't be personal
when it comes to work, you know?
You don't have to say yes
to all of his requests.
Choose what's best for you.
I will.
All right, then.
I hope to be hearing from you soon.
If you're done speaking,
we'll go now.
We're running out of time.
Okay, okay.
- Goodbye.
They're making me jealous.
Lucky them.
Wait. How do I look?
You look pretty.
I'm more nervous right now
than when I auditioned for a movie.
Don't be. I'm sure he'll like you.
Let's go.
You should stop staring
and start eating.
She may have an upset stomach
thanks to you.
All right.
Enjoy the meal.
You too.
Eat up.
Thank you.
Thank you for dating my son.
You two look happy.
It makes me happy as well.
This one looks really nice.
It looks artistic.
I'm going to hang this in my car
when I go back to the States.
Didn't you say you'd do the same...
with the photo you took
while having lunch yesterday?
Then I'll hang this in my bedroom.
That's what you said
about the one we took...
three days ago at the observatory.
You should stop using
your excellent memory...
for teasing me.
You look cute when I tease you.
I plan to use my memory often.
Just when you tease me?
Thank you.
For what?
For suggesting
to visit my mother's grave first.
I asked you
because I wanted to pay her a visit.
And it didn't have anything
to do with you.
She and I got along really well.
I think she thought the same...
on the day when you met her.
I've never seen her smile like that.
I'm thinking about visiting her
whenever I come back to Korea.
I can say hello to her
and go for a drive with you.
That will be nice.
Sounds good to me too.
Then, let's take one more photo.
In 1, 2, 3.
Yes, Ha Kyung.
I'm in front of my house.
There are a lot of reporters.
Well, we saw this coming though.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Are you ready?
I just needed to rely on you
from the beginning.
Aren't I really reliable?
Yes, I'm not scared at all...
now that I have you by my side.
I feel the same way.
Shall we go in?
Yes.
- There's Yeo Ha Jin.
- It's Lee Jeong Hoon.
Did you come back to Korea
because of Anchor Lee Jeong Hoon?
- Why did you suddenly come back?
- What's your plan?
- Why did you come back to Korea?
- Do you plan to get married?
- What's your plan?
- Please answer our question.
- Did you get back together?
- Are you guys dating again?
- Do you love him?
- Anything for your fans?
- Are you going to marry him?
- Anything for the press?
- What's your plan?
- What does this mean?
My gosh, who is it?
It's too early in the morning.
That's for me!
That's for me! Mine! Don't touch it.
Don't touch it! It's mine!
(Hana Camping Mall)
What's all this?
Are those clothes for Anchor Lee?
No, camping gear.
You can't stay out all night.
Camping?
Yes, I really wanted to go camping,
but I've never gone camping before.
Have you ever gone camping before?
No, me neither.
That's great.
I bought everything we might need.
Already?
You're going camping with me
this weekend, okay?
Here you go, Anchor Lee.
Okay. Is this everything we need?
We loaded everything.
And this is my finishing touch.
Do I look good?
Perfect.
- Let's get going.
- Let's go.
No way. Is it raining right now?
I do see some raindrops drizzling.
And now, it's pouring.
Can we still go camping in the rain?
Yes. We can.
How much longer?
I'm hungry. Do you need some help?
No, it's going well.
Go get some rest.
You're sure it's going well, right?
I'm following the recipe,
but I can't guarantee
that it'll be tasty.
All right. I just need
to put beer in it and cook it.
What? Gosh.
What is it?
I was supposed to marinate
the meat for three years.
It's okay.
I don't mind eating bland food.
Okay.
Then, I just need to cook it now.
All right. I'm supposed
to cook this on a charcoal fire.
I see. A charcoal fire.
"When you don't have
a charcoal fire,"
"cook it on the stove for..." What?
- What is it now?
- It takes four hours to cook this.
What should we do?
You must be starving.
Do you want to cook ramyeon instead?
Are you sure that will do?
I love ramyeon.
Ta-da.
- Is it that good?
- It's so good!
Eat a lot.
No, I shouldn't.
I need to save some space for beer.
Let's watch a movie
while drinking beer.
When will you go home?
I can't go home tonight.
Why not?
I'm eating ramyeon.
Didn't you watch that movie?
When you eat ramyeon
at a man's place, you can't go home.
I see. Really?
- Yes.
- I see.
Eat up.
We were best friends.
Here.
- Hey.
- This is nice.
Hey, are they...
Doesn't this feel like
we're camping?
You're going to drink one too?
I'm good at drinking beer now.
Cheers.
Hey, listen. He's so handsome.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I've dreamed of drinking beer
with you for so long.
I also dreamed of drinking
beer with you too.
Then, we can drink beer
together often from now on.
This is not good.
What do you mean?
I keep getting ambitious.
In what ways?
I want to make you
the happiest woman on earth.
My gosh, this is not good either.
Why?
Because I want to make you
happier than that.
It's done.
Where are you?
I'm on my way now.
I'm so nervous.
Did you take the calming pill?
I took it 30 minutes ago.
But why am I so nervous?
I'm more nervous than...
when I had to attend
promotional interviews in the US.
Don't worry.
I'm sure you'll do a great job.
But I'll only be able to calm down
once I see your face.
I'll try to get there
as soon as possible.
Okay.
I'll try to hang in there
until you arrive.
Get here safely.
Okay. I'll see you there.
I still remember too many memories.
I'm pretty sure these memories
will not fade away...
for the rest of my life.
They will remain inside me
like tree rings.
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Isn't this more nervous
than the actual filming?
I think so.
Now, we will receive questions
from the reporters.
You decided to come back
with a Korean movie.
After you've been active
in Hollywood,
it's been a while since you've been
active in the Korean movie industry.
How does it feel?
Well,
first of all, it was really great
to say my lines...
in Korean, not English.
I thought I was used to doing that,
but it felt new.
Ms. Yeo, you came back to Korea
after two years,
so it has been a while
since you met with your Korean fans.
Please share a few words for them.
("Find Me in Your Memory")
I missed you so much,
and I wanted to see you.
I could adapt quickly
in an unfamiliar environment...
thanks to the support my fans showed
even while I was overseas.
I really want to thank you.
We're very glad to
have you back in Korea,
but you must have been torn.
Why did you decide to film
"Find Me in Your Memory"...
instead of "Kill the Venus 3",
which is guaranteed to be a hit.
Actually, I begged her to join me
because I desperately wanted to...
make this film with her.
Of course, it's because I trusted
the scenario and the director.
And the story was perfect too.
That's my official statement,
but someone made an analysis...
and said doing this film will be
a huge plus to my future career.
Really?
I should show
my deepest gratitude to that person.
Thank you.
Ms. Yeo, why did you decide...
to return to Korea
after your long hiatus?
Is there any other reason
other than the film itself?
Is it because of
Anchor Lee Jeong Hoon?
No.
It was for me.
I decided...
to become a person
who's remembered daily and forever.
I wanted to remember and love...
in this place.
I'm Lee Jeong Hoon of HBN.
There's a question
I'd like to ask you.
Now I know how to etch
those memories in my heart...
and move forward.
I know how those memories can become
good memories, not wounds.
I just need to
live this moment beautifully.
(We thank Park Jin Woo
for his guest appearance.)
(We support our viewers' tomorrow
along with Jeong Hoon and Ha Jin.)
(Thank you for watching
Find Me in Your Memory.)