(Episode 5)
Jung Seo Yeon?
Yes. Jung Seo Yeon.
Do you know her?
No, I've never heard that name before.
Who is that?
(Patient Chart: Yeo Ha Jin)
Why are you asking me?
You need to explain to help me take a guess.
Is she famous? Is she an actress?
I may have met her,
but I could have forgotten.
I don't have a great memory.
You said you got injured and stopped doing ballet, right?
When exactly was that?
My first year in college.
I got into a motorcycle accident...
and hurt my ankle badly.
Why do you suddenly ask me this?
What's with you?
(Ha Kyung)
Take that call.
Call your sister here and go.
What do you think you're doing?
No.
I can't leave like this. I won't.
You need to tell me...
why you're doing this and who Jung Seo Yeon is.
I'll go once you tell me.
I can't tell you.
So you need to go.
Call your sister,
take a taxi, or walk.
You need to go.
Then I'll drop you off.
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Why wouldn't she explain anything and just tell me to come?
I think we're here. Could you stop?
Sure.
Please wait a minute.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
You're early.
Where are we?
It's his house.
"His house"?
What did you two do in there?
Nothing.
I just dropped him off.
You did what?
Can't a grown man go home alone?
It's late. Let's talk at home.
What are we doing outside so late at night?
Please go back.
Why did she leave her car here?
So what? Am I supposed to get it back?
Of course, I should. Right.
Let's go.
There wasn't a traffic jam, right? Do you want some coffee?
Forget about coffee. Let's straighten things out.
What did you do with Anchor Lee?
I already told you everything yesterday.
I want to check.
So you two decided to act as if you're dating.
No, wait. You officially asked him out,
but he said no?
You heard me right the first time.
I'm so speechless.
Why would he dump you then ask to be dropped off at home?
I offered to do so. It's nothing.
Why are you getting all worked up?
I know you're the exhausting type...
and have been dumped often.
But no one has ever rejected you from the beginning.
I was dumped only once for being too exhausting.
No, there were numerous times. They just didn't tell you.
Like who? Dong Joon? Min Seok?
Forget it. What's the point?
There's no way.
Forget what I said.
I'm getting hungry from getting all worked up.
Are you going to have ramyeon?
Yes. You can't, right?
No, I'm on a diet. Lucky you.
Tell me right now if you're going to have some.
If not, I'm going to cook just enough for myself.
No, I won't eat.
Right, do you know who Jung Seo Yeon is?
Are you okay?
I'm so famished that I have no energy.
What was the name again?
Jung Seo Yeon.
Do you know her? I don't.
Me neither.
But why all of a sudden?
Jeong Hoon asked yesterday whether I knew her or not.
He did? Why?
I don't know. He didn't say why.
I can't take this. I'll have half of the ramyeon.
I can exercise afterward, right?
Yes.
Don't cook it for too long.
"Jung Seo Yeon"?
(Ha Na and Yeong's Exchange Diary)
(Ha Na's)
(Yeong's)
Get ready. And one.
And 2, and 3.
Plie, up.
And passe.
Two.
Three.
Hold on. You guys got it wrong.
You've made the same mistake again.
You have something in your teeth.
Ha jin, Seo Yeon. What did I tell you?
You shouldn't eat anything before your performance.
- Look at that. - This won't do.
- Come on out. - It's nothing.
- Why did you laugh? - What?
You laughed first.
- Bend your knees. - It's all because you laughed.
I laughed because you did.
I'm so hungry.
Let's go have tteokbokki.
"Tteokbokki"?
Right now?
Yes, let's sneak out. My arms are getting sore.
Sure. I got allowance today, so it's my treat.
Let's go.
And 2, and 3.
Up and...
You two.
- Oh, no. - Hurry!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
We need to change our shoes.
- Yeo Ha Jin! Jung Seo Yeon! - Let's go!
Stop right there!
Let's go!
That one! We need to get on that!
Stop!
Hello. Two people.
Oh, yes. We did it.
Gosh.
I'm out of breath.
What should we do?
I thought you had everything planned out.
We can start now.
Then do you want to bike along the Han River?
- Let's have cup noodles too. - I want a sausage as well.
Okay. I'm starving.
Isn't the weather so nice?
I know.
- Sausages are the best. - They are!
It's so hot.
- Why am I still hungry? - It's delicious.
- It really is. - What should we tell them tomorrow?
Worry about that tomorrow. Let's go to karaoke. Okay?
Okay.
What should we have there?
- Tteokbokki. - And?
And the sweet and sour chicken we talked about before.
I love that.
It's really good, right?
(Dear Ha Na, this is the last page of our diary.)
Ha Kyung, come on out. The ramyeon is getting too soggy.
I'm going to finish it.
Stop right there. I'm coming.
- Look this way! - Ha Jin!
I love you!
Ha Jin, so many of your fans are here.
Really?
We'll begin now.
I'm Kim Ea Na, and this is "Nighttime Letters".
Ever since its release, the movie has received a lot of love.
I'm here with Yeo Ha Jin,
the female lead of "My First Love".
Could you describe the movie...
in one phrase?
I could say that it's a sadistic movie.
"Sadistic"?
Is it the same definition...
that I'm aware of as in to abuse someone?
Yes, that's correct.
This movie can shake things up emotionally,
so if you watch the movie, it might be painful.
I see. So you chose that description in a positive way.
Yes. Here's a story from the movie.
Love can shake things up for people, you know.
So it gets painful.
And the most painful moment is...
when your happiest moments...
become the saddest memories.
So on some days, you want to forget about them.
But on some days, you never want to forget.
So in the movie, Ae Young is torn...
because once she forgets about them,
it means she'd lost her brightest moments.
So in the end, she...
Go on.
Please watch the movie to find out what happens.
My gosh, that was great timing to stop.
You're a pro.
All right. Let me stop here for a moment then.
Let's listen to a song.
Ha Jin, you chose this song yourself.
Yes, it's one of my favorite songs.
The lyrics are beautiful.
Great.
Let's listen to "Two People" by Sung Si Kyung.
You're early.
Look at this. You ordered my coffee too.
I like you very much these days.
You're doing very well.
My favorite song is playing.
I guess the owner of the cafe also likes this song.
This cafe plays this song often.
Right. Did I tell you?
Ha Na was the one who introduced this song to me.
She told me the lyrics were beautiful.
For some time, she recited the lyrics as if they were a poem.
I am still learning a lot
And I'm still lacking in many ways
But I will always stay by your side
Even if we get lost in the dark
The two of us
Will become each other's light
Ha Na is a terrible singer.
She keeps saying she's not,
but she is.
Come to think of it,
I've done a lot of things for the first time with Ha Na.
The two of us went to karaoke for the first time.
And we drank alcohol for the first time together.
We drank whiskey together, swam together,
and went on a blind date together.
You have a long way to go if you want to catch up...
with our friendship.
Work harder.
Sure.
I hope we get to see her together next year.
I think I've met...
your friend, Ha Na.
It took me a while to recognize her because her name changed.
I'm sorry. I'm late.
No, it's all right.
I apologize for suddenly asking you to meet me.
It really has been a long time.
I don't think we've met after Seo Yeon's funeral.
Yes, you're right.
By the way, what is this about?
I had a question...
about her friend, Ha Na.
Seo Yeon and Ha Jin were really close.
You'd never met her before?
No,
I had never met her.
So you're right. Ha Jin is Ha Na.
You know, when you're young,
you change your friend's name for a nickname.
Seo Yeon was Yeong.
And Ha Jin was Ha Na.
That's how they used to call each other.
You're not nervous at all.
You're good with words too.
Gosh, no. You made me feel very comfortable here.
- Excuse me. - Okay.
What?
Where did he go?
My gosh, a radio show is more exhausting than I thought.
What are you thinking?
I need to go upstairs for a second.
Go where? To the newsroom?
Yes. I definitely saw Jeong Hoon earlier.
Ha Jin, no one likes it when you barge into their offices...
without an appointment.
This is why people say they get sick of you.
No, that can't be true.
I'm so sick of you.
Wait. Hello.
Okay. Thank you.
What? This is Reporter Jo Il Kwon.
- Hello. It's been a while. - Hi.
Don't be like that. It's Reporter Jo.
I see. I thought he was your fan or something.
But which program do you work for?
"News Live".
You and I talked on the phone. And before the interview,
I even said hello to you. Do you not remember me?
I'm sorry. I'm usually good at remembering people's faces.
- But you... - What about me?
That's a common face you have.
I do? No way.
A lot of people tell me I have unique looks.
I see. Well, I see.
Is Jeong Hoon in the office?
No, he stepped out.
I see. Really?
- Doctor. - Yes?
You have a visitor.
A visitor?
I'm here.
You should have just come in.
I must go through the proper channels.
You're the director of the biggest psychiatric clinic in this area.
Do you want something to drink?
We're fine. You should all go home.
Okay. Have a nice time.
Thanks.
You didn't answer any of my calls.
What brings you here all of a sudden?
I need to hear something from you.
About what?
You said you didn't know Yeo Ha Jin.
That was a lie.
You knew, didn't you?
That Ha Jin was Seo Yeon's friend.
But Ha Jin doesn't seem to remember Seo Yeon at all...
when I know for a fact that they were friends.
Explain to me now.
What on earth happened?
What is the truth that you know, but I don't?
I can understand why people...
who were interviewed by you had the same look on their faces.
Well, there's no way I can get out of this mess.
Ha Jin has been my patient for a very long time.
Two months after...
what had happened to Seo Yeon,
Ha Jin's mother came to me.
At first, I didn't know...
that Ha Jin was Seo Yeon's friend.
After finding out everything, I wanted to stop being her doctor,
but I couldn't...
because she reminded me...
of you back then.
(Operating Room, Intensive Care Unit)
(Intensive Care Unit)
(Operating Room)
Jeong Hoon... Jeong Hoon.
Jeong Hoon.
Tae Eun.
Seo Yeon died.
Goodness, Jeong Hoon.
Goodness.
Seo Yeon...
died.
Nothing.
I don't want to do anything.
I just want to disappear...
as if...
I never existed.
Ha Jin had as much of a tough time as you.
She was much different back then compared to now.
She was like an empty shell,
completely empty inside.
It was as if she couldn't hear or see anything,
as if she's unable to feel anything.
She would never eat or sleep,
collapse, get taken to a hospital, and be woken up against her will.
After about three months...
Ha Jin, how are you feeling today?
The weather is so nice that I want to go ride a bicycle.
What about you? Do you want to do anything?
I'm not athletic at all,
so it was really tough for me to learn to ride a bike.
I'd always fall down and get hurt.
Are you good at riding a bike?
- How does it sound? Why don't we... - Sleep.
I want to sleep for a bit.
It was the first time...
she said she wanted to do something.
I thought it was a positive sign.
That she was getting better.
So I prescribed sleeping pills for her...
many more times after that.
Ha Jin.
Ha Jin!
Mom!
(Psychiatric clinic, Yeo Ha Jin)
That was the first thing...
she wanted to do.
She was unconscious for days.
When she finally woke up at the brink of death,
she was completely different.
It was as if nothing had happened. She was happy and bright.
I guess that was the only way Ha Jin could cope with this.
Forgetting...
Seo Yeon.
At first, she was very confused.
All the memories and time she had with Seo Yeon...
turned into complete darkness.
(Patient Chart: Yeo Ha Jin)
This is her only picture with Seo Yeon.
We got rid of all the pictures of Seo Yeon which she had...
as well as everything that could remind her of Seo Yeon.
It was her family's choice and mine.
We wanted to help her forget Seo Yeon...
and live a normal life.
(Yoo Mental Health Clinic)
What's your plan?
I'm not sure. I can't seem to put everything together.
Once you take care of the scandal in two weeks,
you'll never have to see her again.
What could I say to someone who erased her memories to live?
I'll turn everything back as if nothing had happened.
What are you doing like a street cat?
You surprised me.
Can't you see?
You caught me drinking the bottles I bought with my money. What?
Exactly. You were asleep. Why are you suddenly drinking?
I have a press conference tomorrow,
so I'm too nervous to sleep.
I can't seem to sleep no matter what I do.
You were completely fine before the live broadcast of "News Live",
yet you can't seem to sleep over a mere press conference?
Man, that's why back then...
What about back then?
What?
Did you drink back then?
No.
I was going to, but I couldn't.
I just had a smell.
I see.
You're insane. You're so crazy.
What if other people find out?
Fine. You had no idea before I told you either.
This isn't good.
I'll help you fall asleep for sure. Get changed and come out.
Where are we going at this hour?
Hurry!
How dare she treat her older sister like this?
(Episode 6 will air shortly.)
Hurry up and climb up.
Why are you so slow?
I'm running out of breath because of this mask.
Gosh, that's much better.
Hey, keep the mask on.
There are a few people here.
No, I'll look more suspicious if I hide my face.
Let's start climbing for real.
Goodness.
Hurry up!
Hey, wait!
(Episode 6)
This is great.
I got some exercise out in the open...
and got to see the night view.
It has been forever.
Let's come out from time to time.
It must be suffocating to only work out inside.
Okay.
This place hasn't changed.
Even the air seems the same.
Is it your first time here after that?
I had no reason to be here.
I was busy too.
And I was kind of sick of it because of someone.
I was always in my room even after I got discharged,
so you always made me come up here with you,
saying I have to exercise to get better quickly.
You seemed like the evilest drill instructor.
Thanks to that time,
you're able to live through such a tough shooting schedule.
Of course, I know that.
When you first said you wanted to be an actress,
I tried so hard to stop you.
You tried to stop me that badly,
but you're still by my side because you were so worried.
So you know?
Is it not tough to be surrounded by people?
It's not. But I do become greedy.
I want to do better.
I had lost a part of my memory.
So I thought I could fill in that gap...
if more people could remember me.
Since I could play different roles,
it feels like they're filling in the gap.
I'm thankful.
I keep forgetting things, but they remember them.
They remember the expressions on my face, the things I said,
the clothes I wore, and where I've been.
I do feel bad for you and Ms. Park...
every time the paparazzi takes photos.
But I like that I can relive those moments...
by looking at the photos.
I'm not worried about forgetting them.
Don't get me wrong. I don't anticipate the paparazzi.
If you're that happy, why don't you start...
doing live streaming?
Should I start doing that from tomorrow?
Do you want me to confiscate your phone?
Ha Kyung, you're so adorable. It's getting cold. Let's go back.
Stop right there.
- Go? - Go.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- Do you want some tteokbokki? - What?
Fine, I'll be nice. One tteokbokki, please.
And this one too.
No.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Don't eat the rice cakes. You'll bloat.
Just have the fish cakes.
How could I skip the rice cakes? Don't be absurd.
Just one.
Bite it.
Do you think you can sleep well?
Yes, I'm about to fall asleep.
See? Let me know if you have trouble sleeping again.
I'll give you another painful training session.
I should've had the sausage as well. What a shame.
If you're ever hesitant about eating something, then don't.
Don't eat anything past 6pm.
Just don't eat.
Goodnight.
Sausages taste the best when you play hooky.
Remember when we used to have them at the Han River?
They tasted so good.
- The Han River? - Yes.
We used to have two each.
Hurry up and go to bed when you still can.
Why do you keep bringing up the past?
- Goodnight. - Goodnight.
It feels like they're filling in the gap.
Oh, no...
How could this happen?
No...
Don't go...
Let's go inside.
I can't.
I don't think I can look at her.
Still, you should bid her farewell.
I feel sorry for her.
I do.
That's why I can't.
I just can't.
- Hello. - Hello.
("My First Love")
Hello, I'm Ji Hyun Geun, the director of "My First Love".
Thank you for coming.
Hello, I'm Jung Ha Jun. I play the role of Min Seok,
Ha Jin's first love.
Hello, I'm Yeo Ha Jin. I play the role...
of Ae Young. It's nice to meet you.
Now, the reporters will ask questions.
Yes, sir?
This is a question for Ms. Yeo.
This is your first movie...
and also your first time playing the lead.
Why did you pick this movie?
I didn't. The director picked me.
I had a lot of trust in him.
I also enjoyed reading the script.
And since the title was "My First Love",
I thought I could transform my image into a lovable one...
and win the people's hearts.
I took the role immediately.
Your character has high standards for men.
What did you like about Anchor Lee, your actual lover?
You don't need to answer that.
Like I've mentioned before,
please only ask questions related to the movie...
That's okay. I can answer that.
Either way, you're still going to write an article.
But make it write 1, write 1 free.
If you post an article regarding my dating life,
please write one for this movie as well.
And a good one, if possible.
I'll tell you what I liked about him.
He's very intelligent, wise,
has a great voice, is eloquent...
But most of all,
he's so sexy when he spews biting remarks.
Didn't I answer the questions well?
Yes, you did.
You sure did.
Good work, Ha Jin. You looked beautiful today.
Good work to you too.
You need to leave right away for an interview, right?
Yes.
It's a pity we can't have dinner together.
Let's make sure to eat together next time.
Good work today. Bye.
Bye. I'll call you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Are the articles up?
Let me check.
("My First Love", Actress Yeo Ha Jin)
What a surprise. They posted many good articles.
"A New Side of Yeo Ha Jin".
Really?
There are many articles on Jeong Hoon as well.
The titles are all about how sexy he looks when criticizing.
Why did you have to say that?
Ms. Park?
No way.
Ha Jin. Ha Kyung. It's number one!
What is? The ticket sales?
Yes. Do you know what the current ticket sales are?
It's 40 percent.
The movie won't be premiering until two days later,
but it is higher than those of current movies.
It's the most popular movie right now.
Are all the current movies that bad?
Did you hoard the sales or something?
Don't be ridiculous. The movie's really a hit.
All the articles are complimenting it.
People are posting wonderful things on their social media as well.
It's the most anticipated movie.
I know one of the critics...
who came today, so I asked him.
And he complimented you on your acting.
He said the movie will be a hit thanks to you.
Really? He complimented on my acting?
Goodness, Ha Jin.
You're great at both acting and dating.
I can't believe you finally snatched a great guy like Anchor Lee.
"Met", not "snatched".
Thanks to him, your reputation got better,
and your movie has become a hit.
Great job, Ha Jin.
I hope you and Anchor Lee date for a very long time.
But get married late.
Don't forget that I'm always cheering for you.
Okay.
Yes? I guess you read the articles. That's right.
I bet 10 million people will watch the movie.
Don't be ridiculous. I didn't hoard the sales.
- Let's keep it a secret... - From her.
If she finds out that you two aren't dating,
she'll probably collapse.
She'll be worried sick about people's finding out...
and collapse from high blood pressure.
You're right. Let's take it to our graves.
I've never seen her so happy.
We've finally agreed on something.
We have.
Hold on.
This means our movie may be up for more than two weeks.
You're right. We'll have to find out,
but judging by the current situation,
I doubt it's a flop.
Really?
Then should I extend the period to two months?
(Yeo Ha Jin)
Forgetting...
Seo Yeon.
I guess...
that was the only way Ha Jin could cope with this.
(Yeo Ha Jin)
- All right. - Hello.
- A little bit more. - Check that.
- I did. - Okay.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Here you go. - From the rehearsal...
Thank you.
- Thank you. - A bit more.
- Is that good? - Yes.
That's good. Thank you.
My gosh, they are flaunting their relationship.
- Who are you talking about? - Who do you think?
I'm talking about Jeong Hoon. His article is in the limelight.
You know what? I'm quite surprised...
to see Anchor Lee date an actress.
When I first read the article, I wasn't sure.
But seeing how he's keeping his silence, he must be dating her.
Then, when Ha Jin came to our show for the interview,
did they already know each other?
Gosh, isn't that obvious?
They were already dating even before the interview.
And that's probably why he messed up that day.
I'm not sure if they had a fight...
or they are head over heels for each other.
You're right. Anchor Lee was a bit different that day.
Right. He did seem a bit off.
- Here's a revised script. - He's dating her in secret,
and he didn't tell us.
Number 7 and 9 got switched.
- That's right. - Thanks. Thank you.
He totally fooled us.
(New message, Yeo Ha Jin)
You're not answering my calls.
Please don't tell me you're dodging my calls.
Let's meet. I need to talk to you about something.
Anchor Lee, you're looking good.
You must be happy to be in love.
Well, I guess.
"Well, I guess"?
Does it mean you're happy or not?
You sound quite arrogant.
It's not just any woman. You're dating the actress, Yeo Ha Jin.
You don't have the right to say that you're not happy.
Yes.
I am happy.
Thank you.
That's right. You ought to be happy.
You're dating her...
after making a huge mistake on air...
and making our lives very difficult.
You must be happy.
Let me ask you a question.
Why did you freeze during her interview?
Were you not able to speak...
because you couldn't be so mean to your girlfriend?
Or were you not able to focus because things were going...
so well between you two and she was sitting next to you?
Were you thinking about something else?
She said you were sexy when you were critiquing others.
What about you? What side of her do you find so sexy?
Wait, you don't have to answer that. I think I already know.
I saw her photos in the magazine. She has a fine body.
I can't put up with this anymore.
What? What will you do if you can't put up with it?
What just happened? What's he doing?
Come on, man. You went too far with this.
I agree.
What did I do?
You know what? People make mistakes when they talk.
That doesn't mean he can be rude to his senior like this!
What will he do after he storms out?
Will he come over here and punch me or something?
Why are you here?
Anchor Lee told me to inform you that he's using the restroom.
- What? - He couldn't hold it anymore,
so it was urgent.
That jerk.
It's about Ha Jin.
What happens if she gets her memories back?
She'll probably...
be in a lot of pain.
And things might get worse like before.
Is it possible that she might never get her memories back?
Yes.
It's rare, but it happens for some people.
Her memories aren't coming back even after a long time.
But I still can't guarantee anything.
A part of me is envious of her.
And a part of me feels bad for her.
I can't even imagine how she must be feeling.
Living a life without precious memories.
Which one of us is more pitiful?
Me who can't forget my memories for the rest of my life?
Or Ha Jin who had to forget her memories to live?
(New message, Yeo Ha Jin)
It's me again.
Are you sick?
Like do you have the pink eyes, so you can't read my text?
Or did you hurt your fingers, so you can't text me back?
If it's neither, call me. It's important.
It's mine.
It's mine. Someone is calling me.
It's mine! My phone!
(Ms. Park)
Yes, Ms. Park.
I see. She has an interview tomorrow? At what time?
Okay.
What are you doing? Slapstick comedy?
I thought my phone was ringing.
You took yours earlier. Check your pocket.
Yes, right.
What is it? Did you think Lee Jeong Hoon was calling?
Yes. But he still hasn't gotten back to me.
Is he that busy?
Anchors on the news program are busy, right?
Do you think he's not calling back because he's busy?
- No. - So you know.
Are you serious? Do you really like him?
Is it serious?
Why aren't you answering me?
I was thinking.
What? But you never think.
My gosh. I don't know no matter how much I think about this.
To say that my feelings for him are serious,
we haven't met that many times.
- But... - "But"?
I'm curious and worried.
What are you curious and worried about?
Like when he froze on the news,
there are times when it looks like he's somewhere else.
He freezes and stops talking.
I know that he's in front of me,
but it looks like he's in some other universe.
But whenever that happens, he looks sad.
And it looks like he's in danger too.
For some reason, if I don't hold onto him,
he looks like he might disappear into thin air.
What are you talking about?
You won't get it.
Oh, that. Silence is always harder than words.
You were the one who told me that.
Right, I did.
It's pointless if it's one-sided.
I doubt it's going to work out for you.
He rejected you right away and ignored your calls and texts.
It's all right. It's not over until it is.
Gosh. This is not the right time to use that expression.
It's a really cool saying.
Excuse me. Hey.
The news must be starting now.
What are you doing? Answer the phone.
What? Is it mine?
(Anchor Lee)
Anchor Lee, we're starting in 10 minutes.
Give me a minute. I'll be right in.
Okay.
Hello?
This is Lee Jeong Hoon.
I'm sorry I didn't get back to you sooner. I was busy today.
I see. You were very busy today.
Hey, he was busy.
It's all right. I understand.
But what's so important that we needed to talk?
Well, the situation has changed.
It's a long conversation.
I'd like to talk to you about the details in person.
Sure. Let's meet then.
I have something to tell you too.
Are you free tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
How about today instead of tomorrow?
After your news program. That will work for me.
Okay, then. Where should we meet?
Well... We failed at the Han River.
Let's meet somewhere else.
I know a cafe.
I'll text you the address. I'll meet you there at 1am.
Okay.
What is this? He ignored you all day today.
Did he agree to meet you?
Yes. He said he needed to tell me something too.
Like what?
I don't know. What does he want to talk about?
I doubt that he will agree to your plan.
If you ask him to continue...
this fake relationship for two months, he'll be appalled.
- He won't be appalled. - I don't think so.
Hello, everyone.
Let us begin "Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live".
But what does he want to say to me?
Is it something good or bad?
I don't think you should be sitting around.
Are you going to see him like that?
What? No!
You have to be ready in 40 minutes to get there in time.
Gosh, this is bad.
I won't go if you run too late.
Hey!
Which one do you think looks better?
Can you see?
- The silver dress. - The silver one? Okay.
If you're going to wear whatever you want, why did you ask me?
No, you were very helpful.
I left out everything you liked, and it ended in no time.
Hey, he's here already. I'm getting off.
Call me when you're done talking.
Okay.
You got here early.
I just got here.
I enjoyed the news today.
Although I only caught half of it trying to get ready to go out.
Your tie looked great on you.
Really?
I'm glad.
Let's go inside. It's chilly.
It's right here.
No one is here.
Yes, it's not her business hour,
but I asked her for a favor.
I'm close to the owner here, so I came here from time to time.
Our table is on the second floor.
Isn't the night view here awfully pretty?
I came here often to see this with Ha Kyung and...
Goodness.
Be careful.
I should never let my guard down when I'm with you.
Walk up carefully. Don't fall down again.
Okay.
Do you know who Jung Seo Yeon is?
Jeong Hoon asked yesterday whether I knew her or not.
Gosh, no way.
I'm sure it's someone with the same name.
It's not like she was the only one with that name.
I didn't want to interrupt you in the middle of the news,
so I ordered everything myself. Is that all right?
It's a cocktail.
Yours is a virgin.
You have to drive, and you don't like alcohol.
I think this is yours.
Yes, this is the one without alcohol.
See that? I can never let my guard down.
You're right.
It's good.
And I like the ambiance here.
Right?
One second. It's way too pretty.
May I take some pictures and come back?
I'll leave you out of the picture, and I won't post it either.
I just want to keep it for myself. Is that okay?
Sure.
I'll be back soon.
Don't people like you usually hate taking pictures?
You already get a lot of pictures taken as a celebrity.
You're right. Some people hate taking pictures.
But I like it.
It's harder to forget if I have these pictures.
I don't have a good memory,
so I forget a lot of things.
But if you take pictures, these memories don't disappear.
And I won't have to be nervous about not remembering.
When I look at these pictures later,
I feel reassured that...
I've been living very well and diligently.
Why?
Did I seem weird again?
No, come to think about it, I can see why you do that.
I have too good of a memory.
What is this?
Are you showing off?
Anyway, what's this important thing you have to say?
Right, our prediction was completely wrong.
I think my movie will become a huge hit.
We held a press preview today, and everyone loved it.
And it's the number one on ticket sales too.
Really?
I doubt it'll be taken off after just two weeks,
so our contract...
I mean, it's not really a contract, per se,
but I thought we should extend this period.
How much longer?
At least two months.
Or maybe longer.
Well, you know, it might be a huge failure,
but if I ruin its success...
because of my breakup news,
I'd feel too bad for everyone who worked hard.
Okay.
Let's do as you'd like.
Really?
I don't care about the period. You can do that.
Okay.
By the way, is something going on?
Like what?
You seem a little different.
How can I put this? You seem nicer and gentler...
as if you had a change of mind.
To be frank, you were awfully cold to me.
What did you say?
Yes, right.
You hated someone who is reckless, thoughtless, and inconsiderate.
You're a good person.
I want you to always be happy.
I mean it.
You mean that in a good way, right?
But it sounds like...
you'll never see me again.
Yes, you're right.
I hope you will never contact me or ask me to meet...
ever again.
That's why I wanted to see you.
You just said you didn't care how long it lasts,
that I can do whatever I want.
That doesn't matter. It's all fake anyway.
So you wanted to say...
you never want to meet me again?
Yes.
What's the reason?
You and I were...
strangers until a few days ago.
We're just going back to our places.
It's simple.
"It's simple"?
I'm responsible for playing along with the love scandal,
so you can release...
the news of our breakup when your movie stops playing.
Let's go.
(We thank Kim Ea Na for her special appearance.)
(Find Me in Your Memory)
I ended it well with Ha Jin.
I'm sure the wounds will become dull over time.
Don't be too concerned.
I can never tell what he's like.
Did you never think of me once ever since that time?
I hope you'll be happier...
in the times to come compared to the times of the past.
There's no way he can live a normal life.
Someone who's suspicious?
Have you ever received...
any weird photos or threatening letters?
We ran into each other quite a few times.
Don't you know me?