(Episode 11)
Hello, Director.
Nice to meet you.
I already heard from Tae Eun.
Is this your first time here?
Yes, it's my first time.
Please, let's go inside.
May I ask you for the reason?
You never visited us for the last eight years.
Why did you suddenly want to visit?
I wanted to check...
that he was stuck in there...
with no rights whatsoever.
I wanted to know...
(Quarantine Treatment Room 1: Moon Seong Ho)
that there was nothing he could do.
And I also wanted to know...
that I'd never lose someone again because of him.
This is the first and the last time I'm doing this favor for you.
Going there doesn't do you any good.
I know.
I just wanted to check that it really wasn't him.
I know what you're thinking.
It's not true. That won't ever happen again.
You saw him locked up.
Ha Jin is a celebrity.
She may have some obsessed fans.
She can be more careful from now on.
So don't take it too seriously.
I thought the same thing eight years ago.
I thought it was just a coincidence.
I thought it wasn't a big deal.
Did you wait for long?
I saw him at the convenience store.
Are these silver?
Doesn't it look nice?
Yes.
I saw him at a cafe.
I saw him many times but thought nothing of it.
I thought it was understandable since he lived nearby.
Had I...
suspected him at least once...
Had I taken it more seriously, I would've been able to stop it.
I'm the reason...
Seo Yeon died.
I don't think I'll be able to live if the same thing happened again.
I can't lose Ha Jin.
Are you looking for something?
I can't find the other one.
Didn't you keep them together?
I thought I did, but I can't find one of them.
I had purposely set them aside for today's meeting.
Maybe it got snatched by one of your clothes.
Look carefully.
Are you sure you didn't wear it?
Not in a million years.
Gosh.
This would've been perfect.
You're here early.
Hello.
- Hello. Take this first. - What?
If you're hesitant about saying something, then don't.
Just answer their questions. Don't say anything unnecessary.
- Okay. - Should I wait in the car...
around 9pm?
- Yes. - That's okay.
I'll drop her home.
That'd be great.
- Let's go. - Okay.
You two look great together. Right?
I guess.
Do you have a lot of time today?
I'd like to ask you every single question I have.
Sure.
I always study beforehand,
but I get stuck every time I write my scripts.
Let's drink. They seem busy.
Okay.
Look at this.
These are all the questions I have for you.
I see.
I saw your movie.
You looked beautiful from the opening scene.
I liked your acting as well.
Really?
Let me be honest.
I was a bit hesitant at first.
But after watching it, I was sure.
I realized I could count on you.
Thank you for saying that. I'll do my best.
Okay.
Let's eat while we chat.
Our food was served a while ago.
I'm sorry for blabbering on and on.
Enjoy your meal.
Ha Jin, this is really delicious. Try it.
Okay.
When Ha Na was young,
she didn't know she was allergic to shrimp...
and thought they always stung.
She always thought it was strange but continued to eat them.
In the end, she was carried to the ER...
but still didn't know it was because of the shrimp.
Isn't that funny?
Yes, it is.
You can't have shrimp.
That was shrimp? I didn't know.
What is it? Are you allergic?
Yes, my throat swells.
I break out in hives as well. It takes me a while to get better.
I'm so sorry.
It could've been dangerous.
I'm glad.
Your boyfriend knows everything about you.
Lucky you.
We should eat this.
How did you know?
Have I told you before?
Please excuse me. I need to go to the restroom.
Sure.
It's probably best for her to practice reading the news...
as soon as possible, right?
Yes.
But then again, he'll help you with that.
I have nothing to worry about, right?
Of course. I bet he'll be very strict.
Excuse me. I need to take this.
Let's drink.
Okay.
Are you confident?
This drama won't be easy.
I'm not confident, but if I try my...
You're not?
Then you shouldn't do it.
You should take work seriously.
Sorry?
Writer Hwang wanted to cast you, so I said okay.
But I'm not happy with this.
I want the lead actress to be elegant.
But you're...
You probably know it too.
You're far from it.
Let's be honest.
Do you think you're fit for the role as a news anchor?
Aren't you embarrassed?
I know you picked this because of your boyfriend.
But then again, I guess it's a talent to date competent men.
I think...
you're out of line.
That's great.
You don't like me, right?
Then let's not waste any energy and just put an end to this.
Writer Hwang is just infatuated with Anchor Lee.
But she'll come to her senses after hearing you read the script.
So put an end to this.
Say that your schedule is busy or that you're feeling sick.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry. It was urgent.
What were we talking about again?
Right. We were talking about how excellent of a teacher...
you'd be for her.
Of course. I'm going to do my best.
You'll be taken aback during the script reading...
by how realistic she sounds.
Oh, my! I'm already looking forward to this.
By the way, she didn't win this role...
because of our relationship, did she?
Not at all.
I'm just worried...
that people might think she got this role...
because of her boyfriend.
Not at all. That's absurd.
We wouldn't do that.
After all, she's the one who'll be acting.
Right? I guess that was unnecessary to ask.
Those who think such foolish thoughts...
are the weird ones.
Of course.
We shouldn't deal with scumbags like them.
Right?
Right.
Ha Jin, don't be hurt by such rumors, okay?
Okay.
Can you buy me a can of beer?
You drank a lot of wine earlier.
Just one can.
It's just that I feel so frustrated.
Just buy me one can of beer.
Thank you.
Does that hit the spot?
A bit.
Here.
I'm going to get off.
Are you all right?
Why did you drink so much?
You heard everything earlier, didn't you?
You heard everything earlier.
The conversation between the director and me.
Not everything. I caught a few sentences.
But why are you speaking casually to me now?
It's about time that we did.
Until when do I have to address as Anchor Lee?
Is this the alcohol talking?
If you think it's unfair, you can talk to me casually too.
Is that what you think too?
Do I look cheap?
Am I that awful?
Do you have the same opinion of me as the director?
Director, my foot.
He's such a scumbag.
He couldn't say anything in front of the writer,
but he threatened an actress behind the writer.
Why would you care about a scumbag like that?
You said you really wanted to be in that drama.
Then, you should be in it.
Isn't going after what you want your thing?
Can an anchor...
badmouth someone like that?
Why not?
I'm really good at badmouthing people.
There's no other way. I give up.
You'll give up on the drama?
No, I'll be in the drama.
I must do it out of spite if I have to.
Not the drama. I give up on speaking casually to you.
I won't do it, so you don't get to talk to me casually.
It makes my heart flutter, so I can't have that.
And...
don't blame me later.
You brought this upon yourself.
What is it?
We can't do this.
Why not?
We'll regret it.
I won't regret it.
No, you will.
Perhaps, you'll regret more than me.
Gosh, why won't she call?
What? I told you to call me before you got here.
How did the meeting go? Did you do well?
Why are you quiet?
Did the meeting go well?
Yes? Hello?
Hello? Excuse me.
What on earth happened?
You reek of alcohol.
Ha Jin, did you get drunk and cause trouble?
Is that why you look sad?
I didn't cause trouble.
You did. I can tell.
How did you mess it up?
Don't tell me you got excited and overly friendly with them.
You did. That's what you did.
How will you fix this now?
Seriously. You're making this very difficult for me.
What if they say no and reject you?
Why not? Why can't I do it?
Why can't it be me?
You can't do it? Did they already reject you?
- Then, why was he nice to me? - Nice to you?
He should have let me eat that shrimp.
Shrimp?
He took care of me, sided with me, and acted cool for no good reason.
Cool? What did you say?
Forget it.
I don't want him, either. Tell him I don't want him.
Weren't we talking about the drama?
- Get out. - Hey.
Get out!
I don't want you. Gosh, I don't want this either.
Goodness.
Unbelievable.
Aren't you hungry?
There's a famous sushi restaurant nearby. Should we get some?
I'm tired. Let's eat at home.
Okay.
You're not asking about Anchor Lee today.
Whenever you came to do a radio show,
you would think about calling him.
Something happened between you two, right?
What is it?
Nothing happened. I'm just tired today.
Yes, I just came down.
- Where are you? - What are you doing?
I'm in the lobby on the first floor. Where?
What is this?
You said nothing happened. Why are we hiding?
Right.
Why did I hide? I didn't do anything wrong.
What about Mr. Jo? I thought the three of us were meeting.
He'll be back soon.
I told him to pay for the meal since he's late.
So order something expensive.
You did something wrong.
When you met the writer and the director,
did you mess up in front of Anchor Lee?
Mess up?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Right.
Why must I avoid him? I didn't do anything wrong.
I can just say hello to him.
We can surely exchange greetings.
I'm not sure if I'll be of any help in writing the article.
Schizophrenia isn't my area of expertise.
You'll be just advising him.
But make it sound as difficult as you can.
I want him to suffer a bit.
Let's go say hi.
What?
What brings you here, Doctor Yoo?
Hi, Ha Jin.
It's been a while.
My gosh. It's been so long.
I had no idea that I would run into you here.
By the way, do you know each other?
Why are you guys together?
I'm sorry. I'm late.
Hello. I've heard a lot about you.
I didn't know it was possible for Jeong Hoon to have any friends.
You're his only friend, right?
"Friends"?
Doctor Yoo and Anchor Lee?
- Goodness, hello. - Hello.
Are we all eating together?
Oh, no. We aren't.
If I'm not too much of a nuisance, may I go with you?
I'd like to ask something too.
Doctor Yoo was here to give advice for my article.
I took on a new report...
on crimes committed by schizophrenic patients.
Oh, I see.
But it doesn't look so great.
I wouldn't have come if I had known.
Exactly. You shouldn't have. You're very slow.
Excuse me. I'd like three sushi A sets for that table...
- and three sets for us. - Okay.
Three for us? Are we expecting someone else?
No, I just like sushi a lot.
Why? Is this your 1st time seeing someone eat 2 sushi meals?
Yes, it's my first time.
My girlfriend can't even finish one.
She must eat very little.
People usually eat at least two sushi meals.
No way. People usually eat one.
That's why it's called one serving.
You eat a lot. That's what.
Yes.
Anyway, isn't something weird about the three of them?
No. Not at all.
Stop minding that table.
It's none of your business.
It really is a small world.
I never imagined that you two would be friends.
Anchor Lee, I told you before...
that...
there was a problem with my memory.
Doctor Yoo was actually my counselor for about two years.
Then we lost contact as I went into acting.
It wouldn't be good if people found out I was counseled.
I see.
It's shocking to think that it had been five years already.
Isn't that so, Doctor Yoo?
You're right.
But you two seem like an unlikely match.
Since when were you two friends?
For a long time. Since when we were 11.
Yes, it's a pretty gross relationship.
You two must be very close.
Oh, right.
Anchor Lee, may I have a word with you after we eat?
Sure.
I've been here once for a production presentation.
It's kind of strange to see how quiet it is.
There aren't a lot of places in our building where we can have privacy.
I didn't know...
what to say or how I should face you when I ran into you again.
Did you already know...
that I had a problem with my memory?
And that I had Doctor Yoo as a counselor?
Did you know?
Yes.
Was that why you were so good to me?
Did you pity me?
No.
You pitied me, didn't you?
I never pitied you.
I'm not in a position to pity anyone,
and there's no reason for you to be pitied.
You are very difficult,
Anchor Lee.
You always seem to tell the truth,
yet it doesn't seem like the truth.
I hear a lot from you,
but it seems like I heard nothing.
It's frustrating at times,
but I keep wanting to know more.
I find you very difficult,
Anchor Lee.
Hello?
Doctor Yoo, this is Yeo Ha Jin.
You haven't changed your number.
This place is still the same.
And it's still empty.
There are a lot of customers during lunchtime.
I see.
You're still the same too, Doctor Yoo.
You haven't gotten old at all.
Wouldn't it be heartbreaking if I grew noticeably old in five years?
Is that so?
It's really great to see you again.
I was too shocked before to celebrate our reunion.
- Hello. What would you like? - Hello.
Two bowls of rice soup, please.
- Okay. - Yes.
Right, what did Anchor Lee say about me?
I'm sure you two talk a lot since you're friends.
Well, I don't know.
I'm guessing it wasn't anything great.
To be honest,
I like him a lot.
But he won't accept my feelings.
It feels unfair to have him push me away...
after he confuses me by leading me on.
I've always wondered why he acted like that.
But I think I kind of get it...
thanks to you.
What do you mean?
You once told me...
that your best friend has a disease where he can't forget anything.
I had so much fun and was very happy.
I remember those feelings vividly.
But I have...
no idea who I was with at that time.
It definitely wasn't Ha Kyung.
There's no need to remember everything.
People all forget and move on.
That's normal.
This is normal?
I know one person who isn't like that.
He's my best friend since when we were 11.
He can't forget anything.
Why not?
Because of a disease.
A disease that won't let him forget.
I can tell by your face that I must be right.
I thought so.
Anchor Lee often said...
he has too good of a memory.
- That's... Did I... - I heard many things from you...
when I was counseled,
but I could never forget what you said about your friend.
I guess it's because that sounded very special to me.
It feels like I finally resolved my riddle.
Did you say it was hyperthymesia?
The name of that disease.
(Hyperthymesia)
Reporter Choi Yul.
I heard people who were arrested...
for using violent language and behavior...
against medical staff has doubled in the last three years.
Yes, although the punishments became reinforced...
after the amendment of the Medical Service Act in April,
there aren't many people who became detained...
because most cases are settled.
Not many can easily...
- deal with a lawsuit. - "There is no known cure."
In the end, it'll be the most important...
to stop these things from happening...
and to efficiently control the situation when this happens.
Thank you, Reporter Choi Yul.
Thank you for watching "Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live".
Have a great night.
- Great work. - Great job.
- Great work. - Great work.
- Great job. - Great work today.
Great work.
You're very difficult,
Anchor Lee.
You always seem to tell the truth,
yet it doesn't seem like the truth.
I hear a lot from you,
but it seems like I heard nothing.
It's frustrating at times,
but I keep wanting to know more.
I find you very difficult,
Anchor Lee.
(Tae Eun)
What suddenly brings you here?
I caused a bit of an accident.
Like what?
Ha Jin found out...
about your disease.
It's my mistake.
I once mentioned you during our session.
It was just once, but she remembered it.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault I have that disease.
There's no reason to hide it from everyone forever.
So...
how much does she know about her condition?
Why does she think there's a problem with her memory?
A motorcycle accident.
She thinks she got badly hurt...
because of that accident, fell unconscious, then woke up,
and that it caused a momentary problem with her memory.
That's what she knows.
By any chance,
did she ever tell you about her condition?
I heard she said she isn't normal.
Yes.
She still thinks there's a problem with her memory.
And she seems to be confused.
Why didn't you tell me?
It seemed like she didn't want others to find out.
I can't tell you something she wants to hide.
To be honest, I'm nervous...
that things will get out of our hands.
If...
she remembers Seo Yeon,
you also know what could happen.
I don't want to see you or Ha Jin get hurt.
Don't do anything you'll regret.
I'm doing my best.
I also don't want her to be hurt.
Don't worry.
Yes, Anchor Lee.
If it's okay with you, may I check the footage?
The security footage?
I thought I'd better check.
I'm sure it'll be fine. Nothing special happened.
But I'll tell Chul to send it over.
(Episode 12)
What? Since when was that camera there?
Darn it.
Yes, Ha Kyung.
I was going to send it over,
but the settings were all messed up.
Nothing was recorded.
Really? What happened?
Everything is fine now, right?
Yes, I fixed the setting.
Okay.
(Do you want to delete this footage?)
(Footage deleted.)
Do you have the new big scoop?
Why have you been running around with Il Kwon since the morning?
Oh, it's nothing.
It doesn't seem like this is nothing.
It looks like something is going on.
- Hello. - Yes, hello.
Goodness, look who this is.
I can't believe I ran into you.
- Nice to meet you, Anchor Lee. - Yes.
- Anyway, who are you? - Who are you?
She's the director. And she's my CEO.
I see. Nice to meet you.
Yes, you're like Anchor Lee's mother.
Please do take good care of my Ha Jin, Director.
Goodness, Director.
His mother? I'm just his boss.
I'm not that much older than him.
- One second. - I see.
Anyway, what brings you here?
We have a meeting for a drama with the writer and the director.
Oh, yes. I heard you might play the news anchor.
Let me know if you need anything.
I was really relieved when you said you'll help us...
by taking up that documentary, so I should help too.
Then we should ask if she can do research here.
You wanted to do that, didn't you?
Do you need to do research?
Oh, yes. I hardly know anything, so I didn't know what to do.
It would be great if I can study by seeing it in real life.
Go ahead, then. That's nothing difficult.
Come over whenever you have time.
You have nothing tomorrow.
You can come tomorrow, then.
Is that all right?
Yes. Yes, of course.
Thank you. Then I'll see you tomorrow.
- Sure. - Please excuse us.
- Goodbye. - Sure, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Goodness.
- Thank you. - Here's your coffee.
- Thank you. - I'll take that.
- Are we parked right outside? - Yes, it's right outside.
Let's go.
Chul looked at it, but the setting was wrong.
He fixed it now, so it should be all right from now on.
I'll keep checking from time to time.
Goodness, Ha Jin. Great work today.
Get a good rest at home.
Okay, Ms. Park. Goodbye.
- Goodbye. - Okay.
- Great work. Drive safely. - Yes, goodbye.
- Yes. - Okay.
It's the director.
Which one?
Director Ji? Don't pick it up.
- Why not? - Don't pick up.
Yes, Director Ji.
I told you not to pick it up.
Right now?
Do you like that picture?
Yes.
But it'd be better if it was in my room.
It's your work, so I'll buy it from you.
I can always give it to you,
but that picture looks the best when it's here.
But I'll give you another present.
A present?
Yes, come here.
("Goodnight, Darling")
I kept you waiting, didn't I?
Something about the ending didn't seem right.
I couldn't make up my mind, so I finally finished it this morning.
That's why I wanted to see you.
I thought Ms. Yoo Mi So will be starring in this one.
I saw the article.
Mi So had a misunderstanding.
I always told you...
that you'll also play the lead role of my next movie, Ha Jin.
I see.
We'll start filming at the end of the year.
The lead role is a pianist,
- so you need to learn to play... - I'm sorry, Director Ji.
I don't think I can do this.
- What do you mean? - I'm starring in a drama,
Writer Hwang's work.
I thought Ms. Yoo would be playing the lead for this one.
You haven't signed the contract yet, have you?
Read it first. It'll help change your mind.
You know what? Read it right now.
I'm sorry, but I really want to do this drama.
I'm truly sorry.
I said,
read it right now.
I'm sorry. I was a bit flustered.
You understand me, right?
You didn't have to buy this.
- Thanks. - No problem.
Is he crazy or what?
He was always so loving toward Mi So,
so why is he upset at you?
He's the one who changed his mind.
If it's too difficult for you to say no, let me talk.
I'll tell him that our agency decided to do so.
I should.
- Are you okay? - Yes, I'm fine.
("Goodnight, Darling")
Jeong Hoon.
Anchor Lee, I came to study.
I see.
I was just about to show her the studio control room.
Do you want to come with me?
No, go without me.
Why is he so cold?
Does he usually come to work around this time?
No, he's a bit late today.
He usually comes around 10pm.
On Mondays, he comes at 9pm.
He comes to work early.
The news ends at 12am.
You're right. The last news team doesn't come to work that early.
He's just meticulous.
Thanks to him, I have to come to work early as well.
Please keep this a secret from him.
Okay.
"He comes to work at 10pm and 9pm on Mondays."
Why would you write that down?
It's important.
- Shall we go? - Sure.
What are you doing there?
I was curious about what you were reading.
You should've just asked.
You seemed very focused. I didn't want to disturb you.
Staring at me like that is worse.
Really?
So what were you reading?
Can I read it too?
Come sit next to me.
Okay.
These are the articles we'll cover during the news.
They're not finalized yet.
They'll be finalized a bit after 6pm.
I see.
My news will be recapping the articles...
from the 9pm news.
So it's important to determine which ones to omit...
and which ones to dig in deeper.
Can you hold on?
But I won't be repeating the same thing.
I might cover the same news,
but the anchors are different and mine starts late at night.
Since your character works for the 9pm news,
it'll help you more if you watch the 9pm news.
Ha Jin found out...
about your disease.
Then when will you read the 9pm news?
I heard that's the main one.
I'm not sure. That's not up to me.
I've never considered it either.
Not anyone can do the 9pm news.
Since when were you there?
I had a food coma and was napping.
What? Was I not allowed to?
I didn't see you at all.
You probably couldn't.
You were busy pulling each other...
closer.
You were too busy being lovey-dovey...
to notice me.
We were neither pulling each other closer...
nor being lovey-dovey.
We were only talking about the news.
Right, I'm sure.
You must be professionals.
Out of all the great places to date,
you picked this busy workplace...
to act all lovey-dovey.
- Wait. - Right.
Let me clear something.
I'm the one who's in charge of the articles for his news.
I'm the one who decides what to omit and what to dig deeper.
Got it?
After all, I'm his boss.
Make sure you write them all down.
Look at you acting all cool in front of your girlfriend.
What's wrong with him?
I have no idea either.
What are you writing so secretively?
Nothing.
I'd like two cups of Americano, to go, please.
That'll be nine dollars.
How was it today?
Was he nice enough to explain everything?
Yes, he was. But I'm going to come again tomorrow.
Why would you? Wasn't today enough?
What's wrong? I'm free tomorrow.
It's good to be thorough.
That's true.
By the way, how many cups of coffee do we need?
- I want a chocolate drink. - No.
Hold on.
Hello? You may speak.
Hey, don't even talk about Anchor Lee. He irritates me.
He thinks he owns the broadcasting station.
This time, he even invited his girlfriend over.
It was ridiculous.
I can't take it.
Can you send me the tentative proposal?
- I need to go to the toilet. - Okay.
Oh, my.
When did you come?
Just now. You can finish writing.
That's fine. I'm all done.
I hope I'm not taking too much of your time.
Don't worry. I have all the time in the world.
Isn't that your team leader?
What was that?
Oh, no.
I'm so sorry. I thought you were my manager.
Even still, why would you slap your manager's head like this?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
You two have similar-looking heads.
I'm sorry. That must've hurt.
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Hello.
I'm Jeong Hoon's mom. It's nice to meet you.
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
Me too.
Have you eaten already?
Do you want to join us for dinner?
We're going to have something nice.
Come with us.
Do you want some hand cream?
- Hand cream? - Do this.
This?
Do it like this.
Doesn't it smell nice?
The food's already here.
You're right. That was quick.
Jeong Hoon, listen to this.
Ha Jin said she slapped your team leader on purpose.
She said he was being so annoying.
You told me about him before.
Is he really that bad?
You'll understand me once you get to know him.
He's so pesky.
It must've felt great to slap him.
Extremely. I was waiting for my chance.
I think you have a call.
Oh, excuse me.
It's my sister. I'll be back.
She's so cheerful.
I bet she makes everyone around her laugh a lot.
I haven't seen you laugh this much in a long time.
Really?
Then don't you think it'd be nice to meet up like this more often?
Are you sure you're all right?
I'm totally fine.
When you become my age, every day becomes boring.
You know you can't lie to me.
What is it?
Later.
I'll tell you everything later.
I've always kept my word.
I promise...
to tell you later.
Really.
Okay. Let's eat.
Gosh, it's been a while since I had steak.
Wait. I'll cut it for you.
Yes. I'm having a meal with Anchor Lee and his mother.
No, it's not uncomfortable at all.
She's really nice.
Okay. I'll be back soon.
Okay. I got it.
Okay.
Here you go.
I had such a nice meal thanks to you.
Please let me treat you to a meal next time.
Will you?
Then, I should have a really expensive meal then.
Please do. I have a lot of money.
I'm laughing a lot thanks to you today.
Let me.
Okay.
I have a way with scarves.
I know about ten different ways of wearing them.
And I'll use the most beautiful way of wearing a scarf.
I should learn them from you sometime.
There you go.
I see. I didn't know you could wear it like this.
This looks beautiful.
Jeong Hoon, what do you think? Doesn't this look nice?
Is it any different? They look all the same to me.
My goodness.
This is why having a son is no fun.
Ha Jin, do you want to take a photo with me?
It would look really nice if we take it over there.
Yes. Sounds great.
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
You're the photographer.
I was the photographer?
- Of course. - Of course.
All right.
In 1, 2, 3.
Ta-da.
If you want, I'd love to take a photo for you guys.
Yes. That sounds great. Please take a photo of us.
Jeong Hoon, come over here.
Hurry.
I'll take it now.
In 1, 2, 3.
We have to mark the spot for surgery tomorrow,
so you have an endoscopy.
You can't leave the hospital without permission again like today.
You know that, right?
Okay.
I don't need to leave the hospital now.
I'll believe you.
I haven't seen many patients...
getting surgery after going through stage four chemotherapy.
That's really impressive.
You just need this surgery to go well.
Hang in there a bit more.
Okay. Thank you.
You ate a lot today.
Shouldn't we go for a run before going to sleep?
I'll do it if you let me eat late-night snacks.
What?
Do I need to come tomorrow at the same time as today?
Well, I'll just drive her around.
- Take a day off tomorrow. - Okay.
You'll be back after the news, right?
Yes, I should.
Good job today. Go home now.
Okay. Call me if you have a problem.
Okay. Bye.
I want fried chicken.
Go get changed.
Where? To go for a run.
Be careful.
I think I dropped it somewhere over here.
(Anchor Lee's Day)
(Anchor Lee usually listens during the meeting.)
(After the meeting, he checks articles and writes lines.)
(He always uses the same pen when he works.)
He always uses the same pen when he works.
Look at you acting all cool in front of your girlfriend.
What's wrong with him?
I have no idea either.
What are you writing so secretively?
Nothing.
The person that annoys him the most is Team Leader Kim Chul Woong.
I can tell that he's thinking about punching the guy.
Then, what should I do?
Are you asking me because you don't know?
Or because you're testing me to see if I can get it right?
Of course, I know what to do.
He hates it the most when people ask him what they should do.
After having lunch, he always drinks an Americano.
When he's done with the news,
he stays in the green room and is the last one to leave.
He looks so lonely when he's alone.
You're here.
Let's talk.
Where did you find that?
I looked everywhere, but I couldn't find it.
Did you read this?
I was just...
Don't get the wrong idea. It didn't mean anything.
I hope you're not upset.
I won't get the wrong idea.
And I'm not upset either.
I'm just uncomfortable about this kind of situation.
I hate that you're walking on eggshells around me...
because of my condition.
I've had this condition for a long time.
And I'm used to this.
So you don't need to try hard for my sake.
I wasn't trying hard.
To be honest, when I found out about your condition,
I just thought that I got to know you a bit more.
That's not true. It got harder.
I studied and kept thinking about it,
but I still don't know...
how it must feel to live with all the memories one has.
On one side, I'm jealous.
And on the other side, I feel bad.
I'm sorry. I won't write notes if this upsets you.
But please don't misunderstand my intention.
I'm doing this for me, not for you.
I can forget about other things,
but I really want to remember everything about you.
I don't want to forget anything when it comes to you.
Why isn't he answering his phone?
Why are you still here?
Chul was supposed to come, but he's not coming.
And he's not answering either.
What about your sister?
She left earlier because she had an important meeting.
That's why Chul was supposed to come.
Chul must be here.
Hey, Chul.
What? Why can't you come? Where are you?
Okay. I understand.
No, I'll manage.
Okay.
Hop in. I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. I'll take a taxi.
My friend got hospitalized, so I have to go to the hospital.
Get in.
Thank you.
I'm sorry you had to do this instead of going home.
It's okay.
Does he break his promise very often? Your manager, I mean.
Oh, we told him before to take today off,
so I guess he was hanging out somewhere far away.
He's usually not like that. He's very diligent.
Really?
Right.
Ta-da. I bought this. Your mother's poetry book.
That was published a while ago. How did you find it?
I got curious and looked for it right away as soon as I met her.
I don't know much about poetry, but I loved it.
I instantly became her fan.
If I get to meet her again, I'll ask her for an autograph.
She'll be thrilled.
She looks a lot like you.
Especially the way you smile.
I'm sure you only have good memories of her.
You're right.
She always...
gave me nothing but good memories since when I was a kid.
(Soojeong University Hospital)
Thank you for the ride. Go home safely.
Will you be all right by yourself?
There are a lot of people.
What's wrong?
(Father)
Anchor Lee.
(We thank Shin Dong Mi, Kim Nam Hui for their guest appearance.)
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Can you fix my disease?
Anchor Lee, time can't help you.
Just keep your eyes on him.
Keep my eyes on him?
I can't let Jeong Hoon get destroyed.
What on earth happened to Mom?
She wanted this.
She felt too bad for you.
She did this out of love.
I'm so happy that you're with me, Jeong Hoon.
Are you sure that you were happy?
It's okay, Jeong Hoon. It'll be fine.