(Episode 9)
How did you know I was here?
What's wrong?
Is something going on?
It's all right now.
It's all right.
What?
Who are you?
Who do you think you are to suddenly run in...
and why are you hugging her out of nowhere?
Then who are you?
It's Anchor Lee.
It is him.
He's her boyfriend.
"Boyfriend"? Is that true?
Yes. I'm her boyfriend.
So what were you doing with her?
It's a misunderstanding. I made a mistake.
There was an accident.
"An accident"?
I was distracted for a split second...
and crashed into their car.
- Gosh. - Get out.
- Gosh. - It's a brand new car.
Are you okay? Oh, no.
I'm sorry. I am.
This is totally my fault.
I'll compensate for everything as you wish.
Hold on.
Are you...
Yeo Ha Jin? You are, right?
No way.
We... We were just on our way back home after watching your movie.
Really? Yes, it's me.
I can't believe this!
- Could we take a photo? - Can I shake your hand?
- Sure. - Thank you.
Let's take a photo too.
Let's go somewhere that's not too dark.
- Sure. - Let's go.
(Anchor Lee)
You called me a lot.
You must've been worried sick.
Don't misunderstand.
Anyone would've gotten worried in this situation.
It's late.
You went to the movies alone, and I couldn't reach you.
I see.
Is that why you called Ha Kyung incessantly...
and went all the way to the movie theater?
Okay, I won't misunderstand this.
From now on, don't go anywhere alone.
And be wary of people.
"People"?
They're good people.
They were kind to me.
Just because people are kind to you...
that doesn't mean they're good people.
Don't trust people so easily.
Okay, I'll be careful.
You're not a teenage runaway.
Why would you go out so late at night and cause trouble?
I'm sorry. I knew you'd take at least three hours...
to come home from the gym.
I was going to watch a movie and go home.
I didn't know this would happen.
It's getting late. Get home safely. Goodbye.
Already?
Then what? Are you going to work out together or something?
Let's go.
Go home safely.
You too.
I'll text you when I arrive home.
I don't want you to worry again.
Okay, please do that.
What?
Goodbye.
What are you looking at?
I'm waiting to see if any photos are getting posted.
Those men promised me...
not to tell anyone about the accident.
Don't worry about that.
I'm not talking about those photos.
Then what?
Photos of Anchor Lee and me.
It would've been nice if there were photos.
I'd like to look at them whenever I wish.
There weren't many people.
It's a shame.
You should be relieved.
Had more people been there,
we wouldn't have been able to keep this on the low.
I don't even want to imagine it.
Do you know what he said to those men?
What?
He said he was my boyfriend.
He said that himself.
What's going on?
What do you think? It's a romance.
After all, he ran over there because he was worried about me.
You're right. He seemed pretty worried.
He made it seem like something happened to you.
Yes. This is romance, indeed.
Are there seriously no photos of us?
It's Jeong Hoon.
I need to talk to you regarding Ha Jin.
Please call me when she's not around.
What are these photos?
Jeong Hoon speaking.
These photos were sent to you?
Yes. I had received them a while ago,
but I only opened them today.
I didn't check every single one of them,
but I don't think these photos were from articles or online.
Are you saying they took them while stalking her?
Don't take it too seriously just yet.
Like you said, she's a celebrity.
A fan of her could just be obsessed over her.
It's highly likely.
But nevertheless,
I thought you should know about this.
It's better safe than sorry.
I'll keep this a secret from her. I don't want her to feel anxious.
If you notice anyone suspicious around you...
or receive strange mail, let me know right away.
I will. Let me know as well.
All right.
My goodness!
Who are you?
Who do you think? They're security guards.
"Security guards"?
My security guards?
We're late. Let's go.
This way.
Why do I have security guards all of a sudden?
What's going on? Tell me.
Hey, your older sister is asking you a question.
I'm going to get mad.
Tell me.
- Put on your seatbelt. - We're departing.
All those men will be escorting me?
Stop asking.
Why would they?
I've been fine alone all this time.
Things have changed now.
You're no longer the old you.
Plus, all the other celebrities have security guards.
We were the exception.
Right, Chul?
She's right. Your fan base grew significantly.
We can't manage them on our own anymore.
I don't think it's that much.
Did you look into it?
I visited the post office.
But I got nothing.
The post office requires you to write down your information...
in case the mail gets sent back.
They said this mail was put in a mailbox.
We can't identify them through this.
And this type of envelope can be seen everywhere.
Did I receive any more mail?
No. You did receive more,
but none of them look suspicious.
Okay, I'm heading back right now.
("Romantic Nurse, Director Choi")
These scripts are all for me?
These were handpicked.
We had twice as much.
We rejected any with you as a supporting actress.
You? Supporting actress? That's absurd.
You're the lead actress in all of those.
We took out any that centered around the lead actor...
and only picked the ones with you in the center.
What if the drama is a flop?
Can I just be a supporting actress?
It won't be a flop.
You need to be in the limelight.
Your schedule will be less hectic for the time being,
so focus on picking out your next work, okay?
Then do I only have the signing event for tomorrow?
That was canceled.
Why all of a sudden?
We had issues with the venue.
That's disappointing. I love signing.
That's ridiculous. It's just tiring.
This is actually better for you.
Hello?
Not at all. We're not looking down on you.
Ha Jin isn't the type that becomes pompous...
just because of fame.
There was another reason.
Let me take this outside.
Hello?
Yes.
- What was that? - What do you mean?
We canceled the signing event, didn't we?
The whole security guard thing is fishy too.
What is it? What's going on?
Nothing. It's true that the signing event got canceled.
Don't lie to me.
I'm not. Why can't you believe me?
I really hate it...
when I'm the only one in the dark.
Tell me what's going on now.
Anchor Lee got a threatening letter.
A threatening letter?
I think your stalker sent him the letter.
There were some photos.
What about the photos?
Do you have them now? Let me see.
(Yeo Ha Jin)
Hello?
You're answering your phone right away now.
Before, I'd call you several times, but you wouldn't answer.
You must be busy preparing for the news,
so I'll cut to the chase.
Hiring security guards is the best,
but I'm sure you'd never go for that.
So be careful when you go home at night.
And don't go out by yourself.
And make sure you always lock up.
I'll be worried,
so after the news, when you get home,
please leave me a text. Okay?
Did Ha Kyung tell you?
She told me about the stalker and I saw the photos too.
But when I thought about it,
you're in bigger danger than I am.
The stalker who sent you the photos...
is angry at you, not me.
He cut your face in the photos.
And he sent the photos to you.
I doubt that's the case.
The stalker wants you and is obsessed with you.
Now that you say it like that, it does bother me a bit.
Okay. I'll be careful.
Then, we both should be careful.
I have my own security team.
And I won't be attending events that could put me in danger for now.
So the signing event was canceled.
In other words, don't worry about me.
I'm glad to hear that.
And...
if something like this happens again,
tell me that in person instead of telling Ha Kyung.
I'm not a kid.
I'm somewhat professional.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I wasn't fishing for an apology.
Anyway, it starts today.
When you get home, text me.
Will do.
I am...
madly in love.
(Director Ji Hyun Geun)
Hey.
I saw Director Ji Hyun Geun in the studio earlier.
In the studio?
My gosh, he must think he owns this place.
He's been all over the place with a camera.
I wanted to give him...
By the way, what are you up to these days?
I'm not up to anything.
Yes, you are. The blue envelope.
- I see. - I was right. There's something.
What's in it? Why is Il Kwon going around with that envelope?
I'm sure you were the one who gave him the assignment.
What is it? Did someone give you a tip?
Come to my office.
Director Ji Hyun Geun is in my office.
What is it?
I don't know what you mean. I'll ask Il Kwon about that.
Director Choi wants to see me in her office.
Come on.
They always leave me out of that.
Great. Excellent.
Can you smile more broadly?
Okay. Great. That's great. All right.
All right. Smile!
This is excellent. Yes.
It's the last one. Smile.
Great.
Can you smile more broadly? A bit more.
- Great. Nice. - Hey.
Anchor Lee, you're here.
Come in. Come on in.
Can we stop now?
Yes, I got great shots.
These photos look amazing.
The director has such a likable face.
I begged her to let me take photos of her.
I thought taking her photos would inspire me.
- I see. - By the way,
are you here to get me?
Hold on.
Look at the time.
Time flew by when I was talking to Director Choi.
Right. I think it'd be better if you start getting ready.
Well, it's a live broadcast.
So you'll be more nervous than you expected.
I think it will be a lot of fun.
I'll get going.
I'll give you the photos as my present when I develop them.
- I'll see you then. - Sure.
- Good luck with the interview. - Okay. Bye.
Hey.
I need to talk to you. It's urgent.
Come here.
Goodness. He's such a weirdo.
Are all artists off-the-wall like him?
What were you doing?
I mean, he barged into my office out of the blue.
And he bragged about himself for 10 minutes.
He talked about his inspirations and such.
And he started taking photos.
I thought he'd go away if I played along.
My gosh, but that was endless. Seriously.
Gosh.
By the way, are Director Ji and Ha Jin close?
- Why do you ask? - He sounded...
as if he knew something. He kept sussing me out.
You know, about your fake relationship.
He kept sussing me out,
so I shut it down.
But I don't know what he's thinking.
Hello.
What a great studio.
You're here.
You have a fine studIo.
Isn't Ha Jin beautiful?
Yes, she is. She's especially pretty in my eyes.
You must keep a close eye on her.
As passionate as she is,
she's not the type to go steady with just a man.
That's why there were countless love scandals.
Not every guy can handle a girl like her.
That's why I still can't believe it.
Are you guys taking your relationship seriously?
I mean, the photos I saw in the articles...
seemed a bit awkward.
To tell you the truth, I think you're faking it.
Well, I'm pretty sure I'm wrong.
We'll put on the microphones.
Okay.
I think it's too early to talk about my next project.
Just like the title, this film is like first love to me.
I want to get immersed in this movie for the time being.
Did you hear him? He kept bugging you to scout for the next film.
I see. Unfortunately, we will have to...
patiently wait for your next film.
- Text him and say he did well. - Thank you for coming today.
- Thank you. - Okay.
Should I?
- That was Director Ji Hyun Geun. - Can I send this during the news?
What if I distract him?
No, I meant the director. Not Anchor Lee.
I see. You want me to text the director?
(Director Ji)
(Director Ji Hyun Geun)
Director Ji is calling.
You're here.
Anchor Lee.
I didn't know you were joining us.
Why didn't you tell me?
You said you needed to talk to me.
I just assumed that you'd know.
That's odd.
Isn't this when couples can't wait to be with each other?
Couples text and call each other all the time in the beginning.
Anchor Lee, do you drink?
No. I don't.
Come on. That's no fun to hang out with a man who can't drink.
Join us.
Sure.
Cheers.
I drank it on his behalf. I'm his stand-in.
What was that? That was rude.
He really can't drink.
Please be understanding about it.
I'll drink this instead.
You're an awfully boring person.
Yes, I'm like that.
What? No way. He's really funny.
You'll know if you meet him a few more times.
Okay. All right.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Excuse me! Is anybody here?
What were you going to do?
- Were you really going to drink it? - We need more drinks!
No.
I wanted to steal your move.
This isn't a move that anyone can make.
It's really humiliating if anyone catches you doing this.
It seems like he's quite drunk.
We should break it up once he comes back.
Can you keep a watch?
What? Keep a watch?
Let me know right away if he comes. Hurry.
Hurry up. Go.
Why do you ask me to keep a watch?
What are you doing?
Are you going to steal...
No, right?
No. What do you think of me?
Keep looking out. Hurry.
He's coming.
What do we do? Hurry. Hurry up.
He's almost here. He's near.
Hurry up!
I think I might catch his eyes.
Hurry up. He's almost here.
- He's almost here. - What are you doing? Sit down.
They didn't bring the drink yet?
Excuse me!
You look quite drunk. Let's go home.
Yes, Director Ji.
Ha Jin. I need to talk alone with you.
Director Ji, you're drunk. Let's talk next time.
No, I have to talk to you now. Come on, you and I are going out.
Let me go.
Let me go while I'm still nice.
That's enough.
No. Let me go. Let go of me!
Let go!
Why is he so drunk?
Anchor Lee, you really didn't have any alcohol, did you?
He didn't.
Then please take care of her.
Sure.
You know where he lives, right?
You've been there once.
Yes, the address should be saved on the GPS.
Drive safely.
Okay.
Call me when you get there.
Why did you do that before?
You looked through his stuff and got angry at him.
Do you still meet him often?
We met every day while we filmed the movie...
and pretty often while we did the promotion,
but not recently. We had no reason to meet.
Why do you suddenly ask?
You didn't know that he likes you?
Me?
Come on, no way.
Anyone could tell.
You're pretty slow in this area.
No way. I'm very quick-witted.
Do you think...
it was Director Ji who sent you those pictures?
Why would someone like him do that?
It really isn't him. There's no way.
You never know.
People like that have no reason for doing such things.
I told you before. Don't trust people that easily.
Then what about you?
May I trust you?
I'm not sure.
Don't trust me too much.
But I'm definitely not your stalker.
Thank you for the ride.
You must be tired. You should get some rest.
Okay.
It was great to have spent some time with you today.
I'm afraid I'll ruin everything if I tell you this now,
but I thought I should say it.
I'll lose my chance to tell you if I hesitate any longer.
What is it?
I'm saying this for the first time to you, Anchor Lee.
To be honest,
my head isn't normal.
I don't remember the things that I should remember.
There are moments when I remember something I know nothing about.
That means I'm weird. I'm not all right.
I thought I wasn't the only one who was weird.
I mean, you.
You always left me with question marks...
from the day we first met and to this day.
Why do you want me to be happy?
Why are you so concerned and are sensitive about me?
But you don't even like me.
I want to know why you're doing that.
Does it have something to do with the things I forgot?
You know something, don't you?
Have we always known each other?
Have you always known me?
Are you a part of that time...
which I can't recall?
Tell me.
I don't exactly understand...
what you mean by that,
but we first met at...
the waiting room of the TV station on the day of your interview.
And I worry about you...
because I had a friend who got into a similar accident.
That's why I was concerned and sensitive about you.
Does that answer your question?
I'm sorry I suddenly brought this up.
But since when...
Ha Jin!
Hello, Anchor Lee.
Hello.
Why are you suddenly here? Did something happen?
Ha Kyung told me to come.
She told me not to let you be alone at home.
That's not necessary. She'll be back soon.
She said she'll be a little late.
Director Ji threw up in the car, so she has to clean it up.
It'll take a while.
Really?
Go inside. Hurry.
(Episode 10)
It looks like he's the guy who took those pictures.
Right?
What should we do?
Did you report it to the police?
Yes, they'll be here soon.
Don't worry.
Wasn't it too dangerous to let Anchor Lee go alone?
Should I go after him?
Will you be all right?
Yes, I'm sure it'll be better than being alone.
Don't go anywhere, lock the doors, and stay inside.
Okay, I'll do that.
Be careful.
Okay.
Who are you?
- Who do you think you are? - Wait!
Mr. Lee, it's me. Reporter Park Soo Chang.
I'm with Naeil Media.
You've seen me before, right? I'm close to Il Kwon too.
What? It's you, Reporter Park.
Yes.
Give me your camera.
Oh, yes. I was about to erase these.
It's not that I have any feelings against you.
I had to take Ms. Yeo's pictures, so I ended up... Darn it.
I can erase those myself.
- I have my personal pictures... - Calm down.
Send me the bill.
I'll reimburse you.
And don't ever let me catch you again.
If you do, I don't know what I'll do to you.
Okay. Please excuse me.
I'm sorry about that. Sorry.
See you later.
He always followed her around, and now he's at her house.
What about Ha Jin?
What happened? Did you catch him?
Well, it was Reporter Park Soo Chang.
You know him, right?
The one who released the exclusive on your love scandals.
What about Anchor Lee? Is he all right?
Yes, Anchor Lee.
Yes, Chul just told me.
Where are you?
I'm still in front of your house.
Hello?
Why haven't you left?
I was about to.
I was worried about you.
What were you going to do by running after him like that?
If he really was someone evil, could you have dealt with him?
Am I not that trustworthy?
That's not the case.
It's dangerous, that's why.
Don't do that from now on.
I'm more scared of seeing you get hurt than a stalker.
Go inside.
You need to go in for me to go home.
Okay.
And...
forget about what I told you just now.
I made it sound serious, but it's not that big of a deal.
It's not like I'm awfully ill...
or have trouble in my day-to-day life.
You're right. It's not a big deal.
I can say that as the one who went through this,
but you make it sound so easy just because it's not your problem.
Of course, you should forget about things of the past.
Memories are...
supposed to lose color and fade away as time goes by.
So don't feel tormented or try hard to remember the past.
What's important is the here and now.
Thank you...
for many things.
And don't let what happened to your friend get to you.
I don't know what happened,
but it's not your fault.
That stalker is the one who's bad.
Then I'll go back in.
Go home safely.
And text me when you get home.
Okay.
I'm home.
You're here.
Yes.
Let me print it out right away.
Soo Chang just called me...
and asked me to put in a good word for him.
I heard you took his entire memory card.
- Are you two close? - No, not at all.
Why?
He's a bit of a delinquent.
He says it's exciting and thrilling to infringe on celebrities' privacy.
He hides in women's waiting room, in restrooms,
and he was sued many times for breaking and entering.
It's just that everyone dropped the suit.
And he threatened them with the pictures he took.
Here.
It was really tough for me to get these.
Anyway, do you suspect that those two could be...
the one who sent those pictures?
(Personal Information: Moon Chul)
(3 minutes on foot)
Managers often live nearby.
It gets too hard to drive around.
Jeong Hoon, aren't you a little too sensitive?
The pictures came just once...
and nothing happened ever since that time.
Nothing happened so far.
But what if something breaks out?
Then it'll be too late already.
Let me know if you need me to do anything else.
(Moon Chul, Park Soo Chang)
Ms. Park! What's all this?
I just brought some side dishes.
We could've come by.
You didn't have to come all the way here.
I'll take it.
Why did you bring so much stuff?
Stop starving yourself to keep your body in shape.
You need to eat well, then work it out.
Those are just the appetizers.
My real business is something else.
I came to give you this.
A script?
("Hello, Everyone" by Hwang So Seon)
Is this Writer Hwang's?
Writer Hwang So Seon?
No way. You're right.
I want to do this. I will. I really want to.
You don't even know what your role is.
That doesn't matter. It's Writer Hwang.
I want to do this no matter what.
Tell her right now.
What if someone else takes it?
I told them you'd do it as soon as I received the script.
No way. No way! I'm so exhilarated!
It was my wish to work with her.
What's her role? She's the lead actress, right?
Of course, she is.
I got goosebumps when I read it.
Your character is a news anchor.
"News anchor"?
"Hello, Viewers."
Doesn't it seem like fate?
Even Writer Hwang thought so.
She said you were perfect for this role.
- Really? - Yes.
It suits you.
She doesn't worry about the tone of your voice...
since Anchor Lee can teach you.
The writing and directing teams...
would like to receive advice from him.
Is that okay?
From Anchor Lee?
She'd like to meet him right away.
Can you ask him when he's free?
Does Anchor Lee need to be there?
Yes. It'll be Writer Hwang, the director, Ha Jin, and him.
What if he can't attend?
You know how busy he is.
He should still do it.
After all, his girlfriend will be taking the lead role...
for the first time.
The drama is also from the same broadcasting station,
and Ha Jin's in it.
Wouldn't it be strange to ask another news anchor...
other than him for help?
Well, I guess.
Don't tell me you got in a fight.
Try to get along. This is an important period of your life.
Don't ruin your hard-earned reputation.
Okay?
Hey, do you have ramyeon?
Okay.
What's wrong? Is the script boring?
It's very...
"Very"?
Interesting.
"Interesting"?
It's the most interesting script I've ever read.
I must do this. If not, I'll regret it forever.
Okay, let's do it.
But what about Anchor Lee?
Do you think he'll help you with your tone, give advice,
and play a cameo role?
No.
"I don't like to do those things."
I bet he'll say this.
I thought there was romance between you two.
There is but...
They wouldn't remove me from the drama...
just because he refused to give advice, right?
That's ridiculous. Being a cast is serious business.
But do try to ask him.
It'll be better if the director and the writer like you.
Right.
Yes, I bet he'll do it.
He's been nice to me lately.
- Really? - Yes, he'll say yes.
He probably will.
Right? What do you think?
What do you think?
We're here.
Oh, my.
You've both aged quite a bit.
Still, let me hug you.
Do we need to do this every time I come here?
What do you think? It's obvious.
Happy birthday.
Why are you so thin? Are you sick?
Do I look slimmer?
That's great. I'm working out a lot these days.
Move aside, now.
- Let me give you a hug. - Hello, ma'am.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's eat.
- Thank you for the meal. - Sure.
I heard you're seeing someone.
Bring her home. The sooner, the better.
It's about time you got married.
It's still too early for that.
How long are you going to live like that?
That's enough, honey. Let's eat first.
They'll have indigestion.
Eat up.
- Okay. - Okay.
All right. Eat up.
Enjoy your meal.
("Hello, Everyone" by Hwang So Seon)
Thank you for the meal, ma'am. Your cooking skills have improved.
You really love soy sauce marinated crab, don't you?
How could you finish three bowls of that?
Is your stomach okay?
I need to take this.
Hello?
Where are you? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you have any favors you want to ask of me?
No, I don't. Why?
Think carefully. I'm willing to do anything.
Do you want to ask me for a favor?
Yes.
What is it?
I can't tell you just yet.
You must do it for me.
You can't say no.
So think carefully.
Who knows? You may need my help in the future.
I'll call you again later.
Okay.
Gosh, that was short.
I wouldn't have minded had you talked longer.
Tell me.
How did you two meet?
How long has it been?
How is she?
I saw her on TV often. How is she in real life?
Slow down.
Don't avoid my question.
Do tell me, will you?
It's not true.
What do you mean?
The articles are incorrect.
It's complicated.
Ha Jin's movie is being shown in theaters right now,
so we decided to wait until they took it down.
That's all.
We're not dating.
I see.
I guess this is just one of those fake dating rumors...
that you see on TV often.
You even fooled me.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
You're here early.
- Good morning. - Hello.
All right.
- Here. - What is all this?
I usually skip breakfast.
You need to have breakfast if you want to be healthy.
Here.
I have a favor to ask.
I didn't bite it yet.
It's not much.
Could you be the narrator...
for the founding anniversary special documentary?
- Me? - You and Ha Jin.
Why her?
Why do you think? You're a couple.
It's a documentary about wolves' instincts...
and their majestic love.
It'd be great if an actual couple narrated.
I thought you two wouldn't last that long,
but you're still standing strong.
You know we're faking it. Stop trying to get us together.
My gosh.
Can you just do it?
The company invested hundreds of thousands of dollars.
Let's make it interesting and add some commercials to it.
There's no harm in getting higher ratings.
We should give you a new nickname.
Ratings Fairy.
You...
No, we need to do well.
After what you said to Chairman Oh,
Hwarang took back all their commercials.
I'm not saying you were wrong.
That's just the current situation.
Just sound them out a bit...
and humor them a little. Simple, right?
You do know how much respect I have for you, right?
Yes, and I'm honored.
So shut it and have some.
Just do me this favor, will you?
Okay, I'll do it. I think it'll be fun.
You don't need to make a decision right now. You can say no too.
No, it's okay. Remember what I said?
I'm willing to do you any favors.
So please do me a favor as well.
I won't misunderstand you. I don't have any ulterior motives.
I just truly want to do this drama.
After becoming an actress,
I auditioned for Writer Hwang every single time.
I never got in.
This only happens once in a blue moon.
Fine, but I won't be a part of it.
Okay. I'll tell them so.
They can ask for my advice through email.
And I'll only help you with reading the news.
That's enough. I won't take much of your time.
All right. Let me know once the meeting is scheduled.
Thank you!
Hold on.
That didn't mean anything.
I hugged you because I was happy.
Okay.
Hello. Good day.
- Where is it? - Here.
Right here.
It's the same envelope.
The envelope is the same color without the sender's address.
(Don't get the wrong idea. Ha Jin loves me.)
Seo Yeon.
It's snowing a lot now.
Aren't you glad that you listened to me and took an umbrella?
Right.
It's snowing a lot today.
Hello?
Don't you know me?
We met several times with Seo Yeon.
Who is this?
Who is this? Why are you answering Seo Yeon's phone?
Don't get the wrong idea.
Seo Yeon loves me.
Not you, Jeong Hoon.
Seo Yeon.
I don't think Jeong Hoon believes me.
- Hello? - Right.
Seo Yeon, you should talk to him.
Hey.
Hold on.
Hello?
Don't hang up the phone.
Seo Yeon.
- Jeong... - Tell him.
Tell him that you love me, not him. Isn't that right?
- Tell him. - Seo Yeon, are you all right?
Please...
spare me.
Hello? Seo Yeon.
What are you talking about, Seo Yeon? Why would I kill you?
Don't you know that I love you so much?
We can be happy together now.
You love me, don't you?
Right?
Jeong Hoon!
Seo Yeon. Are you okay?
- It's all right. - Seo Yeon, where are you?
Answer me, Seo Yeon.
Hey.
I brought a gift for you.
- Seo Yeon. - Okay?
- Are you okay, Seo Yeon? Seo Yeon! - I made this while studying.
Seo Yeon!
- No! - Seo Yeon.
Are you okay, Seo Yeon? Seo Yeon!
Jeong Hoon, save me.
- Save me, Jeong Hoon! - Where are you?
Jeong Hoon!
- Seo Yeon. - Seo Yeon!
Please get yourself together, Seo Yeon!
- Don't do that! - You scumbag.
If you lay a finger on her,
I'm going to kill you! Got that?
- Jeong Hoon. - This is all your fault.
Seo Yeon changed all because of you.
It's all your fault,
Lee Jeong Hoon!
(Seo Yeon)
Where is she?
There you go. That's it.
It's all right. You'll be okay.
You're okay.
One more step. Let's take one more step.
Don't move. Stay still.
Please stay still, Seo Yeon!
That's it. Good girl.
Good.
Seo Yeon, this will be over soon.
Don't worry.
Seo Yeon.
There he is. He's here.
He's here. He came.
(Seo Yeon)
Wait for me there.
Seo Yeon.
Seo Yeon. Are you okay?
Stay with me, Seo Yeon!
Seo Yeon.
Seo Yeon, stay with me.
Stay with me.
Hold on.
I'm going to call the ambulance now.
Seo Yeon, stay with me.
Seo Yeon.
No. Don't. No, stay with me.
Seo Yeon, stay with me. Please stay with me!
I'm sorry.
Seo Yeon.
No. Please don't. No, Seo Yeon.
Seo Yeon, open your eyes. Seo Yeon! Open your eyes.
Open your eyes, Seo Yeon!
Lee Jeong Hoon!
You came sooner than I expected.
You jerk.
Why did it have to be Seo Yeon?
Why did it have to be Seo Yeon? Why?
Why? Why?
Why her?
Why?
Why did it have to be Seo Yeon?
Why would you ask me that?
What do you mean why it had to be Seo Yeon?
It was you...
who broke us up, Lee Jeong Hoon.
- What? - You.
It's all right, though.
No one can come between us now.
We will be...
together eternally.
Put that down!
Let go! Let me go!
Lee Jeong Hoon!
Lee Jeong Hoon! Lee Jeong...
Where are you going?
(Quarantine Treatment Room 1: Moon Seong Ho)
(Find Me in Your Memory)
- I caused a bit of an accident. - Like what?
Ha Jin found out.
If it's okay with you, may I checked the footage?
The security footage?
Does he always run late? Your manager, I mean.
I always told you...
that you'll also play the lead role of my next movie, Ha Jin.
I can't do this movie.
I'm sorry, Director Ji.
No, I'm telling you to read it now.
To be honest, I'm nervous...
that things will get out of our hands.
Don't do anything you'll regret.
We can't do this.
- Why not? - Because we'll regret it.
Don't blame me for this.
It's all because of you.