I am crazy.
I am, but...
are you confident?
Can you really treat me?
You are not crazy.
You're in pain.
If you just admit that
you're in pain,
you can be treated.
It looks like
you also have a sickness.
An occupational sickness.
Everyone you meet
must seem like patients to you.
But you see, I'm not in pain.
I just have a nasty temper.
Thank you for the offer,
but I'll take care of myself.
Goodbye.
What kind of a doctor
gathers his own patients?
Maybe I should've told him
that I'm already seeing a doctor.
Ms. Han refused to get treated.
I think it's going to take
some time.
(Ji Young Won)
So what if it takes some time?
It's fine as long as
you don't give up.
A bad doctor isn't someone
who's incompetent.
It's someone who gives up.
You know that, right?
What's with the blackmailing?
(Episode 5)
Hello.
Did you sleep well?
Go. Go away.
Go.
- Go away.
- Last night,
he didn't sleep a wink.
Go.
Go. Go away.
Do you still eat nothing but snacks?
Just give me my medicine.
Don't bother asking me questions.
If you keep refusing to talk,
you won't be able to get treated.
Hello.
Did Dr. Park call you?
You too?
I wonder why he needs us.
It's probably regarding
an emergency patient.
Sung Min Ho. 32 years old. Male.
A few days ago, he came to the ER
due to abdominal pain.
The gastroscopy and X-ray showed...
a foreign substance in his stomach,
so they took him straight to the OR.
And it turns out he had pica.
(Pica: An eating disorder where one
craves things that are not food)
Sir, what was the foreign substance
that was found in his stomach?
Paper.
(Sung Min Ho)
He swallowed an entire house.
I think I know this patient.
How?
Sung Min Ho!
Dad... Dad.
You pathetic punk.
What is the matter with you?
When will you become a decent human?
I'm... I'm sorry.
He looked very nervous.
I want you to treat this patient.
Okay, sir.
How is Hwang Bo Young?
I've prescribed her
some drugs for now.
The antihistamine cyproheptadine...
is said to suppress serotonin...
to control satiety and
increase one's appetite,
so I'm looking into that.
I'm also carrying out psychotherapy,
but I haven't been able to
get a conversation going.
Keep an eye on the patient anyway.
I will.
Keep up the good work.
Yes, sir.
- Bye.
- I'm off too.
- Okay.
- Good job.
- You too.
He really ate a lot.
Where is he now?
I was getting ready to leave...
when I was told to go to Psychiatry.
I was surprised.
Why? Do you feel uncomfortable?
Rather than feel uncomfortable,
it's more like I don't get why.
Did you eat paper?
That's called pica...
and it's an eating disorder.
It's caused by feelings of
depression or anxiety.
I'd like to have a chat.
Do you eat paper often?
It was the first time.
How did it taste?
I've never tried it.
Every kind is different.
They have different textures.
There's a slightly sweet taste.
You know well considering
it was your first try.
Do you have a super palate?
- Why did you eat it?
- Because...
I guess...
I was curious as to how it tasted.
Something happened right before?
Can you tell me what?
I work at a paper craft company.
We make miniature buildings
out of paper...
and supply them to
paper museums or model houses.
I think that's when I felt hungry.
It was meant to be
handed in that day.
- Who did this?
- What happened?
- My gosh.
- Who did this?
- What happened to it?
- We worked so hard on it.
- I know.
- It's a mess.
Was it you? Did you do it?
You psycho. Are you crazy?
- What?
- What's wrong?
- I couldn't breathe and...
- Min Ho!
I fainted.
What is your father like?
My dad?
I respect him more than
anyone in the world.
He started from nothing
and succeeded.
Someone like me
can never even reach his feet.
When will I become a decent human?
I feel guilty
towards my dad all the time.
I saw in the photo that
you'd swallowed the house whole.
Why is that?
What if it got stuck in your throat?
I didn't want to chew the house.
Then it would become damaged.
But one morning the fog was dense
And we were dragged away
By men with swords
We didn't know why
or where we were going
No one told us anything
Just like our country
Your singing's good and you can act,
but your scandal bothers me.
Try again once it has died down.
What a load of nonsense!
Hey, I heard
you're putting on a show.
Do you need an actress?
I won the Best Female Newcomer.
What do you mean
why did I accept it?
Why should I refuse the award?
What did I do wrong?
How dare you say that to me?
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
- Can we order?
- Just a moment, please.
Can we have some water?
You have to get it yourself. Sorry.
- Is our food not ready yet?
- It's coming.
I'm coming.
I'll take your order.
- Two spicy stir-fried pork.
- Two spicy pork.
Do you want some water?
- Which table?
- Number two.
Okay.
- Can we order extra?
- Here you go.
Give me a moment.
Something happened today.
Sung Min Ho!
I didn't want to chew the house.
Then it would become damaged.
Hey.
Sung Min Ho was
treated for anxiety three years ago.
Caused by what?
Fear of his father.
If it was three years ago,
wouldn't he be cured by now?
We should say it got worse.
Pica occurs mostly in...
children aged 1 to 4, not adults.
Whenever Sung Min Ho
becomes anxious,
he stutters...
and chews on his fingernails.
They're all symptoms
commonly found in children.
I say the pica is
connected to his anxiety.
What's more is that the reason
he swallowed the house whole...
was due to attachment.
We should assume
he was traumatized as a child.
In this case, the person
who actually needs treatment...
is the person who caused
the trauma, not the victim.
Dr. Lee. What do you mean by that?
To treat Sung Min Ho,
we must treat his father first.
How can we treat a man
who never comes in?
Figuring out a way to do that...
is your job, isn't it?
Hi, Ji Sun, it's me.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
It's been a while, Dr. Lee.
It has, hasn't it?
- Woo Joo, you're here too?
- Yes.
Is she the musical actress
from last...
Yes, that's me.
I lost my job because of that
and now I work here.
I apologize.
Will you join us
if you haven't eaten yet?
Part-timers
don't eat with customers.
What will you have?
Come by again.
I'm sorry, but we're closed.
We won't stay for long.
We're out of ingredients.
- I apologize.
- We'll eat real quick.
When you come next time,
I'll give you a lot of extra food.
- It's her, right?
- Who?
Aren't you the musical actress?
Yes. I'm Han Woo Joo.
You're just fine.
After being humiliated like that,
I don't think I'd ever
appear in public.
But then, people
should be thick-skinned.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Bye.
I didn't drink and drive.
As if you didn't.
I saw you get handcuffed on live TV.
He wasn't a real policeman.
I didn't do it!
Are you out of your mind?
- Why did you scream?
- That's enough.
I didn't do it.
Get your facts straight
before you talk.
Have you lost your mind?
Will you hit me?
Do you want to hit me?
Hit me so I can
make some money off you!
- Let go!
- Don't!
Hit me!
- Jong Hoon!
- Step aside.
Sir. Hey. Shouldn't we call 911?
Everything will be fine.
Don't worry.
Go home safely.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you for the food.
Bye.
What if that customer
got a concussion?
I just got really angry.
Sorry.
Do you think we don't know
how to get angry?
You really need to do something
about that temper of yours.
You already got in so much trouble
because of your temper.
You already lost so many people.
I tried really hard
to hold it in today.
It burst because I couldn't
hold it in anymore.
You don't get counseling
these days, do you?
Do you also think I'm a patient?
What is the matter with everyone?
Hey.
Hey, I should be the one mad at you!
What did I do wrong?
Everything was fine
up until you brought it up.
Why would you ask
about her counseling?
I'm just worried about her.
A lot of things must've
made you angry today.
How did you know?
By the strength in your arms.
Bam.
Did you fail your audition?
Are you a shaman?
Ever since I was young,
people told me
I have a real good hunch.
Are all psychiatrists like you?
No, not at all. I'm very unique.
Gosh, what a bunch of fools.
Your singing touches so many people.
But they don't even know that.
Right?
Have you ever heard me sing?
No.
You really are unique.
- What is this?
- A gift.
Open it at home.
The hospital is always open.
You know that, right?
You can come whenever you want.
Oh, goodness.
I'm sorry. I really have
an occupational sickness.
Forget what I just said.
You really are persistent.
(Prescription)
Prescription. Exercise at night.
What is this?
What am I doing?
(Nursing Home)
Hello?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Dad! Dad!
Si Joon?
Yes, it's me.
Gosh, look at yourself.
Aren't you cold?
I'm cold. It's freezing.
It's cold.
Sir!
Sir, where are you?
- Sir!
Sir!
He still does rounds twice a day.
Our patients ask for your father
instead of me.
They think of him
as a very skilled doctor.
A while ago,
he recognized me.
He gets his memory back
very frequently these days.
And he tries to escape
every time that happens.
How is the patient that my dad
almost tried to do surgery on?
He's at the nearby hospital.
Thank goodness
he only needed stitches.
Things could've
really gotten out of hand.
We can't keep our eyes on him
every minute of the day.
But it's not like we can
tie him up either.
I'm so sorry.
Who are you?
Are you the new resident?
What are you doing here?
Hurry up and get ready for rounds.
What are you doing, you fool?
You don't need...
to do rounds today, sir.
What?
I already checked on
all the patients.
Everyone is fine.
How arrogant of you.
Who do you think you are?
We haven't had
a smart doctor like you in a while.
It'd be great if my son
was also smart like you.
He's a doctor, too.
I guess he became a doctor
because of you.
He'll never be as great as me.
Do you know why?
Because he's just a psychiatrist.
Meanwhile, I'm a magician.
My son never satisfied me.
I should've stopped him
when I had the chance.
Would you like to be my son instead?
Don't you want to?
I can even give you all my wealth.
I guess you have a lot of money.
No, I don't have any money.
Money isn't my wealth.
These hands are my wealth.
Those hands really were something.
Everyone agreed to that.
I always envied you as well.
Dad.
We cut a part of his brother's liver
and transplanted it into his body.
That's how we managed
to overcome the rejection.
Currently, it's been four weeks
since he got the transplant.
And he's still very healthy.
That is all.
(The First Success Case of a New
Organ Transplantation Method)
Dad!
Gosh, it's cold. It's freezing.
(Episode 6)
Are you taking your medication?
I did, then I threw up.
Why do you torture yourself?
Because I'm what Mom
treasures the most.
Ruining what one values the most
hurts that person.
Ms. Hwang. If you keep this up,
the extreme malnutrition and
hormonal disorder will ruin you,
and possibly even your brain.
If torturing your mother
is your purpose,
how about we find another way?
Is there a security camera in here?
No. You can speak freely.
You know...
Did you just assault me?
I can post it on social media.
- Ms. Hwang!
- Tell my mom.
That I don't need to see a doctor.
I really don't want to
come here. I hate it!
Sexual assault?
She did as her mom said
for 25 years.
She ate and wore as she was told.
She went to the university
she was told to go to.
Then she suddenly exploded.
And she chose to abuse herself.
I think she needs to focus on
psychotherapy first.
Anorexia patients
secrete excess endorphins.
Because they're happier when
they starve than when they eat.
I think the deficient
happy hormones...
are being paradoxically
supplemented by the starving.
That's an interesting hypothesis.
That hypothesis
could explain why people...
get addicted to starving.
So you'll redistribute her hormones
with medication?
Yes. And psychotherapy will follow.
I look forward to it.
Your pica patient's symptoms
were caused by the fear of his dad?
My approach could help him as well.
Early this morning,
I went to see my dad.
I realized only today
how small he actually is.
On my way back,
I wondered how my dad
ended up like that.
Everyone becomes
small and old with age.
Why did I try to avoid him
all my life?
I don't know what happened to
Sung Min Ho,
but maybe this is what
he needs to find out.
- Thanks.
- Dr. Lee.
I just got a call that Sung Min Ho
canceled his appointment.
Who gave permission?
Would you like some?
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thanks.
The food here looks amazing.
It's quite a spread.
Is it always like this?
Dr. Lee.
Wh-What are you do-doing here?
Are you flustered?
You're stuttering.
You canceled your appointment,
so I came over
in case you were busy.
A change of scenery helps
shift things around sometimes.
Let's eat. I'm hungry.
This is lovely.
I'm full and the weather's great.
How tall is your father?
Why do you ask?
You don't know?
What size shoes does he wear?
I guess you two aren't close.
You don't know much about him.
My dad's no-not my friend.
We ca-can't be cl-close.
I should re-respect him.
Let's fix your stutter first.
This wasn't the first time
you ate paper.
When was the first time?
Why...
Why are you do-doing this to me?
Because I want to treat you.
Why?
Because I'm a doctor
and you're my patient.
I know that you tried
immensely hard to fix yourself.
I bet you saw doctors...
and looked yourself
in the mirror to stop.
You said last time that...
you didn't want to chew the house.
I know what that feels like.
At one time,
I feared my father
more than anyone in the world.
Trust me.
Ca-Can you...
re-really...
fi-fix me?
Are you still angry?
No.
I was going to come and help out.
Forget that. Do you know
the musical "Cinderella"?
The director of music is my senior.
I mentioned you to them
and they want to cast you.
Are you sure?
It's not that big a role.
Hey! Come on.
Why didn't you tell me that
you had such connections?
Thank you. I won't forget
what you did for me.
Are you that pleased?
I didn't just grow on my own
I didn't
Every breath I took was a sigh
Where is your love?
There is a thing as destiny
- Of course!
Are you waiting for
your prince charming?
That's how the world is
Your first love is waiting for you
That's what I'm looking for
Let's go!
To the right!
To the left!
This way!
Now it's time to dance!
- This is your destiny
Okay, let's take a 10-minute break.
- Thank you.
- You guys have improved.
Excuse me.
Oh, Ms. Han.
Ji Sun told me about you.
We're just a small ensemble group.
Are you okay with that?
Of course. I'm ready to do anything.
I'm sure you're talented
since you even won...
the Best Female Newcomer Award.
Can you practice right away?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
You should thank Ji Sun.
I agreed to her offer
since she promised...
we can always
hold our team dinners there.
What?
You didn't know?
I guess you really didn't know.
Oh, then...
Then you're letting me work here
because Ji Sun promised you...
that you can eat free
at her restaurant?
Well, I guess that's what you call
helping each other out.
Excuse me, but...
I can't work this way.
I won't do it.
Even if I was humiliated
in front of the whole nation...
and fired from my previous job,
I'm not cheap enough to be
used like this for free food.
What do you think you're doing?
I went through hoops
to persuade our producer.
Anyhow, I won't do it.
You failed all your auditions,
yet you still don't know your place.
I do know my place.
That's why I won't do it.
You really are a lunatic,
just like the rumors.
Look here.
Do you think you failed
your auditions...
merely because of drunk driving?
You're totally mistaken.
It's because you're a total lunatic.
Don't you know everyone
in this field knows that?
If felt as if
I was staring at someone else.
When I saw my reflection,
I saw someone whom
I had never seen before.
Why do you think
I suddenly felt that way?
Maybe you wanted to deny
your recent life.
I didn't know...
I made people feel so uncomfortable.
After I got mad, I was always
the first to apologize.
Even if it wasn't my fault.
And everyone said it was okay.
But I guess they didn't mean it.
No matter how small it is,
getting rid of a wound
is not as easy as you think.
I guess I really am a lunatic.
Dr. Ji. I'm thinking of
leaving this field for a while.
Do you have plans on what you'll do?
Someone offered me
a part-time job.
What kind of job is it?
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, my gosh.
Did you come to see me?
Yes.
Let's go inside.
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
Did you make up your mind?
About what?
Didn't you come here
to receive treatment?
- No.
- Then?
The part-time job you mentioned
last time.
I'm wondering if the offer
still stands.
You know, stage therapy, was it?
Yes, you're right. Stage therapy.
I still think of
acting in front of Cha Dong Il...
from time to time.
Strangely, it made me feel better.
I want to try it.
Can't I?
This is perfect.
I was concerned about it anyway.
You are my savior.
Really? I'm so glad.
These are some materials
on stage therapy.
- Can you start right away?
- Of course.
What's the big deal of
letting them eat for free here?
Are you doing charity or something?
That's what you're good at.
What about my pride?
Didn't you think about that?
I thought it was more important
for you to get up on stage.
Since you can protect your pride
only when you're on stage.
I appreciate the gesture.
But I'm not even going to go near
that place for now.
What are you talking about?
I've decided to work part-time
at the hospital.
What will you do there?
- Stage therapy.
- What is that?
People with illnesses
all have trauma.
It's a way to find what it is
by acting out a certain situation.
It's hard for me too.
Is this the time for you
to be like this?
Good job. You did well.
What are you talking about?
Stop getting mad.
They're all like that at their age.
Just leave me alone!
I'll live as I please!
How dare you talk back to
your mom?
Do you want to die?
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
You want to go to college?
I told you that you can't go.
I don't have money to afford that.
Do you think I'm filthy rich
or something?
You don't even want to go to
law school like your older brother.
As long as you live wisely,
you can become successful
like me...
even if you don't go to college.
How can someone like you
think of going to college?
Hey. With the money
to send you to college,
I'd rather buy your brother
a nice meal.
Stop thinking of
meaningless things...
and get a grip!
Min Ho, don't you have
something you want to say?
Don't hold back and say it.
Someone like me?
What kind of person is that?
You don't know?
My gosh, you idiot.
I raised you alone all this time
without even your mom.
You should be grateful
and live a proper life.
Is there even something
you're good at?
Are you even interested...
in what I'm good at?
Dad.
I'm a person.
I'm a person too.
I'm your son too!
Yes, you are a son too.
Say it bravely.
Don't you have something to say
to your dad? Go on and say it.
Why do you only look at my brother?
Why can't you see me?
I'm not a ghost.
Stop treating me like I'm invisible.
Be more specific.
He can't understand you.
When I was 12,
you don't know I ran away
from home...
because I was so lonely, do you?
I thought you'd look for me, Dad.
I wandered the streets for a week,
then returned home because
I couldn't take it anymore.
Dad...
You didn't even know I'd been gone.
My brother had won some award,
and you took just him
out for dinner!
I was so hungry...
but there was nothing to eat.
So I ate...
tissue soaked in water.
I ate it because...
I wanted to die then and there!
People who hurt each other...
usually aren't strangers.
Like family, lovers, or friends,
they are usually closer than anyone.
- Wasn't that cool?
- Yes.
It was incredible.
I guess this could be a hit.
Dr. In.
Hello.
Ms. Han. You did so very well today.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
- See you.
- Dr. In.
We're going for a drink.
Would you like to join us?
Next time.
Okay then.
Let's go.
A human brain has
about 100 billion nerve cells,
and the neurotransmitters from them
alter our conscious state.
No way.
Adrenaline is secreted
when we're stressed,
and oxytocin strengthens
our bond with others.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Shall we drink?
- Yes.
- Sure!
- Great job.
- Well done!
Dopamine wakes us up,
and GABA calms us down.
Oh? How are you? My gosh.
My question is,
how do these neurotransmitters
come to be?
I'm home.
It comes from your feelings.
Where are your feelings or mind?
In ancient times, people believed
the mind was in the brain.
Some thought it was on
the diaphragm or under the ribs.
People use the phrase
"to be broken-hearted".
Maybe they thought
it was in the heart.
Greek philosophers said
the mind was non-material,
so it didn't exist in the body
as flesh and blood.
That's why they said
it doesn't die with the body either.
I agree with the Greek philosophers.
So the mind is the soul,
and I'm a repairman.
I'm sorry for calling you over.
I was going to hire a driver,
but I had something to tell you too.
It's fine. We go in
the same direction.
You know Hwang Bo Young, right?
She's your patient.
Do you know her too?
Yes. She's practically
a hospital family.
You didn't know.
I didn't.
How are you treating her?
I don't think she's taking
the medicine I prescribed.
We're not getting anywhere.
Shouldn't psychotherapy come first
when treating anorexia?
I'm doing both at the same time.
Anorexia can't be cured.
You know, don't you?
I do.
Don't you think anorexia should be
treated with Si Joon's method?
I'm sure you'll do what's best,
but people we know personally
tend to pick on minute details.
I trust you, of course.
You know that, right?
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
(List of Outpatients)
(Outpatient record)
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
Okay, I understand.
Sure.
The meeting for patients
with eating disorders.
It's today.
Ask if Ms. Hwang Bo Young
can attend.
Okay, I will. Bye.
What is it?
Why is Dr. In suddenly
interested in stage therapy?
(Jinseo Trading)
Let's go inside.
Do I really have to meet my dad?
There's something
you want to say to him.
You must say it in person.
See a psychiatrist?
I guess you're spoiled.
Do we have money to waste?
There's something Min Ho
really wishes to say to you.
Would you like to hear him out?
If you want to talk,
be quick. I'm busy.
Min Ho.
Dad.
When I was 10 years old,
you woke me up and scolded me.
For stealing money from your wallet.
I kept saying it wasn't me,
but you told me not to lie.
It really wasn't me.
I really didn't steal your money.
You crazy...
Did you come here to say that?
That was years ago.
I felt wronged.
Until now,
that stayed with me right here.
I felt wronged!
You pathetic fool.
Your older brother told me that
he took the money.
Why do you still
hold that inside at your age?
That's why you're the mess you are.
You're just the same as you were.
When will you grow up?
Dr. Lee.
My dad...
has dentures.
I didn't think he'd have that.
You had no idea?
I never imagined it.
All the dads in the world...
become smaller,
their hair turn white,
and they lose teeth.
Your father isn't
the scary man he used to be.
I won't tell you to understand him.
The treatment begins now.
We'll start by building up
the self-esteem you lost.
Okay.
Before we begin, let's
close our eyes for a few seconds...
and feel the air in this room.
Ms. Han Woo Joo's here too.
I guess she's here to help.
I'm excited.
You can open your eyes now.
You all look a bit brighter.
Shall we begin, then?
You first.
I have anorexia nervosa.
I was a model,
but I gain weight...
even when I drink water.
I got stressed out that...
I'd become too fat to work,
and now I feel afraid
just looking at food.
It's a load of nonsense that
water makes you gain weight.
Why would people in Africa starve...
if water would make them fat?
Thank you for sharing.
How about you?
I'm being treated for
binge eating...
while looking for a job.
I applied to over 100 jobs so far,
and that's how
I started binge eating.
Once I start to eat, I can't stop.
Whenever I see food,
I must shove it in my mouth...
and chew to feel better.
If you keep that weight on,
you'll never get a job.
What are you... Don't say that.
You two.
Thanks so much
for having the courage to share.
How about a round of applause?
What do you have?
Anorexia.
I eat, puke, eat, puke.
Why is that?
My mom treats me like I'm a doll.
But I'm not a doll.
So, to show my mom
I'm not a doll,
I throw up in front of her.
I do that to torture her.
You're so spoiled.
What?
You don't know what's precious.
Torturing your mom is your goal?
What do you know to say that?
I was abused!
You're being childish!
Dr. In. They might end up fighting.
Some people crave that
all their lives.
Shouldn't we stop them?
The streets are
full of people who try...
so darn hard to get noticed
while nobody cares!
So don't do something
you'll regret...
and live your life properly
and be grateful for it.
How about a round of applause?
Woo Joo. You're done already?
I was hoping to watch. I'm too late.
How did it go today?
What's wrong?
Is something the matter?
I'm sorry. I ruined everything.
What?
I don't think I can do this.
I apologize.
(Stairwell)
Some people crave that
all their lives.
Welcome.
I'd like fried chicken, please.
Will you keep coming here?
I haven't yet found a place
that sells chicken this good.
I adopted you then abandoned you.
Why do you keep
coming here to see me?
Do you do this on purpose?
To make me feel bad?
From when I was 6 until I turned 12.
You raised me for six years.
I miss you sometimes, Mom.
I'm not your mom.
Mom.
Back then.
I'm really sorry about that.
Stop it.
I forgot the past because
I'm busy making a living.
Leave when you're done.
Woo Joo. What are you doing here?
How did you find this place?
I thought I'd never
get to tell you if not now.
You're right.
I'm a patient.
Please treat me.
You can, can't you?
(Fix You)
Woo Joo. You changed
other people's lives.
Hey!
Hand him over to Dong Hyuk.
He's my patient.
You ignored all protocols.
Why are you
so obsessed with the patient?
Hey, hey. Hey!
Why do you still wear
the watch I gave you?
What if Han Woo Joo is borderline?
We'll carry out
a search and seizure.
Do you have any idea
why they had a warrant?
Someone planned this.
A burial or drowning. Which one?
- Or a cremation?
- What?