(Episode 7)
Woo Joo.
What are you doing here?
How did you find this place?
I thought I'd never get to tell you if not now.
You're right.
I'm a patient.
Please treat me.
You can, can't you?
You see,
I don't have a family,
and Ji Sun is my one and only friend.
I never got along with anyone I met on stage.
They all hated me saying I had a bad temper.
And in order to make friends,
I sometimes stooped too low to please everyone.
I get why my boyfriend cheated on me.
You do too, don't you?
Who would want to be with a person like me?
Last time, you told me I can get treated...
as long as I admit that I'm sick.
Woo Joo.
- Yes? - I'm hungry.
Can we eat first?
I can't believe he's actually eating right now.
I didn't know you recorded podcasts.
What's that scar anyway?
There, on your wrist.
Oh, this?
I was just curious.
- Did you want to die? - No.
I never once thought that I wanted to die.
I always wanted to live.
Even when I failed every audition and suffered enough to die,
I wanted to live so that people would...
notice and love me.
I got this because I wanted to get noticed.
I didn't even use a knife.
I used a plastic ruler in case it hurt.
I got this scar because the ruler snapped.
Why did you want to be noticed so much?
Isn't everyone like that?
- Aren't you? - I'm not.
It's a huge nuisance when someone notices me.
What a show-off.
Do you remember Cha Dong Il?
How could I forget that fake cop?
You have no idea how hard he studies these days.
He goes to the library in rain and snow.
Isn't that amazing?
So what?
- How is that related to me? - How isn't it?
You helped change someone's life.
As if I helped.
Sung Min Ho had an anxiety disorder,
yet he was able to express what he'd kept inside all along...
because of you.
Woo Joo,
you aren't someone whose boyfriend is allowed to cheat on you.
You changed someone else's life.
There's no illness without a cause.
There must be a reason you always fight.
Let's high-five.
That randomly?
This is Day One.
I'm your doctor, you're my patient.
Don't become a bad doctor who gives up...
when it gets too hard to handle me.
Don't think of running away and do as I say.
I will.
The temperature will be similar to today or slightly higher.
The weather will remain clear for a few days.
That was the weather.
There were many incidents today.
Why don't you let go of your worries...
and see cherry blossoms...
- with your loved ones? - Cherry blossoms, my foot.
That's all for News 24.
- Wait. - Goodnight.
Why is he still wearing the watch I gave him?
(WBS News 24)
- Hello? - It's been a while.
Return the watch. You don't deserve to wear it.
You don't even know what kind of watch that is, don't you?
It shouldn't be on the wrist of a scumbag punk like you!
What?
"By courier"?
Do you have a death wish?
Forget it.
I'm coming over. Wait right where you are.
How dare he say he'll send it by courier?
It shouldn't be on the wrist of a scumbag punk like you!
Do you have a death wish?
What have I done?
I'm a psycho loser.
What is wrong with me?
- Did you want to die? - No.
I never once thought that I wanted to die.
I always wanted to live.
What makes her want to live that badly?
(Inpatient ward)
Keep an eye on him. Don't let him out of your sight.
New York, Paris, Tokyo, anywhere where I'm not going!
Anywhere, anywhere, I'm not going! Anywhere!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
Anywhere, I'm not going. Anywhere, I won't go.
Anywhere, I'm not going.
Will you just observe him?
Tokyo, anywhere, I'm not going.
The current medication isn't working.
Switch the prescription to...
an anti-psychotic with a stronger sedating effect.
Anywhere where I'm not going.
Give me the order and I'll take care of it now.
Give us a little time. Dr. Lee's on his way.
If he wakes the other patients, it'll only be more work for us.
Luo's positive symptoms are getting worse.
He'll end up not eating, sleeping,
and lie in bed like a corpse.
I'll tell Dr. Lee when he arrives.
Dr. Lee.
Tokyo, anywhere where I won't go.
Paris, Tokyo, anywhere, wherever I'm not going.
His visual hallucinations worsened.
- Shall we increase the dose? - Go! Go! Go! Anywhere...
Nurse Oh suggested we switch to another sedative.
You said he worsened.
Why increase if he got worse?
Dr. Lee. You must let him sleep.
He's been screaming at night for a few days now.
It's hard on the patient and us.
Anywhere, I'm not going!
His cognitive skills are worse too.
I'll take Luo out for a walk.
What? At this hour?
- Dr. Lee. - Evening walks aren't allowed.
The hospital prohibits nighttime walks.
I'll stay close to him.
If you take him out, it'll ruin his sleep schedule,
and he'll become harder to care for.
Paris, Tokyo, anywhere...
- Park Luo. - I'm not going!
Shall we go for a walk?
He seems to be in a better mood.
His room must be claustrophobic.
He first started to hallucinate...
in Korea when he lived in a tiny room.
His hospital room could've made his symptoms worse.
That's why you brought him out?
Why is there so much crammed into the head of a 15-year-old?
Dr. Lee, do you think it'll be okay to break the rules?
Nurse Oh seemed very angry.
That's why I suggested the walk.
Pardon?
She turns nasty whenever she sees me.
I wanted to escape.
- Luo! Luo! Oh, dear. - Luo!
Hey, Luo! Where are you going? Hey!
Luo!
If I catch you...
Luo, it's dangerous.
Luo, where are you going?
Watch the steps. They're dangerous!
Luo, stop! My gosh.
Hey! That punk.
Luo!
(Positive symptoms are getting worse.)
(Severe symptoms of visual hallucination)
(Decrease in cognitive functions)
The Medical Psychiatry Center will get built faster than planned.
Oh, really?
Dr. In, be honest with me.
Who do you think will be the first person to make director?
Can I really be honest, sir?
Of course.
I think Dr. Park will get appointed as the director.
That was too honest of you.
But I personally want you to be the director...
because I want the new medical center...
to implement your treatment methods.
And of course, that's probably because...
I'm currently following the path that you once took.
Do you really mean that?
You just saw how honest I was.
Then I'm going to need your help.
What do you need me to do?
Find Si Joon's weakness for me.
Give me something I can use to pressure Dr. Park.
The hospital director and Dr. Park graduated the same high school.
You didn't know that, did you?
No, sir. I didn't know.
I'm not trying to be the director because I want authority.
I'm a doctor, too.
I care about my patients as much as everyone else.
But if we continue to let Dr. Park and Si Joon do things their way,
the hospital will eventually shut down.
I don't think many of you know this,
but mental illnesses are contagious.
Look around us.
So many people are suffering from panic disorder.
And it'll only get worse with time.
We can't continue to handle things like Si Joon does.
Are you going to help me?
Yes, I'll help you, sir.
For the sake of the Medical Psychiatry Center.
Great.
Let's work hard for the mental health of our citizens.
Okay, I understand what you mean.
I'll talk to Dr. Lee about it.
I feel a little uneasy...
now that I've told you everything.
I understand that Dr. Lee cares a lot about his patients.
But there should be a limit.
Patients need to sleep at night, but he never sleeps.
I get what you mean.
I'm worried that the nurses working at the ward...
might start a protest or something.
Considering Luo's condition,
it's better to just give him sleeping pills so he could sleep.
He's about to turn into a zombie.
We should use a stronger...
Ma'am.
I understand what you mean.
But the doctor in charge has full authority...
over what he or she prescribes to the patient.
I must've crossed the line.
I'm sorry.
I'll be off now.
Hello, you're Luo's mother.
You want to have him discharged?
We need to go back to Vietnam.
If he goes to school there for another semester,
he can go to college through a special admission process...
for Koreans who reside abroad.
That's the main reason we lived abroad.
And I can't just give that up now.
Luo can't get discharged.
I have every right to take my son home.
Why can't he get discharged?
His condition got worse.
Why?
I'll have to look into it.
He was hospitalized for three months.
How could you let his condition get worse?
Three months is nothing compared to how long...
he's been discarded.
Are you saying...
he turned out this way because I discarded him?
Do you think I wanted him to stay in that tiny apartment room?
I had no idea that he was being called a returnee...
(Returnee: A student who returns to Korea...)
(for having failed to adjust abroad)
I didn't know that.
As his doctor,
I'm just saying he needs more time to receive proper treatment.
Dr. Lee.
Are you confident in curing my son?
I asked if you're confident.
- Everyone, follow me. - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
From now on...
- "From now on..." - "From now on..."
Forget about the painful past!
- "Forget about the painful past!" - "Forget about the painful past!"
And let's just have fun!
- "And let's just have fun!" - "And let's just have fun!"
Let's do this!
1, 2, 3, 4.
(Stage therapy room)
Nice.
Get ready.
Turn!
Woo Joo,
you aren't someone whose boyfriend is allowed to cheat on you.
You changed someone else's life.
No, I'm not confident.
And it's not like my confidence helps me treat my patients.
Today, I will listen to your stories and give you answers.
People are sending me their stories right now.
And here's one I just received.
I don't know when it began,
but I hear a voice whispering in my ear every day.
What drives me crazy is that I keep doing what I'm told...
even when I know it's an auditory hallucination.
Right now, I'm at Seogang Bridge.
And now, the voice is telling me to jump in front of a car.
Soul Repairman, please help me.
Hey, wait!
No! Hey!
Wait!
Unlike other schizophrenics,
Luo knows he hallucinates and hears things.
He also knows he is sick.
And therefore, he knows he needs to take medication.
The problem is...
that his body keeps denying the drugs.
That's where the side effects occur.
Then there's only one answer to the problem.
Dr. Lee.
What should I do, Dr. Lee? I made a huge mistake yesterday.
What did you do?
I couldn't focus on anything else in that very moment.
All I could see was that watch.
All I could think of was that he didn't deserve...
to wear that watch.
So you called him and asked him to give it back?
I didn't know I could be such a loser.
Because of that,
my self-esteem hit rock bottom,
and I even feel depressed.
Was it expensive?
Yes, very.
I got cast as the main character for the first time in my life,
and that's when I got it for him.
Come to think of it, it was very pathetic of me.
Why did I get him a watch when I was the one who got the role?
He should've been the one congratulating me.
After I bought him that, I was broke for a while.
So I went around looking like a homeless person.
I was suddenly reminded of that, and it made me furious.
I couldn't believe I went through all that just for that jerk.
You did great.
- What? - I want you...
to get that watch back.
If you have a grudge, you should resolve it.
Yes, I know.
But I'm being really pathetic.
It's normal to be pathetic when you break up with someone.
Make sure you get that watch, okay?
- Really? - Call me once you get it back.
(Eun Kang Hospital Medical Psychiatry Center)
What do you think? Do you like it?
The facility is already top-notch.
This is the first medical psychiatry center...
to be established by a university hospital in Korea.
And to be honest,
I'm very excited.
What are you excited about the most?
I'm excited at how this place can hold many more patients...
compared to our current ward.
The fact that we built a separate trauma center.
And the fact that we created a helpline to help prevent suicide.
I'm excited about everything.
Korea is filled with people who have hurtful memories.
You know I was at the scene of the accident...
during the September 11 attacks, right?
Yes, of course.
Back then,
the US government put in a lot of effort to build a trauma center.
They treated not only the survivors,
but they also treated the families of those that were missing.
I also received a lot of help from them.
But there's nothing like that in our country.
Bridges collapse, boats sink,
subways turn over,
and lots of other accidents occur.
But we're told to just bear with it. They just want us to forget it.
How does that make sense?
Lots of people have hurtful memories in Korea,
but no one really gets healed.
So I guess that's why.
That's why you decided to build a medical psychiatry center.
How is it that you're still so naive?
Am I?
Hey, what's up?
Okay. Thank you for the heads up.
I hope we get to meet soon.
The regional investigation unit is going to do a seize and search.
Our department?
Someone must've reported to the human rights commission...
regarding an assault incident at the ward.
What's going on?
I think I should go.
We're from the Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency.
Pardon?
There will be a seize and search.
- "A seize and search"? - What is this for?
Someone reported to us saying you locked up a patient...
in a closed ward and committed assault.
We need all your medical records from February 1 to today,
the CCTVs in the ward, and your drug administration records...
for the seize and search.
You may begin.
I can't let you carry out a seize and search.
A doctor's duty is to protect their patients' medical records.
What's going on?
If you do this,
you could get arrested for obstruction of justice.
Someone sent a report to the human rights commission.
And you're obligated to cooperate...
when it comes to investigating a case...
for the human rights commission.
The medical law states that doctors are obligated...
to protect their patients' medical records.
What are you doing?
- Cooperate with the investigation. - But sir...
It's because of Luo.
- What? - Someone sent a detailed report...
to the human rights commission.
Let them in.
You may go ahead.
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency, Regional Investigation Unit)
(Copying files)
Don't take anything else other than what's written on the warrant.
Okay, sure. We don't need anything else anyway.
Where is the CCTV footage kept?
I just asked you a question.
The Management Support Office keeps the footage.
Can you guess why this is happening?
Why are they doing a seize and search?
What's going on?
I'm getting really worried.
You know why there was a seize and search, right?
When Luo first came to the hospital,
we couldn't reach his parents.
An emergency hospitalization can only last three days,
but we couldn't reach anyone even after that.
And?
So I had him hospitalized without his parents' consent.
I think that's what caused this to happen.
Come back with your mom, okay?
You're supposed to get treated for longer,
but you're leaving because we couldn't reach your mom.
- You have to come back, okay? - Thank you for everything.
- Luo, you don't need to go. - Sir.
His mother called from Vietnam. She's going to get on a flight.
But shouldn't we let him go for now?
He just got discharged.
We can't send him back to that small apartment room again.
He still has visual hallucinations.
It's okay. Another day won't hurt.
But it wasn't just for another day.
Yes, I remember. His mom showed up after a week.
So you're telling me you knew all that?
He's a 15-year-old schizophrenic.
He was showing hallucinatory behaviors.
And I saw him jump in front of a car.
How could I just let him leave?
You must've crossed a lot of people.
What do you mean?
You did what you thought was right,
but that could've made someone feel uncomfortable.
That's why someone sent an anonymous report...
regarding something that happened three months ago.
If you think of it that way, I would've crossed dozens of people.
I can't believe you're making jokes.
I'm even craving alcohol.
Then wrap up and meet me outside.
Are you going to drink with me tonight?
I don't know.
What are you going to buy me?
What are we having?
This looks delicious.
Great choice. I'm so hungry.
I thought a seize and search was for stuff like...
medical malpractice and rebates.
Me too.
I didn't know the psychiatry department could get...
a seize and search as well.
It happens a lot more often than you think.
But who do you think sent a report to the human rights commission?
Do you think it was the guardian?
Guardians are normally the ones to file reports.
They normally file lawsuits against the hospital...
rather than send reports to public institutions.
The fact that the person sent a report to the commission...
means that he or she wants to stay anonymous.
Don't you think this was intentional?
There's a famous saying for a situation like this.
"The person closest to you is the culprit."
- Who's that? - Dr. In.
My gosh.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
The cops will carry out an investigation...
and check the hospital now that they got a report.
Whoever made a report might've aimed for that.
That means someone truly has a problem with something.
The ward nurses always seemed dissatisfied.
I also overheard them whisper to each other.
They had a problem with Dr. Lee...
not prescribing drugs to his patients to have them sleep.
Think back and see if you might've done anything...
to create any kind of an issue with Patient Park Luo.
The police might show up again to investigate.
- Okay. - Okay.
Who made this kind of report?
It was sent to the human rights commission, so we have no idea.
Does this happen often?
Sometimes. It sometimes happens at other hospitals as well.
About two years ago,
a patient filed a lawsuit...
as she got discharged saying she was abused by a nurse.
But we found out it wasn't true thanks to the CCTV footage.
Don't worry, Woo Joo.
Dr. Lee took care of Luo with so much affection.
He didn't even make him take any drugs...
because most drugs didn't work on him.
But because of that, the nurses had to suffer every night.
Someone did this to get him in trouble.
Whoever did this is trying to scar...
- Dr. Lee's reputation. - What?
I'm going to find out who made the report.
My goodness.
What are you doing here?
Are you here to see me?
I'm not exactly here to see you, but...
Oh. Were you worried?
I don't worry.
Why should I worry? You did nothing wrong.
Why can't you worry a bit about me?
This thing called worry.
The more you worry, the more worries you gain.
So you must never start at all.
On a day like this,
I bet you must have a lot on your mind.
So I thought you'd need this.
If there's someone you want to cuss out,
don't hold it in and scream into this bag.
I'm off to pick up a watch.
(Doctor Lee Si Joon)
- Two outs. - Pardon?
I set a rule when I became a hospital director.
Whatever the situation, hold back three times.
Whatever mistake the person made, forgive them three times.
I thought a hospital director should be...
benevolent and broad-minded.
But you just scored two outs.
What'll you do now?
I'm sorry about the search and seizure.
I'll take responsibility for it.
"Responsibility"?
Will you resign as a doctor?
No, not that.
Then will you pull your Dr. Park card again?
It has nothing to do with Dr. Park.
Then does it have something to do with me?
I'm the one who might have to be interviewed by the police.
You?
My goodness. You know nothing about the law.
But, as I said, I will hold back this time.
Because I'm the hospital director.
But next time will be your third time out.
I don't have to tell you what'll happen then, right?
I also got reported when I opened my clinic.
- By whom? - By my neighbor.
He said my clinic scared them and ruined the neighborhood.
That loser said a psychiatric clinic is...
an unpleasant facility and against public welfare.
I still feel like cursing him.
I guess she was really ticked off at the time.
I sued my neighbor right back,
won, and opened my clinic.
Well done.
Si Joon, you look depressed today.
Are you okay?
I don't care what happens to me,
but I never imagined that our director would be investigated.
The director's responsible for all legal matters.
Even so, if we were to turn back time,
you'd do the same thing. Right?
So, how is Ms. Han these days?
She finally admitted that she's a patient.
Oh, that's a huge improvement.
I'm analyzing her.
Do you have the result?
Not yet.
But what's clear is,
it's not a simple intermittent explosive disorder.
- Then what? - Impulsive relationships,
fury, capriciousness, mood disorders.
What illness has those characteristics?
Just one comes to mind.
What's that?
No way.
It can't be that.
You wouldn't have given me a borderline case.
(Borderline personality disorder)
Right?
What happens if Ms. Han is borderline?
This pajeon is delicious.
Why won't you answer?
- What? - You admitted Luo...
against all protocol, but you can't answer this?
Stop it, Dong Hyuk.
Okay. Let's stop.
How are you so carefree?
What?
Your patient died last year.
You're a doctor and you let that happen to your patient.
How are you so carefree?
How dare you...
Listen.
I lost a patient eight years ago,
and even now, day or night,
I can't stay sane unless I run all over the place.
I just don't get how you can be so normal.
How dare you say...
Dong Hyuk, please, don't.
Don't smirk.
Just because I'm over a wound, doesn't mean I'm fine.
Suffering for eight years doesn't make him special.
I guess I messed up.
I shouldn't have referred Ms. Han to him.
I didn't know Si Joon was still suffering so much.
Ji Young Won.
Why do you always worry only about Si Joon?
- What? - Isn't it time you stopped?
Who reported him?
He can't think of anyone.
So that's the kind of problem a psychiatrist has.
Ji Hee should be careful too.
By the way,
he told me to get my watch back from Min Wook.
- What should I do? - What else? Do as he says.
Must I show the lowest of my lows to that jerk?
Listen. He already saw you at your worst.
You said you called him to give it back.
Why do I show my worst so easily?
I'm sorry, we're closed for...
You can't be here to eat.
Are you here to see me?
I'm not here to eat or to see you.
I came to leave this.
You said you'd get it yesterday, but you didn't.
I was going to get it back from you.
Thanks.
Hey. Why are you thanking him?
My gosh.
Is there anything else you want back?
Say so now if there is.
I'm not sure.
What else could there be?
The year I wasted on you?
You owe me for the free food I fed you.
You ate for free so often here.
- Make Woo Joo pay for that. - What?
What about the repair cost for my car you wrecked?
Do you even know how much that cost me?
- Can't we part ways with grace? - Hey!
The moment you cheated on me, that went down the drain.
I can't believe this.
How could you be so brazen when it's your fault?
This isn't your first time breaking up...
because of a cheating boyfriend.
If the same thing keeps repeating itself,
there's a good reason.
I know I'm a jerk,
but you have serious issues too.
Stop acting like you're so tough!
Goodness, darn it.
Hey, why are you...
He's right.
The guy I met before cheated on me too.
Don't cry. He's not worth it.
I won't cry.
You lunatic.
Why are you here at this hour?
Goodness. Is this the only place you can come to?
You pathetic fool.
Woo Joo.
What are you doing here?
I didn't know what to do with this.
Right.
You told me to call you. Why didn't you answer my calls?
I kept calling you.
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
If I take this home with me,
I think I'll be staring at it all night long.
I thought of throwing it in the trash, but that seems wrong.
A burial or drowning?
- Or a cremation? - What?
Drowning it won't be good for the environment,
and I'm afraid it won't burn well either.
- I'll bury it. - Let's do that.
This is what you call burying something together.
That's right.
All right, throw it now.
Chuck it as hard as you can, all the way to the top.
What an amazing throw.
Are you a shot putter or what?
- That felt so satisfying. - I think it went over.
Although it was nothing.
- How did I do? - Nice!
Nice!
All I did was throw a past memory...
into a heap of trash.
But it felt like my wound was buried together in that heap too.
Luo asked for help through a podcast three months ago.
I was doing a live broadcast,
and he said he was hearing things.
He said that voice kept telling him to throw himself at a car.
I had no choice but to get him admitted.
I couldn't reach his guardian for several days.
I did eventually,
but his guardian was in Vietnam and couldn't come right away.
I couldn't send him back...
the small apartment room he lived alone in.
So I admitted him to the hospital.
But that became an involuntary admission.
That was the reason for the search and seizure.
Why is that involuntary?
How could you send back a patient who's so unstable?
We can only hold a patient for three days if there's no guardian.
I knew this would become a problem one day.
What will happen now?
You said you gain more worries the more you worry.
I'm not worried.
Go home then.
Good night.
How about we do some stretching?
You gave me a prescription last time.
That was very effective.
The moon is so bright tonight as well.
Okay?
Let's do it.
- What are you doing? - Why?
You're not trying hard enough.
For every single movement,
you have to do it accurately and with class.
- You try it. - Watch.
Waist exercise. Start.
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8.
3, 2, 3, 4,
4, 2, 3, 4.
Next is your shoulders.
1, 2, 3, 4,
2, 2, 3, 4.
3, 2, 3, 4.
Clasp your fingers together and pull your arms up high.
1, 2, 3, 4,
2, 2, 3, 4.
Keep stretching, more, more!
- Does it feel good? - Yes.
- Body shake. Start! - What is that?
- Come on, shake your body. - What is this?
Shake like there's no tomorrow.
- What is that? - Shake your body like crazy.
How could you call this stretching?
Keep going. Shake it.
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
I knew you'd get into big trouble someday.
The Legal Team is going to call you, so wait.
The Regional Investigation Unit investigated yesterday,
but they didn't find any signs of assault in the security cameras.
I guess they only found that he was involuntary admitted...
after you ignored all the protocols.
I'm sorry, sir.
You knew everything, didn't you?
I had no choice.
You'll have to receive the police investigation soon.
Sir.
Will the director be investigated too?
Of course.
Why are you so reckless?
I have no regrets.
If I sent Luo back like that,
he could've died.
Let Dong Hyuk treat Park Luo.
He's my patient.
Shall I send him to another hospital then?
Okay, then.
You ignored all protocols.
Why are you so obsessed with a patient?
You know why you're like this, don't you?
- That's because... - Don't answer me with a cliche,
saying it's because you care about your patients.
You know well that there's another reason.
Let's begin our counseling.
- Sir. - Also,
you won't be forwarded with any patients for the time being,
so keep that in mind.
Why?
Consider yourself lucky that I'm ending it here.
What are you doing? Get out.
(Medical Psychiatry Center, Lee Si Joon)
(No Reserved Patients)
He took away my patients from me.
They're the reason I live.
Dr. Lee.
What are you doing here?
It isn't time for today's stage therapy yet.
I just wanted to be somewhere quiet.
Do you have no patients today?
Wait. Are you playing hooky?
Oh, do you want this? I just bought it.
No, thanks.
Did something upset you?
I told you clearly yesterday that...
you gain more worries the more you worry.
Talk to me. I'll listen.
It's nothing like that.
(Stage Therapy Room)
What was that about?
What's wrong with him?
It's my daughter's birthday today.
She has such a petty mom like me...
and won't get any birthday soup today.
Instead, she has to work part-time.
Still, you're not allowed to leave the hospital.
Do you know the convenience store right across the hospital?
That's where she works.
I'll call her for you.
It's her birthday today.
A surprise. Don't you know what that is?
You can't go.
It's just 10 minutes.
I said I understand, okay?
Welcome.
Hello.
What are you doing?
- Give me that. - No.
- Give me that. - No!
- Give me that! - No!
What are you doing?
- Give me that! - I can't!
Don't just stand there! Stop your mom!
What? She's not my mom.
- What? - Give it back.
Give it to me. Give it to me!
Give it to me!
Oh, no...
Hey, Gong Ji Hee.
Dr. In...
My gosh.
If a patient loses her mind over a drink,
you should grab her and stop her.
What doctor sits and sobs?
I apologize.
We're psychiatrists.
Good intentions don't always bring good results.
Right.
Hello, sir.
Okay, I understand. Bye.
You treat Patient Park Luo from now on.
Si Joon agreed to it.
Dr. Park. I don't see why we should deprive him of his patients.
We're not depriving him.
It's because you're ideal.
I understand.
It'll be tough on Si Joon.
Help him out.
I should.
Good. You can go now.
Dr. Park.
Who reported him?
You know, don't you?
I don't.
People call me a wild hare.
Because I run off during walks.
I think those people are mistaken.
Hares are fast. You're slow.
That's why I always catch you.
Luo.
You'll have...
a new doctor from now on.
Why?
Are you upset?
I understand.
It'll be confusing and upsetting.
I'm fine.
Are you really?
Now I feel sad.
I heard it from another patient.
The police came here because of me.
Who said something like that?
It's not true.
I'm fine.
Park Luo.
I told you to say so if you're hurting.
Did you forget why you got sick?
Because I never say I'm afraid,
when I am afraid.
Because I don't say I'm lonely,
when I am lonely.
So why keep it in?
I won't keep it in.
I took notes of Luo's condition from the day he came. It's for you.
(Doctor In Dong Hyuk)
(April 26, Withdrew all medications)
Si Joon's out of his mind.
He's a mad doctor.
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
(Doctor Lee Si Joon)
What is wrong with you?
- What do you mean? - You don't know?
Why are you acting like this?
Did I do something wrong? Did I mess up?
You didn't do anything wrong or mess up.
I just have a lot on my mind, so...
Let's talk later.
Why did I hurt my wrist?
To get noticed.
When I was young,
I wanted my adoptive parents to love me,
so I even set fire to the house.
Of course, that just got me rejected.
I never wanted to die.
I just...
wanted people to look at me.
(Fix You)
Why did you refer Han Woo Joo to me?
You knew from the start, didn't you?
Do you really know who reported him?
The culprit is...
Why did you get involved?
I'll quit stage therapy.
How can a nuisance like me...
help other patients get treated?
What is the matter with me?
Doctor Si Joon! Si Joon!
- Luo got into trouble. - Darn it!
The best heart specialist took secret videos of women?
Wouldn't it be nice if I could turn time back just one day?