(This drama is fictitious...)
(and all characters, events, organizations, and settings...)
(are unrelated to real life.)
- My gosh. - Oh, dear.
I hear something back there.
A passenger is relieving herself.
But I should check.
Check on a passenger peeing?
But...
Why didn't you say anything after finding out who I was?
It's you, isn't it? You're Michael.
A good night's sleep will make you feel as good as new.
(Good Casting)
(Episode 6)
We're here already?
What's wrong?
I can't open my eyes.
I can't open my eyes!
Oh my goodness.
Did you eat peanuts?
Don't you know I don't touch them because I'm allergic?
Wait.
(Pistachio cookies made from locally-grown wheat)
Did you eat pistachios?
I ate pistachios but not peanuts!
Keep hold of my hand and just follow me.
(Taipei International Airport)
You know you wouldn't have made it if it weren't for me, right?
So I'll lead the interrogation once we land back in Korea.
You have no right to decide.
I'm the team leader, not you.
Competence is more important than rank.
You're always so inflexible,
and that's why you always get passed over for promotions.
What's the use of being a skilled agent?
You never get good results because you fail to control your emotions.
- Verruckt. - You just swore at me, didn't you?
(Verruckt: Insane, Crazy)
I guess you've become more quick-witted...
with age.
Don't you get funny with me.
You may begin boarding the flight to Incheon.
"To Incheon"?
(Taipei International Airport, VIP Lounge)
I promise you that Kang Woo Won...
didn't eat those nuts on purpose.
Yes, I know.
Pistachios are also nuts.
So I know he should've been extra careful.
This is all my responsibility. I should've double-checked.
Come back to Korea right now.
Let's talk once you arrive.
Okay.
I'll call you as soon as I arrive...
Water.
"Water"?
What is this?
This isn't my usual French natural bedrock mineral water!
They don't have that brand here.
They may not have it in this lounge.
But dozens of people visit this airport every day.
Do you really think it'd be impossible to find that brand?
Then are you telling me...
to search the entire airport...
And find me the water.
I can see you.
I know...
it's hard to stop looking at me.
But...
if you're going to look at me for more than three seconds, pay up.
I have expensive portrait rights. You know that, right?
She should know her place if she doesn't have any money.
This feels nice.
This feels great.
How nice.
You were saved, so now you must repent.
Get the item.
Pi Cheol Woong will be on a flight that departs...
in two hours.
Could you please sit down?
It's you, isn't it? You're Michael.
Darn it!
(Wash and Clean)
- Let's go. - Yes, sir.
Where to, sir?
That place I told you about last time.
Instead of going to HQ?
Just do as I say.
Okay, sir.
(Chief Seo)
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to voicemail.
Check how things are going with the guys in Taipei.
Hey, Team Leader Dung.
Don't ever make me wear a uniform again.
I practically had to squish my body...
into this uniform. How do people wear this thing?
Why don't you lose some weight?
This is my charm.
Cut the nonsense.
What? Did you get hurt?
- Let me see. - No, I'm fine.
You're not fine.
Chief Tak hurt you, didn't he? Let me take a look at it.
I should've checked over my shoulder.
Let me take a look.
No, I'm fine.
Did you check if Ye Eun got back safely?
Hey!
Will you please slow down?
I'm not the one moving.
What?
Where do you think you're going without me?
No, that's not it.
It's just that my hands are really sweaty.
Don't let go of my hand even for a single second.
You have trouble trusting people, and you get scared so easily.
How could you think of going to an overseas event...
with no one else but me?
This wouldn't have happened if you took your manager with you.
I hate having a lot of people around me.
And people from the agency get on my nerves.
He only cares about himself.
He just wants to make me suffer.
They don't like me.
They like me as a celebrity since I earn them money,
but they don't like me as a person.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Where are you? You'll pay for this.
Come here. Get over here!
You're dead meat.
No wonder people hate him.
I'll teach you a lesson once I can see again.
You'd better be prepared.
I can't believe this. I just saw Kang Woo Won.
(I can't believe this. I just saw Kang Woo Won.)
(Kang Woo Won, Airport)
(Kang Woo Won is at the airport!)
(He looks so cute wearing a mask.)
(He suddenly came back to Korea.)
(He's back!)
How did they find out?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Stay right beside me.
1, 2, 3.
(NIS Safe House)
What's this cell phone?
Who are you people? Untie me right now.
I said untie me!
You little... I guess words won't be enough.
Mu Hyeok, bring it here.
Yes, sir.
Gosh, it's heavy.
Look at this.
We're going to use that later, so put it away.
Okay, sir.
(Special Substance, Handle with Care)
Liquid nitrogen. Ever seen it before?
This is really clean and clear.
Spilling blood, pulling off fingernails,
and cutting off feet.
We just hate dirty stuff.
Yes. You'll just love this.
My gosh.
Now watch.
Isn't that nice?
Why in the world... I mean... Why are you doing this to me?
The minus 196℃ smoke.
Just smelling it will kill you.
Why waste time explaining?
Let's get to work.
No, wait, ma'am.
You won't dunk me in that, will you?
You can't.
Get the hammer.
Okay. Hammer.
Wait. Let's talk a bit first.
What? Just a few seconds?
You must keep it in at least five minutes...
to make it nice and crunchy.
My gosh. Darn you all.
Yes. Do it over.
Wait.
Give me time to think.
- Darn you. - No!
Who?
Wang Kai.
Wang Kai?
What are you doing with Wang Kai?
Talk in chronological order.
In... In Taipei...
I'm supposed to meet Wang Kai...
and give him the package.
- What's this? - When I arrive,
Wang Kai said he'd call me on that.
Who gave this to you?
I don't know who it was.
I really don't know.
I think it's true.
Make sure to flush the dry ice...
down the toilet.
Dry ice... Dry ice?
You could burn yourself. Be careful.
Are they good?
This is my favorite ice cream flavor.
How can ice cream be so hard?
I can't scoop it up.
- Give me some. - Here.
Isn't it good?
Do you want some?
I don't want any!
He wants some.
Poor thing.
Are you out of your mind?
Not only am I exhausted by the 10-hour round trip,
but due to your poor care,
I can barely see because of my nut allergy,
and you'll leave me, top star Kang Woo Won to go?
Your being alone...
without me would be a bit tough, right?
What do you mean? Of course I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Then can I really go?
I said so.
You are annoying, always in the way, and a complete nuisance.
You are a huge headache.
Yes.
You were from the start.
So you mean...
I'm like fine dust particles.
What a great analogy.
You're not just fine dust particles. You're ultra-fine dust particles.
I'll have no problem without the likes of you.
You bet I won't.
Call me if you need anything.
The French natural bedrock mineral water that you drink...
is right beside the couch.
Your organic gluten-free snacks...
cooked by the Italian chef are on the table.
Your air purifying system is on,
and so are the hygrometer and humidifier.
Go.
I'm really leaving.
Are you still here?
She really left because I said so?
Are you gone?
Hello?
She's gone.
I can't see properly.
So, fortunately, we got the item.
With this chip,
we'll lure and catch Wang Kai.
We'll use him to get to the buyer...
and get the broker Michael as well.
Simple, right?
Simple, my foot.
Wang Kai's in Taiwan.
How are we to bring him to Korea?
I think he'll come without us calling.
Wow. The tracking device is as small as an ant's booger.
The new model...
is so small, it's the size of a mosquito's booger.
Darn it.
Why is ours so huge?
It's fine as long as we can track you.
Does size matter?
This isn't the time to complain!
Even if the item's right here,
would Wang Kai...
willingly come all the way to Korea?
For hundreds of millions of dollars?
Then he'll come.
He'll come in no time.
Mu Hyeok. Guard our bait until we hear from Wang Kai.
Everyone's on standby until then.
That's all. Good work, everyone.
Thanks.
Let's get going.
- Hi, honey. I'm going home. - Yes, hello.
- I just got back. - I took Mr. Kang home.
There's rice in the cooker,
- food in the fridge, - I meant to call...
- and soup in the pot. - right away.
- It's rude to call on weekends. - Why is there no food?
- Am I your cook? - As soon as Mr. Kang recovers,
- Hang up! - he can work.
Hello?
(Auntie)
Chan Mi.
Your aunt said she can't reach you.
She called the office number.
Shoot.
Take the call.
You're back?
Was it rough?
I'm so sorry.
I'm looking for a helper to...
When did you last change her diaper?
I don't know. Some time ago.
Was it in the morning?
Or during the day?
So Hui, mommy will change your diaper.
Lie down.
Did you give her a hard time because Mom wasn't around?
You should be working in the field,
not babysitting over the weekend.
I'm very sorry.
Then pull this one off.
I spent my precious weekend babysitting for you.
I'll feel better if you catch Michael.
Do you think Michael even exists?
What do you mean?
So many people tried to catch him for years.
No one succeeded,
let alone set eyes on him, and that feels weird to me.
Someone did see Michael.
Three years ago, during the Busan operation,
when one of our agents died, Ms. Baek...
Did someone die?
I should go.
The nonstop return trip from Taiwan must be draining.
Why do I feel as if I made the round trip?
Do you know...
how to gain access to information that...
I'm not cleared to see?
Get higher clearance.
Or ask someone who has access.
Forcing something not meant to be will only cause problems.
Get some rest.
You should take a taxi.
No, thanks. See you.
I planted these because I thought gardening would be fun.
Look at what is causing me problems now.
That's an insecticide and this is prickly ash extract.
They're both great at killing insects.
I can't use chemicals on what I will ingest.
People prefer foods that were eaten by insects because they're organic.
A couple of bites made by insects don't even show.
They're just trying to survive, so we should let them eat.
But...
it gets on my nerves when they ruin my food.
And when that happens, it's best to just exterminate them.
How?
By killing them before they can even reproduce.
You're off the project.
I want you to leave everything behind.
Hello, Ok Cheol speaking.
From now on, I want you to be in charge.
Yes, sir.
Don't worry, sir.
I'll make sure Chief Tak's absence doesn't show.
I'll get the job done perfectly.
Yes, sir!
Chief Tak got appointed to our branch in Malaysia.
- All of a sudden? - Yes.
Director Myeong must have decided to discard him.
I doubt that.
He won't be able to abandon Chief Tak that easily.
He's been taking care of all his dirty work...
as his right-hand man for a long time now.
Did you look into what I asked?
Oh, according to the branch manager in Malaysia,
Chief Tak came back to Korea...
as soon as he arrived in Taipei.
Then the trip to Taipei must have something to do...
with why Chief Tak got sent away.
It could mean things didn't go as planned.
Do you think this is a good sign or a bad sign?
Hey.
I'm fine.
What's this?
I think it's a good sign.
In China, turtles are considered good luck.
There should be one more.
I gave it to someone as a gift.
- What about me? - It was one of my favorites.
What if it turns out to be a bad sign?
Then I should step up.
I should stop taking care of things from behind like I'm doing now...
and start doing things out in the open.
Is that really necessary?
I'm just worried...
something bad might happen to you just like your father.
That's why...
I need to do this.
I need to do it for my father.
What are you doing?
Well, the thing is, I'm pretty sure I'm wrong,
but this doll somehow seems very familiar.
By any chance...
Never mind.
He never gave me a doll,
so there's no way he'd give one to a new recruit...
who has only been here for less than a month.
No way. It's absurd. That can never happen.
What am I saying?
Next time!
Next time we meet,
I'll give this back to you!
I love you. I love you.
Sir.
I'm sorry, but I have an important appointment tonight.
So I think I need to go now.
Oh, okay. You can go.
Thank you, sir.
By the way,
it's nothing bad, right?
Pardon?
You said it's something important.
So I got a bit worried.
It's something personal.
You may leave.
(Financial Statements)
(A doppelganger? Chan Mi. Jang Mi.)
(Is she really Baek Jang Mi?)
Sorry for leaving without even saying goodbye.
Good luck on your SATs.
I hope you get accepted to the university you applied to.
Where did she go?
Sir, you need to pay.
Right.
Hello?
(Intensive Care Unit)
Just as I suspected,
the multimodal method was used to strengthen the password.
The multimodal method?
It's a multibiometrics device,
and its security system is the best...
out of what's on the market.
It'll react to Pi Cheol Woong, no doubt.
It's been set so that the subject of the biometric lock...
and the chip's location is constantly tracked.
If Pi Cheol Woong is 10m away from the chip...
for more than an hour,
the data on the chip will be erased.
Are you saying we can't copy its content then?
Attempting to copy it...
will lead to the content being erased.
So Pi Cheol Woong is nothing but...
a disposable parcel box.
Would they have...
killed Pi Cheol Woong once done?
We get rid of the box after receiving the parcel, right?
Keep an eye on it at all times.
Would the call come in this soon?
In about a day or two.
That fast?
Stolen items lose their value by the second.
Dragging it out would be their loss.
Could Wang Kai be Michael?
We'll know who he is...
once we arrest him.
Right?
Sure.
Kang Woo Won left to attend a rice cooker launching event...
for the company he's been a campaign model for.
This is him urgently heading back home...
due to a sudden medical condition.
His face can't be seen as he is being guarded by staff,
but he obviously looks a little peaked.
Yes, Mr. Kang returned to Korea...
earlier than scheduled to seek medical treatment.
However, photos of him at the airport...
spread across social media platforms...
and a flock of fans crowded the area to get a glimpse of him.
Gosh, look at her.
That's just hilarious.
Is this funny to you?
It's priceless.
We hope to see him in better shape...
What is?
The look on her face, trying so hard...
to get out of that crowd is just so...
("Who Was the Woman Protecting Kang Woo Won?")
Her features are all scrunched up.
Unbelievable. Talk about the most embarrassing photo ever.
You're right. It's hilarious.
Gosh.
My eyes water easily these days.
She threw herself at her job...
which was to protect my image and you find that funny.
Of course not.
I'm deeply touched.
Gosh, my eyes.
I'm so touched that I'm crying.
Don't laugh in front of me again. It sickens me.
What else can I do then?
How about this?
I'm neither laughing nor crying.
Don't make any expressions at all!
You and Cheol Woong are both annoying.
I have one of those naturally smiling faces.
Even when I'm sad, my eyes look like they're laughing.
Woo Won, come on.
(Chinatown)
Are things all right?
Things couldn't be better.
I was wondering if the NIS was onto us.
The NIS?
I'm sure they're suspicious,
but all they have on us is circumstantial.
If the deal goes south...
It won't matter.
And Wang Kai?
He has arrived at the airport.
Already?
Let's see then.
My gosh. These look beautiful.
This is our chance...
to get rid of the NIS...
that has been making life difficult for us.
But we're not in Taiwan.
Is it still possible in Korea too?
It's better that we're in Korea.
Korean law actually favors criminals.
This time,
I'll be making the deal myself.
It could be dangerous.
If things go south and we die,
then I'll be happy not to have died alone.
Let me secure the package for now.
I need to deliver in spades this time.
Only then,
Director Myeong won't ever want to have Chief Tak back.
Darn it.
If only he had died there.
Make the call.
What the...
Wang Kai?
What do I do? Darn it.
My gosh.
Mr. Dong!
Incoming call. It's from Wang Kai.
You make me come all the way to Korea?
The product had better be intact.
Of course. The file hasn't been corrupted.
I thought we could rendezvous at Incheon Port.
It is I who decides the location. Tonight at 10pm.
Meet me at Unit 11-3 of the Paju Distribution Center.
Tonight, 10pm, Paju Distribution Center.
I don't like how he's making his move this fast.
When have we ever operated under safe conditions?
We'll head out soon, so call everyone in.
You're going to notify Chief Seo first, right?
This seems like an operation that requires backup.
Backup?
You crawled back into Korea without reporting to me first...
and now you barge in here with a request.
Backup?
Please authorize it.
You think you landed this case because you're hotshots?
Look at you running around as if you own the place.
I'll wrap this up for sure this time.
What if you don't?
Will you resign?
You got cocky with me...
without willing to put everything on the line?
We're running out of time, sir.
Let me say this again.
You'll be held accountable...
for this operation.
(Wash and Clean)
As you all know, Pi Cheol Woong will make the deal...
with Wang Kai.
He's a new player that hasn't been flagged by us.
There's no manual regarding how to handle him...
and his threat level is unknown.
The deal goes down at Paju Distribution Center.
Pi Cheol Woong will head inside with the watch on him.
Chan Mi and Mi Soon, lead Alpha Team...
and secretly follow Pi Cheol Woong.
The rest will wait outside the building...
and raid the facility...
when Alpha Team gives the signal.
We're here.
All right.
I'll go too.
You should wait here for this one.
Let me join them.
I know I lack in many ways, but I want to help.
This operation is just too dangerous.
Mi Soon, you coming?
I don't care.
This is our job, isn't it?
No one recognizes our service, but it still must be done.
I can do it too, you know.
I can do it and I will.
No, it's too dangerous.
We'll go with Plan B.
But it's our job to do dangerous tasks.
No one recognizes our service, but it still must be done.
You said you have something special planned tonight.
That's all the more reason to do it.
I don't want to be embarrassed of myself.
Unbelievable.
Is this what I get for looking out for you?
Ms. Baek, there's something I need to tell you after today's job.
Are you finally resigning?
If I do,
it'll be like losing a right arm for you.
Who says you're my right-hand man?
Say I'm your left then.
This is our job, isn't it?
No one recognizes our service, but it still must be done.
I can do it too, you know.
I practiced everything you taught me...
during our training sessions...
and I went to the firing range...
whenever I had free time.
Just like you told me to, I can take care of myself now.
Here.
Just in case.
Thanks, Mr. Dong.
Let me carry that.
Don't take it personally.
Chan Mi's always on edge before a big operation.
The more dangerous the operation, the more stressed out she is.
Blame her old age if you must.
How sad.
We've come this far, so let's wrap this up neatly.
I guess I have nothing to lose anymore.
Your confession has already been recorded,
so you can't escape punishment.
It wasn't recorded illegally,
so it's 100 percent admissible in court.
I'm saying there's no point in running.
Isn't it better to stand trial in Korea...
compared to being dragged off to China?
Still,
would they care that you're the NIS though?
These guys are vicious.
We're not trying to scare them off.
Scumbags who deal in unlawful activities for a price...
should be wiped off this world.
That's how we maintain a basic sense of peace.
Be careful in there.
We're ready on our end. Move out.
Our people's safety is the number one priority.
No one shoots until you're given a green light.
I'll say that once again.
No one shoots until you're given an order.
The package?
It's on my wrist.
We have visual on the package.
Transaction is complete. Get eyes on them.
Chan Mi?
- Freeze! - Stop right there.
I'll handle five.
You take the rest.
Five?
The rest? That's more for me to handle.
Don't come any closer.
Please don't let me die.
No one is to enter.
What's going on?
Should anybody take a single step...
You know what'll happen.
There's a bomb.
Contact EOD immediately.
EOD?
The bomb squad?
You've got to be kidding me!
Please save me.
Drop your weapons. All of you.
Why did you bring two guns?
I took Team Leader Dong's, just in case.
You hear me, right?
If I see anyone following us, the bomb will go off.
If anyone tries to come into the building,
the bomb will go off.
Hold your fire.
Let them pass.
Have the license plates tracked.
I need these vehicles tracked.
Hurry. It's urgent.
- Do you have them? - Right here.
- Why don't we have anything? - The license plates must be fake.
There's no information on them.
Oh, wait.
I forgot to mention that it'll go off anyway...
in an hour.
In other words,
you don't intend to blow it up right now.
Defuse the bomb.
You can't leave without me.
Any movement will trigger the bomb, so sit still.
Hold your breath.
Can you defuse it?
I only dealt with small bombs during EOD training.
One of this size...
I need instructions.
The best way is to cut off the power.
It could be risky though. Cutting the wrong wire can...
Why would you mention that right now?
Got it.
Let's disable the control system first.
You don't care if you die?
I will anyway when the bomb goes off, right?
The control system...
It's normally the red wire.
What are you waiting for? He said it's the red wire.
Hold on.
I doubt...
the bomb-maker connected it in such a complicated way.
Wait!
Not the red wire?
What on earth are you doing?
Are you colorblind?
She said it's the red wire. Red.
R, E, D. Red!
Just hold on.
Think this through.
Are you sure about this?
Think it through once more.
Ye Eun...
It's all right. It can happen to anyone.
Be careful of the control system...
and disconnect the power by cutting the third wire...
from the left.
Hurry up, will you?
You only have an hour until the files are erased.
What is he yapping on about?
Who is that punk?
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Step back.
It's you, isn't it?
You're Michael.
Did you really believe that you were in the clear?
What? Why is it ticking again?
There must be another bomb.
What?
This is insane.
What now?
Get out of there. Run!
Get down!
(Epilogue)
(15 years ago)
Ms. Baek,
do you know why first loves never have happy endings?
It's because we don't know how much we should love the other.
But how can we measure one's love...
for another person though...
when it's not visible?
A love that can be measured...
is not love in the purest sense anymore.
Even though you don't love me at all,
I can love you 100.
No, wait. Is it 1,000? Not even that seems to be enough.
Let's make it 3,000. I love you 3,000.
Yes, 3,000.
My gosh.
(Present day, Chan Mi's house)