(This drama is fictitious and all characters, events,
organizations, and settings are unrelated to real life.)
(Episode 5)
What was that?
- Sir!
- What happened?
What happened here?
Did he get hurt?
Mu Hyeok, stay right next to
Team Leader Dong.
Chan Mi. Chan Mi!
Try to make the bleeding stop
and call an ambulance.
- Hurry!
- Okay.
Chan Mi!
Sir! Sir, wake up!
Stop right there! Hey!
That's mine!
Chan Mi! Chan Mi!
- Go and start the car.
- Hey, wait.
That's my motorcycle! That's mine!
There she is.
- It's her, right?
- Yes, it's her.
Go faster!
(68G 3877)
Gosh, she has a horrible temper.
She might break a leg.
Will you drive faster?
Why can't you pass those cars?
- Step on it!
- Okay.
Oh, gosh. Careful. Turn the handle.
What the... Make a U-turn.
That's prohibited here.
Just make a U-turn.
Just do it now!
What are you doing?
You're unbelievable.
(Wash and Clean)
You're driving me crazy.
Move. I'll drive.
- Move. Get out.
- No, I got it.
My gosh, this is insane.
Where are they?
There she is. That's her.
- Stop her.
- What?
Turn the handle!
Oh, my gosh. What is she doing?
What was that?
Get out of there! Come here!
- Chan Mi!
Chan Mi!
Chan Mi, are you okay?
What's going to happen
to our team leader?
Finish getting your IV fluids.
Why are you getting up?
I don't feel comfortable
lying down here...
when she's sobbing her eyes out.
He got shot because of me.
I feel so sorry.
Hey, you can't even call that
a gunshot wound.
What was the name of that brat
who shot me in Gwanghwamun?
- Nitovenihaj.
- Yes, Nito...
Well, whatever her name is,
when she shot me...
right through my leg,
it almost killed me.
Why are you still crying?
My gosh.
What happened to her?
- Are you okay?
- What did the doctor say?
He didn't get directly shot at.
The bullet slightly grazed off.
What happened to her?
Isn't it obvious?
We caught her, of course.
Chan Mi and Mi Soon, go back to HQ.
Ye Eun, I want you to stay
with Kang Woo Won.
Keep an eye on him
until he wakes up.
Yes, sir.
Find out what Chief Tak is after.
She acts all tough,
but she's actually quite clumsy.
Gosh, stop crying.
(Ointment)
You should've been more careful.
Scars never look pretty on a lady.
Did you get injured?
No, it's not a big deal.
(Good Casting)
Yes, sir.
Koo Tae Rim definitely is involved
with the second transaction.
That's not what
Kang Woo Won's agency said.
They told me it was done
by an obsessive fan.
Why would an obsessive fan
abduct one of our agents?
Exactly.
Why did she have to secretly
enter his house...
and get herself in that mess?
Since when did we have to report
every single thing...
Kang Woo Won's agency
says they'll handle the press.
So just hand this over
to the police and close the case.
Then what about the gunshot?
The bullet barely grazed off you.
Since when did we consider that
a gunshot wound?
She was arrested at the scene.
I won't release her until
the legal confinement hours are up.
And I'll make sure she talks...
within the given amount of time.
My goodness.
He's putting up a fight.
Trust the team and wait.
We just have to find out
what the watch is.
We'll interrogate her right away.
You know there's no time.
If Mi Soon is to make her
confess soon,
we need your help.
She said...
she's looking for something.
What?
I doubt you stole from us
without being prepared to die.
Right?
The watch.
Abducting people,
wielding a knife,
and shooting someone.
Too bad.
You got it all wrong.
What do you mean?
The man you were after...
is Pi Cheol Woong.
But the man you abducted
is Kang Woo Won.
They might be
the same height and build,
but how could you mistake
this face for this?
I just can't understand.
Do you need glasses?
Your eyesight must be way low.
You lost your target...
and the thing you're after too.
Don't say that
when you took the package.
We did?
You don't know yet, do you?
That's why you're poking around.
You have 10 seconds.
Tell me what it is.
One,
two,
three,
4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9,
- 10.
- No.
Wait. There's a chip inside.
A chip?
Really?
There's something like that?
I had no idea. That was very close.
To summarize what we know,
there are two identical watches.
The real one that
Kang Woo Won was wearing,
and the fake replica
in which the chip was hidden.
I'm in possession of the item.
The conclusion is that
the Pi Cheol Woong you're after...
took the real watch
and chip and disappeared.
That's why you tried to abduct him.
Hand it over to me.
It's okay now.
Lady.
The fool who took the chip.
Don't you want to know where he is?
That was embarrassing.
Chief Tak.
Do you think we couldn't get him
or didn't get him?
We have all the evidence we need.
Is Baek Chan Mi over there?
She knew about me?
Baek Chan Mi.
Do you think I couldn't get you
or didn't get you?
(Taesan University Hospital)
(Authorized personnel only)
I'm the CEO
of Kang Woo Won's agency.
Woo Won.
What happened?
Why did you suddenly pass out?
Why? Who did this to you?
Who was it?
It was...
He has a packed schedule
starting tomorrow.
You can't be here in bed like this!
It's not serious, is it?
He can get up and walk, can't he?
No, it's okay if he can't walk.
I just need him to be breathing.
I'm glad his nose is okay.
It looks like he had a concussion.
He can't work...
He cracks open walnuts
with his forehead.
What concussion?
He has events
and fan meets lined up.
A full schedule.
Do you know how much that's worth?
The doctor.
Who's the doctor in charge?
His doctor...
Get well and get up soon, Mr. Kang.
I sent you to kill a bug
and you came back with extra trash.
I deserve to die for that.
Did you see me give second chances?
This is why cleaning
must be done on time.
Whether it's a dog or a human,
keeping it for too long
makes it harder to get rid of.
You were saved,
so now you must repent.
Get the item.
It's me.
It's been a while.
How about we meet for a meal?
I will do as you say.
I'll meet Director Myeong
if you want me to,
and get rid of him
if that's what you want.
Do as you wish.
I trust you.
But...
why do you need the files
from Yoon Seok Ho's computer?
We took a look,
but we found nothing suspicious.
So...
Do you know what
the opposite of "to doubt" is?
It's not "to trust".
It's "to know for sure".
I think you got the wrong idea.
You asked me to
look into Baek Chan Mi.
I checked.
She emigrated with her family...
and hasn't returned.
I see.
Why did you want me to find her?
Just in case.
Your new secretary looks like her
and has a similar name,
but they're definitely
different people.
I knew she had left the country,
but she could've returned.
If she hasn't returned so far,
maybe she has no plan to.
By now,
she could've married a foreigner...
and had a child too.
There's an everlasting truth.
Even if you see
your first love again,
it will only get very ugly...
The memories. They can be...
amazingly fond.
Memories.
Turn it off and sit down...
before I throw a pen and hit you.
Okay. Throw it.
You have three seconds.
Throw all you want.
I'll evade them all.
3, 2, 1!
Gosh!
You could've hit me with that!
But I didn't.
What's this?
It ripped!
I can even fit my finger
inside the hole.
That hole was already there.
What are you talking about?
How did you make a hole with a pen?
Stop overreacting. Take it off.
Gosh, no. Get off me.
- Take it off.
- My gosh, what are you doing?
- Oh, my gosh! What the... Let go!
You even know how to sew?
I might not look like it,
but I'm a fine sewer.
You just wait.
I'll fix this in no time.
There. It's all done.
Look at that.
Do you like it?
How did you...
What?
Is this a rose of Sharon?
How am I supposed to wear this?
That took quite a lot of work.
My gosh, get rid of this
and turn it back to normal.
I can't go around
with this on my back.
Why? It looks good on you.
It suits you well.
Don't lie to me. I can't wear this.
You shouldn't have turned on music
during class in the first place.
I didn't know you'd do this.
I'm not going to wear this.
Let's see what happens
if you take it off.
But... I...
Wear it.
It looks good on you. It looks nice.
You can't even
buy this stuff anywhere.
Sir?
Yes?
- Aren't you going to leave?
- Right. I'll be off, sir.
Are you awake?
How do you feel? Do you feel better?
Just a second.
I'll bring your doctor.
Pi Cheol Woong.
Where is Pi Cheol Woong,
and what are you doing here?
- What?
- Why are you here instead?
Where's my manager?
Mr. Kang.
Where am I?
You don't remember
how you collapsed?
No. What am I doing here?
What are you doing?
Bring me my manager!
- Hello? Hey, it's me.
- I don't think he remembers...
anything that happened
during the past week.
He lost his memory?
- I'm at the hospital.
- Sometimes, people experience...
short-term memory loss
after a concussion.
I'll drive myself,
so bring me my car.
Why is my car getting repaired?
My gosh.
Will his memory never come back?
We'll need to run some tests
and keep an eye on him.
But when people experience
memory loss,
they sometimes become
extremely depressed...
due to severe mental stress.
What are you doing?
Bring me my clothes!
But I don't think
you need to worry about that.
Yes, we'll check
all the security cameras.
Kang Woo Won might
get his memory back.
So make sure
you keep an eye on him.
And Pi Cheol Woong might
try to approach him, so be careful.
Okay, bye.
Gosh, will you stop? Go away.
My goodness.
I can't believe that thief
put you through this mess.
Let's just be grateful
nothing worse happened.
But it's such a relief
that he only took your watch.
Don't you agree?
If it weren't for her,
you could've died.
That watch was worth
100,000 dollars.
You haven't forgotten
about tomorrow's event in Taiwan...
regarding Il Kwang, have you?
So are you saying...
during the past week,
which I have no recollection of,
I hired her...
as an on-site staff?
Really?
Here. If you look here,
you can see
that you signed the contract.
You see that, right?
Call the person in charge
to confirm this.
Okay, I'll do that.
What's wrong with this?
(Commercial model contract)
Well...
Since I know there are no photos,
I won't sign the contract.
Your dog.
Poppy ripped it apart.
Don't you remember?
Oh, right.
Hey, I just checked.
Apparently, you called
Il Kwang yourself...
and asked for Ms. Lim
in return for renewing the contract.
They even have a recording
of the phone call.
The employee in charge
will be Lim Jung Eun.
That's all.
Mom!
So Hui, do you want me
to carry you on my back?
- Mom!
- No?
Then how about an airplane?
Or how about a jet?
Mom!
You don't want to do any of those?
Gosh, you're driving me crazy.
Hey, how can you sleep
in this situation?
Mom!
I stayed up all night last night.
Shut it and make sure
the kid stops crying.
- Mom!
- Okay?
- My gosh.
My goodness. There, there.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
It's okay. There, there.
My gosh.
Ye Eun is very brave.
How could she think of
having a baby on her own?
I'm sorry. That was a bit rude,
wasn't it?
They kind of look similar.
- Your mom's here. Let's go.
- So Hui.
Hey, you're here.
I'm sorry.
It must've been really tiring.
No, that's not true. Just a little.
She's very gentle.
Gentle, my foot.
Who does she take after?
She's such a fussy kid.
She's nothing like her calm
and feminine mother.
Maybe she takes after her dad.
She looks just like him.
Have you ever seen him?
Yes.
- I saw a photo...
- You must be starving.
I'll fix you guys a meal.
No, don't bother.
You stayed up all night
doing fieldwork.
We can't make you cook as well.
I'm not your mother-in-law.
Come on. Let's go.
I had a few snacks,
so I'm not hungry.
- See you tomorrow.
- Thank you for today.
No problem.
Something is off
about Min Seok's death.
Didn't he die during a mission?
I overheard the higher-ups
talking about it earlier.
And apparently,
everyone in Min Seok's team...
is being investigated
by Internal Affairs.
What does that mean?
It means there's
something fishy going on.
I'm going to find out
no matter what.
If you died a wrongful death,
I'm going to do everything I can
to reveal the truth.
Mom, are you crying?
No, I'm not crying.
Don't worry. I'm not crying.
Isn't Ye Eun admirable though?
She had the baby first
without getting married...
at a young age.
What do you want to know?
She has no one
to take care of the baby though.
Doesn't she have family?
Or she severed ties with them.
I wonder what her story is.
It'll be easier to find an agent
without a story to tell.
Do you perhaps have one too?
I can be all ears all night long.
I'll see you around.
Why not talk some more over drinks?
Where are you going?
I need a man of mine released.
I see you haven't changed a bit.
I'm no longer someone
you can order around...
for free.
You'll be satisfied
with what's in your trunk.
You know very well that
chump change doesn't motivate me.
Don't tell me
you're aiming for the Chief of NIS?
Would I be satisfied
with such a small position?
And I'm not one to be satisfied with
being Director at Il Kwang Hitech.
The higher you climb up the ladder,
the more you'll need my money.
I don't believe
nor trust promises...
that aren't tangible.
It's been a while.
Three years, right?
Pi Cheol Woong must not
leave the country.
Check ships and flights
leaving our borders.
We're in trouble if he leaves
the country with that chip.
We should catch him before he does.
His photo has been distributed
all across the nation.
I want real-time updates
from the information center.
Got it.
I'll call as soon as I spot
anything that looks like him.
Have you alerted airport security?
Go ahead.
Please take off your cap.
We found him.
Put him on the big screen.
Rewind.
Stop.
Can you blow that up?
We have Pi Cheol Woong's location.
He's taking the 20:58 flight
serviced by Air Taiwan.
If we leave now,
we might be able to catch him.
Do we know where
Tak Sang Gi is headed?
There's no need to snoop around
for his whereabouts.
He's suddenly taking
a business to Taiwan.
It seems like the two
will make contact in Taipei.
You two, be on standby for now.
Why? Until when?
What's going on? We're releasing her
to police custody...
when we're not done
investigating her?
Apparently, there's nothing
linking her to any particular crime.
She was caught at the scene.
Isn't that enough?
Chan Mi,
the gun was dusted for prints,
but only...
Mr. Dong's were found.
What?
Your prints are all over
Kwon Min Seok's gun.
You took it from him, shot him,
and let the perp escape, didn't you?
What tipped the scale...
was the fact that the victim
is suffering from memory loss.
He can't testify as a witness.
The agent died
while trying to apprehend the perp,
but you ran after him...
only to lose him
even after firing at him.
Could it be...
that you let him go on purpose?
How can it be confirmed
when the only witness...
is dead?
Darn it.
Hey.
Chan Mi!
Did you sign off on this?
I knew you were
too quiet these days.
Of course,
the Baek Chan Mi I know...
would barge in here.
Please take back...
this decision.
I wouldn't have signed off on it
if I was going to.
But Chief!
She's...
a material witness in this case.
She's also...
the only lead you have
regarding Michael.
If we apprehend Michael,
the leak within Il Kwang Hitech...
will also be revealed.
That's what you said the last time.
Once we apprehend Michael,
we'll find the leak within Unixen.
You're not
getting out of here alive!
Do you need me to remind you
what happened?
Why did you even...
put me on this case?
Do you know what makes us
different from animals?
Our intelligence?
Our sensitivity?
Our rationality?
No.
It's the fact that
we learn from our mistakes.
That's what makes us human.
It's about time
you broke free from your past.
Live your tomorrow...
and envision your future.
Got it?
We have Pi Cheol Woong's location.
You located Pi Cheol Woong?
A day.
No, give me 20 hours.
I'll have him delivered by then.
You want me to go
on a business trip?
"My Girlfriend Mrs. Kim"
starring Kang Woo Won...
was a huge hit in South-East Asia.
Considering the amount of money
we poured into his contract,
we should milk him any way we can.
Don't you agree?
But it's...
I'm afraid this is
too sudden for me.
The event was already scheduled.
Although, you going there...
was recently requested
by Kang Woo Won.
If you're done complaining,
get going.
(Il Kwang Cookbob Launching Event)
Why launch a rice cooker in Taiwan?
Jung Eun.
You're fluent in Mandarin, right?
I am?
Since when?
According to your resume,
you have a level-five on the HSK...
and can speak Mandarin
at a top level.
We made sure you'll get in,
so relax. Don't get intimidated.
We won't bother hiring
a translator for him,
so be of good service.
What?
Are you hurt?
Are you all right?
Yes,
I'm good.
Watch it, okay?
This suitcase costs more
than your annual salary...
and you almost had it scratched.
The stairs are quite steep.
Carry it then.
I'm supposed to carry it
when it has wheels?
See for yourself.
There may be wheels,
but there's also a handle.
Why?
For it to be carried like so.
Unbelievable.
What on earth are you doing?
The suitcase is in your trunk.
You're ruining the leather!
An Italian master artisan...
made this from
a 10-year processed cowhide.
This blanket is to protect it
from fine dust,
so what'll happen if you sit on it?
Then...
should I move to the back?
The back is also...
Take a cab.
A cab?
You can take a deluxe cab.
Don't you dare be late and make me
unload my suitcase myself.
Move it!
Unbelievable.
Now I get it.
No wonder Pi Cheol Woong left him.
(Wash and Clean)
It's been a while...
since we went abroad.
I'd kill for a three-day vacation.
You two.
This isn't a vacation, you know.
Where's the discipline?
Did you bring the anti-nausea pill?
I always carry some with me.
I'm sorry.
I paid the cab driver
double the fare,
but there was too much traffic.
What an idiot.
- Woo Won!
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
- Woo Won!
- Over here.
- Dear gosh.
- Woo Won.
- Woo Won!
(Why do I hear my daughter's voice?)
- Over here.
Woo Won! Gosh, it's really him.
(Why do I hear my daughter's voice?)
Hello and welcome aboard.
Hello and welcome aboard Air Taiwan.
Please enjoy your flight.
- Welcome.
Welcome aboard Air Taiwan.
Welcome.
Welcome aboard.
My gosh. This is incredible.
What do you think you're doing?
- Sorry?
- You really think you're worthy...
of a 15,000-dollar
first-class ticket?
Then where...
do I sit?
Just think about it.
Where do you think
you should be sitting?
- Business class?
As if.
You're flying in coach.
Get here in 10 seconds
when I call you.
Got it?
Got it.
My gosh. Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine. I'm all right.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm good.
Goodness.
(Earpiece)
Hey.
How did you know it was me?
Only an idiot wouldn't know.
Being in a disguise has
never been your strong suit.
Let me know...
as soon as you spot Pi Cheol Woong.
Welcome, everyone.
We are happy
to have you with us today.
Our flight attendants will...
Pi Cheol Woong is nowhere
in business class.
Please make sure
that electronic devices...
are stored safely
in the overhead compartment.
Here you go.
I'm a fan, Mr. Kang.
Right.
I'm sorry,
but could we take a photo?
Right here.
You!
What did I say
about swatting the flies away?
Get over here in 10 seconds.
My gosh.
I made a bad decision.
There's a fly in here?
It just flew away.
Since you're here,
hand me the headset.
- The headset?
- Yes.
This blanket is too dirty.
Get me my cardigan.
My slippers.
(Pistachio cookies made
from locally-grown wheat)
Kang Woo Won's allergies.
(Kang Woo Won allergies)
He's allergic to peanuts?
No way.
He couldn't have eaten
this pistachio cookie.
Pi Cheol Woong isn't
in first class either.
Then he's flying coach.
I'll look for him.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are now taking off.
Please fasten your seat belts.
All areas including
the lavatories...
Darn it.
You being here must mean
that you're stressed out.
Isn't it obvious?
Doesn't this add to the stress?
(Semicon Event List of Attendees)
The list of attendees
for the Semicon Event?
It's odd how Mr. Tak...
is among the list of attendees.
What's weirder is that...
he's flying in to Taipei
but flying out of Kaohsiung.
As soon as Mr. Ok
moved up the development schedule,
Mr. Tak pretends to go to Taipei...
when he's actually
heading to Kaohsiung.
He's there to conduct...
some other business.
I can't believe
you missed every shot.
It looks easy, right?
But it's hard to even
land 1 out of 100.
1 out of 100?
Remember the plant manager
who was fired...
when Director Myeong
gave the job to a man of his?
The branch manager in Malaysia?
Have him be our eyes.
I want to know who Mr. Tak meets
and for what reason.
We might not
find out everything,
but it could at least
lead to something.
Did you see that?
You finally hit one
after spending 250 dollars.
I may get even better at this...
if I spend double that money.
Why not just
buy the game for himself?
Is this out of order or something?
It's perfectly fine.
The seat belt sign
has been turned off.
However, we do recommend
that you keep it on when seated...
in case of sudden movements
due to turbulence.
When the seat belt sign is on,
please understand
that other services...
may be limited due to your safety.
Cell phones
and extra battery packs...
could burn and cause a fire.
Please make sure...
that you have yours with you
or know where yours is at all times.
Pi Cheol Woong will be...
on a flight
that departs in two hours.
Mr. Tak is on the plane.
What on earth? Is there no signal?
He's not in section A.
Check Section B.
Anybody?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will soon arrive in Taipei.
- Hurry up.
- Please fasten your seat belts...
for your own safety.
We will soon arrive
at our destination.
Return your seat
to an upright position,
stow your tray table,
and fasten your seat belt.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will be landing shortly.
Please make sure
that your seat belt is fastened...
and your seat back...
is in the upright position
and your tray table is closed.
Mr. Tak is on the plane.
I'm sorry, sir,
but could you return to your seat?
Are you all right?
I need to use the toilet.
Sir, please take your seat.
Sir? Please return to your seat.
Handle the flight attendants.
Okay.
Sir, please return to your seat.
But I really need to go.
You can use the lavatory
after we land.
But I really need to go.
Please return to your seat.
- I'm about to burst, you jerk!
- Sir!
- Sir?
Sir, please return to your seat.
I know that,
but I really need to go.
It can't wait.
- Please return to your seat.
- We appreciate your cooperation.
- Move!
- But sir!
Why didn't you say anything
after finding out who I was?
It's you, isn't it? You're Michael.
My gosh.
Oh, dear.
He wet himself.
I hear something back there.
A passenger is relieving herself.
But I should check.
Check on a passenger peeing?
But...
In one blow?
That's what I call talent.
I've never done that
to a person before.
Are you all right, young man?
Why are you on the floor?
Mind your own business.
A good night's sleep
will make you feel...
as good as new.
Package acquired.
No, this way.
(Epilogue)
Yes, Mr. Yoon.
Could I perhaps...
ask a personal favor?
A personal favor?
Go ahead.
Well,
do you have a needle and thread?
A needle and thread?
You didn't have to do it for me,
you know.
No, it's all right.
Just so you know,
I'm a fine sewer.
I see.
Someone I knew
was also a fine sewer.
Did I mention...
that you look a lot like her?
A lot of people in this world
look alike.
I guess you're right,
but I first thought
that you were her.
The difference in name and age...
made me wonder if you were twins.
If you knew her a long time ago,
she could look
completely different now.
You're right. 15 years have passed,
so she'll be 38 now.
She's probably a wife and a mom.
I'm not sure.
I don't think
it's right to assume...
that women at the age of 38...
are all wives...
and mothers.
Gosh, I didn't mean it like that.
She was just very popular...
and also had a series of boyfriends.
Are you saying that
she had a messy dating life?
Why are you getting upset
about this though?
It makes me uncomfortable...
to hear you talk about her
behind her back.
I guess I understand.
To be honest,
I thought that you were her
and that you lied about...
your age and name...
- on your resume.
- Gosh, that stings.
Why? What is it?
You're bleeding. Are you all right?
Hold on a second.
It's all right.
Wait, I have a bandage.
Is there a lot of blood?
My goodness.
I should...
get back to work then.
Right, of course. Thanks again.
What am I thinking?
It would be a miracle...
if I met her again after 15 years.
(Good Casting)
Take my hand and follow me.
Water.
Getting physical with you
is the answer.
No!
You are to get
the job done yourself now.
We'll lure Wang Kai out
with this chip.
- What are you going to do?
- I'll make my move.
I'll show myself.
I'll be fine even without you.
I'm really leaving then.
Why are you still here?
I should go.
Is everything all right?
I'm just worried.
The deal will take place
at a distribution center in Paju.
We'll raid the place
and make arrests.
The package has been verified.
Transaction is complete.
Head inside.
Stop right there!