HI BYE, MAMA!
THE YEAR 2013
It's so good.
How can you eat that? Isn't it spicy?
It is. That's why it's good.
-Do you want some? -No.
Hold on.
Gosh, capsaicin.
That's not for people.
I know it'll give me diarrhea.
You get used to it.
Spicy food relieves stress.
Why would you get used to it?
I'd rather not eat it. I don't understand why people eat that.
Forget it.
You'll never know this pleasure.
Anyway,
look how much steamed offals I got.
-She knows I love them. -Because you're a regular.
-It's starting. -Okay.
-Is it the last episode? -Yes.
-It's me, Hae-ram. -That kid is a good actor.
I go to kindergarten...
THE SPICIEST CHICKEN FEET
Come out and have some chicken feet.
You should've bought something else.
That's going to give him diarrhea.
Chicken feet.
This is really spicy, isn't it?
Yes, it's delicious.
Will it be too spicy for you?
Yes, of course. He's going to die if he eats this.
I'll give it a try.
Hey!
Is it too spicy?
It is,
but I can take it.
Doesn't it relieve your stress?
Yes.
It's good.
Will you watch the news?
I'll turn the TV on.
Min-jeong! I bought some really spicy chicken feet.
-Really? -Yes.
It's a place next to the hospital.
People say it's the best.
I guess you're into spicy food now.
It looks good.
How is it? Is it spicy?
Is it?
It's spicy and yummy.
-Really? -Yes.
How is it?
It's not spicy.
I think it's okay.
Throughout my life,
I believed that nothing around me would change.
I put extra since you're a regular.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
-Please come again. -Okay.
SPICY AUNTIE'S TTEOKBOKKI
CLAW CRANE SHOP
-One, two, three. -One, two, three.
Hey, I told you not to smoke.
However, even when I was being forgotten,
the world kept on turning every day without fail,
and many things were changing.
EPISODE 12: THE DAYS I WAS FORGOTTEN
Ta-da. Where should we put this?
Hey.
Where are you going, Seo-woo?
Why did you bring that?
Gosh, great job.
Did you want to put it there?
But Seo-woo, who is this?
Cha Yu-ri.
Seo-woo.
-Who? -Cha Yu-ri.
Cha Yu-ri.
Seo-woo, who is that?
The pretty auntie.
What?
What did you say?
Seo-woo
knows your name.
That's impossible.
How could she know my name?
There's no way.
She clearly said Cha Yu-ri.
That's impossible.
What is this?
Seo-woo put that sticker on there.
She said
that is Cha Yu-ri.
Gosh, you're so good.
Is it fun?
-Gosh, it's so fun. -Cha Yu-ri!
Why?
-We need to go. -Where?
I guess Dad won't be coming home today.
Let's have the cake first.
Let's get up.
Yu-ri, what's wrong?
What is it?
Seo-woo has been watching me.
That's why...
Are you the pick-up helper?
You can take her.
Sorry?
Seo-woo, you don't know who I am, do you?
I do.
You do?
Who am I?
I don't know.
She must've heard Hyeon-jeong calling my name.
I'm sorry.
She shouldn't say my name in front of Min-jeong.
What should we do?
Gang-hwa, you should--
Why are you doing this?
Stop it now.
You should
see Seo-woo as her mom.
I'll tell Min-jeong.
No.
Why not?
Don't.
Then should we just
let your heart break and keep Min-jeong in the dark?
Is this the right thing to do?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
But...
No. You can't tell her.
Why not? What's the reason, Yu-ri?
Yu-ri.
You...
You gave up everything to save Seo-woo.
Didn't you?
Please save my baby.
Help.
Why did you do this to me?
What should I do now?
What am I supposed to do?
You and I,
we saved Seo-woo.
You're Seo-woo's mom. Why are you hiding?
No, I can't.
Even when I'm lonely or sad
I'm going to take 50,000 won
50,000 won
Someone put the till in the celery...
I mean, someone put a celery in the till.
Hi, Hyeon-jeong.
What's wrong?
You lost.
You did.
My Hyeon-jeong lost.
You wouldn't look like that if you won.
You'd have your shoulders pulled back.
"I'm Go Hyeon-jeong. How dare you!"
What's wrong?
But come to think about it,
I love him too much.
Hyeon-jeong.
-Gosh! You scared me! -Goodness.
Damn you!
Did my good looks scare you?
Pull yourself together.
You win some, you lose some. You can't always win.
Do you think I lost?
No. You probably killed them all.
Good job. I'll take care of the settlement.
Well done.
Hello?
What the...
Wait. Hey.
Hey.
You.
Hey!
Who are you?
I'm here for your daughter.
Guk-bong!
Let's not be so unethical!
Ms. Mi-dong.
Who is that?
Is he talking about Seo-woo?
Take a break, Ms. Mi-dong.
I said I'd take care of them.
Until when?
When every exorcist in the country swarms to this place?
What is he talking about?
Ms. Mi-dong.
Snap out of it.
She's not your friend. She's your job.
Next time, I'll see you with your daughter,
Cha Yu-ri.
What does that mean?
He's here to take Seo-woo?
Why would shamans and exorcists swarm here?
Ms. Mi-dong.
Your daughter still sees ghosts.
Yes.
I got rid of all the local ghosts,
but she still sees ghosts.
Why would she see them when they are not around anymore?
Well... That's...
I don't know.
Anyway, if your daughter keeps seeing ghosts like that,
she will have to live like me or the exorcists you just met.
No. Not a chance.
Well...
Maybe that's because she still has the energy of the local ghost.
She won't see them in a few days.
I'll make sure to keep ghosts away from her during my time here.
Do you still not want to get your place back?
No.
I don't.
Why not?
Anyone else would do anything to get their place back.
You have a chance to stay alive.
Do you know what Seo-woo likes the most?
What is it?
Her mom.
Do you know
when Seo-woo wears the broadest smile?
When she runs to her mom.
It's so pretty.
This is your favorite princess doll.
Mom.
Mom?
Do you like your mom?
Mom is my favorite.
Seo-woo.
Mom!
Seo-woo, are you all right?
-Don't run. -Mom.
I told you not to run. Are you all right?
Seo-woo loves her mom so much.
She can't live without her mom.
I can't take that away from her.
My gosh.
I'll go. I'll disappear.
Then Seo-woo will be fine, won't she?
She won't have to see ghosts.
I don't know that for sure.
I'll go up there and beg.
I don't have to be reincarnated.
I'm willing to fall under.
I was dead anyway.
I have no regrets.
Only those who can't give up anything have regrets.
I've given up everything already.
I have no regrets or lingering attachments.
Fine.
I get it.
A mom can even kill herself if it's for her child.
There's nothing that can stop you.
Stay by your daughter and protect her
until the 49th day.
That exorcist will be back.
He will make your daughter live like us.
There's no way it will happen.
I will protect my daughter myself.
Oh, right. Well...
How did you make me stick to this earlier?
I'm a human now.
What?
Well...
It's not like
you're a complete human.
You're neither one nor the other.
If you would do this,
why did you send her in the first place?
-Where's Yu-ri? -I guess she's in her room.
-I'll go get her. -No.
I'll go see her. I will.
That exorcist?
Don't you dare mess with my daughter.
My baby.
Mom.
Come and have breakfast.
Okay.
Yu-ri. Try some of this too.
You like potatoes.
She likes rolled omelets more.
She likes potatoes too.
I bought a lot of potatoes when you guys were young.
You did? Did he do that?
I like everything.
I like potatoes and rolled omelets.
She will eat what she wants to eat.
Stop making a fuss and eat your food.
She might feel too pressured to eat.
Mom, don't you think you're being
unfair to us with the soup to say that?
Your dad and you have had a lot of it.
Make sure to eat it all up.
Okay.
-Go ahead and eat. -Let's eat.
Hang on.
-No. -Let me say that again.
-You can't. -Again.
-Let's do this again. -Okay. Fine.
-So you're... -Me?
-...38 years old. -Right.
-I'm 38. -And you're 44.
Gosh, that's a lot.
-Hey! -What are you talking about?
Gosh, I can't believe this.
This is why we shouldn't hang out with young girls.
She's young and pretty.
She's pretty, and she's even young.
I really hate you.
I just hate pretty girls.
I will just call you by your names.
-Whatever you want. -Hyeon-jeong.
Do-yeon.
This is nice. I got some friends.
She said she left others out.
Is this her first time to make real friends?
-Yes, you're right. -What did you say?
She was like a voluntary outcast.
Excuse me.
You guys are having fun. Can I take a photo of you?
-No. -Yes!
-Let's do that. -One, two, and three.
I bet it will look cool.
Let me see.
Let's see who looks prettiest here.
Gosh, there's nothing.
It's so strange.
Nothing's on here.
What's wrong with this?
Seo-woo has been watching me.
That's why...
What was she looking at?
Are you leaving?
Yes.
We've become very close, right?
I think so.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I laugh a lot when I'm with them.
-I'll see you later. -Gang-hwa.
It might rain today.
I have one here.
You need a bigger one not to get wet.
I see.
You're right.
Don't look at me like that.
I said I'd stop being considerate.
This isn't being considerate?
No. I'm just doing what I want to do.
And you shouldn't be considerate of me.
I wasn't so considerate in the first place.
See you.
Min-jeong.
Yes?
Let's
get a new pick-up helper.
You darn exorcist. You'd better stay away from us.
Good.
Seo-woo.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I was out taking a walk.
I happened to be passing by, so I thought I'd walk with you.
Okay. Come with us.
Let's go Seo-woo.
Seo-woo, you look even prettier today.
I don't think you like all kids.
What?
You care only for Seo-woo.
Oh, well...
I do like many kids.
Seo-woo is just adorable.
Isn't it that you want to be a mom?
What? Mom?
Why are you so surprised?
If you like a kid of her age,
it means you want to get married.
Oh, I see.
You're not married yet.
Yu-ri.
Seo-woo, it's okay.
It's been fine these days.
Are you all right?
It's strange,
but dogs used to bark at Seo-woo until not long ago.
Stop it. Seo-woo is terrified.
Go away!
Stay quiet! My gosh.
Stop!
But that doesn't happen anymore.
Is it because she got bigger?
I just realized something amazing, Dad.
Something amazing? What?
Popo is a genius dog.
-All of a sudden? -Think about it.
It barks at everyone but our family.
It even barks at the delivery guy who comes every day.
But it didn't bark at Yu-ri even once.
You're right.
Come to think of it,
we brought Popo after Yu-ri left. Popo didn't see her before.
My point.
It knows that she's our family.
Isn't it genius? Do you think it should be on TV?
-Make a call. -Okay.
It's unbelievable.
Honey.
About Yu-ri.
Don't you think she needs to see Seo-woo once?
Don't worry. She's been seeing Seo-woo already.
Did she see her? When?
Did Gang-hwa let her meet Seo-woo?
I'm glad to hear that.
No.
Is it a good thing?
She must've been devastated to see Seo-woo.
Now that Yu-ri's back,
don't you think we should bring Seo-woo back?
What are you talking about?
It's not like she's a thing. Why would we bring her back?
I mean, Dad and you want to see her too.
Forget it.
I can't tell a six-year-old kid
that Yu-ri is her real mom just because of my greed.
There is no end to the greed of people.
I know she misses Seo-woo too.
I'll walk fast and get there before you.
I'll win. I'll be the winner.
I'm winning.
-Hyeon-jeong. -I'll walk faster than...
-Hyeon-jeong. -Hyeon-jeong.
-Hello, Seo-woo. -You were like this earlier.
It sounds like you've never called your friend before.
It sounds really awkward.
What did I do?
Hyeon-jeong. It's not awkward at all.
Hyeon-jeong, let's just go.
-Okay. Let's go. -Okay.
-Let's go, Min-jeong. -Okay.
It did sound awkward though.
Okay.
-This is all your fault. -What did I do?
Now I understand
a stray cat that lost a fight.
-Hey. -Why would you take it out on me?
I don't know. Let's just go.
It's really strange.
How did Yu-ri know that?
I don't know.
She said she just got the feeling.
Feeling? What feeling? Is she a detective or what?
What could she feel? Even a doctor wouldn't know that without a closer look.
My point.
I'm sure she's hiding something.
Everything is so strange.
You knew all along that she was strange.
It was strange that Yu-ri asked you to stay quiet for 49 days.
And it was strange that she knew about Min-jeong.
Don't sigh.
Please stop sighing.
I didn't sleep a wink because of that sigh.
Why?
Is it about Hyeon-jeong? Hey, did she say anything?
Hey.
Hyeon-jeong didn't say anything.
But...
-I just think... -Think what?
I think she's crazy.
She has to live.
That's right.
She can live, so she should.
She has to live. I'm going to save her.
Gosh, but they love each other.
She's not getting divorced.
I was out of my mind.
Why did I do that?
But I didn't know
this would happen.
No. But she still has to live.
I'll make them divorce.
Then
what about the kid?
Right. That's the word.
I'm sure she's crazy.
Didn't she say anything?
She seems to know something.
But she stopped talking about Yu-ri at some point.
She just keeps sighing.
My goodness.
Are you being chased or what?
-Why are you walking so fast? -What?
-Was it you guys? -What's wrong?
Gosh, you startled me.
Her name? Are you insane?
Why would I callout her name around Seo-woo?
You're right.
I knew you didn't.
-Why? -The thing is,
Seo-woo knows Yu-ri's name. She said Cha Yu-ri.
Isn't it strange?
I'm sure she's hiding something.
Everything is so strange.
What's strange?
At first, I just thought
she found out about my marriage or Min-jeong somehow.
But come to think of it,
she wasn't even surprised when she saw me for the first time.
She just
looked as if she got caught.
I don't know. It's all strange.
You know something.
I'm sure you do.
She does.
I can tell she knows something.
This is how she looks when she knows something...
Hyeon-jeong.
Hyeon-jeong, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Hyeon-jeong.
I don't know.
What should I do?
I don't know what to do.
What's going on?
What's the matter?
All right. Fine. Don't cry.
Stop crying.
LAW FIRM
JW LAW FIRM DIVORCE ATTORNEY
What are all these?
This is an expandable baton.
You can expand it
by swinging it with a wrist snap.
And this is a self-defense alarm. It rings if you pull this.
If someone tries to take Seo-woo,
pull this pin off
spray this in their eyeballs, okay?
Is someone taking Seo-woo?
I mean, there might be an abductor.
There are a lot of abductors these days.
They are dressed in black.
And they kidnap kids of Seo-woo's age. Make sure to carry them around with you.
Okay.
All right.
All your classes are over now.
You are the best.
Seo-woo, do you have fun in the classes?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
You know who I am, right?
You've seen me the whole time, right?
Yes.
I had no idea.
I've been with you all along.
You must've been terrified.
I'm sorry.
Gang-hwa?
What are you doing here?
I was passing by.
Raise your head and keep your shoulders back.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Just be a man.
I'm totally lost.
I don't know what to do, Father.
Just live your life
like you used to.
We'll live our lives.
You being like this
makes us feel bad about Yu-ri coming back.
So
brazen it out,
okay?
About Seo-woo...
Thanks for raising her to be so sweet.
I'm grateful to your wife as well.
Yu-ri.
Yes?
Why don't you quit
being their pick-up helper?
Mom.
Seo-woo
is just as lovely as you are, isn't she?
After
raising you for 30 years,
I still adore you so much.
I can't imagine how much you'd adore
that munchkin you never got to hold in your arms.
Still,
you can't go on like this,
fooling that innocent woman.
Just tell Gang-hwa's wife the truth
and ask her to let you see Seo-woo from time to time.
I can't do that, Mom.
Why not?
Why is my girl being like this?
I'm sorry.
You must miss your granddaughter too.
Not at all.
I missed you a lot more.
You being here doesn't stop
Guk-bong from taking you away.
Go back to your urns.
I'm too scared
to go back.
Who would have known this would happen?
Where is Hye-jin, by the way?
Since she killed herself,
she's supposed to be sent up first.
I'm sure she's hiding somewhere.
Gosh.
COMPANY EDGE CAUSED A HOPEFUL YOUNG WOMAN TO DIE
Mom.
Do you know
what's the biggest regret of my life?
Killing myself.
Why did you kill yourself?
I was bullied.
I was bullied at work.
-You could have quit. -I know.
I know that now.
Back then, I couldn't think of that.
It was my dream since childhood
to be a fashion magazine editor.
I worked my butt off
to enter this company.
Continue working.
Wow, impressive.
Do you have a second?
Can you take a look?
But the reality was completely different from what I had imagined.
My coworkers were mean.
Hello.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
My bad.
I couldn't stand it.
I was lost and couldn't seem to fit in.
I became an outcast.
In the end...
But the thing is,
the moment I killed myself, I regretted it.
Mom, I'm sorry.
My dream
wasn't all I had.
Mom, Dad, my friends...
I had them in my life too.
I thought my dream was all I had.
Why do people always regret things when it's too late?
Are we idiots?
If we only did things we'd never regret,
we'd be deities.
It's me. If you're busy today,
I can babysit Seo-woo all day.
What difference does it make if I bring Seo-woo here
instead of the playground?
No, don't worry.
CHO GANG-HWA
Seo-woo.
Something came up unexpectedly.
Can you babysit her for a moment? No.
Actually, I might be a while.
Is that okay?
Of course.
Seo-woo, I'll pick you up later.
Have fun.
See you, Seo-woo.
Oh, sweetheart.
My sweet girl.
Come here, sweetie.
What's going on?
What is Seo-woo doing here?
-Gang-hwa asked us to babysit her. -Really?
-Yes. -Seriously?
Why didn't you wake me up?
She'll be here for a while.
She's all yours.
Really? She's all mine?
Seo-woo, do you want some apples?
Here. Good girl.
Chew it carefully.
Does it taste good?
Seo-woo, we've met before, right?
You remember it, right?
-Give her some tangerines too. -Okay.
Here you go. You don't want it?
Should I eat it then?
You don't like tangerines?
Do you want more apples?
-Eat more apples. -Yes.
Do you want to finish this?
It seems like you don't like tangerines.
You don't want any tangerines? Should Auntie eat all of them?
You can't give her such a big piece.
I'll eat it.
Here are two grapefruit juices.
Thank you.
You did a nice thing.
With Yu-ri back, Ms. Jeon can finally see Seo-woo too.
She must have wanted to see Seo-woo so badly.
I told Min-jeong we're taking the kids somewhere.
Make sure Hyeon-jeong knows.
O, K. Okay.
T, Y.
"T, Y"? Is that a swear word?
Why would "T, Y" be a swear word?
What does it mean?
Yes, it is a swear word.
What is this?
I'm not cheating on my wife, but I'm still lying to her. Gosh.
If you think of Min-jeong and Yu-ri separately,
there's nothing morally wrong with it.
You're not cheating on anyone.
If you think about it, both of them are your wives.
Still, that's what it looks like.
-What? -It sounds like you are cheating on her.
Gosh.
What are you doing?
I can't get the grapefruits out.
Oh.
How did you get into medical school?
It's so fresh.
You're smart.
-And you look like a cheater. -Gosh, come on.
-See you. -Bye.
You're so excited. Are you happy?
You went grocery shopping?
Yes. What is Ha-jun doing here?
What? Well...
He's been clinging to me all day.
Is Seo-woo at home?
Pardon?
Well, yes.
Seo-woo, sit here.
Why don't you pack a lunch?
Are you going to eat out?
Well, don't worry.
Geun-sang is packing lunch for us too.
Seo-woo, you must be excited to spend the day with Ha-jun.
Next time, let's all go together.
What?
With Ha-jun's family, the six of us.
Sure, let's do that.
YU-RI
Hi, Yu-ri.
Daddy is here, Seo-woo.
Hi, Seo-woo. Did you have fun?
She could have stayed longer.
No, we're fine.
Min-jeong must be waiting.
How are your parents?
They're happy. Very happy.
That's good.
That's really good.
Seo-woo, let's go home now.
Well. Don't stop by anywhere.
Go straight home.
Hold Seo-woo's hand at all times. Be careful.
Okay?
Sure, of course.
It's cold. Go inside.
-Okay. -Let's go, Seo-woo.
Gang-hwa.
Thank you.
Where are you?
MIN-JEONG
Seo-woo.
Who are you?
I said, who are you?
I'm Yu-ri's friend.
What?
You woke up, and you were at a charnel house?
I remember that I died.
But I woke up, and it's the present.
She says I'm nice. Isn't that weird?
Yu-ri said that? How would she know?
It's not easy to know that if you aren't close.
But I feel like Yu-ri have known Min-jeong for a long time.
Is it just me?
You don't know who Cha Yu-ri is?
She's been following you and your kid around.
She's a ghost.
-What? -For
five whole years.
Creepy, right?
A ghost?
Yu-ri has been a ghost
for five years?
And she's been following Gang-hwa around?
Yes.
Are you crazy?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I found out only recently.
My gosh.
If Gang-hwa finds out,
how is he going to handle it?
What's wrong?
What's the matter, Gang-hwa?
Did something happen?
You've been
next to me the whole time...
You
saw everything?
How
could you stand it?
What if I like her?
What's next? What do I do next?
Date her?
Marry her?
See you.
Bye.
What's going on? Why do you look so pretty today?
Do you want to dance?
-Okay. -Dance.
-Do you want to fly? -Yes!
One, two, three.
One more time. One, two, three.
How could you stand it?
You saw...
all of that?
THE YEAR 2015
Hey, go take a shower and shave.
I know it's the weekend, but you look gross.
I told you to squeeze toothpaste from the bottom!
Dry your hair in the bathroom.
Otherwise, your hair will get everywhere.
You're forgetting your umbrella again.
Even while you were gone,
the world kept spinning.
The time we spent together
was changing me desperately.
Subtitle translation by Soo-hyun Yang