Why the heck am I sitting
in this place?
Where on earth did it all go wrong?
(Park Chan Hong)
Tada. Legendary winner in a match
of 10 to 1.
He died a heroic death.
You said you were a good fighter
like Iron Man.
You've got to be kidding me.
Before your face gets hurt more...
- hand it over.
- No way!
If you don't hand it over,
your friend will die.
He's not my friend. We had
a contract.
Heo Don Hyuk, I shouldn't have been
involved with you.
You're getting on my nerves.
This is wrong.
This darn,
nonsense, crazy situation
came to be...
because wet sand...
remembers one's footprints.
What?
(Shin Seo Jung)
That's right. I shouldn't
have bothered to write a poem.
Everything started...
because of that darn poem.
Mom!
(Two months ago)
- Mom!
- What is it?
- Why didn't you wake me up?
- What?
It's your vacation.
School starts today.
- Right, I forgot.
- Did you pay for the tuition fee?
Gosh, didn't it come to your mind?
Mind your grades.
You're so peaceful for someone
who'll be a senior in a month.
Gosh, stop nagging the kid.
Son, have breakfast before you go.
I'm late.
It won't kill you to be a little bit
more late.
Just keep things average.
Yes, keep things average
like your father.
- Just as he does.
- My goodness.
How can you always aim high?
You've got to look down sometimes...
- like water flows.
- I'll be going now.
Eat your breakfast before you go.
The water will overflow!
Goodness.
I told you not to put that
on the table!
We don't have any space
to put things.
I should throw it away.
(Episode 1)
You shouldn't always aim high
as Dad said.
I realized that was the truth
from early on.
At one point, being average became
my goal.
Maybe that's why.
My height, weight,
even grades are...
just the average
for an 18-year-old.
It's Um Sae Yun.
She's the prettiest girl
in Jaeil High School.
She even gets straight As.
I can't even dare to have
a conversation with her.
Would she...
even know I exist?
So, Boy,
forget your ambition and throw
it away.
Let wild animals have it.
My face is just too common.
Did you bring it? Did you?
- Your bag looks nice.
- What is this?
I'm not very visible.
At least, I don't become prey.
- This is why my nickname is...
- Hey, ninja!
Ninja.
I'm everywhere so it's hard...
- to guess exactly where I am.
- You psycho!
- I'm Ninja.
- Ninja!
Guys and girls have different
classrooms. This is not coed!
- They should've mixed us some way.
- You'll be recycled anyway.
Well, I'm kind of unique, aren't I?
- Crazy jerk.
- Ninja! Follow me.
(What could you possibly do
with a poem?)
What is a poet?
A poet sees the world
in a different way.
He has a different point of view.
If people in this world see
this mire...
and call it smelly, dirty...
- and frown...
- Teacher of literature,
Woo Tae Jung,
also known as Spitting Woo.
A dirty flower bloomed
from dirty mud.
It stinks!
It's dirty and hideous. How hideous!
He's so crazy about poems...
that whenever the topic comes up,
he becomes too excited.
That is what I call a real poet.
That's what I think.
Are you ready to discover the truth?
- Yes.
- Let's begin.
We're looking for someone
to represent the school,
so you'll be appropriately punished
for not doing your best.
Anyone who has finished may leave.
("I might be more stupid
than fish locked in a fishbowl.")
Are you out of your mind?
Those are song lyrics.
Old guys don't know Beenzino.
I'll get this done quickly and go
to lunch.
You should write one quickly too.
Today's lunch is pork cutlet
and stir-fried spicy pork.
Then I'll write E Sens's lyrics.
Sweet choice, man.
("Poison")
Who is giggling?
Have you done writing? Let me see.
"I might be more stupid
than fish..."
"locked in a fishbowl."
You have that about you, Kyung Pyo.
It's quite confessional.
I like your honesty. Pass.
What was she looking at?
- Do you think the rumors are true?
- What rumors?
You know our senior, Seo Jung,
who committed suicide a year ago.
She fell on the flower bed and died.
Who?
You know on the day
you had your accident.
The school was turned upside down.
You might not remember
due to the accident.
There was a rumor about speed dating
before she died.
There was a lot of talk about it.
- Weird pictures also went around.
- You're kidding.
(No Entry)
She took her life because
of her grades? That's too bad.
I'm never giving up my life
for such things.
Depressed about grades?
That's what police say.
The police couldn't find
her cellphone.
Why do you think that is?
She must've hidden
or gotten rid of it.
Why would she hide that?
Rumor has it that Sae Yun
and Seo Jung...
were something like a couple.
- They could have kissed...
- That's nonsense.
Why would she date a girl?
And as you know...
- Sae Yun was...
- Why are you acting up, you jerk?
Hey, Chan Hong.
What is it? Did I say something
wrong?
- We'll run out of pizza bread.
- Hey, you!
She never dates anyone, even though
she's so pretty.
- Does that make sense to you?
- So, they loved each other?
That's it, but when Seo Jung got
a boyfriend, that was it for them.
- Mi Ra, what is it?
- Hey, King Psycho.
Are you a pervert?
What are you looking at?
I wasn't looking at you, and
I'm definitely not a pervert.
Don't stare at us. It gives
me goosebumps.
- What a psycho pervert.
- Goodbye!
See? It's like she was mad
at us for ogling at her lover.
- Those two are suspicious.
- Ninja.
Ninja!
Oh, Ninja.
- Hey, Ninja's here.
- Oh, you were here?
- Yes, I was. Why?
- Spitting Woo wanted to see you.
- What? Why?
- What about me? Do I have to go?
- No, just Chan Hong.
- Yes!
- Beenzino's raps are the best.
- I can't believe this.
How come Beenzino is okay
but E Sens isn't?
(Literature, Poetry)
E Sens?
Mr. Woo. I'm sorry...
It's you this time.
You'll be the representative
of this school.
Look at your writing.
The sentences, the title.
If you can write this good
in the contest...
you'll be able to win an award.
Let's try this.
- Your application will look good.
- Mr. Woo,
- it's not...
- Everyone, please focus.
I think we'd hear some good news
from this year's writing contest.
We found a great poet.
Here, read it out loud.
Mr. Woo.
Don't be embarrassed. You have
talent. Read it confidently.
Come on.
Do I really have to read this?
Then I'll read it.
Title.
"Poison" by Park Chan Hong.
"The memories..."
"covered by dust after
much time has passed."
"The poison that gathered in me
with the passing time."
"My urge to be free has grown..."
"so much."
"These days, I am..."
"about..."
"About half dead."
Is he crying?
I'm sorry. Let me continue.
"All that's in front of me is..."
That's good, Ninja.
He finally shows himself.
Tada.
What do I do? I've never written
a poem before.
I'm just going to go
and confess right now.
Hey!
If you go and tell the truth,
I'm sure...
you'll be going
through the fiery pit.
What's more, you might drag me
down with you.
You traitor. I'm going crazy.
There's nothing to a poem.
Write down your desires with reason.
That's it.
Put what your lower half is thinking
to your brain.
- Then write it down nicely.
- I really...
want to kill you.
Now, use me as an ingredient and
come up with an inspiration.
Use me!
Lewd,
filthy, moist, cringy, anger,
and sigh. Are you happy?
That lady's got some backbone.
I'm sorry, are you...
Heo Don Hyuk's mother?
Yes, I am.
Don Hyuk had to be somewhere
so I came instead.
- I see. Come in.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Heo Don Hyuk.
I've heard that name before.
You mean, that Heo Don Hyuk?
Who is he?
Don't you know the Iron Man
of Dukmun High School?
He has a reputation for being cruel.
I recall it was last winter.
He was in a brawl
against ten guys...
and he sent all of them
to the hospital.
I think he went to
the detention center for that.
I guess he's coming to our school.
There will be a storm now.
Anyway, don't get involved with him.
The school will turn into
a fiery pit in an instant.
The contest will be during
spring break so prepare yourself.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Can I go to Grandma's house during
spring break?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean? The cute grandson
just misses his grandma.
Don't you miss your mother?
My son!
That's a splendid idea.
- Right? It is splendid, isn't it?
- Yes, it is.
Splendid, my butt.
Why?
It's been so long since you visited
your mom.
You should take Chan Hong with you.
Put some fresh country air
in your lungs.
Look at you both.
Park Chan Hong.
Do you ever think about studying?
And do you think that I don't know
what you're up to?
What are you going to do without
me around?
Are you going to pick up more
garbage and stack it there?
Get your head out of the gutter.
What do you mean, I pick up garbage?
Mom, I'll do better after
I come back.
Be quiet.
- Chan Hong.
- Yes.
You heard her.
Forget about it.
Just fold this.
Okay.
My mother said she hates her mother
What?
That's how life goes
That's how regret goes.
That's how you shed tears
I'm telling you. I have a very
important family event then.
Is that so?
What's your mother's phone number?
Pardon?
I'll put a good word to her.
What's the number?
What I'm saying is
I have stage fright.
- So I won't be able to...
- Over here!
Come here.
This is...
Um Sae Yun,
she'll enter the contest for art.
You know her, right?
Of course.
This is Park Chan Hong, entering
the writing contest.
He's a representative for
the poetry.
What are you standing around for?
Do some cheering...
or shake hands or something.
That day I dreamt of the day...
I would die for someone,
not for grades.
- Have some of this.
- Okay.
And this is for you.
The color green is in trend
this winter.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Strangely,
my hands don't get cold.
You can do this, son!
I can't believe he's studying.
I can do this.
(I will be sitting in a foggy bar
someday. Poems by Hwang Ji Woo.)
"In the spot that you were
going to be,"
"I was there waiting for you."
During then, all the footsteps
"coming towards me..."
"are thumping in my chest."
"All the people entering
through that door..."
"were you,
"had been you,"
"and will be you..."
"then the door closes."
"Oh, my loved one."
"As I was waiting for you,
who will never come..."
"I had finally..."
"moved towards you."
"Through the door that others
passed through..."
"following all the footsteps that
were thumping in my chest,"
"I am moving towards you..."
"while waiting for you."
Why isn't he coming out?
I guess you still have
the same taste.
Sorry? What's that?
That sweater.
That's also purple.
It's just...
I just like the color purple.
People call you a psycho if you like
the color purple...
but I'm really not a psycho.
I'm not strange like Kyung Pyo.
Although I am close to him.
But I like it a lot.
So the color purple...
That color doesn't suit you.
It's tacky.
Was I too harsh?
No, it's okay.
Men aren't supposed to be hurt
by things like that.
I didn't mean it any other way.
Your skin tone is pretty dark,
so I think you'll look good
with wine or navy color.
Wine or navy color?
Wine or navy...
Thank you, I'll remember that.
But Park Chan Hong.
She even remembers my name.
Yes, what is it?
Um Sae Yun called...
my name, Park Chan Hong.
Um Sae Yun knows my name.
Wait a minute.
Who was it that said:
"It was nothing but a gesture
before I called out its name?"
- What are you doing?
- I read it somewhere.
It's "Flower" by Kim Chun Soo,
isn't it?
What are you talking about?
Geez.
Don't go too far off from the poem.
You will be given three hours
from now.
This is the submission area,
but you are free to walk around.
Let's start.
(Gangpo Writing Contest)
It looks nice but it's a bit cold,
isn't it?
The more winter is
cold and painful...
our love was once so radiant.
The poem just popped out
of my head.
Sure.
You must like the color blue.
- Yes.
- Me, too.
I knew it. There must be...
- something happening between us.
- Right.
- I think so.
- Don't you think so?
- It seems like...
- It's a wall.
It's a very high wall.
Chan Hong.
Why are you following me?
Well,
I was just...
Aren't you going to paint?
They're only giving you three hours.
Then why aren't you writing poems?
That looks like you.
You're good at making a snowman.
We still have two hours.
Why aren't you writing poems?
It was my first time seeing
Spitting Woo compliment anyone.
Then why aren't you drawing?
You're good at it.
I'm afraid I might hate it.
What do you mean?
It's my dad.
If he goes against me
majoring arts...
even if I win this contest,
I think
that might really be hurtful.
What about you?
What about me?
How do you feel
about studying the arts?
Why is that important?
What are you doing? It looks weird.
My dad said it's only...
when you run after it unconsciously
that you know you love it.
I don't...
care if this snowman is
destroyed,
but I guess
it's not the same for you.
Hey, you.
Don't try to act cool.
I wasn't trying to be cool.
My unspoken words...
finally reached you...
when it fell as the snow.
It was the first snow I saw
in 18 years.
Your feet lie upon the white snow.
I try to match...
my footsteps on top of yours.
I know they wouldn't match...
but I click my feet
like they were...
a bunch of keys...
as if they would open up your heart.
It was like there wasn't any snow
in the world...
before you painted the snow.
("As if there wasn't any snow...")
"Wet sand remembers..."
"one's footprints."
I didn't know back then...
why that particular sentence came
to my mind.
(Award Certificate)
Look here.
Writer Park.
Let's make you
look more like a writer.
- Make a big smile.
- Wait a minute.
Your hair looks nice.
You're so beautiful. We're all set.
All right.
Let's take away the flowers.
The flowers.
Okay.
- Writer Park, that's great.
- Sae Yun, where are you looking at?
- Look here.
- Writer Park.
That's good.
The other students need to see this
when school starts.
It goes well...
with the painting
like they were already a set.
You're right.
"My unspoken words have..."
"finally reached you."
Miss.
Wait.
You painted so well.
How do you paint so well?
(Wet sand remembers
one's footprints.)
That sentence...
"Wet sand remembers
one's footprints."
Was it your idea?
I guess so.
I did write it.
Is it weird?
No, I just think it's amazing.
We should say hi from now on.
- This is not mine.
- I'll get going. See you around.
I'm home.
Oh, you're home.
Go to your room and rest.
Yes, sir. No, it's all right.
I see.
Yes, sir,
I genuinely appreciate your concern.
Yes, sir.
Why are you standing there for?
Go to your room and study!
(Certificate of award: Grand Prize)
Grand prize...
Um Sae Yun.
Congratulations.
Park Chan Hong.
I hope you become a great poet.
Dad will support you all the way.
How will you support him?
Poets starve to death these days.
Geez.
Write something other than poems,
like a soap opera.
What could you possibly do
with a poem?
You're spoiling the mood again.
How can you compare a playwright
with a poet?
I'm not spoiling the mood.
- He can write a soap opera...
- What will I be doing?
And a film and it will be great.
I'm about to start a relationship.
I'm amazed...
at how I managed to write that.
Am I a genius?
As a talent I did not know I had
shown itself,
the whole universe shook.
Sae Yun managed to find me.
I...
became a visible ninja.
This is how...
the spring of our 19th year began.
Spring that does not pardon
dying things...
and reveals things hidden
in the snow.
Spring that urges you...
to shoot up.
(Enter your password.)
(Verifying)
(Incorrect password)
Could it be Seo Jung's birthday?
(Starting the phone)
(You broke your promise again.)
(Send me the money now.)
(Do you want this to be spread?)
Spring that tells you to forget
about winter.
That cruel spring...
has begun.
Gosh, he's massive.
He deserves to be called Iron Man.
- Shut your mouth!
- Gosh, man.
It's ominous.
I have a bad feeling.
Who's call are you waiting for?
I'm not waiting for anyone.
I have a bad feeling.
We're in different classes
for the first time in our lives.
- Isn't that ominous?
- Why would it be?
That's super fine.
- Get lost, class two.
- Kill yourself, class four.
- Move out of my way!
- Gosh.
Welcome.
This way, please.
I'm grateful that you decided
to donate to our school.
It's what I have to do.
This way, ma'am.
Is something up?
Of all people,
I'm in the same class as him?
I hear you write poems.
Park Chan Hong
who won the top prize.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kim Dae Yong.
You know me, right?
I do know you.
Heo Don Hyuk is a punk as I heard.
He should sit be in his chair
as soon as he's in school.
How rude of him.
This is supposed to be my seat.
Being late on the first day
of school?
You're acting cool.
You're only a year older than us...
so don't expect any respect.
Got it?
I went to school a year early.
What's that?
We can be friends
since I went to school early.
Nice to meet you.
We'll see about that.
Okay.
Tell me when you're done
talking.
Hey, Chan Hong. Let's go
to the cafeteria.
I'm buying.
Lim Seong Doo!
(Shin Seo Jung)
That's about seven dollars.
I see. I'll take this off of
your interests. You can go now.
Interest?
Thank you, I'll be upstairs.
Have some. I picked the best snacks.
Thank you. I'll enjoy them.
Chan Hong.
I heard you're close to Sae Yun.
Me? No, I just entered the contest
with her.
So we're acquaintances.
Acquaintances? Many people saw you
two hang out together every day.
Are you two dating?
No, I'm not dating anyone.
Is that so?
Then introduce me to her.
Timing is of the essence
with these things, right?
And the thing is, I hate waiting.
Okay.
What's this?
What?
I'm leaving.
Come and help me.
Hey, Ninja.
Why didn't you log in yesterday?
Sorry, I went to bed
early last night.
I lost the game
because you weren't there.
I have something to tell you.
- Would you come...
- Hey.
- Do you want to die?
- Sorry?
I'm talking to him right now.
We're having a talk.
Sorry.
Let's talk later.
Please continue.
Then, you'll introduce me
to Sae Yun.
Do you want anything else?
It's my treat.
Do you want these? How about these?
Come closer.
- You talk too much.
- Stand straight.
Chan Hong, do you have
some time later?
Have you had that experience?
You've seen something scary...
and if I turn a blind eye, it can
pass like it was nothing.
Me acting like I noticed it won't
make a difference...
so it's something scary that
I want to avoid.
Do you get it?
What would you...
do if you saw things like that?
Should I confront them
even though they are scary...
or let bygones be bygones?
If it was me...
I would like it
if you wouldn't get hurt.
I don't know
what you're talking about...
but whatever it is...
I want you to make the choice
that makes you happier.
You said it doesn't change anything.
Maybe you're right.
I also want to be happier.
I don't want to...
- introduce you to him.
- Wow, Chan Hong.
You're so smart.
It's nothing.
Hey.
Please, let this go.
Hey, do I look good to you?
It's not like that.
Right?
Someone saw you two being close
in a pizza place.
There's no way you took me for
a pushover.
You have until this evening.
If you ignore me this time...
I'll make you piss your pants every
time you even think about school.
A cafe in downtown at 7 p.m. today.
If you don't come up with results,
I'm going to kill you.
Sae Yun.
Don't come here.
- Go to the pizza place...
- Hey.
What is it?
- Why did you want to see me here?
- I know.
- This place stinks. Let's get out.
- Are you okay?
What happened to your face?
What's going on?
It's nothing.
- Let's get out of here.
- Okay.
I also have something...
Chan Hong?
Yes, Dae Yong.
I heard you were close. Are you here
to take a break from studying?
Chan Hong told me multiple times
that he would introduce me to you.
I didn't think we would bump into
each other here.
Hey, you should have
given me a heads up.
I would have dressed better.
What is up with this place?
I'm sorry. He's never dated anyone.
I guess you're right. It must be
because he never dated anyone.
(Mom)
I think your phone's ringing.
You should take it outside.
I'll go answer this quickly.
Let's have a seat.
Mom, what is it?
What do you mean why?
You told me to call you on time!
My mom told me to come home...
so I have to hurry back.
See you tomorrow.
It was difficult to be normal.
I was below average.
- I'm home.
- Are you here?
- Have you eaten?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Chan Hong.
Show me your face.
- Take off your hoodie.
- It's nothing.
Chan Hong, are you not going to
tell me what's going on?
- What happened to your face?
- I said it's nothing!
You...
Come back out here.
What are you going to do
inside there?
Let's leave him be.
Turn a blind eye for him.
His face...
(Reminiscence of Kim Sung Ho)
We weren't even dating,
but why am I crying?
(Letter of Appointment)
You know that girl
who died last year.
Where is...
her mobile phone?
Hey.
Why do you have so much money?
Don't do that.
That's for my academy fees.
Who pays academies in cash
these days?
I heard your dad has a business.
Is he evading taxes?
He must be.
("Footprints")
(My unspoken words have
finally reached you...)
(Wet sand remembers
one's footprints.)
(Park Chan Hong)
(Wet sand remembers
one's footprints.)
Wet sand remembers
one's footprints.
(Seo Jung)
Please stop hitting on her.
A female high school student was
found dead this afternoon.
The police are under investigation.
The Gangpo Nambu Police Station
reported at four this afternoon...
that a teacher found...
a female high school student...
who was on the school flower garden.
The students and teachers
who found the girl made the report.
The firefighters
and police arrived on the scene,
but she had already passed away.
There weren't any addresses
or possessions near the body.
This is an announcement.
Just as announced in the assembly,
there will be a safety drill
after lunch.
All students shall gather
to the schoolyard.
Announcement to all.
Did you introduce Um Sae Yun
to screw me?
What are you talking about?
Why is that screwing you?
He's lying until the end,
and it disgusts me.
Grab him.
Do you want to die?
Why aren't you grabbing him?
What is it?
It's nothing.
I'd just like some time with him.
I just read the poem he wrote,
and I was so touched.
I want to tell him
how I felt about it.
Are you kidding me?
There's something I'd like
to ask you regarding that poem.
"Wet sand remembers
one's footprints."
Was that really your idea?
Tell me honestly.
Did you come up with that?
Yes. I think so.
If you need my help,
just say: "The weather is great."
Or you could keep
getting beat up here.
But you have to pay me back for it.
Think carefully.
We're all done. Thank you
for sparing the time.
Do you know...
why the ground freezes
during the winter?
It's holding onto the water...
that the seeds need during spring.
Wet sand remembers...
one's footprints.
The weather is so great!
Thank you so much.
No, don't be.
You need to pay me back.
- You agreed to it.
- What can I do for you?
- You can tell me anything. I'll...
- Jump.
What?
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Do you know...
the girl who died here last year?
Hey.
Did you kill Shin Seo Jung?
I should've never written
that darn poem.
(Seo Jung, Sae Yun, Mi Ra,
the beautiful girls of art club)
(Sae Yun, please give me a reply.
It's not me.)
(You don't believe me, do you?)
(Wet sand remembers
one's footprints.)
Our spring...
has begun.
Spring that does not pardon
dying things...
and reveals things
hidden in the snow.
Spring that urges you to shoot up.
That cruel spring has begun.
(I'm in trouble.)
(What's wrong?)
(The message has been read.)
(What did you say?)
(It wasn't read when I last checked
two weeks ago.)
(What are we going to do?)
(What else can we do?
We should find out who read it.)
(And we're going to make
that person die as she did.)
(What could you possibly do
with a poem?)
(The end)