(Episode 3)
Let me ask you one thing.
For someone who used to be
a loan shark and rogue,
how did you make it as a city
councilor?
What do you think...
politicians who have little to do
and much time do in the countryside?
You know what I'm talking about.
- I can help you with that.
- Gosh.
Those guys are not what I want.
I need real guys.
Young guys who really know nothing
about these things.
(Oh, you're a junior
from Jaeil High School.)
(The Limits of Poetic License)
In this way,
poetic license refers...
to a deviation from fact or form
for artistic purposes...
even though it may be grammatically
incorrect.
It allows spacing words
and ungrammatical sentences...
Having Kim Dae Yong is enough...
and now Heo Don Hyuk.
I must be jinxed.
How do you know that sentence?
What sentence do you mean?
"Wet sand remembers
one's footprints."
- How do you know that?
- I heard it at the flower bed...
from that girl.
- Can you prove it?
- I mean it.
I swear I heard it then.
If I find out it's a lie,
you're dead.
- Attention. As of now...
- You're not allowed to play here.
It's dangerous up there.
Please get down.
Those who overuse poetic license
as a way...
to cover up their inadequate writing
skills...
will have to pay its price.
See you somewhere quiet,
after school.
This type of people...
all likes the word "quiet."
They say: "Be quiet."
Or:
"Shut your mouth and keep quiet."
Hey, Poet Park.
- Let's talk, somewhere quiet.
- No!
Sorry?
It's nothing.
What did I tell you? You should
always keep writing.
It's hard to get inspiration.
How many times have I told you
Mr. Inspiration doesn't come easy?
What happened to your face?
Well, it's...
I'm getting my wisdom tooth.
You should get your wisdom tooth
pulled out soon.
Hey, wisdom tooth.
That's a good idea.
- Write a piece about wisdom tooth.
- Pardon?
I'll give you a week, okay?
- Got it? I'm giving you one week.
- Okay.
I have something to discuss
with you...
- regarding writing poems.
- I see. What is it?
I can't tell you here.
Could we go somewhere quiet?
Do you want to have dinner with me?
Yes, I'd love to!
- Oh, Miss.
- Yes.
- Where are you headed?
- Oh, we were...
going to discuss her plans
for college over dinner.
What a coincidence. I was just about
to have dinner with Writer Park.
You should join us.
Our two heroes as well.
Yes, why don't we?
It'll be good.
You guys know each other.
Yes, I'm fine with it.
- How about you, Writer Park?
- Yes.
I am a visible ninja.
- What is it?
- Oh, I just remembered...
I promised to go somewhere
with Heo Don Hyuk today.
- Can't you go there another time?
- I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Hey, where are you?
I saw Iron Man take you.
Text me if something comes up.
Text any word if you're in danger.
Come in. I live alone.
Alone?
It's cold.
I bet the house isn't soundproof.
You must hear everything
from the other rooms.
I hope anyone who lives next door...
can hear me when I scream.
("Wet sand remembers
one's footsteps.")
Is Seo Jung's boyfriend
that King Psycho mentioned...
Heo Don Hyuk?
Sit down.
When I watch movies from now on...
I think I'll understand what
the culprit is thinking.
Tell me...
anything you remember.
That day,
Kyung Pyo hid...
my cellphone so I went around
looking for it.
I saw Seo Jung at the flower bed.
Excuse me, did you...
What else?
She wore dirty sneakers...
- and had a pink cellphone.
- A cellphone?
- She had a cellphone?
- Yes.
Iron Man.
It had an Iron Man figurine on it.
And what else?
Well...
I was involved in a hit-and-run
accident that day.
So I can't remember properly.
- I mean it. Believe me.
- Hello, there.
I know you're inside. Hello?
Don Hyuk,
I barely live on rent money.
You're making things difficult.
I apologize. I'll get the money
in whatever way I can...
- Look.
- Ma'am.
Will this be enough?
This is enough. See you again.
I...
Why would you pay for that?
If it weren't for you...
Dae Yong would've taken it.
Can you let me go in return?
Let me go now.
I don't want to be involved in this.
Chan Hong!
That sentence you wrote was...
the last sentence
Seo Jung sent to me.
Before she died,
weird pictures went around.
You know that, right?
Yes, I heard recently.
Someone took those pictures...
and deliberately sent them to me.
Oh, the girl who fell
off the rooftop and died?
She was completely drunk.
Some guy was right next to her.
Then I guess she was
actually sleeping around.
- I know.
- So she was promiscuous.
- I should've met her first.
- I knew she was so easy.
Tell me, now.
Did you really see it?
Who was with Seo Jung?
It's true!
She was with a man with
a tattoo on his ankle.
It was a card tattoo.
A joker card.
He had a joker card tattoo.
Seo Jung's phone wasn't
with her body...
so I'm wondering if he was the one
who hid her phone.
And I think you were the last one
to see her phone.
Let's make a deal.
Sort of a contract.
A contract?
Don Hyuk asks for help in
a peculiar way.
I'm not asking you to help me
for nothing.
Dae Yong won't give up on you,
or Sae Yun.
Try to remember anything.
Then I'll protect you
from everything.
It's an offer I can't refuse.
But...
I'd really love to help...
but I can't remember anything.
I'm sincerely sorry.
(Chan Hong.)
Jerk.
Sae Yun.
You believe me, right?
I never did the things
as the rumor says.
Yes, I believe you.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
I knew I could trust...
Why aren't you looking me
in the eyes?
(The day of Seo Jung's death)
- Did you take a look at her locker?
- Not yet.
Why am I here?
I'm a pathetic fool.
I'm a small boat.
You are a wanderer.
If you do not visit me...
I will wait for you...
in the wind, snow, and rain.
Through day and night,
I am waiting for you to come.
But...
I know in my heart...
that you will come someday.
(Ms. Kim Ara, welcome to the VIP
date club. Click the URL below.)
(Following unknown link could harm
your device and personal data.)
I guess my faith has been answered.
Our bait is taken.
Sang Pil came up with such
a nice text.
I bet that person couldn't
resist but to click it.
We have the location.
Only seven students from Jaeil
High School live there.
I'll take care of this
as quickly as possible.
Who would've guessed that feisty
thing would have taken a video.
Hey, Ninja! Good to see you alive.
Beat it.
Why did you ignore
my texts last night?
Do you know how worried I was?
I guess Iron Man is more merciful
than I thought.
Please. I have a killer headache.
What happened? Tell me.
Who knows? I might be able to
help you.
I just feel sorry for you.
You're so popular
with Dae Yong and Don Hyuk.
- Am I your friend?
- Sorry.
I need to talk to you
about something.
Before that,
you should pray that you live.
I should go. You're bad luck.
We'll learn how this equation
can be used.
I told myself countless times.
If Sae Yun can forgive me
just once...
I would never back down ever again.
That I could do this...
even without Don Hyuk's help.
That oath was broken so easily.
I don't know why that punk
looks after you,
but if you act out because of that,
I'll kill you.
Answer me!
I'll get rid of Don Hyuk soon.
But we need to settle things
between us first.
Especially Sae Yun.
I am lethargic.
I'm dirty and cowardly.
What are you contemplating?
It's a great offer.
Iron Man becomes Ninja's bodyguard.
Tada!
My memories are so messed up
so I can't make a proper deal.
A dying message sent to
her boyfriend and an idiot.
Look at all the goosebumps I got!
He's looking for a missing phone,
but what do I know?
Hey, Mi Ra.
You dropped something.
Maybe it's one of your charms.
Psycho, you're giving me
the chills again.
I really don't want to talk to you,
but let me say something.
Okay, go ahead.
You're not smart, athletic,
or good looking.
The words you say are even worse.
What are you good at?
Mi Ra, until when do I have to
give you my answer?
You're so annoying. Move.
Sae Yun, let's go.
What do I say, she's so feisty.
That feisty fox!
Ninja!
- There!
- What the heck?
- Geez.
- Are you crazy?
I can't find it
how much we look for.
What are we doing on a weekend?
What have I done wrong to be
with you on a nice spring day?
King Psycho, if only
you hadn't pulled the prank...
and hid my phone,
this wouldn't have happened.
You're blaming the wrong person.
Stop blaming me
and start using your head.
For Pete's sake.
How dare he races
in this sacred school...
where the youth are studying?
- I almost forgot.
- What is it?
Cigarette butts.
- What are you talking about?
- When Shin Seo Jung died,
I was hiding in the corner
to surprise you.
But the hit-and-run car threw
a cigarette butt and ran away.
What did you say?
Hello, I'm Oh Kyung Pyo.
What a coincidence
that we meet here on holiday.
We need to go back.
Say it in detail.
I mean...
This is all that I saw.
I'm telling the truth, Don Hyuk.
I may look like this,
but I'm a nice kid.
Please believe me.
Okay.
Why aren't you eating?
Help yourselves.
You can eat while talking.
Really? Can I really eat them?
You can stop being so formal too.
We're the same age.
It's okay
because I have a late birthday.
Hey, your birthday is in May.
Yes, I was born in late May.
Don Hyuk, I love
that you're older than me.
Have you changed your mind?
Honestly, I don't want
to get involved.
I don't even remember anything.
Okay.
Why aren't you talking politely?
You jerk.
You're quite tough.
All right. If the second hand makes
one round...
and reaches number 12,
you will go back
to the year before...
Are you sure this works?
- Why do I have to do this?
- Come on.
Focus on the watch.
Y♪♪tube is always right.
You need to remember this
for the both of us to live.
I helped with the cigarette story.
How could you mess it up?
This isn't only your problem
anymore.
Focus.
Here.
If the second hand reaches 12,
your eyes will...
close automatically.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
All right. Here we go.
You are now...
lying down on a green pasture.
You are now going...
into the deep...
where you will find...
the abyss.
All right.
- We're going back...
- Where did he throw my phone away?
To that day a year ago.
This is driving me insane.
What are you talking about?
Excuse me.
Have you seen a cellular phone
around here somewhere?
It had a drawing of a ninja
on the case.
I haven't.
Okay. Thank you.
Wait a minute.
Seo Jung is talking...
about the grass and trees.
She's worried about me.
She's trying to look
for my phone together.
She's asking where I lost it.
Was there...
any other person around you?
I hear something at the back.
Let's go...
and see who's there.
It's suddenly dark.
I can't see anything.
Okay.
Go further inside.
Go deeper...
into your mind.
The darkness will be cleared now.
Who's there?
I like you.
What did you say?
I really like you.
I like you as much as the universe.
I like you as much
as the stars in the sky.
Who are you talking about?
- Hey.
- I like you.
- Son, your father's home.
Your mom is home too.
Hey, Chan Hong.
- I like you.
- Chan Hong!
- Wake up!
- Chang Hong.
Your parents are here.
- Hey!
- Are you asleep, Chan Hong?
Wake up, Chan Hong.
Get back to your senses.
Why are you so quiet?
What's happening here? Who are you?
I'm Kyung Pyo.
And?
What are you doing
with all these candles?
I don't know where to start.
I'm in love.
Excuse me?
Why, you!
Do you think this is New York?
What are you doing?
Put out the candles.
(Do you have a problem logging in?)
Which jerk took it?
What was he trying to hide?
- Are you from Jaeil High School?
- Yes.
We need to track some people down.
You don't need to know the details.
Call me right away
if you see someone...
who has a pink phone
among those names.
Yes, sir.
(Um Sae Yun)
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Please come in.
(Beautiful three musketeers
of art club)
You can look around as you wish.
(The day Sae Yun won the award)
I had once dreamed...
of becoming an artist.
I feel moved by this.
I see.
I hope your business grows big...
so you can help our artists.
Because I have various businesses,
I get to hear different rumors.
I think it was a year ago.
I heard something bad happened
to one of the artists here.
Well...
Dear children.
Cheer up.
(Episode 4)
Many things happen in life.
Don't try too hard to forget.
If...
there's anything your friend left
before she left,
cherish her by taking a look at it.
About Seo Jung...
Yes.
What about her? All of a sudden?
Did she call you or anything
before she died?
Why would she call me?
Well, we used to be friends.
We weren't that close.
You guys were close so I hung out
with her, too.
About that post on the online
dating board...
do you think Seo Jung really posted
that?
She must have.
It was the same ID...
and she even used to stole money.
Isn't it strange?
Why would she use the same ID
on those sites?
It's not like she's not well off.
That's funny.
Do you have to be poor
to steal money?
Why are you being so sensitive?
Oh, I'm sorry Sae Yun.
It's just that...
you kept talking about someone
who has died.
Let's talk about something else.
You trust me, right?
Of course, I do.
I have a secret.
Can you promise me not to tell
anyone?
What is it?
Aren't you going to check?
It seems to be urgent.
Give me a minute.
Sae Yun,
I got an urgent call from home.
I'll talk to you next time. Sorry.
(I want to stop this.)
(Stop it? I'll tell everyone
what you did.)
(You just looked up and around,
didn't you?)
(Art Room)
Hey, Mi Ra.
Have you seen Sae Yun...
Get out of my way.
We had a talk just the two of us.
You're being so cold.
I have nothing to say to you.
I have something to ask you.
I was wondering about something.
Let go of me.
Hey, Sae Yun!
You have a pink cellphone,
don't you?
I guess you do have it.
Let me take a look at it.
I said let me see it!
Where is it?
Is it in your pocket?
Get it out!
- What are you doing?
- Take it out.
Come on now.
Where's the cellphone?
Give it to me right now.
- What are you...
- I'll protect you.
Give it to me.
Remember whatever you can.
Darn it.
I can't remember anything.
What do you think you're doing?
If I find out it's a lie,
you're dead.
The poetic license refers
to a deviation from fact or form...
for artistic purposes...
even though it may be grammatically
incorrect.
It allows spacing words
and ungrammatical sentences...
as well as incorrect spelling.
- What for?
- Beauty.
To achieve the utmost beauty.
Let go of me.
Hand it to me.
Yes, Chan Hong.
Hey, Don Hyuk.
- I want to take a look at it!
- I remembered.
I'll make a contract with you.
If you want to sign this deal...
come to the back door.
Get it out of your pocket.
I said give it to me!
- Do you have it here?
- What are you doing?
Take everything out from
your pocket.
Where is it?
You jerk! Are you insane?
Geez!
Listen to me.
From now on,
you're not going...
to touch Chan Hong and Sae Yun...
or else you're dead.
I'll take care of this.
You guys should get going.
Okay.
Thank you.
You don't have to be ashamed.
Don Hyuk.
How can this all stop?
You have to be honest...
to yourself.
Even if you're shaking now...
or scared,
you don't have to be ashamed.
You just have to acknowledge
and accept it.
That's how you cross the line.
When you cross the line...
you can sometimes see
something else.
Get back to Sae Yun.
Don't make a mistake as I did.
If you don't say it...
she'll never know how you feel.
What about the contract?
Take some rest today
and we'll talk tomorrow.
Consider this a down payment.
Seo Jung!
Hey, Seo Jung!
Arent' you going to get it straight?
What's with you these days?
Oh, hey, Don Hyuk.
Sorry, I'm not so good these days.
Are the rumors all true?
Is that why you're acting like this?
Would you believe me if I told you
it's not true?
I said I'll believe it!
Seo Jung.
I believe you.
Tell me quickly.
Tell me now!
Don Hyuk,
can you just...
believe none of the pictures are me?
Just say: "It must've been hard..."
"but it will all pass..."
"as if nothing had ever happened."
And can't you just let it go by?
You won't tell me to the end.
It's not that I didn't believe
Seo Jung.
I was only mad at myself
because she couldn't rely on me.
What was left within my heart...
had no power.
Hey, Chan Hong.
Why are you following me?
Sae Yun.
I...
like you.
I like you a lot.
I really like you...
but...
the thing is...
I have to cross a line.
- But...
- I know.
I know you like me.
Let's get drunk.
Let's let our souls be drunk.
It's only 21 grams.
Instead of alcohol...
let us get drunk on
tears of comfort.
This is a game I played...
with someone I was close with...
when we got out for fresh air
while drawing.
Our love is...
boiling like a pot.
So...
let's cool down underneath
a palm tree.
You're good at this.
- I'm good, right?
- You are good.
Our ending will probably be...
(Motel)
Did anything...
happen with Dae Yong that day?
No.
I was annoyed with
his weird jokes though.
I'm sorry.
This is strange.
Why do I always feel at ease
when I'm with you?
I forget about my worries with you.
(ChungGyver, computer, networks,
electronic appliances)
Chan Hong.
That thing's existed since 1990.
Throw out all your garbage.
What are you talking about?
You can use this for more than
100 years after I'm done with it.
Are you going to give it to
your son?
I'm done.
Wait, do you really want to
try using this?
Does it even work?
Of course!
I have a long history with
this thing.
Do you see these scratches
in the corner?
When I see these...
I relive the memories all over.
If I exaggerate a bit,
I am giving...
a bit of my life to you.
Do you want to listen to this?
Lee Ji Yeon.
She was the queen during our times.
Isn't she pretty?
Lee Ji Yeon.
Even though...
the audio of this is worse
than a CD or an mp3...
when you flip the sides after
you're done with one...
that's when...
I kind of feel like...
I'm intruding a bit into
this singer's life.
I think about what
she went through...
when she was deciding the song list
for side A and side B.
- Dad.
- Yes?
You talk like a poet.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I guess I take after you.
Thank you.
For saying you're like me.
Spring flowers aren't...
afraid of withering.
They do not think...
of the days they will pass
and bear fruit.
They just bloom...
in their own shapes and forms.
They live in the moment...
and bloom...
to the best they can.
"Wet sand remembers
one's footprints."
Yes.
That sentence you wrote
in your poem...
it's the same sentence Seo Jung sent
me before she died.
That's why I wanted to talk to you.
I was afraid to tell you
because I'm not brave...
but I want to be honest now.
Seo Jung left this in my locker
before she died.
That's right.
When you love a princess...
a venomous snake always
tags along.
You've finally gone crazy!
Where are you going?
We have to go to Don Hyuk!
No way.
If he finds out it was
with Sae Yun...
things will go down.
Do you remember anything?
No, right?
Yet you still made a deal,
didn't you?
If we give him this, everything
will be solved. Let's go.
I said no.
So, you will die with this bomb
in your arms?
What a great choice, sir!
I give you my utmost praise!
If he finds out
you have the phone...
he will rip you to shreds.
No one will find your remains!
I don't care.
Sae Yun is more important to me.
Dang it.
I took it from her
because it seemed dangerous.
"Sae Yun is more important to me."
Stop pooping from your mouth.
Do you watch a lot of
romance movies?
Is this some "my first love will be
my last" kind of a deal?
What do we do
with this pitiful youth?
What is it?
When should we meet? I'm ready
to listen now.
You see?
Ninja, I hope you rest in peace.
I'll be sure to pay my respects.
It was nice knowing you.
Oh, no.
Goodness.
Ninja.
Let's do this.
Let's tell him...
something half true and half lie.
Is it really possible?
How do we find
who Seo Jung met with this?
I'll show you
what a dangerous thing...
your smartphones can be.
You said the email was logged in
automatically, right?
Check it.
Okay.
It's here.
Tada!
What did I say?
Hacking?
You don't have to know any of that.
She was beautiful, wasn't she?
Look at her smile.
Right.
(Unknown user)
This smells fishy.
Bingo. Chan Hong.
You must trust this Oh Kyung Pyo.
Okay.
Let's see.
This account has already
been deactivated.
Let's see some photos he shared.
He looks normal.
(Images that are likely
to be relevant)
It's a private account.
Let's make
a fake foreigner account...
and wait for our request
to be accepted.
Why does it have
to be a foreigner's account?
If the request is from a foreigner,
they usually don't get suspicious.
Plus, if it's a girl,
he would completely
let his guard down.
You're dead now.
After your work, tell him
that you suddenly remembered...
and spill some
of the important information.
He took the bait.
He's addicted to social media.
He's uploading a photo every hour.
His name is Kang Hyun Ku.
He must've been smart because he's
an art major at Hankook University.
He's even...
What's that?
That's our school uniform.
Then he might've known Seo Jung.
We'll have to ask him in person.
I wonder if we can do it.
You told me
we shouldn't call Don Hyuk.
I'm against that.
Then...
- shall we launch our operation?
- It's what we do all the time.
It hurts so much.
You took some medicine,
so you'll be fine anytime soon.
It hurts.
Hey. She's gone, isn't she?
- Yes.
- Hurry.
This is hot.
Ninja,
how many times
have you been to Seoul?
I think I've been there five times.
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
I heard there are too many people...
in the Seoul subway
that you can't get off sometimes.
Is that true?
- It's not true, is it?
- I went with my parents...
so I'm not that sure.
But there really are
a lot of people.
And there are
many subway stations too.
- Give me your phone.
- What do you need it for?
Hurry up.
- Don't do anything stupid.
- All right.
- What are you doing?
- It's nothing.
This will protect you and me.
Here you go.
Why would you install
a location tracking app for couples?
We have become one.
With our 12 years of friendship,
we are like a married couple.
I love you, Park Chan Hong.
- You're such a lunatic.
- Don't delete it.
I get lost easily,
so don't delete it.
You're here.
- Yes.
- I've heated it for you.
- You're crazy.
- What?
You're a crazy psycho.
Get ready and put it on. It's hot.
My legs hurt.
Hey, you said you've been here
a couple of times.
He doesn't seem to know the way.
Do something.
It's my first time in this area too.
Why does he keep going straight?
How many times have we gone
back and forth?
Have we come here to walk?
Doesn't he get tired?
He's not an Iron Man for no reason.
Taxi.
You should've grabbed one earlier
if you were planning to do that.
- Taxi. Hurry up.
- Taxi!
- Here!
- Taxi.
Are you sure it's this person?
What if we're wrong?
Don't worry.
He mentioned class registration and
that he's studying hard on his feed.
No one asked,
yet he showed his class schedule.
It's Abstract Art.
Arts College Room 105
under Professor Kim Myung Hee.
King Psycho, it's my first time
realizing that you're quite useful.
Just wait for a moment.
I'll catch him even if it means
I have to risk my life.
Hey, it's that person, isn't it?
You're right.
She was with the person
who had a tattoo on his ankle.
I need to see
if he has a tattoo on his ankle.
Don Hyuk!
You stand out
because you're too tall.
Look around.
No one else has a body like this.
Who has hands like these
in an art college?
How are you going to hold a brush?
You look like you'd hold a bat.
Don't you agree?
- What did you say?
- Excuse me?
I didn't mean in that way.
You're too tall,
and I look unique too.
There's no one else but you, Ninja.
Go on now.
Geez.
Hello.
What am I going to do?
Go in.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
- All right.
- Okay, down.
- Down!
Let's do this. Here we go.
- Ready.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
You're Hyun Ku
from Jaeil High School, aren't you?
- Who are you?
- I'm...
Park Hong Chan.
- I'm in the art club.
- I see.
How can I help you?
You knew Seo Jung, right?
- It's Shin Seo Jung.
- Shin Seo Jung?
What about her?
It isn't here.
Can't you find it?
Look on the other side.
- It's not here.
- It's not?
Hey, you over there.
Who are you guys?
I almost forgot.
The more fragrant a flower is,
it does not
only attract butterflies.
It attracts bees
and all other pests.
Darn it.
(What are you up to, Sae Yun?)
(I just got home. I'm hungry.)
(Haven't you had dinner yet?)
(I came with my family here.
It was really nice.)
(I envy you. It looks delicious.)
(You have a message from MITHRA.)
(You killed Shin Seo Jung.)
(The Limits of Poetic License)
(The end.)
Why are you doing things
you don't normally do?
You took pictures of her
and asked for money.
I told you I was going to kill you
if you lied.
Kiss is all about timing.
It's a timing battle.
Things that are slightly twisted...
sometimes create excellent rhythms.
That post on the online
dating board wasn't...
written by Seo Jung.
If you go after the punks
who are trying to catch Sae Yun...
That can't happen.
That puts Sae Yun in danger.
The day Shin Seo Jung died,
you were at school too.