HYENA
THIS DRAMA IS PURELY FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH
ACTUAL PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, ASSOCIATIONS,
OR LOCATIONS
EPISODE 14
Ms. Jung Geum-ja.
Yes?
While working on
Ha Chan-ho's divorce case,
is it true that you and Mr. Yoon were
involved in an inappropriate relationship?
What exactly do you mean by
an inappropriate relationship?
COMMISSIONER KIM JUNG-SU,
PARK DAE-HO, LEE SANG-HO
I'm asking if you were close enough
to share private information.
Yes.
That's right.
COMMISSIONER GANG MAN-SEOK
Ms. Jung approached you imposing
as Kim Hee-sun, an old friend from school.
Is that also true?
Hey, what's up?
Hee-jae.
Today, I met the investigators
from the Korean Bar Association.
I told them
that Ms. Jung lied to you
and approached you as Kim Hee-sun.
I also told them that you guys dated
and that I think that's when
she stole information from you.
Hey.
-Gi-hyeok.
-Hee-jae.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
for me.
Ha Chan-ho's case is crucial to me.
You know my position in the firm.
You know that better than anyone.
I...
I also want to make partner.
I want to have my own team,
be in charge of a case,
make arguments in court,
and do everything on my own.
But...
But in order to do that...
You and Ms. Jung need to be gone.
That's how...
That's how I can seize this opportunity.
Once you're in my position...
Actually, never mind.
That will never happen.
But if you were ever to be in my position,
you'd understand.
I know...
I know your dad got injured.
I really can't believe
I'm being such a horrible friend.
I don't want to be like this.
Gi-hyeok.
Why don't you just apologize?
Just say you're sorry
as my colleague and friend.
Do you feel too sorry
to apologize?
I'm sorry, Hee-jae.
Thank you for telling me
before things got out of hand.
That has
nothing to do
with this disciplinary hearing.
Why did Ms. Jung
willfully approach you
by telling such lies?
Wasn't it so that
she could illegally
obtain information on Ha Chan-ho?
No, sir.
It's true that I felt
a sexual attraction to Mr. Yoon.
I didn't think he'd see me
if I told him who I really was.
It was my way of getting to know him.
That's ridiculous.
He was the opposing lawyer.
No one can blame us for falling in love
even if that person killed your family.
Have you not read a romance novel
or watched a romantic movie before?
So you're saying
that you two were in love?
Yes.
-We were.
Then do you admit
that you both shared information?
-No.
-We never did.
Ms. Jung.
Then how did you come across
Ha Chan-ho's personal information?
It acted as conclusive evidence
for the divorce suit.
I'm
just
extremely competent.
That's how good she is.
She sometimes does things
that other lawyers can't.
She obviously fooled you
to get that information.
Do you have evidence?
It's obvious judging by the circumstances.
Then you can go ahead and think that
based on the circumstantial evidence.
I never
gave her
my client's information.
Ms. Jung.
As a lawyer, I'm obligated to keep
my client's information confidential.
So I can't tell you everything.
But one thing is for sure.
Mr. Yoon and I never once
shared any information.
How did they find out about Kim Hee-sun?
We all have our reasons for doing things.
What an amazing friendship you have.
I want to know what you said.
I bet they asked the same stuff.
Is that really important?
What do you think the result will be?
If there are no variables,
it'll get rejected.
There's one variable, though.
Song Pil-jung.
This isn't merely about
two lawyers dating each other.
It's about trust,
which is the most fundamental thing
that a lawyer needs to keep.
Then do you want this to end quietly?
If the reporters find out,
it'll harm your firm's reputation--
He's willing to risk that
and wants you to make a proper judgment.
Mr. Song cares about
the overall legal field.
Okay, I understand what you mean.
He thinks the decision
you're going to make
will act as a great example
regarding the work ethics of lawyers.
Congratulations, Mr. Ha Jun-ho.
You're now the CEO of Issume.
This is all thanks to you.
Don't mention it.
This was possible
because you have what it takes.
I guess other people disagree.
Why would you say that
when we're gathered here to celebrate?
The stock price is plummeting.
It shows that people don't trust
the new CEO of Issume.
The company will disappear at this rate.
The stock price will recover with time.
Issume has gone through a lot,
but I know it'll endure it.
That's how sturdy Issume is.
I guess I didn't know much about Issume
seeing that I was so worried.
Hye-won!
Do you even know
what you're going to have to deal with?
You should help him out.
Don't be so mean to him
like you were with Chan-ho.
-Dad.
-Do it for Issume.
We're going through hard times,
so we need to overcome it together.
That's what you call family.
"Family"?
Don't worry too much, sir.
Pil-jung.
When did we
first meet?
I can't even remember.
Sir.
Well...
What do you think will happen
with Supreme Court Justice Yoon?
He worked as a judge for over 30 years.
It'll be humiliating for him
to even stand in court as a defendant.
He won't say anything to harm Issume.
If he does,
he'll be denying his own verdict
and his career as a judge.
Okay, hurry up
and take care of what happened
with Chan-ho as well.
Okay, sir.
I want to get some rest. You should go.
Get some rest, sir.
-What are you doing?
-I thought we got fired.
Not yet.
"Not yet"?
Then when?
The disciplinary committee
will need time to make a decision.
I'm suspicious of everything that
Seo Jeong-hwa did on the day she died.
She's still thinking about her?
She told Han Su-jeong
that she's going to leave with Ha Jun-ho.
HA JUN-HO, SEO JEONG-HWA
ELOPEMENT
And the painting.
"The painting"?
Seo Jeong-hwa
was looking after a painting.
She was going to sell that
to prepare money.
Ms. Jung.
How was she going to sell it
when she didn't even own it?
She was only looking after it.
She was looking after a painting.
What did Seo Jeong-hwa always do?
Money laundering.
Yes.
It's highly possible that it was
someone's slush fund.
A slush fund?
And why do you think
she went to Yeonan Pier?
She wouldn't have gone there
to eat sashimi all by herself.
And then White Hotel.
The drug test results.
She took sleeping pills with alcohol.
But neither Ha Chan-ho
nor Seo Jeong-hwa had sleeping pills.
I know she hated drugs,
but she could've secretly brought it
to sedate Ha Chan-ho.
Ha Chan-ho found Seo Jeong-hwa by
tracking the GPS device on her cell phone.
Ha Chan-ho called Seo Jeong-hwa
at 7:20 p.m.
And he entered White Hotel at 8:00 p.m.
She wouldn't have had enough time to get
a doctor's prescription and the pills.
Room service.
Either the person who brought room service
brought the sleeping pills,
or that person
secretly put them in their drinks.
Did you find out who it was?
No, it wasn't a hotel staff.
The person was from another company.
Mr. Na is busy making phone calls.
Okay.
And...
the second phone.
Seo Jeong-hwa used that to contact people
other than Ha Chan-ho.
I wonder where that went.
Who owns White Hotel again?
White Corporation.
Mr. Kim, I want you
to look into White Hotel's stocks,
the company history,
and when it was built.
Aren't you going to come
to the meeting soon?
A meeting?
Yes, it's about Ha Chan-ho.
Did Mr. Ga gather the meeting?
-Yes.
-Okay, I got it.
Should I start packing again?
PARK JU-HO
Hey, it's me.
Ha Jun-ho?
The newly appointed CEO of Issume Group?
Didn't you know?
Ms. Jung and Mr. Yoon
already knew about this.
The relationship between Seo Jeong-hwa,
Ha Jun-ho, and Ha Chan-ho.
So she was cheating with Ha Jun-ho?
I mean, CEO Ha?
If the trial lasts too long,
people will start talking.
We already have enough rumors as it is.
It won't be good
for both Issume and our firm.
So please make sure that doesn't happen.
Okay, sir.
You may leave.
Hey, Mr. Ma.
When will the disciplinary committee
come up with a decision?
I did ask them to hurry.
-When is the EP general meeting?
-In 15 days, sir.
Why don't you request Ms. Kim's
dismissal in the meeting as well?
That's not important right now.
Fifteen days?
It'll be too late.
Gather the steering committee now.
Okay, sir. What is the agenda?
The expulsion of Ms. Jung and Mr. Yoon.
Okay, sir.
I'm sure you've all heard,
but I'll be in charge of Ha Chan-ho's case
from now on.
Mr. Yoon and Ms. Jung
will have to stay out of this case
until the disciplinary committee
tells them their final decision.
Why was the disciplinary hearing held?
Do you know?
Everyone in the firm knows.
Why are you so slow?
First, let's check what's going on.
Please tell me
what you're in charge of doing.
Mr. Kim.
-I was given a task a while ago.
-"A while ago"?
I was told to check White Hotel's history
and the ownership of shares.
"White Hotel"? Why?
-What about you, Ms. Boo?
-I'm looking into ArtSky's clients.
I'm searching for the guy
who delivered room service.
I see.
I want all of you to stop
what you're working on.
We're going to go
with involuntary manslaughter.
Keep it short and safe.
One mistake can turn it into murder.
So we're going to admit that he's guilty?
He was caught red-handed
at the crime scene.
You know what that means.
Then what about the work we put in--
We don't have time.
What do you mean
it could turn into murder?
I'm saying he had a good enough reason
to murder Seo Jeong-hwa.
You know Ha Jun-ho, right?
Ha Chan-ho's stepbrother.
And Seo Jeong-hwa.
They were in a love triangle.
It's too obvious.
I'm just going to keep doing
what I've been working on.
-Mr. Na, tell me once you're done.
-Okay.
MEETING ROOM
Mr. Yoon.
HANKOOK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sure you're going through a lot.
Sorry I can't do anything to help.
It's okay.
I'm sorry for not being able
to take care of the team.
I'm not here as your teammate.
Do you know how it feels
when you want to help someone out
in any kind of way possible
but you can't?
All you can do is
watch that person from afar,
and so it hurts even more.
I bet you know how it feels.
You also once liked someone from afar.
I feel like this is my only chance
to tell you this.
Ms. Boo.
But I'm still going to help you whenever.
If you need my help,
I'll help you with whatever.
Go ahead and use your smart colleague
as much as you want.
Cheer up.
I came to tell you that.
I'm not going to use you,
but thanks anyway.
I don't want to put others
through this mess.
YOON CHUNG-YEON
You should eat a bit more.
I'm done.
Dad.
I'm your lawyer.
I'll be the one defending you.
Can you
be honest with me?
Hee-jae.
I'm not going to say anything.
I thought so.
You tried to keep your secret
by even sacrificing your life.
So I figured you wouldn't change your mind
just because you managed to survive.
It's all for your sake.
Who?
Me and Hyeok-jae?
Grandpa thinks you're innocent.
He asked me to prove that you're innocent
in court.
I...
I should've died.
Then why don't you jump from here?
This time, you'll be able to die.
Why don't you go ahead and jump?
You know those people
who commit suicide
to keep their boss' secret?
They act like some kind of loyal servants.
They think everything will be fine
if they sacrifice themselves.
People who exist for no one else
but their superiors.
They practically volunteer to be a minion.
You're a judge, Dad.
Your job is to make a verdict
after you check
if someone is guilty or not.
So you shouldn't do anything
that goes against your conscience.
That's your job.
Dad.
You were against
the Inheritance Tax Act, weren't you?
You're that kind of judge.
Please let me continue to respect you.
What...
do I need to do?
Just reveal the fact
that you're a scapegoat.
Just admit what you did wrong
and get punished for it.
That's the only way
I'll be able to defend you.
I'm not going to let them frame you
for something you didn't even do.
The person who was in charge
of the room service was a guy
named O Chang-u,
but he took the day off today.
It was his last day.
Is it something urgent?
Why did you come all the way here?
It's not something he can stop.
What?
He messed with the wrong person.
What do you mean?
When can I get the forensics report?
Eun-yeong, I heard they were told
to keep things confidential.
It's too late for that.
They told the press
as soon as Ha Chan-ho got arrested.
You think the cops did that?
No way.
They didn't know
he'd get arrested red-handed.
I heard the press got there really fast.
But I wonder how that was possible.
What if they knew that Ha Chan-ho
was going to get arrested red-handed?
What?
What if it was all a set-up?
-What are you saying?
-Isn't that him?
Yes, it is.
Hey, O Chang-u.
Hey, wait. He went that way.
Gosh, he's very fast.
Why did he run? He doesn't even know me.
Well, that proves one thing.
He's hiding something.
Hey, Ji-eun, it's me. Send me
Seo Jeong-hwa's GPS location record.
Forensics got there at 12:40 a.m.
Judging by the cadaveric spasm,
she was killed about three to four hours
before the autopsy.
-Let's go.
-Yes, ma'am.
If you look at the next picture...
-Hand them out.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Ms. Jung, we're having a meeting--
-I'm aware.
Please take a look.
SEO JEONG-HWA'S TIMELINE
7:30 P.M. SPOKE WITH HA JUN-HO
ON THE PHONE
Seo Jeong-hwa's estimated time of death
is between 8:40 p.m. and 9:40 p.m.
However, the tracker on her phone
was turned on and off at 10:12 p.m.
What about it?
Jeez, let's keep listening.
Please continue, Ms. Jung.
At that time,
neither Seo Jeong-hwa, who died,
nor Ha Chan-ho, who was asleep,
was able to fiddle with her phone.
It's possible that someone else was there.
That also explains
why the second phone vanished.
Ms. Jung.
That hypothesis only works
if we believe Ha Chan-ho, right?
But you see,
if Ha Chan-ho actually killed her,
then this hypothesis is useless.
-Mr. Ga.
-That's what the prosecutor will say.
What I'm saying is...
And the sleeping pills too.
Ha Chan-ho is a junkie.
Sleeping pills may not even affect him.
Are we
prosecutors?
No, we're not.
The important thing here is...
It's the fact that you've been removed
from this case.
SONG & KIM HR TEAM
AS THE RESULT OF THE MEETING...
YOU ARE DISMISSED FOR VIOLATION OF DIGNITY
AND DEFAMING THE FIRM
Why did they send this?
"Dismissed"? So they're fired?
-Ms. Jung, did you hear--
-Start packing up.
The disciplinary committee
hasn't even decided, yet they're fired?
So the disciplinary committee's decision
doesn't even matter?
Isn't this so unfair?
I guess the decision was made
by the steering committee.
It's what Mr. Song wants to do.
Still...
Let's just wrap up the meeting.
YOU ARE DISMISSED FOR VIOLATION OF DIGNITY
AND DEFAMING THE FIRM
It's me.
Yes, I know. What's up?
You got the notice, right?
What about it?
So we're not just removed
from the Ha Chan-ho Case.
Our limbs have been cut off.
Shall I tell you
what your next move should be?
Stand tall and clear your office.
Be confident.
You're
really leaving?
Thanks for all your help.
I mean...
How could you just leave?
This is too sudden.
And I can't believe the firm decided
to do this just because of the rumors.
I guess everyone knows
about the rumors now.
They call it
"The Fall of a Judge and His Family."
That's why Mr. Song deserted me.
And apparently, I leaked information
to Ms. Jung
because of my personal feelings.
No, that's not what I meant.
It's all right.
But only believe half of those rumors.
Half of them is true,
but the other half is not.
Well, can I give you a hand with anything?
Shall I help you pack?
This office...
Mr. Ga will use this office, right?
-Yes.
-You should
help him out a lot.
About the Ha Chan-ho Case...
Whether it was involuntary manslaughter
or murder,
there are many things
that seem suspicious.
I figured you wouldn't notice them.
At the moment,
you just want to stay focused on one goal
while obeying Mr. Song.
-Hee-jae.
-I was like that too,
so I know what it's like. That's all.
You see,
the only thing I can do now
is wrapping this up as soon as possible.
That is my task.
Becoming a partner at Song & Kim...
It's very cool.
Your parents will be proud of you.
Everyone around you will be.
Hee-jae.
I guess...
we might end up meeting
in the courtroom one day.
If that ever happens,
I won't go easy on you.
We're still friends, right?
Gosh.
I'm sad that
you're actually leaving the firm.
I have to say,
you've definitely grown on me.
Well, do you have another job lined up?
Oh, right.
There will be many law firms
that would want to hire Mr. Yoon.
And as for you, you're a tough lady.
We'll meet again, wherever that may be.
So don't be sad.
You were going to leave
without even saying goodbye?
I'm very sad
that we're letting you go like this.
However,
I had to put the firm before you
even though I care about you.
I hope you understand.
If I get reprimanded by the association,
I'll protest and appeal
to the Ministry of Justice.
They haven't notified me
of their decision,
but I think I know what it'll be.
I'm sure they're busy trying to figure out
exactly what it is that you want.
-Hee-jae--
-My father is recovering pretty quickly.
He'll stand trial after he recovers,
which will be soon.
And I'll be his attorney.
Yes, he'll be able to trust you
and rely on you.
You'll be summoned
to appear in court as a witness.
Get ready for it.
You know how I like to work
better than anybody else does.
I won't disappoint you.
I'll look forward to it.
Dad.
What now?
AP EON is buying Issume's stocks in bulk.
Did you know?
Hye-won, I said I'd try to stop--
The stock price has already plummeted.
Why did you let this happen?
AP EON?
All our subsidiaries are struggling
because we pushed ahead
with the acquisition of Gnosis.
We have no way of stopping AP EON
because money has run dry.
That's impossible.
You still can't see the big picture.
-Dad!
-Call Mr. Song.
Until when
will you blindly trust Song Pil-jung?
He never lets his power slip away
even when a new administration
takes office
or in case of political power shifts.
Do you really not know how he does it?
He only sees
and cares about what he needs.
I'll call him. You should get out.
Dad, you don't have time
to be lounging around like this!
I said, get out!
-Sir! Are you okay?
-Dad.
-Dad!
-Stay with me, please!
Chairman Ha got home from the ICU.
We'll have to see how he recovers.
All right.
What was that about? Good news for us?
Well, it's not bad news.
Great, although I don't know what it is.
Oh, right.
Did you ever share any information
about Supreme Court Justice Yoon
with Ms. Jung?
That was very reckless of you.
-I was just--
-Why did you
try to use Ms. Jung?
-It's personal.
-No, you can't say that.
It's affecting me, as you can see.
So you can't say it's personal.
Why did I have to hear
that ridiculous nonsense from her?
I just
wanted confirmation on Song Pil-jung's,
I mean Mr. Song's intentions.
I also wanted to tell you
that I've only just begun.
This isn't over.
But I'm sure she doesn't know
where that information is from.
You obviously don't know her well at all.
I'm sorry.
What's done is done,
so let's shake it off and forget about it.
AP EON
is now Issume's
second-largest shareholder.
But to outdo Chairman Ha's family,
you'll have to persuade other shareholders
to entrust you with their voting rights.
That's why I have you.
The shareholders trust you
a lot more than Ha Jun-ho.
But Ha Hye-won would've been
a different story.
You think so?
If I step in and reveal myself,
people will think a foreign investor
is acquiring a Korean company.
You'll have to do this for me.
Anyway, congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm with a client.
Do you realize how rude this is?
Why? I know both of you well enough.
-It's been a while, Kevin.
-Yes, hello. You look great.
Bullshit.
I heard you fired Jung Geum-ja
and Yoon Hee-jae.
Were you that anxious?
You couldn't even wait
until the EP general meeting?
I guess you want to get me fired
at that meeting.
It doesn't look nice
to fire a number of people at once.
-Right?
-Min-joo.
I heard Chairman Ha collapsed.
You see, I'm pretty quick too.
Some people are still loyal to me.
If you're done, we can leave.
-Okay.
-No, wait.
Why are you getting up?
I'm going to leave.
Sit back down, Kevin.
Come on, just sit down.
You're wining and dining here,
knowing Chairman Ha collapsed,
which means he's no longer useful to you.
How did you get to where you are now?
Chairman Ha introduced you to my father.
But the mutt is now biting its owner.
-Kim Min-joo.
-That's all you are.
A mutt raised by my family.
You think you've become someone worthy,
but that's not the case.
Once a mutt, always a mutt.
Shut the fuck up!
That's right.
That's the Song Pil-jung I know.
No wonder my sister
came to hate your guts.
It's too bad you missed.
I would've sued your ass
if I had been hit.
Anyway, wrap up your conversation.
Just so you know though,
I am going to take a stance this time.
What do you think? Sounds fun, right?
So where were we?
Like I said earlier,
the other shareholders...
I didn't expect you
to talk back to Mr. Song like that.
You've toughened up.
I guess someone rubbed off on me.
Are you done being
the rich spoiled kid then?
That rich spoiled kid
never existed in the first place.
You gave me that nickname
on your own accord.
Besides, a rich spoiled kid?
-You're so--
-There was someone else.
Someone other than Ha Chan-ho
was at the scene.
Right, of course.
But who?
The one who took
Seo Jeong-hwa's second phone.
Exactly, but who was it?
It could be the one
who killed Seo Jeong-hwa.
You don't know who it is, do you?
Can I get a refill?
You always do that
when you have nothing to say.
Same here.
We may not know who it is,
but we know who's involved.
Here are the shareholders of White Hotel.
Here's the client list.
This is probably illegal.
Throwing around sensitive
information like this
will make you suffer the way we just did.
Also, we didn't call you here to work.
It's to grab a final drink--
We can hold off on the drinks.
Let us share the information.
Ms. Jung gave us the order herself.
And I'm the kind of person
who likes to wrap up things neatly.
And I just came by to see you.
SHAREHOLDER LIST
He was the major shareholder,
but he sold most of what he had.
It's why we didn't know.
The owner was different.
SON BONG-U
It seems like I missed a lot of things.
White Hotel is among ArtSky's clients.
WHITE HOTEL
So we found a decent lead.
Someone related to Seo Jeong-hwa.
WHITE HOTEL
Chairman Son Bong-u.
SON BONG-U
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
Why follow me all the way here?
Why carry those for me?
Because you've grown on me?
Or maybe I'm worried you might grow on me.
What are you yapping about?
Don't tell me this place
can collapse at any second.
Let's head inside then.
To celebrate today,
we'll have not soju, not wine,
but surprisingly beer.
That being said, I...
need you.
To help with your father's case, right?
That's not the only reason.
This time, you'll be needing me too.
Ha Chan-ho's case?
Song & Kim will only
represent him for his first trial.
Then, let's go over this once again.
Ha Chan-ho and Ha Jun-ho
are half-brothers.
The prosecution will argue
that Ha Chan-ho murdered Seo Jeong-hwa
after finding out that she had
betrayed him for his brother.
What we must do is argue
that it was in the heat of the moment.
Ha Chan-ho must plead guilty
and show remorse in court too.
VISITATION: PLEASE PRODUCE ID
You want me to plead guilty?
What we must show is that
your actions were accidental
and that you're deeply regretting them.
But I didn't kill her.
You don't clearly remember that.
You must've been in an unfit state
for the court to give you
a sentence below ten years.
Where's Ms. Jung?
What about Mr. Yoon?
They were taken off your case
for personal reasons.
What?
Then bring them back.
Who cares if they don't work
for Song & Kim? Bring them back.
I'd rather have them
than a clown like you!
Mr. Ha,
what you need is Song & Kim.
A prolonged trial
will only make it harder on you.
If it's me you can't trust,
put your faith in Song & Kim.
Are you Prosecutor Kwon Yong-un?
Yes.
Both lawyers and prosecutors
surely are busy, aren't they?
A blind date...
at this hour?
Lawyers?
Yes, I dated one for a while.
Why? Was that wrong of me?
Please don't tell me that
you haven't had a girlfriend before.
That's not it, is it?
Of course not.
-Coffee?
-Sure.
-Excuse me.
-Coming.
-What can I get you?
-Two cups of coffee, please.
Yeon-ji?
My gosh, Hee-jae?
How have you been these days?
You're only skin and bones.
I guess the breakup was hard on you.
Then you should've called.
I would've gladly dated you again.
From what I remember, I dumped you.
Exactly.
Who dumped whom doesn't matter.
The one who loved more hurts more, right?
The way you look says everything.
-What the hell are you two--
-This is great.
I have something to say
to Prosecutor Kwon here.
Could you excuse us?
Do you two know each other?
He's the one who indicted my father.
Yong-un,
I'm sure you heard about my father.
He's fit enough to appear in court.
Are you sure he doesn't need
treatment for every other past illness?
This is exactly why
I wanted to see you in person.
I knew you wouldn't take this seriously.
I'm representing my father.
I'll come at you with all I have,
so I suggest you do the same.
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that this case
isn't just linked to Issume.
A string of upper-class members
are probably involved too.
So don't get scared, don't run away,
don't let yourself be bulldozed over,
and dig deep into this case.
You'll understand what I mean in court.
How did you know I was here though?
Everyone at your office
knows about this blind date of yours.
It's your first as a prosecutor.
Gosh.
It's about time you got lonely too.
Guys, the Korean Bar Association
came to an agreement on your case.
Your license will be suspended
for two years.
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
-We'll appeal.
-Okay.
IRON WILL, SINCERE HEART
-It's similar. Nicely done.
-Right.
-Thank you.
-Vintage again?
Are you aware of more sophisticated styles
that look modern, sleek, and Scandinavian?
But retro is what's been trending.
Yes, it seems that way.
Why? It looks great to me.
I knew you'd understand my taste.
-What--
-So is this Choong...
It's nice and cozy.
Congratulations on the opening.
Oh, please. I'm only reopening it
after a short break.
You didn't have to buy any snacks.
Thank you.
Well, they're tasty.
I was somewhat hungry, so thanks.
-I like these.
-Do you want one?
Whether you're opening or reopening
doesn't matter.
Are you taking Ha Chan-ho's case?
I'd like to join you.
Are you saying you'll leave Song & Kim?
I earned a small fortune
investing in stocks.
I won't ask for a salary,
so let me do what I want to.
Let's dig into his case
without bosses breathing down our necks.
That's him acting with bravado.
Truth be told, he was fired.
He kept questioning
the firm's decisions on the case
which didn't sit well with Mr. Ma.
So will you accept me or not?
If the Ministry of Justice
presents us with the same ruling,
we'll need a trustworthy lawyer
on our side.
Sure. Okay.
Okay? You mean it?
What about me?
Aren't you going to ask about me too?
-So which desk should I use?
-I resigned on my own accord.
-My fellow Koreans.
-After seeing
-what they did to you...
-To make Korea
an economically developed country,
I will run for president in
the upcoming 20th presidential election.
-Lee In-yeop!
COURT OF LAW
COURT OF KOREA
DEFENSE COUNSEL, DEFENDANT
Pleading guilty to involuntary
manslaughter won't get you many years.
Let's hope it's accepted.
COURT OF LAW
We will now make a ruling.
The defendant claims
he wasn't in the right state of mind,
but we acknowledge his gross negligence
in the case of Ms. Seo Jeong-hwa's death.
According to sentencing guidelines,
we sentence him to eight years.
That concludes this trial.
I hear that Song & Kim won't appeal.
-That's right.
-Ms. Jung?
Then...
we will.
"We"?
Yes, at Law Office Choong.
Will you appoint us to represent you?
Of course.
Let's go.
Good job today.
-What happened?
-What did he say?
Will Ha Chan-ho let us take his case?
Guys?
COURT OF LAW
At Choong, we pick stars for our clients.
Our clients will forever be loyal
out of gratitude.
Is Ha Chan-ho letting you represent him?
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
HYENA
Checking the scene could give us
a new insight.
We can go and check
if they really don't have CCTV cameras.
Do you see this or not?
Still, you can't do that here.
ArtSky's paintings and White Hotel
which belonged to Chairman Son.
And Seo Jeong-hwa.
It's possible
that she looked after those paintings.
Using Son Bong-u's slush fund, right?
What if something goes wrong?
Okay, sir. I'll take care of it.
-Are you going to see your father?
-Don't call him that.
I want to have proper closure.