HYENA
THIS DRAMA IS PURELY FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH
ACTUAL PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, ASSOCIATIONS,
OR LOCATIONS
EPISODE 11
You think
you know about me?
Well, you couldn't be more wrong.
Keep your advice to yourself
from now on.
Actually, I do know enough about you,
Jung Eun-yeong.
What more do you know
other than that name?
I just told you that I know enough.
So what?
Are you worried that she might stir me up?
Shouldn't I be worried?
It's useless to worry about some people.
And those people are celebrities
and Jung Geum-ja.
-Get it?
-I personally disagree.
What I see is a woman,
who can't escape from her past,
making a wrong judgment.
I do a fine job of taking care of myself.
If I see a pit, I jump over it.
If I see a stone, I kick it away.
But what about you?
You never even go near an unpaved road.
Your dad and brother
help you avoid all your troubles.
-Watch what you say.
-So...
if you don't like my method,
stop getting involved
and just stay out of it.
You grew up too sheltered,
so you'll never be able to understand me.
Plus, you're busy these days
doing something very important.
Jung Geum-ja!
How did you know that about me?
It's true that I'm a crazy bitch like you.
And like you, I lived through hell too.
If Baek Hee-jun gives up Gnosis,
we aren't going to press charges, are we?
We'll forget anything ever happened
which is your style.
Who says that I prefer
such boring endings?
Can you pass me a bottle of water?
Let's finish the petition
for Baek Hee-jun.
Right now.
-Hee-jae, about the inheritance tax law--
-Get out.
Okay.
-Then what time should I come back...
-Damn it!
What?
She thinks I grew up sheltered?
Hee-jae, I left my cell phone...
Damn it.
What's my cell phone doing on the floor?
What?
It's a little cracked.
I have 23 more months
until I pay off the installment.
I guess I'll have to buy a new phone.
-Ms. Jung, did you...
-Later.
Ms. Boo, do you...
Did she just shush me? Shit.
Okay, fine. My phone has
turned into a piece of shit anyway.
COMPLAINT
Yes, that's good enough.
Let's go with this one.
By the way, what was that all about?
What? What are you talking about?
You told her that you lived through hell.
And that scar on your shoulder.
Well, if you're that curious...
It was back when I was your age.
Back then,
I also had beautiful skin like you.
You were probably just a baby
having the time of your life
with your parents
and eating chestnuts with your grandma--
Okay, I get it. I'll file the complaint.
Anyway, your method worked again.
Are you not happy with that?
Ms. Baek Un-mi.
COMPLAINT
I'll be honest.
You seem like a psycho.
You're obviously not a philanthropist.
Why are you trying to help me?
You talk to me like I'm your friend.
If you weren't my client, I would've...
I'm doing it for money. Nothing else.
Your mother stole money from the church
and invested in a certain company.
I'm going to use you to take that back.
-Are you fucking crazy?
-What's wrong with that?
Money gives you the freedom to choose.
You've been through enough,
so you should know that already.
What about you? What is it that you want?
A sincere apology?
Or do you want to humiliate her?
What's your goal?
Look at you glaring at me.
Should I answer that for you?
You want to humiliate her
and make her apologize.
On top of that, you even want her money.
I'll let you have all that.
You just need to trust me.
I am your
I'm your source of money,
your best choice, and your future.
Are all lawyers so cocky like you?
I'm of a different breed.
Made in hell?
Bingo.
Do you know why hyenas shit white poop?
They eat the bones of their preys
whether they're alive or dead.
You just wait and see
how I eat up
your mother.
We're already living in heaven.
We were all born equally as humans.
We, humans, aren't god,
so we make a lot of mistakes.
However, if you repent your faults
and do volunteer work,
you will eventually turn into god
and live eternally.
And that's what you call Trinity.
Trinity, Hallelujah.
-Trinity, Hallelujah.
COMPLAINT
This one's for you.
It's the original copy.
So what does this mean?
Well, you see,
it's a bit complicated.
It could become a ticket to hell
or turn into a business license.
And that's up to you.
Do you really think
Un-mi wants to do this to me?
I guess you really are her mother.
Are you actually worried
about your daughter?
What you're doing for her is nothing
compared to what I want for her.
Why do you think I did that
to my own daughter?
Heaven is right before her eyes.
All she needs to do
is eat, sleep, read, and pray.
She just needs to do as I say,
and she'll be blessed.
She's such a fool.
You're pressuring her
to go to heaven and be blessed.
It's so cliché.
But normally, people call that abuse.
You have no evidence or witness.
This isn't the first time Un-mi
tried to do something like this.
The problem is that the people
who helped your daughter
had no idea that you were a genius
when it came to investment.
You know my law firm, right?
Why do you think people
are obsessed with Song & Kim?
All I need to do
is make a few calls
to dig into your slush fund.
I wonder how Un-mi was able to afford
a lawyer from Song & Kim.
You're after something more, aren't you?
My gosh, obviously.
Do you want to guess what I'm after?
It's one of the companies
that you invested in.
It's called Gnosis.
I want all your shares.
Don't get greedy. Be reasonable
and stick to the market price.
Then I'll let you continue your business.
I'll also withdraw the suit.
But of course,
you'll have to compensate your daughter.
Why should I listen to you?
Your prayers are effective.
So why don't you ask your god why?
Or I could just call an investment analyst
and tell that person everything about you.
Then you'll get to hear
how badly things will go
for both your church and Gnosis.
If you miss the right timing,
you won't get paid properly.
The press is here.
I think you should leave.
Which broadcasting station? Is it SBTV?
You've never been on TV before, right?
I called them so you could make a debut.
You've done a lot of preparation.
Yes.
Today, I'll just show you
the entrance to hell.
Once we file the lawsuit,
you'll realize that there's more
to this world than just heaven.
Don't make me wait for too long.
Okay, then. Have a good night.
Everyone in your team already went home.
Why are you leaving so late?
"Your team"?
Our team got split into two
and are working on different cases.
MERGER AND ACQUISITIONS AGREEMENT
You already printed out the M&A draft.
And the price is...
You guys have set yourselves a high goal.
An agreement to drop the suit?
Ms. Jung is pushing forward like always.
Right.
I'm sure she'll see it through
until the end.
AGREEMENT
-I can't believe this.
-I know, right?
This is crazy.
-Hee-jae is here.
-Really?
My gosh, Hee-jae!
-Hee-jae!
-Hey, come over here!
Join us! Come on!
How did you know we were here?
Come on.
Ready, set, go.
It's my turn to hit you.
I got you!
Ready, set, go. I got you again!
-Ready, set, go! My gosh!
-Oh, no.
Gi-hyeok.
Since when were you so perfect?
Since the day I was born.
But I tend to be very humble.
I find it very difficult to show off
and boast about myself.
That's what you call a grown-up man.
You shouldn't go around showing off
like someone I know.
That's not very mature. It's like a kid.
-My goodness.
-Right?
You're leaving already?
Yes, my cochlea is starting to hurt,
and it's making me cuss.
What's the matter with you?
You should stay.
We haven't met in ages.
You can't leave this quickly.
You should stay and join us for round two.
Yes, she's right. You should stay.
Join us for round two.
Hee-jae,
I have a question.
When did you get back together
with Geum-ja?
What
did you just say?
Am I wrong?
Gi-hyeok, tell him.
I heard you started liking her again
after that Kevin guy came in between.
No?
-Gi-hyeok.
-Yes?
You're here having fun
because you're done
with the report, right?
What? Yes. No.
Now that you have a girlfriend,
you've become a lot gutsier.
I'm impressed.
Let me know if you don't like your job.
I'll ask around to see
if you can join another team.
See you.
Okay, Hee-jae.
I'll have it done by tomorrow.
Be careful on your way home.
Thanks, buddy.
What's up with him today?
ATTORNEY JUNG GEUM-JA
INCOMING CALL
ATTORNEY YOON HEE-JAE
CONNECTED
What do you want?
I'm hungry.
Then go eat something.
Would you like to join?
I already ate.
I see.
If you're done, I'm going to hang up.
I'm sorry.
Now, it's your turn
to apologize.
I'm too old
to deal with a drunk ex-boyfriend.
So you do think of me
as your ex-boyfriend.
-I'm not going there again. Bye.
-Have you thought about
what kind of bridge
Baek Un-mi will end up crossing?
It's too late for that.
She's already crossed that bridge,
and there's no turning back.
-She can't undo anything.
-Like you?
I'm warning you.
Stop acting like you know me.
Why do you live that way?
Isn't it exhausting?
What about you?
What about that thing you're working on?
Isn't that exhausting?
You're chasing after conglomerates
so you can help them change the law.
I'm tired. Let's drop it.
CALL ENDED
First, here's the title I came up with.
"The Revised Inheritance Tax
and Gift Tax Act"
which will vitalize the succession
of family businesses for competitive firms
which will then lead to more employment
and economic growth.
It's cliché, but I like it.
All great laws are cliché.
First, we'll include large corporations
by getting rid of the sales regulation,
and then adjust three things.
The extent of deduction,
the prerequisites,
and the follow-up requirements.
How do you plan to adjust them?
Raise the extent of deduction
to 200 billion won.
Have over five years
of management experience.
And maintain 50 percent
of the inheritance for 5 years.
That's right.
The point is to help them inherit
a lot of money in a short period of time.
To be honest,
you can't call this a big change.
You're just trying to turn back time
to the 1980s.
It's too obvious
that you're doing this for the rich.
I honestly don't think
this bill will pass.
The next presidential candidate
is taking initiative along with the help
of the senior presidential secretary
for economic affairs,
the Supreme Court, and the media.
-What about the public sentiment?
-What about that?
When did we ever care about that?
I agree that this goes against the trend.
But our VIP clients
really want this bill to pass,
which means our stance
is already set.
CURRENT VERSION, REVISED VERSION
It's a lot more extreme
than what I expected.
If you want, we'll make changes.
No, it's okay.
INHERITANCE TAX AND GIFT TAX ACT
It's very daring. I like it.
The process will be daring as well.
Are you okay with that?
It'll be risky even if
we don't do anything.
As the head of Song & Kim,
it's a dereliction of duty to stay quiet
when there's a problem
with our country's legal system.
I should endure the aftermath.
It'll be better to table the bill
along with the other bills
rather than attract attention to it
by proposing it on its own.
You should meet Congressman Lee In-yeop
before tabling the bill.
Do it quietly. Keep it confidential.
Okay, sir.
Is everything okay with Ms. Jung?
Well, yes.
Hee-jae.
It's important to focus on
how useful that person is going to be.
Your preference shouldn't be the priority.
That way, you won't miss your chance.
The chance to keep that person near you
and the chance to get rid of them.
One day, you'll get what you want.
But until then,
keep Ms. Jung by your side.
You need to keep her a lot closer.
Are you really going to file a suit?
What do you think?
What Baek Un-mi wants is important.
But that's not our goal.
But think about
how much this will hurt her.
What if...
And I know this won't ever happen.
But what if we lose?
What would I know?
This is delicious.
We're not filing a suit.
Pardon?
I know for a fact that she'll call.
She'll be holding a white flag.
So let's
eat up and be ready for victory.
Okay.
Is it Baek Hee-jun?
Hello, this is Jung Geum-ja
from Song & Kim.
It's me, Baek Hee-jun.
Hello, Ms. Baek.
First, I'd like to meet.
When should we meet?
INHERITANCE TAX AND GIFT TAX ACT
The writer and director seem to have
no consideration at all for the actor.
Judging by your silence, I guess
that means I can't ask for any changes.
Am I correct?
Yes.
As you already know,
there's a long way to go
before this reaches the plenary session.
We need to go through at least ten steps.
Do you think we'll be able
to get it done quietly?
The world isn't exactly as peaceful
as this temple.
All the other bills that were
adjusted by Song & Kim
had to go through the same process.
Fortunately, we received help...
No, we were led by people like you,
and that's how we won.
That's what determined whether or not
they became our clients.
Mr. Song really wants this.
That's all I can say for now.
I thought you were a cattle dog,
but you're actually a hound.
You're the best at Song & Kim,
so I guess I'll trust you.
MR. SONG PIL-JUNG
Sir, I just met with Congressman Lee.
How did he react?
We're going to proceed with it as planned.
But he does seem a little worried.
This is a huge deal.
So I bet he doesn't want to attract
people's attention.
His public image
means a great deal to him.
Anyway, all right. Thanks.
Of course. Have a good day, sir.
I thought you were a cattle dog,
but you're actually a hound.
All right. Then let's talk about
what can happen at the tax evasion trial
for the senior presidential secretary
for political affairs.
Any variables?
The judge in charge
is Chief Judge Yoon Hyeok-jae
of Seoul Central District Court.
Chief Judge Yoon Hyeok-jae.
What about him?
People call him Mr. By-the-Book.
In the legal circle, he's...
-The hound and Mr. By-the-Book...
-"Mr. By-the-Book."
Then will the court's decision...
Are you getting married?
What are you talking about?
If that's not the case,
this is just weird.
What's weird?
I mean, why would you
want to see me for no reason?
You don't think it's weird?
Do you think
I'm like a dog?
What the hell.
Sorry.
Did someone call you a dog?
Don't laugh. I'm serious right now.
I suppose you're asking
if I think you're Uncle Pil-jung's dog.
You didn't have to spell it out like that.
What? Do you feel shitty
because I saw through your ambition?
The moment you joined Song & Kim,
following the rules of--
Okay, stop.
What did I even expect?
Hee-jae.
Okay. Let's drop this topic.
Finish your food.
I lost my appetite.
And wouldn't you say
this is a type of hypocrisy?
Do you want to look like a commoner?
Chief Judge Yoon Hyeok-jae,
Mr. By-the-Book, of Criminal Department 2.
You're not exactly a commoner.
That's why I should be
even more mindful and careful.
Because I've been enjoying
many privileges.
Both you and I.
Let's not take it for granted
or disgrace the family name.
You can live like that.
I'm going to keep doing things my way.
Why do you keep canceling
your appointment with Ms. Baek?
This is the third time.
What will you do if she changes her mind?
She won't.
In fact, it'll make her more anxious.
How much has it gone up by?
It's going up rapidly.
The price might end up being way too high
in about a month.
Why don't we gauge the situation
and change our target?
-Where are you going?
-To make money.
AGREEMENT
THE PRINCIPAL AGREES
TO DONATE ONE BILLION WON
So you all want to rake in money
without even lifting a finger.
That's what you did.
The amount may be less
than what you were expecting,
but considering
all your earnings to date...
You should quit this and change careers.
And I'm sure you know.
After this,
you'll never receive
an offer like this again.
Didn't you call me
because you understand what's going on?
If I sign this,
there will be no more problems?
That's right.
BAEK HEE-JUN
It's okay. Sit down.
Well, I heard AP EON has acquired Gnosis.
Yes.
And Song & Kim handled it?
Led by you?
Correct.
Then,
shouldn't you run away from me
instead of setting foot in my house?
I'd like to keep this short,
so I'll get right to the point.
Go ahead.
Issume Pharmaceuticals can buy Gnosis.
What are the conditions?
Pay twice the amount AP EON promised.
As you know,
when Gnosis' market value is revealed,
you won't be able to buy it
even with a lot more money.
And if one of your
international competitors acquires it...
Is that the only condition?
Desert Song Pil-jung.
Partner up with me instead.
I am aware that
it's an unexpected, rude request.
It is rude.
Mr. Song and I go back a long way.
But I must say, this is interesting.
It'll be interesting to see how things
will change. It'll be entertaining.
Right?
Well, then...
Proceed with it. I'll be watching.
And Ms. Kim...
Hello. Let's go in.
You go in first.
I see that you're doing very well
for yourself these days.
I always do well.
Attorney Jung is the star of the case,
not you.
Yoon Hee-jae is just a sidekick?
It doesn't suit you.
I'm working on something
very important as per Mr. Song's order.
And as you know,
Attorney Jung took such great care
of what Ms. Kim asked her to do.
You think this will last forever,
don't you?
I heard that team makes people
forget their places at first.
Be careful.
You'd better prepare
a safety net in case you fall.
You've already fallen,
so I shall remember your advice.
See you.
Hey, wait.
You little...
Gosh.
M&A SIGNING CEREMONY
AGREEMENT
BAEK UN-MI
You've agreed to never request money again
or take legal action regarding
this matter. You remember that, right?
I know I agreed to be used, but why do I
feel like I was forced to panhandle?
I have to say, it feels pretty shitty.
The money will be deposited in a few days.
You're getting a billion won.
Isn't it a sweet deal?
So? This is it?
Of course not.
You'll have to do something
that doesn't involve requesting money
or taking legal action.
Mr. Yoon.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I say that
because I've only seen you
in the most unexpected places.
Anyway, thank you for everything.
Ms. Jung and I...
I mean, we always fill in
for each other when needed,
so I'll accept this on her behalf.
Is that so?
Well, it's different
from an attorney-client relationship.
What we have is quite special.
Shall I say we desire...
Hello, Ms. Jung.
Tonight?
Yes, I'm free tonight.
Yes.
I'll make a reservation.
Congratulations.
You hit a home run
as soon as you got back.
-You're amazing.
-Congratulations.
So what's up?
Congratulating me must be just an excuse.
Don't you have something to say?
Well...
Nothing's up, but...
We think there's something going on
between Ms. Jung and Mr. Yoon.
-What exactly is going on?
-Pardon?
The thing is...
Take the Issume Case for example.
We have reasons to believe
that Ha Chan-ho's medical records,
which were considered top secret,
ended up in her hands.
So?
Are you saying Yoon Hee-jae leaked
that confidential information to her?
Or are you speculating it
because they're close?
-That's right.
-Yes.
Mr. Ma, you're telling me this
just after Ms. Jung successfully closed
an important deal.
Don't you think I might get the wrong idea
because of the timing of this?
Let's drop this.
I don't want to ruin this happy day.
Please leave.
Yes, ma'am.
Did we perhaps choose a rotten rope?
What?
A rope?
Do you think I'm someone
who relies on such things? Seriously?
Crap...
Mr. Ma.
If Vector5 can actually be used
to treat dementia,
Gnosis' market value will surpass
100 billion won.
With strategic manipulation,
it'll go up exponentially from there.
Not bad, right?
Song & Kim will get 20 percent
of AP EON's profits,
and 20 percent of that
will go to your team.
What do you say? Are you happy with that?
There's something Guus Hiddink said.
"I'm still hungry."
Thank you for everything.
To tell you the truth,
you exceeded my expectations.
Anyway, enough about work.
Shall we talk about us?
Then...
can we talk about
Issume Pharmaceuticals now?
You're really something.
That's a compliment, right?
All right, then.
I'd like to propose a deal.
Let's
start seeing each other.
Will anything change if we do that?
Many things can change
if you make up your mind.
I'll tell you one of my secrets.
Things that I can
touch, chew, and eat.
That's all I care about.
Everything else is useless to me.
You're like a roller coaster.
Enjoy the ride while you can.
That's my charm.
INHERITANCE TAX AND GIFT TAX ACT
What about you?
What about that thing you're working on?
Isn't that exhausting?
You're chasing after conglomerates
so you can help them change the law.
That's why I should be
even more mindful and careful.
Because I've been enjoying
many privileges.
Everything will go according to our plan
after some simple paperwork.
Isn't it amazing, Kevin?
So how much did they offer?
What?
Well,
twice the takeover price.
What's wrong? Is it not enough?
Don't forget that it was me
who told you about
Issume's interest in the company.
Of course I remember.
But it was me who figured out
why Issume was interested.
Ms. Jung is here.
I asked her here to celebrate.
-Let her in.
-Yes, ma'am.
Good job, Ms. Jung. Have a seat.
Thank you.
Don't hesitate to tell me
if there's anything you need.
Whatever you need
will be my first priority.
That's not her style.
You should offer her
something more tangible.
What?
I'll keep that in mind.
In the meantime,
I'd like some paperwork done.
-Paperwork?
-I'm sure you're aware of this,
but it'll properly kick off now.
The merger of
Issume Pharmaceuticals and Gnosis.
Why don't we discuss the process
over a meal and improve teamwork?
Isn't it the first time
us three are getting together?
I'd like to discuss the merger
between Gnosis and Issume too.
It'll give you more options.
Kevin?
Oh, right.
I hope you're free today.
I'm sorry, but it'll have to be
just you and Ms. Jung today.
Why? Did something come up?
I'll tell you when I have all the facts.
Anyway, please enjoy your meal.
I'd like for you to hold off
on the merger between the two companies.
What? Hold off?
I don't want to rush anything.
I'll see you.
The meal seems
to have gone out the window,
so I'll get going too.
Just so you know though,
Mr. Song's generosity...
How do I put this?
Well, the man knows how to impress.
He gave us bonuses and then paid for R&R.
I thought you'd be eating with Ms. Kim.
So what's with the twist?
I'm afraid this is something
even you can't know about.
It must be something big then.
Depending on the outcome? Yes.
I'd love to hear all about it.
Does that mean I'll get to see you more?
Hello.
You busy?
What has you in a good mood?
Do you want to check out
the entertainment I prepared?
It'll begin soon.
-Here we go.
-We'll now begin...
-It's showtime.
-Ms. Baek Hee-jun
of Community Chest of Trinity will donate
to the families of young cancer patients.
Please give her your warm welcome.
LEE JA-YOUNG: THANK YOU, MS. BAEK.
NUNNU: SHE'S BEAUTIFUL!
Like always, I stand here before you
to take another step closer to the Lord.
For his blessing to reach
every corner of the world
and that we live a full life
in his embrace,
I will pray every day.
-Thank you.
-Please give her a round of applause.
Let me now introduce you
to another generous donor.
I hear this person
has a special relationship with Ms. Baek.
Please give this donor a warm welcome.
KIM SEON-YEONG: I'LL REMEMBER HER NAME.
THANK YOU.
LEE GEUM-BI: I'M SO PROUD OF HER.
MARGARINE: SHE'S AMAZING.
GOMMIL: SHE DESERVES A COMMENDATION.
OGUOGU: THIS IS SO TOUCHING.
ONE BILLION WON
EUNYA: YOU'RE THE BEST. YOU'RE AMAZING.
KKONDAE: IT'S SO HEARTWARMING.
It's been a while, Mom.
EOMMASON: WHO IS SHE?
I am only able to stand here today
as a good person
because of what I learned
from my mother, Ms. Baek.
Aren't I right?
This is me giving back
the money you gave me.
It went on for more than ten years, right?
I was locked in the basement
without any water. I'd escape,
get caught, break a rib,
and get tied up again.
What else was there?
MONRYE: WHAT? WHAT IS SHE SAYING?
We're leaving.
Ma'am, let's go.
MAIN_KIM: IS SHE EVEN HUMAN?
SEO SANG-HWA: HOW DESPICABLE.
My mom must remember it all too.
And you still say you know me?
No, I thought I did, but I guess I didn't.
How do you like this emotional side of me?
I honestly hate your antics,
but I still like you, which is fucked up.
Jung Eun-yeong doesn't exist anymore.
The woman in front of you is Jung Geum-ja.
Fine, I admit defeat. I get your message.
Still, you won't be able
to stop me from worrying about you.
It's not something I can control anyway.
When will you stop acting like a child--
Hee-jae, did you know about this?
Unbelievable.
If it weren't for Ms. Boo,
I would've missed the show.
It was too good to watch alone.
I felt iffy about us dropping the case.
I can finally sleep tonight.
What will the daughter do now that
she's donated her settlement money?
Have you forgotten about
the donation clause
we added to the Gnosis deal?
THE PRINCIPAL AGREES
TO DONATE ONE BILLION WON
So that's the money she donated?
No wonder. That clause had me baffled.
Me too!
-Shouldn't we celebrate?
-He's right. Let's celebrate.
-Let's celebrate.
-How about dinner and drinks?
-What should we have?
-Pork rinds.
-I object.
-Even I'm against pork rinds this time.
No, thanks.
I doubt you want to hand over
the technology
you fought intensely to win.
I had no idea that AP EON
would be satisfied with
just tripling its investment money.
I'm here to hear about
this other option you have in mind.
What if you grew in size
before the merger?
It's a new company that studies dementia.
Merge with this company first
and postpone the deal
with Issume Pharmaceuticals.
If you give the approval,
Chairman Ha of Issume and I
will lay the bridge for you.
I'd like to hear your terms.
The deal will be worth ten times more,
and you will be offered
the shares of Issume Pharmaceuticals.
Many people
call you Chairman Ha's personal butler.
What is the reason behind the offer?
Relationships and partnerships
are like flowing water.
The speed may seem consistent,
but a variable could easily
alter the speed at any time.
During these times,
opening up another canal
could be a decent option.
Sorry.
I don't understand your metaphor.
It's true that
I've been attentive toward Mr. Ha's needs,
but he's not who I answer to.
I figured it's time I told you that.
And that must include
Ms. Kim Min-joo as well.
I will share with you the holes
in Issume Group's shareholder structure.
Who knows?
Issume Pharmaceuticals could
take over as holding company.
And Song & Kim will be
at the center of that shift.
What do you say?
How's that
for an alternative option?
On day two of
the Assembly's provisional session,
up-and-coming presidential candidate
Congressman Lee In-yeop
was surrounded by vehement protesters.
They were showing
strong objection to the revised
Inheritance Tax and Gift Tax Act.
Protesters and the public claim
that the bill is only for the rich
and are criticizing Congressman Lee
for trying to pass the bill
without a public hearing.
Mr. Yoon Hee-jae,
you knocked a bee hive this time.
He is a bootlicker of the rich.
Lee In-yeop must step down!
-Step down.
Lee In-yeop's ideas
are nothing but retrograde--
-It's Lee In-yeop!
-There he is.
THE PROTESTERS
SPRING AT CONGRESSMAN LEE
SUDDEN OUTBREAK!
ANGRY CITIZENS THROW
EGGS, CABBAGE LEAVES, AND FLOUR AT HIM!
WILL THE REVISED INHERITANCE TAX
AND GIFT TAX ACT FAIL TO PASS?
And now Round Two begins.
I knew this would happen,
but that was scary.
Let's activate our plan
to involve the media.
We need to move quickly
before he gets branded.
Let's move!
-Sure.
-Got it.
-Mr. Yoon.
-What now?
Mr. Song left you a message.
You're to meet with
Congressman Lee In-yeop immediately.
-Mr. Yoon, about that...
-We'll talk later.
Mr. Lee, you must stay strong.
Tell me you have a countermeasure.
This is all just part of the process, sir.
There are no countermeasures.
Only plans that we've mapped out.
The humiliation I received
is part of the process?
Just think of the outcome, sir.
You'll forget this ever happened.
As if you know what this feels like.
How can I believe
whatever you're yapping on about?
If you can't trust me,
then put your faith in Song & Kim.
Then I'll look forward
to a turn of events.
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
What are you doing here?
This is where you listed your home as.
Is this where you live?
You really live here?
Why do you still live here
when you recently came into money?
What use do you have saving up?
Is it to buy a building someday?
How did you know that? You're right.
Did you come over here to pick on me?
It's odd because
you seemed like a lost puppy on the steps.
Do you want a shot of soju?
Oddly enough,
this tastes sweet today.
Hard day, was it?
As always, you know.
Why?
Do you think I need comforting?
Then go ahead. Comfort me.
SECRETARY JO U-SEOK
It's Mr. Jo.
MR. SONG PIL-JUNG
Mine's from Mr. Song.
-Yes, Mr. Jo.
-Yes, Mr. Song.
Ms. Jung!
Mr. Yoon, you're here too?
In here...
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
HYENA
We need to trace her movements
on the day of her death.
So you think I killed her?
If Issume falters,
things will become difficult.
Issume isn't our only card.
Is that why those people want
Ha Chan-ho to face murder charges?
So Ha Jun-ho can take over?
Someone must be able
to call out what is wrong.
If you want to object,
keep it to yourself and stay silent.
What's your angle?
Why did you show this to me?
This case started with me.
Finding her real killer.
That's the least I can do
for Seo Jeong-hwa now.