HYENA
THIS DRAMA IS PURELY FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH
ACTUAL PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, ASSOCIATIONS,
OR LOCATIONS
What happened?
She was like that when I got here.
-Mr. Ha tried to wake her up.
-Hey.
She's dead.
What are you going to do?
Is this the police?
What are you doing?
What about you? Give it back.
You're going to call the cops first?
We're lawyers. We need to find out--
We need to call the cops
unless you're trying to cover this up.
That's what a lawyer should do.
Just give me some time.
Mr. Ha, wake up.
What happened
to Seo Jeong-hwa?
What? I don't...
I don't know.
Did you kill Seo Jeong-hwa?
No, no...
No, I...
I don't know.
I don't think he even knows
what's going on right now.
He's not in his right mind.
There's never a better argument than that.
Shouldn't we call the cops now?
Buying time won't change anything.
-Just a second.
-Geum-ja!
Once the cops arrive, it'll be over.
They won't even share any photos
of the crime scene.
That's enough.
Is this the police?
I called to report an accident.
EPISODE 12
DO NOT ENTER
My gosh.
That's Ha Chan-ho, the CEO of Issume.
Yes, the Ha Chan-ho.
They're lawyers from Song & Kim.
They reported the accident.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Lee U-tae from Gangnam Police Station.
Who first discovered the accident?
It was me.
-Are you a lawyer?
-No.
I'm Jo U-seok. I work
in the Secretary's Office at Issume.
So are you saying you called his lawyers
-after you saw--
-We came with him.
Yes, we got here together.
I'm just saying I was the first one
to see this scene.
Then can someone tell me
what happened here?
We don't know anything yet.
As you can see,
our client is also very lost.
Well, I'm sorry to tell you
that we're going to have to arrest him.
He might also be a victim.
The bloodstains on his gown and hands
look like he got them from the victim.
Isn't that enough
to arrest him red-handed?
Let's go to the police station first.
Let's wait until he's sober
so we can find out what happened.
-Arrest him.
-Yes, sir.
Detective Lee.
It looks like you missed something out.
Mr. Ha.
Mr. Ha, you are under arrest
as the suspect of Seo Jeong-hwa's murder
due to the possibility
of evidence destruction
and escape. Is that clear?
And just for your information,
you have the right to a lawyer.
So go ahead and hire these people.
Okay?
Cuff him. I'll bring his shoes.
Who the hell are you?
Get off me!
Who do you think you are?
Mr. Jo.
Yes, sir. I'm right here.
No, wait. Give me a moment.
-Is that really necessary?
-Where's Ms. Jung?
-Detective, please.
-Let me go!
Where are all my fucking lawyers?
Why aren't they here right now?
Sir...
What in the world happened in there?
What should we do?
You should go to the police station.
Why don't you go with him?
Just a second.
Geum-ja.
It's time that I know.
What do you know about
Seo Jeong-hwa and Ha Chan-ho?
I'll tell you later.
Where's Ms. Jung?
Are you sober now?
Where is Ms. Jung?
I guess you are sober
seeing that you're looking for her.
You need to be honest
and tell me what happened.
To be honest,
I don't remember.
I was drunk.
So I don't remember anything.
-Mr. Ha.
-That's all I have to say.
Call Ms. Jung.
INTERROGATION ROOM
Mr. Song, it's me, Hee-jae.
What happened to Mr. Ha?
He got arrested at the crime scene.
Do you know what happened?
I think there was an accident.
That's the most realistic story for now.
He says he can't remember anything.
But the crime scene
is already pointing at Mr. Ha
as the culprit.
Was it just you and Mr. Jo
at the crime scene?
Ms. Jung was there too.
What was she doing there?
Mr. Ha called her.
Then
are you with her right now?
No, sir.
-Then keep me updated.
-Okay, sir.
Yes, Chairman Ha.
Don't worry. We'll sort everything out.
Ha Jun-ho. He's Ms. Im's son.
And Ms. Im is Chairman Ha's third wife.
What happened to Jeong-hwa?
I'm Jung Geum-ja, a lawyer.
Yes, I know. You forced her
to stay with Ha Chan-ho.
Tell me what happened to Jeong-hwa.
She's dead.
She's dead?
How... Why...
-Mr. Ha.
-How? Why?
Why did she die?
Did you know that Mr. Ha Chan-ho was
suspicious of your relationship with her?
What?
Did he kill her?
-We don't know yet.
-Where is he?
I'm going to kill that jerk.
-Mr. Ha.
-Where is that fucking bastard?
Listen to me!
No one knows
why Seo Jeong-hwa died.
Ha Chan-ho was next to her when she died.
And he got arrested at the crime scene.
You could end up getting arrested instead.
So you need
to be honest with me.
Did you call
or meet Seo Jeong-hwa today?
I called and told her
that everything will be okay
and that we should go abroad together.
What am I going to do now?
I feel so sorry for Jeong-hwa.
Sir.
First, make sure
the press keeps this a secret.
We won't be able to stop the press.
It's better to come up with a solution.
Does that mean
Hye-won is my only option?
You need to be level-headed, sir.
You know how ambitious she is.
She won't do things your way.
She was a great competitor for Chan-ho.
But she's not good enough to lead Issume.
This may upset you,
but I need to tell you the truth.
You need to listen to me right now.
Think of the company.
Jun-ho is still too young.
That's what I'm here for.
Use me, sir.
I'll make sure he becomes good enough
for the position.
Chan-ho isn't evil at heart.
Right.
I guess we can do what you suggested
for the company.
-But take good care of Chan-ho for me.
-Okay, sir.
Can we talk for a moment?
My gosh, this is like
a National Assembly hearing.
"I don't remember. I don't know."
Lucky we were able to arrest him
at the crime scene.
You're dealing with Issume.
He's the CEO of Issume.
You need to think about the future.
Well, I'm sure you already know this.
But please be careful not to leak this
to the press.
The superintendent already told us
to be extra careful.
Bye, then.
Mr. Ha.
Ms. Jung.
I'll be with you soon.
You guys are so close.
I called for a team meeting.
Let's go back to the office.
Geum-ja.
Ha Jun-ho?
-The Ha Jun-ho?
-I think Ha Chan-ho recently found out
about their relationship.
Why did you call me at this hour?
You knew, didn't you?
About Jeong-hwa and Jun-ho.
What?
I don't have any proof yet.
But I'm sure something is
going on between them.
-No way.
-You're the one
who brought Jeong-hwa back to me.
So I want you to find out.
Do you
not trust her?
She looks at him differently.
She's different when she's around him.
So I want you to find out.
You know what you're saying, right?
You just stated his motive
for murdering Seo Jeong-hwa.
The cops should never find out.
They took Seo Jeong-hwa's cell phone
from the scene as evidence.
Once they look at the call logs,
they'll find out about Ha Jun-ho.
They were extremely secretive
about their relationship.
She probably had another cell phone.
It'll only be a matter of time
before they find out.
We will
just have to check.
Ha Chan-ho was always obsessed
with Seo Jeong-hwa.
You of all people should know that.
We should be careful.
Seo Jeong-hwa is dead.
She's dead, okay?
It looks like you've forgotten that.
Our client
is Ha Chan-ho.
Let's not forget that.
SEO JEONG-HWA, VICTIM, DEAD
HA CHAN-HO, ARRESTED AT THE SCENE
Gosh, what a complete mess.
I'm not even surprised by this.
What do you mean?
This isn't the first time
Ha Chan-ho got obsessed with Seo Jeong-hwa
and caused trouble.
How did you get photos
of the crime scene so quickly?
I took them myself.
What?
It's very dogmatic and illegal.
But let's keep going.
We all know that it's better for us
to have those photos anyway.
Victim, Seo Jeong-hwa.
She was Ha Chan-ho's mistress.
And they've been
living together for months.
The accident occurred
at the White Hotel suite.
As you can see, Seo Jeong-hwa
hit her head on the glass table.
We'll have to wait
for the autopsy and forensics
to know the accurate cause of death.
But for now, it looks she died
due to a severe skull fracture.
Did you notice any other scars or bruises?
We can only refer to the photos
to find out.
She's covered in blood,
so I can't even tell.
Ha Chan-ho got arrested
at the crime scene.
He was completely drunk.
So he keeps saying
he can't remember anything.
What about the bloodstains?
She was apparently like that
when he woke up,
so he was shocked
and tried to see if she was okay.
That's how he got them.
How drunk do you need to be
to not be able to notice anything
even when the glass table got shattered?
Let's say we believe
that Ha Chan-ho is innocent.
But how are we going to prove that?
We need to prove that she either collapsed
on her own or was killed by someone else.
What about the hotel CCTVs?
There are no CCTVs
at the White Hotel suite
because they care about
protecting their VIPs' privacy.
It's better for Ha Chan-ho
to say it happened by accident
because he was too drunk.
If it was accidental, he'll only
get locked up for six months to a year.
He has no motive to murder her,
so I guess we could say he got drunk
and made a mistake.
He's Ha Chan-ho, so he could
just get sentenced to probation.
That's not a bad idea.
We'll consider Mr. Yoon's idea
if we fail to prove that he's innocent.
It's extremely crucial
that we keep this confidential.
Once this leaks,
rumors will start spreading.
Later on, the truth won't even matter.
Yes, it's the best kind of topic
to make things up.
It's Mr. Song.
MR. SONG PIL-JUNG
Yes, sir.
-Let me go!
-Today at dawn,
-Ha Chan-ho, the CEO of Issume,
-Let go of me!
-Where is everyone?
-got arrested
as a murder suspect at a hotel in Seoul.
The victim
-was Ha Chan-ho's mistress
-Let go of me!
and art dealer.
The police are identifying the crime scene
and interrogating Ha Chan-ho
regarding what happened.
Ha Chan-ho is apparently
denying all charges.
But according to their friends,
they fought very often.
And judging by the fact that they were
the only people at the hotel...
Ms. Kim.
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be directed to voicemail.
Damn it. Is he kidding me?
"Kevin"?
Is he still ignoring your calls?
How dare he betray me
when I'm the one who got him here?
And with Song Pil-jung at that?
What do you want?
-Did you watch the news?
-Yes, it's a mess.
Aren't you in charge of Issume?
This time, Mr. Song asked Mr. Yoon
to take care of the issue.
I bet he's very upset right now.
He cared so much about Ha Chan-ho.
Now is the best time to attack.
If Ha Chan-ho loses power,
so will Mr. Song.
We need to use this opportunity
to turn the tables around.
Do you have a plan?
How about using Ha Hye-won?
Should I call her right away?
No, not yet.
Let's see how Mr. Song reacts to this.
If we do anything rash,
it might backfire on us.
I disagree.
I don't care what you think.
I know I'm right.
Don't cause a mess of things and stay put.
Should we get started?
My gosh, we really don't click.
-Pardon?
-Just stay put
if you don't want things to backfire!
What's that supposed to mean?
Sir.
INTERROGATION ROOM
After I found out
that Jeong-hwa ran away from home,
I went looking for her.
And she was at the hotel.
How did you find her so quickly?
I had a GPS device installed
on her cell phone.
I bought her that cell phone.
What happened after you met her?
She told me
that she can no longer live with me.
I fought with her and apologized.
I even begged her.
I did everything I could.
Then I drank.
I already told you
what happened after that.
I found her like that upon waking up,
so I tried to wake her up.
But she never woke up.
Jeong-hwa...
Is she really dead?
How much did you drink?
About half a bottle of hard liquor.
That's all.
I wasn't that drunk.
The police did a drug test, right?
Do not even think
about your relationship with her.
Never.
Do not say anything about it,
under any circumstances.
Maybe it was Jun-ho's doing.
He has an alibi.
So you think
I killed her?
Me?
You really think I killed Jeong-hwa?
You really think...
I killed her?
No, no way.
There's no way in hell that I killed her.
Me? I killed Jeong-hwa?
I'm telling you. No way.
My father doesn't know yet, right?
How did he find out?
The whole country knows now.
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATIONS
It happened when he was drunk,
so I'm sure he's saying
he doesn't remember anything.
It doesn't matter
whether they're rich or poor.
Bastards who commit murder on the spur
of the moment always say the same thing.
About Seo Jeong-hwa's phone
that was found at the scene...
The one under Ha Chan-ho's name?
I have to say, he was obsessed with her.
Most incoming calls were from Ha Chan-ho.
He called her dozens of times a day.
What? Are you going to say that's love?
Lawyers who represent douchebags like him
always say that.
Hey, it's me.
The phone that the cops have
is the one Ha Chan-ho bought for her.
I don't think it has anything
other than call history between them.
How do you know?
Did you steal her call records?
No, the lead detective on the case
told me.
We need to trace her movements
on the day of her death.
Call Mr. Jo and tell him
to get her navigation--
Mr. Na is already on it.
Tracing her trails from that day
may give us some clues.
Ha Chan-ho said he even planted
a GPS device on her phone.
Tell Mr. Na we need the records from it.
You don't believe Ha Chan-ho, right?
What about you, now that you've met him?
Do you believe him?
Let's be honest.
Even if he did it, he wouldn't know.
"Whether we believe him or not
isn't important."
That's what I'm expecting to hear.
As for this case,
the truth is what matters.
Maybe we're trying not to see the truth
that is already there.
Or maybe you're still harboring
hard feelings against Ha Chan-ho.
No, I'm trying to approach this
objectively.
People only see
what they want to see.
And sometimes,
they think that's "objective."
So what, then? Do you believe Ha Chan-ho?
I asked you earlier.
-I'll call you later.
-Wait.
-Did I keep you waiting long?
-No, sir.
Dad.
The stock price has plummeted, Dad.
If we don't come up with
-a solution--
-Then what?
-Dad.
-Even if things get really bad,
I won't appoint you as the new CEO.
Then what will you do?
Don't tell me you're going
to appoint Jun-ho instead.
No way.
That's why you're here.
This time, you've latched onto this?
Ha Jun-ho?
We need Issume.
Ha Chan-ho is in such a mess,
so we need an alternative.
Then what about Ha Hye-won?
The CEOs of the subsidiaries
will strongly object to it.
And it has failed once.
Ha Jun-ho never studied
business management properly.
And right now, he's...
He's a mess now.
Because of Seo Jeong-hwa?
That's why now is a good time.
I bet he's resenting Ha Chan-ho like crazy
at the moment.
If he's given the chance to replace him,
he'll do his best.
-Sir.
-What I need
isn't Issume led by Ha Hye-won.
I need Ha Jun-ho in that seat.
You'd better watch out.
This time, I may stab you in the back.
-Hye-won!
-You too, Dad.
You'll regret this.
Your sons are incompetent morons.
Yet you favor them
just because they're sons?
Hye-won!
-Gosh.
-Calm down.
-That brat.
-She's so self-centered.
You must look at the big picture and think
about Issume's future. Calm down.
It actually worked out for the best.
The whole country is in an uproar
because of Ha Chan-ho.
No one's even thinking
about the inheritance tax law right now.
Mr. Song.
If Issume falters,
things will become difficult.
The election is around the corner.
With Ha Hye-won, it'll be hard.
Politically, she and the chairman
never saw eye to eye.
Gosh, you'll be doing big things.
You need to be gutsier.
Thanks to you, my approval rating
has dropped by at least 15 percent.
So? What about it?
I gave it a bump
and made it drop a little.
What's the problem? I'm okay with it.
Congressman Lee.
Issume isn't our only card.
So they must pass the bill
on the Inheritance Tax Act.
Just stay focused and keep at it.
I got your back.
Thank you.
Mr. Song.
Supreme Court Justice Yoon is against
the revised bill. Are you aware of that?
Everyone at the Legislative Office
seems taken aback by it.
Judge Yoon?
He wouldn't be where he is today
without your help and support.
How could he be against it?
If we fail to persuade him,
we won't really be able
to revise the inheritance law.
I'll take care of it.
Please do not falter.
Do you understand?
It's me. Is everything okay with you?
You must be busy with Ha Chan-ho's case.
Work is work, you know.
Dad, did you have dinner?
What about you?
I hope you're not skipping meals.
Of course not.
Is everything okay?
Yes, all is good.
Dad.
You need to look after your health.
Try to go for walks at least.
Okay, I will.
Well,
we'll talk later.
The autopsy is done,
but they can't reach
Seo Jeong-hwa's family,
so they're keeping the body
in the mortuary.
She lived in Korea
up until she was in fourth grade.
But after that,
there are no records whatsoever.
All we know is she and her family
might've moved abroad.
The autopsy results?
It usually takes about two weeks,
but it can be expedited.
Okay.
Gosh.
Life is so futile.
She died so tragically,
but no one would even collect her body.
Finding and catching the culprit
is probably the only thing we can do
to give that poor soul some solace.
"That poor soul"?
She died with her eyes open.
Thanks. You may leave.
Yes, ma'am.
It's not your fault though.
Ms. Seo? It's me, Jung Geum-ja.
Are you aware that Ha Chan-ho
is suspicious of you?
You must keep your guard up.
This time, it won't end
with just confinement or assault.
Do you understand?
I looked. It's not here.
I don't think she left
her second phone at home.
Maybe she took it with her that day.
Hello.
All right, let's begin.
Mr. Na got all the data
from Seo Jeong-hwa's GPS navigation system
and the tracker on her phone.
We put everything together
to trace her movements
on the day of the incident.
Seo Jeong-hwa left home at 2 p.m.
Then she stopped by the brunch cafe
at 2:30 p.m.
The cafe owned by Han Su-jeong?
-Pardon?
-What?
-Is Ms. Han not here today?
-No, I'm afraid she's not.
-Do you know what time she'll be here?
-No, I don't.
-Is she not picking up?
-No answer.
HAN SU-JEONG, CAFE OWNER
5:30 P.M. YEONAN PIER
Then she stopped by Yeonan Pier
in Incheon at 5:30 p.m.
Well, what am I supposed to find here?
I wasn't even given an address.
Just Yeonan Pier?
Show people Seo Jeong-hwa's photo
and find out whatever you can.
There isn't a single soul here.
But it's a pier.
There must be some people who work there.
Find people and obtain information
on Seo Jeong-hwa.
ATTORNEY GA GI-HYEOK
Wait, hello?
Jeez.
This is what Hee-jae was talking about.
She just hangs up on people.
God damn it.
Have you ever seen this person?
If anyone you know has seen her,
-please call me.
-Sure.
Gosh, I'm not sure.
Please contact me.
Have you seen this woman?
I heard she came here often.
No idea.
7:00 P.M. NEAR WHITE HOTEL
Seo Jeong-hwa entered White Hotel
at 7 p.m.
May I ask you to check
this lady's guest records?
SEO JEONG-HWA
I'm sorry. I'm afraid we can't.
Mr. Kim, what brings you by?
Hello.
I remembered that you work here.
I have a bad memory, so I didn't know.
How can I help you?
I need some information.
SEO JEONG-HWA
SUITE 1325
Oh, you need to bring a warrant for this.
Come on. I'm just a lawyer.
How can I get a warrant?
I can't help you with this.
Your wife caught you and your mistress
in the act in a suite here.
Your wife beat her up,
and that woman hit your wife as well.
I heard you also got beaten up
while trying to stop them. That suite...
The hotel doesn't know you used it.
What kind of information do you need?
Yes, Ms. Jung.
Seo Jeong-hwa used a credit card
to pay for the hotel suite,
and it's a corporate credit card.
The company's name is ArtSky.
The director is away
on a work trip abroad.
It's an art agency.
But the employees don't know
Seo Jeong-hwa.
Okay, find out when the director
will be back.
So no leads at all?
Whether it's to prove him innocent
or guilty.
We don't know much about
Seo Jeong-hwa at all, don't you think?
Ha Chan-ho's mistress.
I'm sure there's more to her
than just that title.
What matters
is not who she was.
What's important is
who she was to Ha Chan-ho.
That's why his motive is crucial.
When will you return to being a lawyer?
When will you start being
Ha Chan-ho's lawyer again?
Ms. Jung,
look at this online tabloid article.
An anonymous man revealed
his relationship with Seo Jeong-hwa.
Apparently, he's a conglomerate heir.
The title, for starters,
is too suggestive.
"The Deadly Love Triangle
of Conglomerate Heirs,
Who Drove Seo Jeong-hwa to Her Death?"
This anonymous man loved her
and he was her first and final love.
He says that Ha Chan-ho
was just a phase to her.
This could be a freaking song.
Could the man be Ha Jun-ho?
-No, it's not him.
-What?
I doubt he's in his right mind
to agree to an interview like this.
I just know.
-Do you know what this means?
-Ha Chan-ho's motive.
Up until now,
we could've argued manslaughter
because there wasn't
any other clear motive,
but this changes everything!
Who will see this as accidental?
This points to murder!
Why would Ha Jun-ho...
I mean, this anonymous man
other than Ha Jun-ho.
Why would an anonymous man
reveal this now?
It's probably someone
who wants Ha Chan-ho behind bars.
And who would that be?
That's a long list.
HA JUN-HO, ISSUME
I'd like to meet. Please call me.
Two favor Ha Hye-won
while two are on our side.
Four are still neutral.
I know a man who can
swing their votes our way.
Mr. Yoon,
will I really be able to do a good job?
You...
must.
Chairman Ha already gave you the reins.
You don't really have a choice.
You know a man who can help? Who is he?
I'm Kevin Jung, the branch manager
of AP EON Korea.
I'm Ha Jun-ho.
We need foreign investors
to show faith in you.
In that sense,
AP EON will be most influential.
Issume is floundering
due to Ha Chan-ho's antics,
so you will step up
and stabilize the company.
Mr. Jung here will support
that decision of yours.
I thank you in advance.
I can't believe you called me.
I was surprised at first.
Mr. Song suggested it. Take care, then.
How's Ms. Jung doing?
I haven't seen her in a while.
She's busy with Ha Chan-ho's case, right?
Rather than asking me,
ask her directly if you're that curious.
I wonder why
I'm so bothered by you.
Because I like her.
She's the woman I like.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
Ha Chan-ho didn't do any drugs.
He was wasted though.
-But zolpidem was found in his system.
-Zolpidem?
A MEDICATION USED TO TREAT INSOMNIA
-That's for insomnia.
-Right.
Can you keep tabs on the investigation?
One of the detectives
is a close friend of mine, so yes.
But Eun-yeong,
anyone can tell that Ha Chan-ho did it.
-Ju-ho--
-Why are you going this far for him?
Because you're a lawyer?
-Forget about that--
-She died.
Seo Jeong-hwa died.
This may be my fault.
Then stay with Ha Chan-ho.
It's the only way
you can keep seeing his brother, too.
This case
started with me.
Every evidence points to Ha Chan-ho.
It's just too easy.
Finding her real killer.
That's the least I can do
for Seo Jeong-hwa now.
The bastard sent this.
"To the people of Korea"?
He wrote in detail how I put him in prison
for attempted murder.
He's threatening to release it
if I don't apologize.
SHE CHANGED HER NAME TO JUNG GEUM-JA
He has no evidence against you.
His only evidence
is his own memory.
You think I'm telling you this
because I don't know that?
Since when do you...
Who told you this?
No one. I'm a former detective, remember?
-I know my law.
-Ju-ho.
I need you to change your mind.
This isn't me asking.
I'm giving you an order.
I'm only doing what I can
in the position I'm in.
-Chung-yeon--
-My objection
won't change anything.
You've got to be kidding me.
Who put you in that seat?
Someone must be able
to call out what is wrong.
-Yoon Chung-yeon!
-You're the one
who gave me that responsibility.
The responsibility is too grave
for me to ignore or disregard.
Just crawl into a hole then.
If you want to object,
keep it to yourself and stay silent.
I'm leaving.
Chung-yeon!
Kevin, it's me.
I have something that might intrigue you.
Right.
A plan to make
Issume's stock price plummet.
That's right.
KEVIN JUNG
AP EON
This coffeehouse chain
also belongs to AP EON.
Nice, right?
You must've made all the customers leave.
I like the quietness.
It's less stuffy than our offices.
So what did you need?
I used work as an excuse,
but it's nice to be here with you.
It feels like a date.
What do you think
will happen to Ha Chan-ho?
I'm not at liberty to say.
He has a competent lawyer by his side,
so I'm sure he'll be out soon.
A trial will take time
and it's good for me
if Issume's stock price drops.
Do you know Prosecutor Kwon Yong-un?
You probably do.
He was the lead prosecutor
in your previous trial.
I see you know a lot.
Of course.
There's nothing about you
that I don't know.
I'd like you to deliver those.
No, I won't.
-Why not?
-Because anyone else could do it.
That's too bad.
What's your angle?
Why did you show this to me?
Because I don't like Mr. Yoon.
It'd be a thrill if you did this for me.
Also, it'll inform me
of your relationship with him.
I'm disappointed that you declined.
-I'll be in touch.
-Wait.
Let's grab a late-night snack.
No, thanks.
ATTORNEY YOON HEE-JAE
It's me. Where are you right now?
Deliver the package.
PROSECUTOR KWON YONG-UN
Why on earth aren't you focused?
Do you even care
about Seo Jeong-hwa's case?
Seo Jeong-hwa?
Because of Ha Chan-ho
who killed Seo Jeong-hwa,
Issume is being shaken to its core.
It's why I'm trying to have
Ha Jun-ho take over for his brother.
Is this Mr. Song's idea?
He chose Ha Jun-ho of all people?
Is that why those people want
Ha Chan-ho to face murder charges?
So Ha Jun-ho can take over?
Get your facts in order.
This is only happening
because of what Ha Chan-ho did.
I told you to set personal feelings aside.
You never believed Ha Chan-ho, did you?
You're the one who's being clouded
by personal feelings.
Seo Jeong-hwa returned to Ha Chan-ho
because of you.
Aren't I right?
That guilt is making you hope
that Ha Chan-ho didn't do it.
You're obsessed over a tiny possibility.
Don't you think that's the reason
why you can't see things clearly?
I'm honestly worried about you.
I'm only doing my job
and I don't need you to worry about me.
It's because I like you.
Because I have feelings for you.
Did you meet with Ju-ho?
Is that why?
You pity my old self?
That's pity, not affection.
And I don't need any of that.
I...
am in love with
Jung Geum-ja
who used to be Jung Eun-yeong.
Your name could be Kim Hee-sun
or anything else
and I still wouldn't care.
Kim Hee-sun, Jung Eun-yeong,
or whatever else,
you're still you.
That's how you used to be
and that's how you will be.
You'll push me away again.
You'll run away from me
using my family and background
as an excuse.
Just know that it's not your style at all.
How well do you know people?
If you hate me, just say so.
And stop being cryptic about it.
I don't hate you.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
That's why I asked you here.
I'm worried about you too.
Maybe...
I should've stayed out of it.
He probably only showed me
because he thought I would.
But I couldn't since it concerns you.
I had to do what I usually don't do.
Your father
will go down.
Stop it from happening
if it's not already too late.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
HYENA
Hee-jae, don't trust anyone for now.
-Dad.
-Leave. I want to be alone.
Dad!
Who knows the best
about Issume and your dad?
Carry out the plan you told me last time.
The two of them...
Mr. Ga is in charge of Ha Chan-ho's case.
We've been totally shut out.
The Korean Bar Association
is going to hold a disciplinary hearing.
I'm asking if you two were close enough
to share information.
That's what a lowly lawyer like you do.
I'll make a team to defend my dad.
I wanted to tell you
that this is only the beginning.
Here at Song & Kim.