HYENA
THIS DRAMA IS PURELY FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH
ACTUAL PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, ASSOCIATIONS,
OR LOCATIONS
NATIONAL LAW INFORMATION CENTER
YOON CHUNG-YEON
OPPOSITE OPINION
OF JUDGE YOON CHUNG-YEON
WHEN A COMPANY IS IN NEED OF MONEY,
A DIRECTOR CAN...
OPPOSITE OPINION
OF JUDGE YOON CHUNG-YEON
Your father will go down.
Stop it from happening
if it's not already too late.
What do you mean?
Be more clear.
All the verdicts decided by your father
regarding Issume.
Someone thinks he did them a favor
because he's close with Chairman Ha.
The tip-off is pretty detailed.
It's going to get sent
to Prosecutor Kwon Yong-un.
How do you know this? Who's behind this?
I don't know the details.
The person who told me this
probably got a tip-off as well.
It's useful information
for whoever that wants
to cause damage to Issume.
ISSUME LOGISTICS' MERGER PRESS REPORTS
ISSUME LOGISTIC'S 2ND TRIAL PRECEDENT
TRIAL REGARDING ISSUME'S ILLEGAL TRANSFER
OF MANAGEMENT RIGHTS
1. ISSUME LOGISTICS' CONVERTIBLE BONDS
SET AT LOW PRICE
JUDGE PANEL: YOON CHUNG-YEON
EPISODE 13
You're here so early in the morning.
Is it because of this?
You're quick.
I only got this a few minutes ago.
Reaching a verdict
is solely up to the judge.
Yes, I know.
But when your father used to be
the chief judge,
he pressured his colleague
that ruled Issume guilty
during the first trial.
And right before the second trial,
he met Chairman Ha way too many times.
You already know that's not enough
to prove that there was a connection
between them.
Then why are you here?
Isn't it because you're feeling uneasy?
The entire world knows
that you're crazy about indicting Issume.
So I came to check
if you know what you're getting into.
This isn't merely about Issume.
Your father should take responsibility
for the mess he made.
I'm going to investigate this, Hee-jae.
Plus, my boss will love it.
Fine.
Don't make the same mistake.
You should do better.
ISSUME HOLDINGS WINS LAWSUIT
ON THE NULLITY OF MERGER
Everything will be fine
It's not like your father
received any money.
My father
would never meet Chairman Ha by himself.
You were always there with him.
That's why everything will be fine.
How many people do you think
know about this?
Someone from Issume
could've leaked the information.
We can make sure it doesn't happen again.
-Sir.
-I'll deal with this issue.
Don't worry.
Just focus on what you're working on.
That's what you should do for now.
My father always trusted you.
That's why he was fine with it
when I told him I wanted to work here.
At least make sure the reporters
don't publish any articles about this.
Please, sir.
I told you that I'll take care of it.
You should get back to work.
What do you think?
Are you asking for my personal opinion?
TRIAL REGARDING ISSUME'S ILLEGAL TRANSFER
OF MANAGEMENT RIGHTS
BRIBERY
I don't agree with this verdict.
They can't be innocent.
And I can't tolerate the fact
that he met Chairman Ha so frequently
before the trial.
You're being hardheaded again.
How could you say that in this situation?
You can't indict a judge
for his or her own verdict.
Yes, I know.
But I'm saying there could be other judges
who think what I think.
But Dad's against the amendment
of the Inheritance Tax Act.
What?
The new Inheritance Tax Act
proposed by Congressman Lee.
He disagrees with the Legislative Office.
He apparently made it clear
that he's against it.
The Legislative Office
is in a pickle because of him.
-Dad's against it?
-Didn't you know?
Aren't you in charge
of revising the Inheritance Tax Act?
ATTORNEY KIM CHANG-UK
Hey, Mr. Kim.
I just sent you some photos.
Look at the ones I marked
Yes, go ahead.
Do you see the shattered table?
And do you see the alcohol bottle?
The one that's half full
If the alcohol spilled that way,
the rug should be wet.
But there aren't any stains on the rug
But it's hard to tell because the photo
was taken from a distance.
It's not a close-up photo of the rug,
so it's not precise.
We'd be able to find out
if we could see the evidence.
What if
there really aren't any stains on the rug?
That means it was a set-up.
It means someone did it on purpose
-Is everything going well?
-I'll call you back.
My gosh.
-It's been a while.
-Has it?
I have something to ask you.
-What is it this time?
-What do you think?
It's about Seo Jeong-hwa.
Jeong-hwa.
She's been on the news for days,
so I'm sure you know what happened.
What do you want to know?
You met her
on the day she died, right?
-Me?
-She searched this place
on her car navigation.
Ms. Han.
I didn't meet her.
We just talked on the phone.
I had to urgently go somewhere.
Was it her cell phone?
Yes, obviously. What else would it be?
Here are Seo Jeong-hwa's call logs.
It's all Ha Chan-ho.
He called her so many times.
I feel suffocated just by looking at this.
Imagine how bad it must've been for her
You guys really talked on the phone?
Yes.
What did you talk about?
You see,
it's too private.
So I expect something in return.
-Ms. Han.
-You and I
already made a deal once.
Why not do it again?
Do you really want to use her death
to strike a deal with me?
I'll think of it
as Jeong-hwa's last gift.
What?
Are you serious?
You’re so messed up.
Sorry?
Prepare some money.
-For whom?
-Han Su-jeong.
PHONE CALL WITH HA CHAN-HO
Drugs? Jeong-hwa?
She hated drugs because of that bastard.
She didn't even take sleeping pills.
The alcohol was already there
when I arrived!
Sleeping pills?
You call that a drug?
I don't take that kind of shit.
Okay, I understand.
Did you and Ms. Seo
really talk over the phone that day?
Yes. Why?
I couldn't find it on her call logs.
Did she happen to own another cell phone?
What time
was your last phone call with her?
CALL LOGS
JEONG-HWA
It was at 7:30 p.m.
Seo Jeong-hwa
entered White Hotel at 7:00 p.m
A MORE EFFECTIVE TAX SUPPORT SYSTEM
FOR FAMILY BUSINESS SUCCESSION
But Dad's against the amendment
of the Inheritance Tax Act.
What?
The new Inheritance Tax Act
proposed by Congressman Lee.
He apparently made it clear
that he's against it
-Dad's against it?
-Didn't you know?
PHONE CALL WITH HA JUN-HO
So you're saying she had
another cell phone
that no one knew about
including us and the cops?
Did you share this with the team?
They don't know about
Ha Jun-ho and Seo Jeong-hwa yet.
For now, it's better that way.
Otherwise, they'd be suspicious
of Ha Chan-ho.
Shouldn't they know that as lawyers?
We work as a team.
It's not that I don't trust our team.
I just don't trust myself.
I might easily get convinced
and think that Ha Chan-ho is lying.
I don't want to end up
ignoring what's suspicious.
It's better to keep this
between ourselves for now.
Remember Zolpidem,
the sedative that was detected
in Ha Chan-ho's body?
What if Ha Chan-ho and Seo Jeong-hwa
didn't have any sleeping pills that day?
Someone could've given it to them.
Well...
Sorry.
I can't focus.
Did you meet your father?
I couldn't go see him.
I couldn't think of what to say.
I wasn't confident enough to tell him
that I'll try to stop it.
I hate myself
for feeling so helpless.
Do you think Prosecutor Kwon
was the only person
who got the tip-off?
Don't you think the press got it as well?
This person wants to harm Issume.
So I asked for help.
You asked Mr. Song?
But something keeps bothering me.
I might be being too sensitive.
About the Inheritance Tax Act...
HYEOK-JAE
Just a second.
What is it?
What?
THE SUPREME COURT JUSTICE'S
BACKDOOR DEAL
JUDICIAL OFFICERS' CORRUPTION
SHOULD COME TO AN END
THE SUPREME COURT JUSTICE
PROTECTS ISSUME
HOW DID YOON CHUNG-YEON BECOME
THE SUPREME COURT JUSTICE?
YOON CHUNG-YEON'S CONNECTIONS
IN QUESTION
SPEC WATCH KOREA DEMANDS
YOON CHUNG-YEON'S CONFINEMENT
We're in front of Supreme Court Justice
Yoon Chung-yeon's house
in Pyeongchang-dong, Seoul
The prosecution is planning to indict
Mr. Yoon for abuse of authority
and obstruction of exercising rights
while he was in charge
of Issume's succession case
Supreme Court Justice Yoon Chung-yeon is
known to be very strict
when it comes to sticking to his beliefs
and the Constitution
and therefore,
he receives a lot of respect
That is why many people are shocked
by his irregularity
Do you think Mr. Yoon will be okay?
Whoever did this
was going to tip off the press anyway.
So that Mr. Yoon would be helpless
even if he found out.
Who?
Isn't it the first time
us three are getting together?
I'm sorry.
I'd like for you to hold off on the merger
between the two companies.
So what's with the twist?
This is something you can't know about.
It must be something big then.
What do you think will happen
to Ha Chan-ho? A trial will take time
and it's good for me
if Issume's stock price drops.
KEVIN, ISSUME, SONG & KIM
SONG & KIM, YOON CHUNG-YEON
SONG
ATTORNEY YOON HEE-JAE
ATTORNEY JUNG GEUM-JA
-Dad.
-Leave.
I want to be alone.
WHEN ARE YOU COMING?
HYEOK-JAE
Pil-jung.
It's me, Chung-yeon.
Yes.
Okay.
I'm going to get some air.
Dad, you'll freeze
if you go outside dressed like that.
Hey, I can't talk right now.
It's about your father.
SONG PIL-JUNG
Who do you think is behind this?
Dad!
Wait right there.
-Hurry up and call 911.
-Hello?
-Someone got hit by a car.
-What's wrong?
Mr. Yoon!
Hee-jae!
OPERATING ROOM
What happened?
I thought you were with him.
How did this happen?
What about you? What were you doing?
Where were you all day
when Dad was all over the news?
-I--
-You were probably in your office.
You were scared
that people might judge you, weren't you?
Is that really the best you could do?
You're a damn judge!
You incompetent and selfish jerk!
He looked so relaxed.
As if he decided to let go of everything.
Dad!
Why do you think he did that?
Pil-jung
It's me, Chung-yeon.
No way.
No, it can't be.
Your father and Issume.
Who knows best about them?
But why?
Issume's stock price
will continue to go down.
Even if Ha Jun-ho becomes the CEO,
it'll cause too much of a mess.
Hee-jae.
Think.
Be calm about it.
You're very level-headed.
You know Mr. Song better than anyone,
so you'll be able to see what's going on.
The Inheritance Tax Act.
Hee-jae.
They finished Dad's surgery and moved him.
Right now, just focus on your father
and yourself.
That's it. Don't think of anything else.
He lost a lot of blood
Tonight will be the hardest.
We'll have to keep our eyes on him
Mr. Yoon!
I asked my secretary
not to let anyone inside.
Oh, I apologize.
Don't worry about it. We're done anyway.
See you.
What's up?
My father
got into an accident.
You're not even surprised.
Is he seriously injured?
I won't beat around the bush.
You talked to him on the phone yesterday.
What did you two talk about?
Why do I have to tell you?
Since when were you curious
about our conversations?
-Sir.
-I'm...
a little baffled right now.
You're talking as if
I have something to do
with your father's accident.
Then say that you don't.
Say it wasn't about anything important.
Say that you spoke with him
because you were worried.
It wasn't a normal accident.
He tried to take his own life.
Don't you know
what kind of situation Issume is in now?
-Uncle Pil-jung.
-You know better than anybody else does.
The company is shaken to the core
because of Ha Chan-ho.
And the thing involving your father
broke out on top of that.
What should I be concerned about now?
If you're the ace of our firm,
you should be concerned
about the same thing.
The Inheritance Tax Act.
I heard my father was against it.
So?
Isn't that why
you're not concerned about him?
Because my father is a roadblock
to achieving your big goals.
-Yoon Hee-jae!
-Am I wrong?
I have known your father for years.
I really did my best.
Then allow me to put a team together
for my father's case.
Song & Kim
will stay out of it.
I beg your pardon?
That will look
much better.
You were the one
who promised my father the position
of Supreme Court Justice.
And you were the one
who introduced my father to Chairman Ha.
From what I can see,
you seem to be at the center of it all.
Watch what you say.
I will put together a team
to defend my father.
Right here, at Song & Kim.
You see, there's a company
called Issume Logistics
It's a very small company,
and it's owned by Ha Chan-ho.
His plan was to grow and merge it
with Issume Pharmaceuticals down the road.
Having control over it
means you have control
over the entire Issume Group.
Because it's a holding company.
However, he tried to grow Issume Logistics
using various illegal means,
so they're dealing with multiple lawsuits.
They got a guilty verdict
in the first trial. Then Judge Yoon...
Anyway, he issued a not-guilty verdict.
So the company will be passed down to...
An accident? He got into an accident?
How did it happen?
Does it mean he's hospitalized now?
-Which hospital?
-He's in the ICU,
so only his family members can visit him.
He's in the ICU? Is he critically injured?
We'll have to wait and see.
Hee-jae.
Are you all right?
Don't worry about work.
You should stay by your father's side.
-This will be the last time.
-See you around.
That day,
Seo Jeong-hwa ordered room service.
I think she ordered a drink.
Find out who took it to her room.
Will do.
There's a rug among the evidence
the police have. Can you check?
-Have a good day.
-Thank you.
Do you know a company named ArtSky?
No, I'm afraid I don't.
I'm not sure what kind of company
ArtSky actually is.
Even people in the art industry
aren't familiar with it.
We must get our hands
on the list of ArtSky's key clients.
I'd really love to get my hands on it.
I wish we had a warrant.
What should we do when we don't have one?
Ms. Seo Jeong-hwa told you about us?
Yes. I've met the director a few times,
but it's hard
to get ahold of him these days.
That happens every time
when the director is abroad.
Which company did you say you're from?
AP EON. It's a private equity firm.
My boss would like to purchase
a number of paintings.
As you know, we're looking for pieces
that can be liquidated easily and quickly.
That being said,
could you show me a list of your clients
and artworks that can be trusted?
-Hello.
-You're back.
As for the suite at White Hotel,
there are no CCTV cameras in the room,
the hallway, and even in the parking lot.
This is from the entrance
of the parking lot.
-The entrance of the parking lot?
-Yes.
All vehicles must pass
through that entrance.
Make a list of every vehicle you spot
from the time Seo Jeong-hwa checked in
to the time when Ms. Jung arrived.
Do you know how many people
visit White Hotel every day?
Not just their guests. Many seminars,
banquets, and parties take place there.
Mr. Na, let's divide the workload in half.
Is this really necessary though?
Everyone knows
that Ha Chan-ho is the culprit.
"Everyone"?
Who?
Mr. Na. When working on a criminal case,
the truth can
only be uncovered through evidence,
not through what someone thinks.
Okay.
THE DAY OF THE INCIDENT
7:00 P.M. SEO JEONG-HWA CHECKED IN
It almost looks as if they knew Ha Chan-ho
was going to kill Seo Jeong-hwa.
EVIDENCE, RUG
THE MEDIA TOOK PICTURES
OF HA CHAN-HO GETTING ARRESTED
Did you find anything?
My eyes are hurting because
I've been staring at hundreds of cars.
You're teary-eyed.
Right?
You can't help but get teary-eyed
because I've been doing this for hours.
-You're actually teary-eyed.
-Sorry?
My eyes hurt so much.
-Gosh.
-Let's go. You need some nourishing food.
What?
You're the best.
Corn and pineapple, my favorite.
My, this pizza looks delicious.
My gosh.
I know what you like. You love pizza.
Do you still love pizza that much?
Yes, because I couldn't have it
growing up.
The pizza you used to get for me
from time to time was so delicious.
My siblings still love pizza so much also.
They're doing well?
They're like vampires
that suck blood out of me.
When my mom ran off
with our housemates' money,
I would've actually died
without your help.
Thank you so much again, for saving me.
Goodness, I can't believe
you took so many pills.
I almost broke my back
while carrying you that day.
Come on. Your back is totally fine.
What?
What will be discussed
at the EP general meeting?
Dismissal of the managing partner.
I mean, your dismissal, ma'am.
-Where is Mr. Ma?
-At the other meeting--
Where is Ma Seok-gu?
What's up?
It looks like
Ha Jun-ho will gain control over Issume.
What great timing.
Something like that can only be done now.
I asked you why you're here.
How did you persuade Kevin?
Did you promise him Issume?
I see.
Now, I understand
why Kevin decided to join hands with you.
With that idiot, Ha Jun-ho,
as a puppet CEO,
you two can do whatever you want
with the company.
You're talking nonsense.
You're getting ready
for the election again.
I suppose Issume will give you
quite the headache.
As for Chairman Ha
and Supreme Court Justice Yoon...
You can just blame them.
But you were the one who recommended
Supreme Court Justice Yoon
to the Blue House.
And they went with your suggestion.
-Min-joo.
-What an interesting dynamic.
Kim Min-joo.
Watch what you say.
I'm just trying to tell you
that I won't back down easily.
My father started this law firm.
I won't let you steal it from me.
You need to step down
if you're not capable of doing your job.
That's only fair.
That's what you think. It is your logic.
Then prove me wrong.
With factual proof,
not something you made up.
Okay?
I guess you still don't know this.
Your father totally used me
and deserted me.
As for this firm,
I didn't "steal" it. I made it mine
with my abilities.
And I grew it to what it is today,
You don't need to worry
about Supreme Court Justice Yoon anymore.
I heard he got into an accident.
Unfortunately,
accidents can happen anytime, you know.
I guess you just never know.
Thanks to it, the Inheritance Tax Act
will pass without much trouble.
You're almost there, so just keep it up.
Okay?
All right.
We could've talked at work.
You never make time for me.
I guess you're very busy these days.
-Still, how could you just show up--
-This is my style,
as you know.
It must be about something important.
I suppose that's why you showed up
unannounced.
It's about the Ha Chan-ho Case.
Was it involuntary manslaughter
or murder?
That will probably be the key.
That is
only if Ha Chan-ho is the culprit.
Are you saying he's not?
I have too many doubts.
And as I investigate them one by one,
I'll become even less convinced
that he's the culprit.
Well, that is my job
as his attorney.
He has a clear motive.
"Motive"?
Seo Jeong-hwa's affair with Ha Jun-ho?
Now, we need to move speedily
with the trial.
Admitting to the crime
would be one way of minimizing trouble.
You know that Issume took a hit
because of this case.
Wrap it up quickly.
No.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
I'll do my best to make sure my client
doesn't experience any injustice.
Even if that drags things out
and makes people gossip
about the case for a long time.
-Ms. Jung.
-One more thing.
Seo Jeong-hwa.
I plan to look into her
properly as well.
You can decide what to do.
Don't show up unannounced like this.
You're this uninterested
in the Ha Chan-ho Case?
You, of all people?
ATTORNEY MA SEOK-GU
It's me.
The thing you mentioned the other day...
You mean, about Attorney Yoon?
Go ahead with it.
Call the president
of the Korean Bar Association
and tell him to call me.
Yes, sir.
But what about Ms. Jung?
Are you thinking...
We'll treat those two...
as one.
Got it.
Me?
That's right. You'll be in charge
of the Ha Chan-ho Case from now on.
What? You don't think you can do it?
It's not that.
I just wasn't expecting this.
As they say,
he who's ready seizes opportunities.
Yes, of course. I'm more than ready.
What about Hee-jae and Ms. Jung?
A report was filed
at the Korean Bar Association.
While working on Ha Chan-ho's divorce,
they sullied the dignity of lawyers
through their misconduct.
Until the disciplinary committee
comes to a conclusion,
we'll have to sit and wait.
However, we don't have that luxury.
Quickly wrap up Ha Chan-ho's case
as soon as possible.
It's what Issume wants
and the order came from Mr. Song too.
He asked me to tell you
how he's expecting great things.
You know how Jeong-hwa
had an eye for paintings, right?
I heard that she personally
handled some pieces.
She was to sell a few of them
and leave the country with Ha Jun-ho.
What now?
-It's bad, Ms. Jung.
-Why? What is it?
The Korean Bar Association
is holding a disciplinary hearing
to discuss you and Mr. Yoon
regarding your possible misconduct
So Ha Chan-ho's case
is now being officially led by Mr. Ga.
"Misconduct"?
Because we dated?
Do they expect lawyers
to be celibate their whole lives?
And there's one more thing
which could be even worse.
Your father...
I mean,
the man who came by to see you.
You know, the ex-convict.
Anyway, he called to say
that he'd come by again
if you didn't come to see him yourself.
All right.
I'm sure you remember this place.
I never wanted to be reminded of it again.
But today,
this felt appropriate.
Because facing this place
will finally free me
from the hold you have on me.
Back then,
death was the only way
out of the hellhole.
It wasn't a bad way to die anyway
At least, my death
would serve some kind
of punishment to you.
That would then stop you
from beating anyone else to death.
But luckily enough, I lived.
Eun-yeong.
Forgiveness
shouldn't be sought out by just anyone.
Especially a fucked up bastard like you
shouldn't ask for it
or even want it in the first place.
Eun-yeong,
I prayed for you.
While serving my time,
That alone was enough
to make atonement for my sins.
It's your turn now.
The prayers were for nothing then
because I haven't forgiven you.
Get this through your skull.
The woman in front of you
isn't the 18-year-old Jung Eun-yeong.
If I need to,
I'll gladly pick up the knife again.
But this time,
I'll stab you instead of stabbing me.
It'll be ruled as self-defense though.
Because I'm that good of a lawyer.
Don't you ever show your face to me again
and shove your bullshit
back down your throat.
Ms. Jung Geum-ja
is waiting for you in your office.
She said she made an appointment.
What do you think you're doing?
You tell me.
What is it that you're doing?
The Korean Bar Association?
That was really fast. You put it in motion
seconds after I met with you.
Are you really that desperate?
I wonder what's been eating away at you.
Why must Ha Chan-ho
be found guilty?
And this quickly, if I may add.
So I've been racking my brain
to think of a plausible scenario.
I already know
you're free for the rest of the day.
It's why I took time off
my busy schedule to come here.
What if it's not to help Issume
but to sever ties with it?
Only that makes sense.
Ha Chan-ho must be out of the picture
and the reins needed to go
to the ditsy Ha Jun-ho, not Ha Hye-won.
Then, you were going to have Kevin
swallow Issume up.
Issume needed to be shaken up more,
-so you used Mr. Yoon's father--
-Ms. Jung!
It was Kevin who reported
Supreme Court Justice Yoon
to Prosecutor Kwon, right?
I wonder who Kevin
got the information from?
Why is it that only one person
comes to mind?
So?
What are you trying to say?
So you admit to everything?
I should at least hear out
someone who dares to threaten me.
All threats lead to demands anyway.
That's exactly how you,
a lowly third-rate lawyer, operates.
I'm not threatening you
and there are no demands.
I just wanted confirmation
on Song Pil-jung's,
I mean Mr. Song's intentions.
I also wanted to tell you
that I've only just begun.
This isn't over.
The tea was refreshing.
HANKOOK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Look at you all gaunt.
-Is that you worrying?
-Are you eating properly?
A haggard look isn't good on you.
It takes away the sexiness.
The one injured is my father, not me.
-Then give it to him.
-He can't eat properly yet.
-Then throw it away.
-Actually,
that's your specialty, not mine.
Why can't you just thank me?
Is it that hard to do?
Fine, I'll eat it then.
Is this why you came by?
How's your father?
Thankfully, he's recovering.
Now, tell me why you're really here.
Mr. Ga is in charge of Ha Chan-ho's case.
We've been booted off the case.
Then our suspicions
suddenly become more plausible.
Mr. Song
isn't just apathetic toward
my father's issue.
No, he could've
orchestrated the whole thing.
He's tossing Issume aside.
Yes, all of it to Kevin.
It's why Ha Chan-ho must be found guilty.
There's no proof though.
It's a dangerous conception.
We were taken off the case.
That's our proof.
-Also...
-There's more?
The Korean Bar Association
is going to hold a disciplinary hearing.
We'll be asked the same questions,
so we should be on the same page.
-As if we're not?
-Hold on.
You'll say that you were tricked
into handing the intel over?
It's true that I was tricked,
but the intel?
How should I know how you got
ahold of Ha Chan-ho's information?
They'll ask about our relationship.
I...
will only speak of how I felt at the time.
I remember it clearly, you see.
Us...
from how we began.
Thank you. It looks great.
I knew it.
Gi-hyeok, I knew you'd make me proud.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Let's sit.
I apologize.
I didn't think I'd be this happy,
but my hard work so far finally paid off.
Of course. No one is as prepared as you.
Just how long did it take?
You had to watch all your friends
become partners before you.
I'm proud of how you hung in there.
Anyway, I ordered your favorite.
Here.
Look at this melted cheese.
I may finally make partner--
-It's delicious.
-Isn't it good?
Does this mean that
I should refer to you as a partner lawyer?
Partner Ga, try this too.
No one calls me that.
Then be the first to be called as one.
What is it?
You seem worried.
No, it's nothing.
It's really nothing.
I feel bad, that's all.
Why would you feel bad on this happy day?
You shouldn't.
Go on. Tell me why.
Someone reported
Hee-jae and Ms. Jung
to the Korean Bar Association.
The case only fell into my lap
because of it.
What? How...
If the disciplinary committee
dismisses the charges,
I mean, rules in their favor,
I could be robbed of this chance.
What's worse is that
I need to testify at that hearing.
I've worked most closely with them
at the office.
This is wrong.
What is?
People must be loyal.
You must be to Hee-jae
and I must be to Geum-ja.
Be loyal.
Ms. Jung Geum-ja.
Yes?
While working on
Ha Chan-ho's divorce case,
is it true that you and Mr. Yoon were
involved in an inappropriate relationship?
What exactly do you mean by
an inappropriate relationship?
COMMISSIONER KIM JUNG-SU,
PARK DAE-HO, LEE SANG-HO
I'm asking if you two were close enough
to share information.
Yes.
That's right.
COMMISSIONER GANG MAN-SEOK
Ms. Jung approached you imposing
as Kim Hee-sun, an old friend from school.
Is that also true?
That has nothing to do
with this disciplinary hearing.
Why did Ms. Jung willfully approach you
by telling such lies?
Wasn't it so that she could illegally
obtain information on Ha Chan-ho?
No, sir.
It's true that I felt
a sexual attraction to Mr. Yoon.
I didn't think he'd see me
if I told him who I really was.
It was my way of getting to know him.
That's ridiculous.
He was the opposing lawyer.
No one can blame us for falling in love
even if that person killed your family.
Have you not read a romance novel
or watched a romantic movie before?
So you're saying
that you two were in love?
-Yes.
-We were.
I want to revisit everything one by one
to figure out at what point
you were being sincere with me.
I, too, am annoyed by how we keep
crossing each other's paths.
But the thing is, I get even more annoyed
when I don't see you around.
How does it feel to do things my way?
It's exciting, right?
I guess that's how memories are.
They're that dreadful.
If you need to, use me.
All right. I'll use you then.
Your name could be Kim Hee-sun or
anything else and I still wouldn't care.
You're still you.
Subtitle translation by Ja-won Lee