(All characters, organizations, places, cases, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
I've been looking for him everywhere.
I can't believe this is where he was all along.
Where did you take him?
Bring him here right now if you do not wish to die!
Professor Hwang, where are you?
I think those two will face a variation in them soon.
You have to come quickly. Professor Hwang?
You have my trust.
M, 3, 4.
(Professor Jo Gi Bum)
Tell me.
Where did you hide the cryonic...
that was here?
I guess...
you've succeeded in thawing them.
Then...
who took Lee Seok Du?
Don't kill Professor Hwang.
If you do, you'll be done for.
Take him.
His body temperature is 32.8°C.
We can't just treat him however we want.
- Did you call his guardian? - No.
Please call...
Professor Jo Gi Bum.
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed...
Hello?
Which hospital is it?
(Episode 12: To Die or To Be Mad)
(Bureau Chief, Na Ha Young)
(Lee Hyeong Du)
Hello?
Seok Du has disappeared.
They made a move before us.
Find him!
Isn't this Ma Dong Chan's phone?
Yes, it is. I'm a nurse.
He's hospitalized.
He's hospitalized?
The toxins are accumulating in your body.
That's why you were in shock.
This is a temporary antidote.
The symptom will manifest itself once again in 48 hours.
But this antidote won't work the second time around.
48 hours?
Then...
will Mi Ran also suffer from this?
Yes.
There has been a variation in the LAP...
and has turned into toxins.
Professor Hwang had mentioned this in his note.
He already knew this would happen.
However, we do not have a reagent that will get rid of it permanently.
I'm currently researching the protocol.
But I need Professor Hwang's help.
I need to know the code...
for the LAP that he administered into your bodies.
Where is he right now?
Are you okay?
What happened? Did you get a fever again?
I'm fine.
What is this?
When did I get this bruise?
That isn't a bruise.
Then?
I think the variation is happening in your body as well.
We'll have to keep an eye on it.
Could this be...
lethal?
I need to see Professor Hwang right now.
That's the problem. I cannot reach him.
And he said something strange.
He said he trusted me.
- What are you doing? - I need to find him.
There's no time.
You just collapsed. You need to rest.
You must remain at the hospital so we can keep an eye on you.
I'll look for him.
Go home.
How can I?
You must protect your immune system,
so go home.
Since when did you have this?
I wasn't aware of it.
How is it possible that you didn't know?
There's something wrong on your arm.
Go home and rest.
I won't go.
- Go. - No.
Professor Jo Gi Bum?
Can you spare me a minute?
Are those two...
in danger?
I need to find Professor Hwang.
Is Professor Hwang the only one who can cure them?
I'm currently looking for a solution.
Where's Lee Seok Du?
Why are you asking me that?
Dong Chan told me.
He told me that the current Lee Seok Du...
isn't really him and that the real Lee Seok Du...
has been in a capsule.
Now, can you believe that...
we're on the same team?
Go home. I'll call a cab.
Why are you trying to send me away?
Your being here won't help me.
My temperature will keep rising.
Then I must go.
All you're doing is worrying.
I like holding hands, looking at each other,
and being happy together.
But I don't want to be sick together.
Fine, I'll leave.
But don't get sick again.
I'm all better now. Don't worry.
Call me if anything happens.
Let's video call instead.
You love me so much, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Me too.
Hello?
Hello, I'm Professor Seo Hyun Jung,
the cultural communications professor.
Hello.
Have you given the essay some thought?
Things are a bit hectic for me at the moment.
I'm sorry.
(Professor Hwang Gab Su)
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to voicemail.
I think the variation is happening in your body as well.
Professor Seo.
This is Ko Mi Ran.
I'll write that essay.
I'm glad you agreed to do so.
May I ask what changed your mind?
There's someone...
that I love.
But we're in an unusual situation.
We don't know what will happen.
I feel like I should write down our story to be remembered.
At the age of 44, I found my first love.
However...
This could be my last.
Where are you going?
I told you to stay at home.
I told you to stay at the hospital.
Why did you come outside?
Because I missed you.
Why did you send me home if you were going to come so soon?
I told you, I'm fine.
Do you want to get a drink with me?
Why are there so many things I can't do?
I'm a bad drinker too.
Why can't I hold the man I love as much as I want?
My life is unfair.
It's not like I had the opportunity to love many people.
This is my first time.
Ma Dong Chan,
why did you come into my life?
Why did you...
make me love you?
I was told my life would get really lucky in 20 years,
and that I'd meet the man I'm destined to be with.
I finally met you,
but I'm going to die.
Who says you're going to die?
We're going to die soon because of the side effect.
We're not going to die.
We won't die like this.
I'm going to drink with you,
and spend a whole day just holding you.
I'm even going to take you to Africa where it's hot.
I'm going to do all of this with you.
Why are you crying?
I think Professor Hwang has been abducted.
Will he be all right?
What Lee Hyeong Du wants is Lee Seok Du.
He won't act recklessly until he finds out...
where Lee Seok Du is.
That person is coming on a flight early tomorrow morning, right?
Yes. The only hope who can help us find Professor Hwang...
is Lee Seok Du.
We need that person in order to protect Lee Seok Du.
By the way, Ms. Na asked me...
where Lee Seok Du is.
- Ha Young asked you? - Yes.
So?
Did you tell her?
If they defrosted him,
that means they're prepared to bring him back alive.
No way.
Could they have contacted Jung Woo?
There's no time.
Ma Dong Chan is scheming something.
Dong Chan?
Find out what he's trying to do.
Are you ordering me right now?
If we weigh the things we want,
which way do you think the scale will lean?
Did you...
forget who I am?
I can unveil a truth that's covered,
or cover up a truth that should be exposed.
On top of that, I know a fact...
that the world will turn their attention to if it airs on the news.
Could there be someone scarier to you?
But you have a weakness.
Ma Dong Chan.
I have Professor Hwang with me.
Without him, Dong Chan will die.
Then,
your other offer will be chucked out the window.
Are you Lee Jung Woo?
How is Father doing?
He's barely hanging on. We have to hurry.
- Yes. - I'm driving right behind you.
Okay.
You haven't found Professor Hwang yet, right?
We've been tracing Lee Hyeong Du,
but we have yet to find Professor Hwang's whereabouts.
By the way, our boys told me...
Lee Hyeong Du met with Ms. Na last night.
Hyeong Du met with Ha Young?
Wait.
They're tailing me as we expected. Let's get started.
Okay.
Hold tight.
Father?
He's ready for the transfusion.
He would've been in grave danger if you hadn't come right on time.
(Certified Medical Institution by the Ministry of Health and Welfare)
Hello?
Hey, how do you feel?
Okay, don't come to work today. You should rest at home.
Okay, bye.
You can't come in here.
But...
Lee Hyeong Du.
You must feel frustrated.
You need to settle a deal with me,
but you also can't admit that you took Professor Hwang.
Then how about I make an offer?
How about you give me Professor Hwang,
and I give you Lee Seok Du in return?
I need Professor Hwang, and you need Lee Seok Du.
How does that sound? Doesn't it sound intriguing?
Think about it carefully.
Professor Jo.
Is he recovering properly?
Okay, thank you.
And as for Professor Hwang,
he won't be able to hurt him. You don't need to worry too much.
Okay, bye.
- What do you want? - Why aren't you here yet?
"Go Go 99" is going to air soon.
You need to be here for the final editing process.
- I'm busy. - Are you kidding me?
You're busy with something else other than work.
How can you proudly tell the chief that you're busy?
I'm saying I'm busy because I am.
When are you going to come to work?
I'm on my way.
Take a look at what's written here and organize the information.
- Okay. - Ask me if you have any questions.
- Okay? - Okay.
Is there anything else you'd like to ask?
I'll give it a try first.
I'll try organizing everything.
Mi Ran, we didn't get to eat dinner last time.
So how about we eat dinner today?
Ji Hoon, I'm sorry. Can we eat together next time?
It's because you seem really down these days.
I'll brighten up your mood.
My gosh, you're so kind.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Get back to work.
Hey, Intern.
Didn't I tell you not to socialize with another intern?
You'll learn nothing from her.
And I told you not to be so kind...
to the other female employees.
Mi Ran and I were friends before I even started working here.
Please don't get the wrong idea.
You're friends? Who says you can be friends?
The thing is, he's my friend's son.
He's your friend's son?
Then why are you treating her like she's your friend?
You should be treating her with more respect.
Plus, I'm not friends with any of my mom's friends.
She's not exactly young enough to be your friend.
And tell me something, Intern.
How exactly are you going to brighten up her mood?
I'm sorry, but I don't really get why you're so upset right now.
Do you think I'm joking around?
Who ever said you were joking around?
I told you to stay at home.
What's wrong?
I'm okay.
Don't lie to me. Let me see.
No, it's okay. I'm fine.
I'm really okay.
Dong Chan.
Yes, what's up?
Well...
Were you guys talking about work?
Yes, that's exactly what we were doing.
- But your hands... - No, we were talking about work.
Oh, okay. Go ahead.
My gosh, he startled me.
You don't think he saw us, right?
- We were really fast. - He couldn't have seen us.
Why are you so busy these days?
I finally tracked down the IP address.
What IP address?
The person who wrote that post about Ko Mi Ran.
It took me a lot of effort to track it down.
You're the one who wanted me to track it down.
You told me you'll think it was me if I don't find who it was.
Oh, right. Good work.
- That's it? - Is Ha Young in her office?
Dong Chan, I'm not her secretary.
Is President Kim in his office?
Dong Chan!
You should go see him. He's been looking for you all morning.
Okay.
You came to work really late today.
What were you busy doing all morning?
Why do you want to know?
Dong Chan.
But then again, I also want to know...
what you did that night.
What? "That night"?
My goodness. Don't worry, sir.
Dong Chan is a variety show director.
There's nothing much he can do.
Chairman Lee is very bothered by him.
Why don't you create a project where he has to work abroad...
and send him overseas?
He won't go just because I tell him to go.
And he won't come just because I tell him to come.
He's here.
I'll call you back.
Okay, bye.
Were you talking about me?
You look really startled.
My gosh, what are you talking about?
What brings you here?
I don't have much time.
I need to differentiate my enemies from my allies.
So let me be straightforward and ask you something.
President Kim.
Do you know who Lee Hyeong Du is?
"Lee Hyeong Du"?
No, I don't.
Okay, then.
Do you know that Lee Seok Du and Lee Hyeong Du are twins...
and that Lee Hyeong Du is just an imposter...
who's pretending to be Lee Seok Du?
What? What did you just say?
Do you also know that the real Lee Seok Du was in a frozen capsule?
Are you telling me...
that there were other people there other than you and Mi Ran?
But Lee Hyeong Du is the person who's helping you...
become a politician, isn't he?
Hey, I really have no idea what you're...
It'd be best for you to find another sponsor.
That sponsor of yours is completely rotten and useless.
President Kim, that guy took...
Professor Hwang.
Do you really not know anything?
I really don't get what you're talking about.
What do you mean they're twins?
And who in the world is Lee Hyeong Du?
Where did he go?
Why do you want to know?
But then again, I also want to know...
what you did that night.
("Go Go 99" Credits)
Are you making the closing credits?
I have the cast list.
Oh, I see. I'll take that.
You don't look so well.
No, I'm okay.
I'm sorry, Mi Ran.
You must've been through a lot.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about my dad.
You don't need to apologize on behalf of him.
Please think of me separately from my dad.
Don't worry.
Hello?
Hey, Young Sun.
Are you sick? You don't look so well.
No, I'm okay.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Mi Ran.
You can't date Ji Hoon.
- Young Sun. - Guys in their 20s...
are all full of passion.
If they like someone,
they don't care about the woman's age.
They're very naive and passionate at that age.
And if a kid like him starts showing that he likes you,
we should try to talk him out of it since we're adults.
That's what we should do as people who are older than him.
Young Sun.
Your son's 20 years old, and you think of him like a kid.
Meanwhile, I've lived for 24 years, and you think of me like an adult.
You're right.
You didn't live as much as I did.
You have changed...
so much.
You used to have trouble differentiating words.
But now, you're so thoughtful.
You're a grown-up now.
You know what?
I'm in love.
Are you dating?
Yes.
(Here is the IP address of the ID you've requested.)
All right. So the person who wrote that online...
was at this cafe?
Okay. I got it.
This is it.
But how do I catch them?
So that's what happened.
Is it important or not?
It is.
Mi Ran, what brings you here?
I came to meet my friend during my lunchtime.
- This is her cafe. - Hello.
(Ko Mi Ran)
(Editing Room A)
How about we do this? Follow me.
- Where are we going? - Just follow me.
Where are we going?
Let's go.
You need to tell me where.
Are they...
"M, 3, 4".
I thought Mi Ran was going to come after work, but you're here early.
What? Were you going to come here?
Yes.
By the way, he has the same thing.
It's progressing around the same time.
Sir, no matter what happens,
do save him.
Cure him first. We have no time.
This is a temporary antidote.
The symptom will manifest itself once again in 48 hours.
Dong Chan.
Are you feeling unwell?
Why did you meet Lee Hyeong Du?
Why do you want to know where Lee Seok Du is?
Why haven't you covered this case yet?
Don't do anything shameful.
Stop here.
You need to know how it feels.
To have aged...
but for the person you love to still be shining brightly.
To be rejected by that person for being old and worn out.
To have aged...
but still be passionately in love with that person.
You need to feel the pain.
You must.
- Please leave. - I need to find Professor Hwang.
I'm running out of time.
Please help me.
- By the way... - I think...
I was told something that I shouldn't have known.
And it's something so intense.
Me too.
What do you know?
You go first.
It's nothing you should know.
(Bureau Chief, Na Ha Young)
I need to find Professor Hwang.
I'm running out of time. Please help me.
It's me. If you want to find Lee Seok Du,
send Professor Hwang back to them right now.
Did Dong Chan tell you to do this?
I'm going to report the disappearance of Professor Hwang.
I'm going to do an exclusive and report all the facts...
regarding that case.
But if you let him go,
I won't do it.
(Lee Seok Du)
Put Ko Mi Ran back into the cryonic capsule.
That's our deal.
You...
What are you planning to do?
You were blinded by love and acted too rashly.
I'm considering releasing this to the press right now.
You need to know how it feels.
To have aged...
but for the person you love to still be shining brightly.
To be rejected by that person for being old and worn out.
To have aged...
but still be passionately in love with that person.
You need to feel the pain.
You must.
I've attached a photo of him and checked the time.
All right, good work. I'll wrap it up.
- Are you in here? - Yes, I am.
What were you watching in here?
Well... I was just...
What is it?
The person who wrote the post about Mi Ran...
turned out to be her friend who runs a cafe.
- Really? - Yes.
Okay, I got it. You can go.
Is that all?
Yes.
Is it because you're afraid your girlfriend...
will get hurt?
I got a strange vibe,
but I didn't know you two would date.
Right.
Don't tell Mi Ran about her friend...
who wrote that post.
Not to your girlfriend either.
What are you talking about?
The three of them are friends.
You know, Mi Ran's friend...
you were seeing in secret on the set of "Go Go 99".
Your girlfriend.
I know everything.
What do I do? What?
Gosh, you must have been stressed out lately.
Darling.
Yes, honey?
Dong Chan found out about us.
How did he find out?
Do you know what's more shocking?
- What? - Dong Chan and Mi Ran...
are dating.
If they have a baby,
it'd be an ice baby.
Should we relocate?
- There are too many eyes on us. - Right.
What is it? Are you embarrassed by me?
It's not that, darling.
Right. I have one more thing to tell you.
The one that wrote the post about Mi Ran's identity...
is your friend who runs a cafe.
You should know what kind of person your friend is.
What? Young Sun?
- Yes. - That's impossible.
One second.
(Young Sun)
Hello?
Yes. It's me.
I know. You're a witch.
You shouldn't live like that.
I understand why you don't like Mi Ran,
but how could you do that to a friend?
You better not call me for a while, witch.
What?
Gosh.
- Honey. - Yes?
How about a nice bowl of warm fish cake soup?
We could have shots of soju to go along with it.
Shall we?
Do you know a good place?
- I know many. - Let's go.
What was that about? Gosh.
I'll get going, ma'am.
Okay.
I thought you wanted to work here so you could work at the station.
Did you give up on finding a job there?
Yes. I don't want to work at the station anymore.
The people there are mean and unfair.
Thank you for everything, ma'am.
Sure. It was nice having you.
- Chae Yeon. - Yes?
You should log out from your account.
It's okay. That's not my ID anyway.
Put Ko Mi Ran back into the cryonic capsule.
That's our deal.
You were blinded by love and acted too rashly.
I'm considering releasing this to the press right now.
Look for Professor Jo.
He knows...
where Lee Seok Du is.
I need to find Professor Hwang.
I'm running out of time.
Please help me.
(Na Ha Young)
Hello?
It's me.
Why did you call me? What are you trying to find out?
Professor Jo is in danger.
I called to tell you that.
Ever since his car explosion incident,
the police have been with him at the lab.
That's why Lee Hyeong Du couldn't do anything to him.
Lee Hyeong Du knows the police aren't at the lab anymore.
You should warn Professor Jo.
How did he know that?
Because I...
Because I told him.
It's me.
Yes?
Can you go to Professor Jo's lab now?
You need to hurry.
You, guard at the front of the lab.
The rest of you can standby outside.
Yes, sir.
(Cold-hearted Punk)
Don't go anywhere...
and stick right beside Professor Jo.
We don't know what kind of symptoms might show.
"Maito Magick"?
What is this?
You have my trust.
M, 3, 4.
M,
3, 4.
Maito Magick number 34.
I've moved out of Mi Ran's house.
I'll stay here until I find a new place.
No. Get out.
Dad.
Hwang Byung Sim, Hwang Ji Hoon.
You two must really be father and son.
You have the same taste in women.
I'm so embarrassed...
to see people.
I gave up on Mi Ran.
The reason is,
more than being Mi Ran's first love,
I believe it's more valuable to be your father.
I compared it on a balance sheet, and that's what I got.
Thank you, Dad.
Can I start dating Mi Ran now?
- What? - She's my type.
You punk.
If your father steps back in such a cool way,
you should say something really cool too.
What do you mean, you'll date her? What are you saying?
You didn't step back. You were pushed back.
No. Mi Ran is my friend.
What's wrong with that?
It's better than dating the mom of a friend.
Gosh.
Is it because you're interning at the Variety Department?
Are you making a joke? How is that any better?
How is it any different? A friend's mom versus Mom's friend?
That's not what I mean.
Both of you, shut your mouths!
I won't allow it.
Gosh. It's Dong Chan's fault.
I'm sure he ruined you.
Mi Ran has a boyfriend.
You two should go home.
I'll finish this even if I have to stay up all night.
I'll be in touch, Mr. Ma.
Okay.
Sweet dreams.
You too, honey.
"Honey"...
I'll pick you up tomorrow morning.
I'll go with Dad tomorrow.
Why?
He wants to do it.
All right.
You should hurry home.
After we resolve things one by one,
we'll be able to live just like ordinary people.
After we take the reagent and find Professor Hwang again,
we just need to get the treatment to get our body temperatures normal.
You're right.
See you, then.
But this antidote hasn't gone through a clinical trial.
So one person needs to get the injection first.
I'll get the injection first.
If I turn out to be fine,
you can give it to him.
Hey, Professor Jo. I'll be on my way soon.
Is Mi Ran there already?
Yes, she's here. But the thing is,
Mi Ran already got the injection.
What?
It's been two hours since she got the injection.
I think the antidote works.
Why did you get the injection first?
Because I wanted to get the antidote before you.
Why do you always do everything first?
This reminds me of the day I first met you guys 20 years ago.
For 20 years,
you guys were frozen and asleep.
But on the other hand, I've seen you guys for 20 years.
I guess that's why I'm not surprised to see that you're dating.
I guess we were meant to be.
We were destined to be with each other.
You both need to keep this in mind.
This is just an antidote.
It's not a cure that will bring your body temperature back to normal.
You both need to keep maintaining a body temperature of 31.5?.
Let me see.
Today, the pilot episode of "Go Go 99" is finally going to air.
It's truly a historical moment.
It was planned by Ko Mi Ran...
and directed by Director Ma Dong Chan.
But where is Director Ma?
I saw him working in the editing room earlier.
He's been in there for days.
I can't believe he isn't done yet.
My gosh, he really lost it. It's because he's old.
And one more thing.
If you're dating a colleague, please be extra careful.
People are bound to make fun of you.
And every couple ended up getting caught.
It's all done.
Mi Ran.
Are you dating Director Ma?
- Yes. - I'll wait for you.
I'm still very young.
- Don't be such a kid. - Stop drawing a line.
We're only four years apart.
The pilot episode of "Go Go 99" is going to begin soon, right?
- Yes, should we watch it here? - No.
Let's watch it with the employees in the lobby.
Okay.
Did you watch the roughly edited version?
Yes, it's fun.
Dong Chan really is the best. The show's bound to do well.
He's so focused on the details.
He's been editing in the editing room for days now.
Hyun Gi, do you hear that? I hear the ratings going up.
Listen to that.
What's taking him so long?
We're going to air the advertisements soon.
Hello?
I'm sorry for being late. I just sent you the file.
I thought there was a problem.
He sent the file. Standby.
("Go Go 99")
Okay, everyone.
- I'm so nervous. - We're finally watching the show.
("Go Go 99")
Let's go!
I love the introduction.
I'm Dong Sik.
- I am ground, introduce yourself. - I am ground, introduce yourself.
During my childhood
I once had a beautiful dream
- For youth! - For youth!
(Let's Go Back to 1999! "Go Go 99")
- What's going on? - What's this?
- Something's wrong. - What's the matter?
What's going on?
Please save my husband. The cryonic capsule...
What happened to her...
on that night of 2019?
(What happened to her on that night of 2019?)
- Shouldn't we stop this? - No, let's leave it.
On that night of 1999,
we were waiting to be thawed after having participated...
in the experiment for 24 hours.
But what in the world happened to us that night?
The two incidents may seem totally irrelevant from each other.
He's...
But this guy was behind both incidents.
He's Lee Hyeong Du,
the younger brother of Unsung Group's chairman, Lee Seok Du.
What the...
My goodness.
Is that really true?
I am...
the real Lee Seok Du.