(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
Knock, knock.
Are you scared of thunder?
Yes.
It's not something to be scared of.
The sky is just showing off that it's giving us rain.
When Mom died, there was a thunderstorm.
And even on the day we put her ashes at the charnel house.
Come here.
- Do you miss your mom? - Yes.
What did she tell you to do...
- whenever you missed her? - Pray.
She's your guardian angel,
so when you're scared or in pain...
I should pray.
- Shall we pray together then? - Yes.
Angel of the Lord
My guardian dear
To whom his love
Commits me here
Ever this day
Be at my side
(Year 2000, 41st International Mathematical Olympiad)
Before we begin the test,
let me do a roll check, okay?
Do we have Chinai from Israel?
Here.
Simon Parker from the US?
- Here. - Okay.
Thomas Jaeger from Germany?
The J is pronounced like the letter Y.
Okay, sorry.
Thomas Jaeger from Germany? Okay.
Next is...
So Mi Kim from Korea?
So Mi Kim?
Angel of the Lord, my guardian dear
To whom his love commits me here
Ever this day be at my side
To light and guard
To rule and guide
Amen.
Dad!
Dad?
Mom, I won a gold medal today.
Angel of the Lord
My guardian dear
To whom his love commits me here
Ever this day be at my side
To light and guard
- To rule and guide - To rule and guide
How did you know to come here?
That's what I get for worrying?
These aren't blanks.
How did you know to come here?
Because your unit told me.
And you beat the dispatched officers here?
It's as if you were waiting for me.
You've got to be kidding me.
Be careful. The trigger's sensitive to touch.
The numbers next to Yeom Hwa Ran's body.
Digging into its meaning led me to a nearby sanatorium.
Dr. Nam Young Moon.
Kim So Mi from 20 years ago...
probably changed her name to Han Sun Mi.
You scanned my memories.
That's how you were able to reenact the murder.
Unbelievable.
Explain yourself.
Calm down for a second.
Memory scans don't work like vacuum cleaners.
I don't suddenly suck in all your memories.
When you grabbed me,
I was too busy reading Park Ki Dan to know what was happening.
Says you.
Okay, fine. I did see a faint scene.
Traumatized memories usually strike first.
All I saw was a drawing in black.
I guessed it was a vase. That's how clueless I was.
- So? - But while scanning Dr. Nam,
I saw So Mi coloring the same drawing.
She saw the killer through the keyhole of her closet.
That's when I knew...
that you were her.
Your logic is all over the place.
Well, I'm known for my hunches.
The killer is playing a sick game...
and he's using my memories.
Who else could do that?
You're right. He's challenging us by messing with us all.
But it isn't just you he's toying with.
He also insulted...
my past too.
What past?
The killer's after us both.
Tell me about this past of yours. If not,
I'll shoot.
This is the hammer painting delivered to Park Ki Dan.
What about it?
I don't know if you heard,
but I don't remember anything from my childhood.
Get to the point.
But there's one thing I remember.
A woman.
A woman dying.
That's what I saw in the painting.
How the victim was laid, crushed beneath an angel.
The face.
Even the sad expression.
She was probably my mother.
The killer mocked the only childhood memory I had.
And now,
we have a common enemy.
- It's locked. - That way.
Captain.
Go ahead.
Me?
Move it.
- It's locked. - Step aside.
Captain.
Why didn't you let us in?
Get out. We have to preserve the crime scene.
Are they bodies?
Are they people?
It's a work of art created by the killer.
Work of art?
Seeing there are numerous scratches, they attacked each other.
Each other? Why?
The killer probably made them do it,
saying he'll let them live if they killed the other.
(Memorist)
(Episode 6: The Second Man)
(Gyeonggi Metropolitan Police Agency 2006)
You say you're Kim So Mi?
From six years ago?
(Kim Young Kook's Murder Crime Analysis)
- What is this? - A profiling report.
- A profiling report? - I analyzed the killer.
- What? - I'm qualified.
I studied criminal psychology in the US.
- How old are you? - My Korean age is 17.
("Spy Family of Seob Island" Cleared of Charges 14 Years After Execution)
So? Who's the killer?
He has a scar by his left ear.
You said that a long time ago too.
Check according to the profile.
You'll find someone with a scar. I'm positive.
Why must we keep it a secret?
I'm sure he's nearby.
The killer...
may have killed both of our parents.
- Obviously... - But what if...
he only came across our past?
- Someone else? - He's probably close.
With high probability.
Someone close? Like a cop?
I like how cautious you are,
but it's the killer from 20 years ago.
Someone could have put together your past from the files,
but not mine.
Because no one knows.
No one?
I said it only once,
but it remained a secret between us two until the end.
Who?
If you don't tell me, the number of scenarios won't change.
By the way...
do you always look at every scenario when you investigate?
Do your instincts not play a role at all with that smart brain of yours?
It's self-centered to follow instincts.
You leave important decisions to luck.
It's what blockheads like you enjoy.
Didn't that blockhead save your life?
- What... - Han Man Pyeong.
- Oh, that? - "Oh, that"?
I would've taken care of him even without your help.
And here I was, a little grateful that you removed me as a suspect.
Who removed you?
- Didn't you? - Definitely not.
You're still a usual suspect.
Then what? Are you saying you want to work...
with a prime suspect?
"Keep your friends close, and your enemies closer."
Words I swear by.
Remember this.
You must keep all of this a secret...
between us.
What are you doing? Is this your first time in a woman's apartment?
What do you mean?
I go to women's homes...
all the time.
Come in here.
What is all of this?
My case.
I've been updating it for 20 years.
(Safety and Happiness, Gyeonggi Metropolitan Police Agency)
Do you know how much I blew?
You said to buy. You said it was a sure thing.
That means to buy.
You're a piece of work.
You think the deputy chief of Violent Crimes...
only goes after murderers,
don't you?
Fine. Okay. You'll see first-hand how I deal...
with jerks like you who commit securities fraud.
If you don't return my money, you won't get your life back either.
Leave already.
What about the investigation?
Shouldn't you be in school?
I got into Seoul University's Grad School for Public Administration.
Good for you.
Did you check the suspects?
Enough!
Do you know how many cases I have?
I have piles of perps to catch!
Stop making excuses! What is more important than murder?
Why you little...
Just put one officer on it, and I'll...
Get out.
I'll do it myself.
I'll find the killer and bring him here myself!
Why that... That brat.
Why do you think our parents' killer came back?
Jumping to conclusions is what happens when you follow instincts.
What I'm focusing on is the killer's motive.
What motive?
Serial killing is very risky.
But he used the corpses to bait us,
taunting us with our pasts.
What could it be?
What is he trying to gain using murder and taunting?
Is he bragging about the perfect murder from 20 years ago?
It's not cost-effective.
Hold on. Your starting position is wrong.
You can't expect logic from a lunatic.
We'll never catch him with an attitude like that.
We have to accept the fact that he's way above us,
so we can stay under him and find his weakness.
Profilers are always like that.
They use too much of their imagination...
and lead the case to the wrong direction.
He brought back the murder he committed 20 years ago.
So we should play along and try to find his weakness...
Make sure you don't come out on camera.
Ms. Han, we've identified the victims.
They're both 20-year-old women.
Do you know the juvenile double jeopardy case?
The juvenile double jeopardy case?
- Those witches... - Well,
six years ago, a little girl who was an orphan died.
And the culprits turned out to be middle school girls.
They were doing volunteer work at the orphanage for school,
and that's when they killed her.
One of them had a crush on this guy, and he was nice to her.
That's why they killed her.
The problem occurred after they got arrested.
They were both 13 years old.
They were underage, so they didn't get punished at all.
Those scums.
But something was revealed after five years.
A screen capture of their text got leaked.
They were mocking the girl who died.
"It felt so great when she died"? My gosh.
The public wanted another trial.
But that wasn't possible because of the double jeopardy clause.
And in the end, they hired a lawyer...
and sued the people who badmouthed them online.
That's completely...
Who's next to you?
How did the autopsy come out?
Are you with a guy? At this hour?
You were right. They seem to have attacked each other.
That was a guy's voice.
Keep me updated.
Okay, I got it.
- It's a guy, right? - What if it is?
It's dangerous. What if he tries to do something?
Why wouldn't he when they're all alone?
- It'd be worse if he didn't. - What?
Ms. Han isn't like that.
Will you wake up already? She won't be teaching anymore.
How long are you going to keep liking her?
I don't like her. I respect her.
Is that so?
Winter break is almost over, so get ready to go back to school.
Don't bother getting your hopes up.
I'm sure it was a guy.
I bet it was a celebrity.
You mean it came from the TV? It must've been the TV.
No, I mean an actual celebrity.
Ms. Han is pretty enough...
to have celebrities lining up to date her.
He had a nice voice, right?
It was really sexy.
I bet he's handsome.
Punishing evil by becoming evil themselves.
This guy is a psycho.
It's not the first time.
This also happened 20 years ago.
An execution-style murder.
Execution?
- Where is Reporter Jo Sung Dong? - Over there.
(Reporter Jo Sung Dong, Taebook News)
- What do you want? - Can...
Can you check a few things for me?
It'll help me identify the culprit.
I'm a reporter, not a detective.
I know.
You wrote about my dad's case.
Mr. Jo, there are other victims other than my dad.
- The murders you wrote about... - Hey!
You should go see a counselor.
Stop imagining things, and go see a psychiatrist.
All these murders lead to the same culprit.
Bother me again and see what happens.
Why don't you just help her out?
Why would I help her? She doesn't even know anything.
She's just a kid.
Don't you know who her dad was?
She should be embarrassed of herself.
She'll hear you.
I want her to hear me.
If she knew what her dad did, she wouldn't be able to do this.
What? The culprit is whom?
(Personal Details Report)
(Name: Jo Sung Dong)
This is absurd. This guy is a famous reporter.
There are five more murders that are very similar.
They were all people who were condemned.
"The amputee murder at South Jeolla Province."
Look at this.
The composite is different.
It was a middle-aged lady.
The only common thing is that the culprit didn't get caught.
My gosh, you know nothing.
There is something in common.
The scoop went to the same person.
Jo Sung Dong?
What about that?
He's a reporter, so that's his job.
He was always the quickest reporter to get there.
He's a famous reporter. He probably has connections...
No, he was a lot faster.
Dad.
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
He definitely got there very fast.
He got there quicker than the cops.
Are you okay? Hurry!
I was too young to catch him back then.
You're still young.
He couldn't have gotten there so quickly if he wasn't the culprit.
My gosh, it's like I'm getting fooled by a kid.
That's why you should've referred to my profiling.
You were suspicious of him from the start?
I checked.
Checked what?
He asked me to drink with him and even wanted to go for karaoke.
- I had to run away from him. - He's always like that.
- He has a problem. - It's really exhausting.
It wouldn't be as bad if he didn't get so drunk.
The Executioner.
Who came up with this name?
I did.
You came up with a pretty good title.
He executes people who deserve to...
Well, apart from your dad.
You're right. All the victims were condemned.
The first murder occurred in 1999 at a mountain trail.
"Jamae Welfare Center"?
They kidnapped and killed people to receive a support fund.
They were like the devil.
1999? Isn't that after they were found guilty?
They didn't get punished.
They got released in two years.
They killed hundreds of people and only went to jail for two years?
It was during the military regime.
I can't believe they didn't hang people like that.
The body was severely harmed.
Why would he harm the corpse?
No, the person was still alive.
I didn't bind these cases together because of the motive.
It had to do with how they were murdered.
"How"?
They were punished while they were alive.
They were tortured for a long time until they finally died.
The statute of limitations had expired,
so he didn't go to jail.
But instead, he was amputated while he was still alive.
Exactly 13 times which was the number of victims.
How meticulous.
The same happened to the others.
They were brutally tortured until they died.
Why didn't they think of this as a serial murder?
Because the suspects all looked different.
There were witnesses?
3 out of the 6 murders.
That witness saw an old man.
In South Jeolla Province, a woman in her 50s was caught on camera.
And the third witness?
That was me.
May I ask how your father died?
He was stabbed 17 times...
in non-lethal areas.
17 times?
The number of deaths...
he was directly or indirectly responsible for.
So what was the conclusion...
of your chase of 20 years?
Satisfied? You can go now.
No, I'll stay.
Unbelievable. This isn't some fun game, you know.
I can tell if he's lying. I mastered psychology too.
Wait for me out there. It'll soon be over anyway.
People like him crumble once you start hurting their pride.
You're a cheeky one, aren't you?
I was thoroughly entertained.
I only have myself to blame.
- What happened? - Isn't it obvious?
I humiliated myself by believing a kid.
- Why? - He has an alibi.
When your father was murdered, he was with other people.
It doesn't matter.
An accomplice could've helped him get a story.
Who on earth would kill for an exclusive in the news?
- I know you're a kid, but... - That's why he's a killer!
At least check for an accomplice.
I already did.
I checked his call logs and traced his whereabouts.
All you did was make me work on a useless case.
It doesn't make sense.
What about the scar near his ear?
It's from when he served in the military.
- That's a lie. - I checked his medical records!
And then what happened?
You're not the type of person who would've let this go.
I believed that there was a trick,
but nothing panned out.
I followed every lead...
only to hit dead-ends.
What if that trick was a telepathic ability?
What if Jo Sung Dong or whoever it is...
can manipulate other people's memories?
Just like those of the witnesses at the prayer house.
- Sleeping gas was used. - That sounds more of a trick to me.
Even the guards outside had their memories erased.
But what if this wasn't a crime committed...
by someone with superpowers?
Then it's someone who knows everything.
Someone who has vast knowledge.
It could be...
a member of the police force.
Why did the Executioner...
disappear 20 years ago?
Why did he stop killing?
Well, he's back now.
Is he?
I thought you told me not to be biased.
My ideas are based on the facts...
while yours are based on your hunches.
Isn't this near Yeom Hwa Ran's vacation home?
This is a recent footage.
Perps circle back to the scene of their crimes.
It's why I've been filming these.
Would he have come by?
No.
There weren't many spectators anyway.
- Then what? - An uninvited guest.
An uninvited guest?
The broadcast van.
The broadcast van drove up before the police line went up.
The pattern is repeating.
The pattern from 20 years ago.
(Honest and impartial, TVC)
I don't quite follow.
I want to know how your broadcast van...
was at the scene.
We never violate an embargo order.
The van was only there just in case.
Are you really this awful at your job...
or just pretending to be?
What? You...
The media is supposed to deliver news to the people.
How did you know...
that there was a case?
There's nothing weird about reporters sniffing stories.
It is if you arrived before the police.
And if it happened on multiple occasions.
You were there before the police arrived.
Who tipped you off?
An anonymous source.
Even if we knew who it was,
we have an obligation to protect our source.
An anonymous source?
Didn't it occur to you...
that this anonymous source could be the killer?
We were cross-checking facts.
The tip could've been a hoax, so...
And yet you rolled out a broadcast van to the scene?
What do you want?
- Tell me who your source is. - We have an obligation...
to protect our sources.
I bet it came from the inside.
Someone from above.
Someone of high status.
The boss?
Only the police officers have been asked to enter.
- What about me? - You are to wait out here too.
His lawyer should be present though.
No, he will only talk to the officers.
I was thoroughly entertained.
Goodness, it's so nice to meet you.
As a fan, I've made numerous requests, you know.
I've been suggesting we do a special featured series with you.
One of at least 20 episodes.
I'd love that too.
Shall we?
I'm too low on the totem pole to do anything freely.
That includes being on TV and even arresting bad guys.
It's Superintendent Han, right?
I'm Han Sun Mi.
I know you quite well.
Almost everyone wants you in charge of their office.
- Are you interested in politics? - I'm happy where I am.
Of course it's satisfying.
But those who are gifted should take the reins...
regardless of what their calling is.
I'm sure you're aware that Park Ki Dan died.
Yes, but the embargo hasn't been lifted.
This country loves embargoes too much.
When will they learn that...
a leading country begins with the transparency of information.
And that is the responsibility of the media.
So where did the information of the murder come from?
Sorry? I don't follow.
Let's be honest here.
Be a member of a leading nation and be transparent with information.
You can't just simply ask for trade secrets, you know.
Why don't I guess?
It's probably tips on murders received from a serial killer.
It wasn't the first time. The exclusives from 20 years ago...
were also thanks to your collusion with the killer.
Collusion.
Either that, or you sent an accomplice to commit the murders.
All for exclusive stories.
Your imagination is way too wild.
Spill it.
If you don't tell the truth, we'll arrest you for murder.
Even if I did receive information, why is that a problem?
It wasn't before the murders. We went afterward.
Are you kidding me?
If you had reported the serial murder,
we would've reduced the number of victims 20 years ago.
The police knew already.
You must be threatening me with the past to get something from me,
but you came to the wrong guy.
You people are the ones who will get hurt if it gets out, not me.
Did you say the police knew?
Are you assuming that the cops back then were all idiots?
They knew.
- That's nonsense. - They buried it.
What cop would admit there is a serial killer on the loose...
that they couldn't catch?
It would kill their career.
Then and now, the cops are the same.
You shouldn't talk. You colluded with a killer for exclusives!
Who colluded with a killer? I did not.
The killer wanted the world to know...
that people who deserved to die were dying at his hands.
But I didn't do it.
Sure,
it would've been a bigger exclusive if I had uncovered a serial murder.
But I had the conviction of a journalist,
in contrast to you people who buried it...
out of fear of missing a promotion.
The conviction of a journalist?
No. You were waiting for the right time to say it was a serial killer.
But it fell through because the police figured it out.
It must be nice being a cop.
You can say any garbage you want.
That's an exclusive right held by journos like you.
They're leaving.
Tell me who the informant is.
How dare you ask for information on a source?
If you're so curious, dig through the records.
They were much smarter than you people now.
I always wondered...
whether the media was garbage because of society,
or if society is what it is because of the media.
Thanks for enlightening me.
(Documents)
- Hey. - There's nothing...
on Kim So Mi's case from year 2000.
I don't need the content. Who was the detective on point?
(Old man)
The deputy chief of Metropolitan Investigation at Gyeonggi...
at the time was Chun Ki Soo. I know him.
He's a section chief at HQ now. Why?
It's not him.
Get me the names of everyone who was on that case.
Why?
- Just do it! - I'm your supervisor, you punk.
I have a higher rank than you.
But you order this old man around without explaining anything.
There you go again. Is this a lover's quarrel?
I need to ask the lead detective something, that's why.
It went to Special Investigations afterward. Do you want that too?
- Special Investigations? - That's right.
They reinvestigated that case and a few other cold cases.
Really?
I called Chun Ki Soo...
because the file was so empty,
and he blamed Special Investigations.
He said they handed everything over so he knew nothing.
What about Special Investigations' files?
There's nothing left.
They dissolved the unit...
and sent them all back to where they were before.
They say what they gathered for this archive is everything.
They were either sloppy from the get-go,
or they lost the entire box.
It was a long time ago.
There are no records from Special Investigations?
There's only one batch of documents.
The lead detective was...
What?
It was Deputy Chief Lee.
Lee Shin Woong?
That's right. The National Police Agency's second in command.
(Special Investigations Unit for Cold Cases)
(Lead Detective Lee Shin Woong)
(Deputy Chief Lee Shin Woong)
Captain? You borrowed money from Baek, didn't you?
Either that, or he read your memory and knows...
your deep dark secrets.
What are you babbling about?
It's suspicious how you serve him.
I don't serve him.
"Old man, go get the file for a cold case."
And you run right over like a dog chasing a ball.
That's what a true leader does.
Like Admiral Yi Sun Sin.
I doubt Admiral Yi Sun Sin would've run copy errands.
If they had copiers back then,
he would've done hundreds.
That must be it.
What?
What is it?
"I've made the copies, my lord."
Shut it before I kick you out.
(Special Investigations Unit for Cold Cases)
Do you think Deputy Chief Lee...
is the man you described?
Someone with vast information.
It's very possible.
What if they buried it because they failed to figure it out?
That's also possible...
since the investigation was up against a brick wall...
and the murders stopped.
Then let's go after him first.
- How? - Either attack head-on...
or tail him.
He uses the Intelligence Bureau like his personal agency.
The Intelligence Bureau?
The NPA's Intelligence Bureau has a wider reach than the NIS.
At least domestically.
We'll be caught before we can catch him.
What are our other options?
We have to find a way.
We're back to square one, but we have a target now.
- Lee Shin Woong. - You're being too relaxed again.
The serial killer is out killing people.
When will we find a way, investigate him, and catch the killer?
Square one.
We had forgotten square one.
The first moment they began hunting the Executioner.
We have a witness.
Someone who clearly saw the Executioner.
As in...
That's right.
You.
My memory.
My memory is already recorded in the documents,
so there's no need to scan it.
Do you know why I didn't close my eyes when my dad was dying?
To remember.
To see every little detail of that horrendous sight...
and remember it clearly.
What happened to that indomitable spirit?
You reached out to shake my hand first.
Let's check and see...
if you missed anything.
Ma'am.
You're wary of investigations using telepathy, right?
You only trust logic and reason.
But you see,
intuition is needed sometimes.
When a person experiences something big,
it mostly happens by coincidence, not reason.
Just like how you witnessed that horrible incident.
What do I need to do?
Nothing.
The mask.
The silicon mask.
Prosthetic makeup.
He purposely made sure there were witnesses.
But he also made sure he looked different every time.
Let's check all the prosthetic makeup artists from back then.
That will take too long.
No, I'm sure we'll find someone.
Wait.
Why Jo Sung Dong?
Why did he only tip-off Jo Sung Dong?
As an executioner who needed to inform his murders,
it would've been better to contact different reporters.
But why...
Why?
Why did it have to be Jo Sung Dong?
Wait. Wait.
(Reporter Jo Sung Dong)
These scoops...
He wasn't alone.
It's him.
The cameraman...
who got there second.
Yes.
He worked with Jo Sung Dong for two years as his cameraman...
exactly during the serial murders.
Before that, he used to work in the prosthetic makeup team.
After he quit, he emigrated to China.
But he came back two months ago.
He's currently living at a place...
that's only 20 minutes away by foot from Yeom Hwa Ran's place.
(Memorist)
We will be carrying out a search and seizure...
at Jin Jae Gyu's house.
Three more people will die.
We need to keep our eyes on everyone.
Ms. Han, HR just called.
Why did you do that?
Are you close with Mr. Jo Sung Dong?
These are the people I touched. You can choose from there.
Thy will die once the moon rises.
It will be a gruesome death.
I found out Jin Jae Gyu's trick.