He escaped through a secret passage.
Jin Jae Gyu always lured us with a hint.
He always left a hint
next to the dead victims.
It wasn't Woo Seok Do either.
- You scumbag.
- He was also in contact with you.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Jo Sung Dong,
the leader of this nation's media.
Stop right there!
Move and this bullet goes in your skull.
Get a grip on yourself!
Get your act together!
Hold on.
Where am I?
Se Hoon.
I can't remember anything...
no matter how hard I try.
I feel like...
I saw someone.
The CCTV isn't working either.
He cut the wire before he came in.
Ms. Han, we dispatched our
men near the secret passage.
How many?
A total of six,
but we're going to send more.
Arrest him as soon as
he enters the passage.
We need to check the victim's bloodstain,
so confiscate his shoes and clothes.
"The victim"?
Jo Sung Dong got murdered.
Should I call an ambulance?
No, just forensics.
The most crucial part is gone.
It's as if he erased that
part of their memory.
This is outrageous.
He has the ability to
erase people's memories.
I should've noticed after what
happened with Park Ki Dan.
I can't believe this.
I can't remember what I saw.
He killed him with a fountain pen.
He punished him for the crimes
he committed through his articles.
He's done for.
(Memorist)
(Ep 7: The Red Herring)
Did you check where the motorcycle went?
No, not yet.
We even have the situation room helping us.
And the secret passage?
We have all our available
manpower waiting there.
Warn everyone...
that Jin Jae Gyu has the ability
to erase people's memories.
What? He can erase them?
Make sure no one makes
any physical contact.
- Okay.
- Attention, everyone.
The target has the ability
to erase people's memories.
I repeat. He has the
ability to erase memories.
Do not make any physical contact.
- He can erase memories.
- He really has supernatural powers?
Hello, sir.
There he is.
What?
He's leaving.
I found it.
Where is it?
It's 5km away from Jin Jae Gyu's house.
But it was 50 minutes ago.
50 minutes ago?
Which way did it go?
Jin Jae Gyu's place.
- What?
- Then it happened...
before the stakeout?
Sir, there's someone...
- in Jin Jae Gyu's garden.
- What?
There's too much of a time difference.
He erased the old man's memory
and disappeared 80 minutes ago.
So when we left from the secret passage...
That's when he came back
after murdering Jo Sung Dong.
We missed him by a second.
We should've stayed there.
Don't let him know that we found
out about the secret passage.
- He might use that against us.
- No.
Gosh.
I see the second victim
has already surfaced.
How did you get your accomplice to move?
- My accomplice?
- Ordering him to do the killing...
won't get you off the hook.
An accomplice?
Either that...
or you're the underling who
takes orders from the mastermind.
Like a crappy old clown who
only serves as a distraction.
I see you're angry...
like always.
I get why Detective Dong is...
since the people he
touched are the ones dying.
But why you though?
- Cut the crap.
- Nothing about this is unfair.
Everyone knows that
your father broke their trust.
What?
He betrayed his colleagues.
He represented 2,000 coworkers
who were wrongfully dismissed,
but he committed perjury on the stand...
that put the labor union at a disadvantage.
- Shut it.
- Thousands of fathers...
lost the trial and were kicked to the curb.
However,
your father received a big fat paycheck.
He was also offered a job
at a subsidiary company.
- Shut it!
- Families were crippled...
and they fell victim to
illnesses and depression.
And when his 17th victim took his own life,
your father was punished too...
by being stabbed 17 times.
How did you know that?
The number of stab
wounds were never disclosed.
Have you ever thought about this before?
Why do you think your father
betrayed his colleagues?
How did you know?
Because of you.
He had to provide for his genius daughter.
Good books, good schools,
his promise to his wife...
You know the drill.
Fathers go down the path of
evil for the sake of their families.
And how would you know
how my father would've felt?
- Unless you're the killer...
- Because I met him.
I met your father's ghost.
- What?
- Now you're talking madness.
The Executioner had the greatest time...
while killing your father.
You scumbag.
Jin Jae Gyu,
you're under arrest as the accomplice...
in the Jo Sung Dong murder case.
- You have the right to remain...
- What about the easier way?
A memory scan.
Read my head.
- Are you serious?
- Of course.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Because those who will die
have already been chosen.
Even the third victim.
Two are already dead...
which leaves only one.
The one you made physical contact with...
will die before the end of the month.
Sign this.
"I, Jin Jae Gyu,
agree to Detective Dong's memory scan."
"Whatever he sees will
be admissible in court."
(Jin Jae Gyu)
- Go away.
- Hyeon Su.
Why is he here?
No one was home,
so his teacher dropped him off...
Then you should've called me!
The kindergarten is to blame though.
I never said he could be dropped off here.
You should get going.
I won't be able to manage
the greenhouse anymore.
Come on.
My reputation has been dragged
through the mud thanks to you.
As if you even had one.
My Lord...
It's a curse.
Everyone you came in contact with will die.
Detective Dong!
Detective Dong.
Detective Dong, wake up!
Yes.
No, not yet.
Okay, will do.
I'm Kim. I'm a manager.
Why is someone from the NIS here?
Can you read memories without contact?
NIS agents are smart idiots.
People who only say their titles...
are either con artists or NIS
agents but only they don't know that.
Sorry for the late introduction.
I've been your handler for a while.
I never asked to be "handled".
It's the third time...
you lost consciousness.
Once, you can chalk it up to being hit,
but the other two times
were while reading memories.
So what? Are you going
to get me a physical?
That's right. They already
finished examining you.
They say there's nothing wrong
in particular, but it's a bad sign.
We've concluded that it'll get
worse if you keep scanning people.
Stay out of it.
I'll take care of my own body.
You're a national asset.
No. You people just want
to use me as a weapon.
You can't continue being a cop anyway.
You'll be found guilty.
If you're done, please leave.
We're not asking you to
quit the force and come to us.
We'll help you stay on the force.
The government can't control
a trial in this day and age.
We can't,
but we can change the public sentiment.
That's our specialty.
Even if you are found guilty,
we can make sure you're not fired.
In exchange for what?
You can just help us now and
then when you have spare time.
Helping with our research would be nice.
Or...
provide crucial assistance
when the nation is in trouble.
I'll just pay for my crime.
I won't be a coward.
Isn't catching perps your joy in life?
I don't want to see you again.
No NIS agent is sinless.
Stay away before I expose
your memories and humiliate you.
You don't need to get so angry.
You're awake.
I'll see you again. I wish
you a quick recovery.
- Who was that?
- A mole.
A mole? Why was a NIS agent here?
- Where are my clothes?
- You're not okay.
You were asleep for three days.
Three days? What about Jin Jae Gyu?
He was arrested and
interrogated for 48 hours,
but the warrant was denied,
so he was released again.
What?
His lawyer is none other than...
that scum of the earth, Im Joong Yeon.
He doesn't look it, but he must be loaded.
He must have spent millions of dollars.
I think Metro is setting a trap...
to arrest him once he escapes
through the secret tunnel.
They didn't search the tunnel yet?
They did.
But they didn't find Jo
Sung Dong's DNA there.
Do you think he'll use it
again? Because he's stupid?
They thought of that,
so they searched it carefully
while he was being detained.
In case they need it later.
Metro is desperate right now.
The last day of the month is 10 days away.
- Where's Superintendent Han?
- Who knows?
We haven't seen her since she
was cut from the special team.
I'm so sad because I
haven't seen her recently.
- She could be your daughter.
- Exactly! She's like a daughter!
That's why I worry about her.
Why must you make it sound so gross?
It's too dangerous.
Hey. Dr. Ahn and the medical
team are freaking out because of you.
They're trying to find the
cause for your fainting.
He's a telepathic killer.
He showed me only what he
wanted to when I scanned him.
He blocked my access.
What?
What? Doesn't that mean
you're no match for him?
You may end up dying too.
(Green Moving)
Maintain a safe distance.
Don't come in contact with him.
I knew it. I'm meant
to be out on the field.
(Bang-eum Station, Gongjin Intersection)
Hold on!
- Hold on! Stop!
- Excuse us.
There's only a parrot left on
him. Only a parrot, that's all.
Backup.
Back up the parrot!
On our way. Turn the car around.
He's heading north from the stop.
Keep the line open.
Backup is on its way, so don't be nervous.
He's in the elevator.
Confirming what floor.
Eighth floor. I'll go up now.
Okay. Eighth floor.
Sorry, but we're closed today.
- Excuse me?
- We're closed.
Sorry.
I lost him.
He's not in the gym on the eighth floor...
Aren't you getting in?
Parrot!
What's wrong with this?
She's in the elevator, so...
Parrot, respond. Parrot!
Are you going to the garage?
Excuse me?
Yes.
But... Where are you going?
It's under construction,
so there are no cars here.
Okay. Go to the third basement floor!
Yes, sir.
How much are these Jerusalem artichokes?
- This costs 10 dollars.
- Can I have half?
- Just take the whole thing.
- Can I get a discount?
Just take it. It won't rot easily.
- I just need a little bit.
- It won't be enough.
- I'll come back next time.
- My goodness.
It's Mr. Jin.
Gosh, this is already pretty cheap.
Then I'll take half.
Parrot.
Parrot, where are you? Parrot.
My gosh.
Hey, wake up! Wake up!
Where am I?
We need an ambulance
on the third basement floor.
Don't you remember anything?
You were following him.
I got off work and fell asleep.
- What?
- What about your gun?
Where's your gun?
Your gun.
- I normally don't do this.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Okay.
Take a look.
Go ahead and choose.
Hyeon Su.
Check the target's location.
I'm sorry,
sir. We're trying our best to find him.
- There he is.
- What?
Have you seen my son?
We were at the market,
and he told me he saw you.
- I should call the police.
- He's going to be punished.
He's going to get punished
for what your family has done.
- What do you mean?
- He will get punished...
for what your mother did.
- What are you talking about?
- Do you still not know...
who I am?
What are you talking about?
I raised you...
when you were young.
Where is the kid?
I guess your dirty hands
also touched the kid.
The kid is now qualified.
What?
He's qualified to be the third victim.
If anything happens to him, I'll kill you.
Why? You're the one who cursed him.
But he still has more to do.
It's going to happen tonight.
You should hurry.
Tonight,
the third victim will get murdered.
Come out here. Come out here, you jerk!
- Calm down.
- Get off me.
- Get off me!
- Stop.
Get a grip of yourself!
My goodness.
He's evil.
How long did you live with him again?
Up until I was nine.
That's when you were very young.
How can you be so confident?
When my grandma was alive,
she always told me...
that my mom didn't commit suicide.
She told me that she was murdered by him...
and that he'll end up killing us too.
Did you check her family?
Her mother, Shim Hyo Sook, died in 1992.
She was living with Jin Jae Gyu,
but she ran away with another guy...
- and committed suicide with him.
- They also found a written will.
I know he killed her for sure.
How do you know your
grandma told you the truth?
Because she saw everything in person.
It was right before my mom ran away.
I'm sure it was around then.
Every day, my mom went to town for work.
And he, my stepfather,
was the only person home.
I got a dog for my birthday.
And that day,
we had just brought him back from the vet.
Dad?
After that, my mom ran away from home.
I was more scared by the
fact that I was left with him...
rather than the fact that my mom was gone.
Because of what you saw in the forest?
I was always scared of him.
He was always so cold.
It got even worse after my mom disappeared.
He left the house for a few days.
And one day, I heard him come home at dawn.
And I realized that he found my mom.
He had taken the necklace from her.
But I only found out what
had really happened...
a while later.
Our condolences.
I made a run for it to
my grandma's that day.
Jae Gyu, I'm sorry.
Please don't kill me.
My mom was found
hanging next to the other man.
Don't kill me!
But I know the truth.
I know that she was murdered...
by him.
Your memory seems clear and vivid.
So why didn't you recognize him?
Even the house is the same.
I was only nine, remember?
It is natural to forget certain events.
But then some memories are too vivid.
How did you come to
live in this neighborhood?
It's where my husband lived.
What a strange coincidence.
Which flight did your husband get on today?
The one at noon. I was on
my way back from the airport.
We'll be able to reach him in the evening.
My husband isn't the issue.
You need to arrest Jin
Jae Gyu and find my son.
Arrest him again.
What for?
You already failed two
of his interrogations.
What else can you do?
Catch him at the scene...
after he leaves through his secret passage.
A kid's life in on the line.
That's how scumbags are.
He's trying to get back
at the boy's mother.
Detective Dong!
Have the district police
search for the kid...
and focus on the secret passage.
He already threatened the boy's life!
That's what he's after.
He's using the boy as a distraction.
The Executioner only kills those
that deserve to die in his mind.
It sounds like you know him well.
The Executioner, I mean.
Who let him in there?
Drag him out.
Can you please just leave?
Block all the roads and
not just the highways.
Check everyone who Detective
Dong came in contact with.
Yes, sir.
He may erase memories
but not hard evidence.
Make sure you record every footage you see.
Are you insane?
I know you don't care
for authority figures,
but you can't talk back to
the deputy chief like that.
What do you have against
me serving the force until...
I'm eligible for a full pension?
Just shoot me instead, why don't you?
If I die on the job, my youngest would...
at least be set until college.
Your youngest is smart and
will get a scholarship for sure.
- Right?
- Yes.
(Han Sun Mi)
I can't believe you didn't
visit me at the hospital.
I didn't think we were that close.
You're right.
I was doing some research.
You wasted your time again.
That's rich coming from someone...
who showed all his cards by
talking back to Deputy Chief Lee.
I see you have a mole in the force.
- So did you find anything?
- Maybe.
- Maybe?
- What did you see in his head?
- The secret passage.
- And?
That was it. The rest was
an illusion created by him.
Just the secret passage then?
He could control what I was seeing.
So his ability overpowers yours.
Unbelievable.
Must you hit me where it already hurts?
He not only erases
memories but can control them.
So what is it that you found?
I analyzed the message
left on Jo Sung Dong's body.
Does it say where he'd kill next?
No, he didn't leave any breadcrumbs.
Maybe you couldn't find it.
He's only been leaving direct messages...
that led us to the next victims.
There was nothing on Jo Sung Dong's body.
What good does that do when
he has already marked the boy.
What if it's a trick?
What if it's a red herring
that he's using to distract us?
- A what?
- A red herring.
And yes, it's the actual fish.
Back in the day, criminals used herrings...
to escape the police.
They were baits to throw naive
hunting dogs off their scent.
You just have a way with words, don't you?
Isn't it strange?
Two children of his victims
are investigating his murders.
- Well, it's a coincidence.
- Of course it is.
He never knew we'd join the police force.
But both of us being hooked on this case...
wasn't a coincidence at all.
Anyone can tell that.
He left clues that'll lead us to him,
but he keeps playing dumb for some reason.
Please stop it from happening.
- The third victim...
- On top of that,
he's been acting like a true psychopath...
and has even...
shown us his supernatural power.
- Just cut to the chase.
- What is his objective?
What is he trying to get
by baiting us like this?
Revenge, of course.
- Revenge?
- What else can it be?
The Executioner killed
to avenge other victims.
He killed people who he
thought deserved to die.
That's what he considers as his calling.
So our parents dying wasn't enough?
There's no other way to explain his game.
He's taking out his wrath
from 20 years ago on us.
The wrath he felt from
all three of our parents.
- Three?
- Yes, Hyeon Su's mom.
Because she ran off with another man?
It can't be a simple lovers' quarrel.
There must be a hidden secret.
Or maybe it's the other way around.
He could be using
revenge to justify his killings.
The Executioner kills
to feel the joy of killing...
and masks that in the name of justice.
And that's what you figured out?
That he really has no specific reason?
What if the third target
isn't the young boy?
Who else could it be?
Well,
me.
Nothing can be heard from the rabbit hole.
I repeat. Everything is
silent at the rabbit hole.
We read you loud and clear.
- How's the GPS?
- Working perfectly.
Officers in cars and on foot...
will take cues from Wild Dog in
an act-first, report-second way.
How many GPS trackers did you set up?
One on his car and one on his motorcycle,
sir.
- Is that enough?
- We don't want...
to risk getting caught.
I thought he wasn't that bright.
He's quite cunning though.
He's been weaving us in his little game.
It only makes sense that we're his endgame.
I'm also one of the people who
you came in contact with too.
You don't have to look so worried though.
I'm not worried.
Anyway, I'm just stating a possibility.
It's not what I truly figured out.
Just tell me what that is already.
An accomplice.
An accomplice?
You're needed, sir.
Keep up the good work, everyone.
- Work hard.
- Yes, sir.
Get back to work.
Pull that up for me.
Hey. Darn it.
It nagged at me.
He's so thorough. Why did he
leave a trail for the water pump?
Do you think it was intentional?
As in, he exposed the secret
tunnel to hide his accomplice?
Read my head.
That's why he showed it to
you when you scanned him.
So? Who's the accomplice?
There was a foreign company
that restored abandoned buildings.
It was a foreign paper company.
We hacked all the Chinese
administration networks...
and found a clue.
The high and mighty Superintendent Han,
hacking?
It wasn't for the case.
I'm saving a child.
And?
The person in charge of the ghost
company came in four years ago.
Shim Sang Ha's husband?
Yoon In Tae.
The kid's dad used his kid...
He isn't his real dad.
He married Shim Sang Ha,
who was a single mom.
He isn't on that flight.
He's probably somewhere near Jin Jae Gyu,
receiving his orders.
Yoon In Tae committed murder?
He isn't your ordinary guy.
We found traces of him in the underworld.
Is Jin Jae Gyu really after a child?
Because of something from 20 years ago?
We can't ignore the possibility.
He'll find any reason for
the sake of his pleasure.
So? Where are we headed?
Their hideout.
Jin Jae Gyu and Yoon In Tae's real hideout.
Don't worry.
Even the riot police are searching for him.
What is that?
That's my husband's ringtone.
Did he leave his phone?
No. I'm sure he took it.
Hold on.
(Restricted Number)
It's my husband's phone.
- Listen carefully.
- What's going on?
- Honey, Hyeon Su's missing...
- Just listen.
- Are you with him?
- Come out the back door.
- What?
- Get out of there now!
Mr. Yoon, this is the police.
Stay here.
This is where the kid went missing.
Yoon In Tae owns dozens of
property here in fake names.
They're all in sketchy locations.
This is where he went missing,
so there's a high probability.
- Do we have a warrant?
- Give me a break.
Do it your way.
- You want me to take the fall?
- They'll go easy on you...
since you're doing it to save a child.
You're as big a lunatic as I am.
He climbed over the wall.
The secret tunnel was a trick.
The child's home was attacked.
The mom was abducted.
Darn it.
Sir, my cell phone.
- What phone?
- It's in the car...
We tracked the phone.
It's speeding toward Incheon.
He's running.
Block the roads to the airport and harbor.
The kid isn't here.
Knowing him,
there's probably another secret room...
Here.
Open the car door.
You found me.
It's a smart world.
Turn around and get on your knees.
Make sure you don't touch
him when you handcuff him.
It'll take five minutes
for backup to get here.
But it'll only take me three
minutes to deal with you both...
and get on the boat.
1 minute and 50 seconds.
Yes, that's enough time.
You'll end up rotting in jail anyway.
I ran away...
after I saw Jin Jae Gyu at my house.
I did what my husband told me to do.
And I found my son in the car.
He told me the only way to stay safe...
is to get on a boat and leave.
Ma'am, where's your husband?
I agreed to meet him at
the Passenger Terminal.
1 minute and 30 seconds.
He has a knife.
Wake up. I'll call an ambulance.
Darn it!
You even tried to harm the kid?
You failed.
The mother and son are safe.
What?
We found them before they left the country.
What did you say?
Are you upset?
No.
No, wait.
Something's weird.
Something feels weird. Wait.
Wait a minute.
No.
(Come back.)
No. No.
Listen to me.
You're the only one who can
protect Sang Ha and Hyeon Su.
Don't ever forget that.
Sang Ha... Let her go.
Let Sang Ha go.
This guy...
doesn't have supernatural powers.
He tried to protect them.
He tried to protect her family...
from the actual murderer.
He... He tried to protect
them from the Eraser.
"The Eraser"?
No!
No! No!
(Memorist)
There was a mob violence 20 years ago.
Don't trust Jin Jae Gyu's memories.
I'm sure it happened.
The culprit is someone else?
You don't trust my memories.
He was definitely someone
close to Jin Jae Gyu.
- Are you sure?
- A black face.
Red eyes.
The guy who suffocated to death.
The moment Jin Jae Gyu's
memory started disappearing.
The moment the murderer first appeared.
3,000?