(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
The mask. The silicon mask.
Prosthetic makeup.
He purposely made sure there were witnesses.
Wait.
Why Jo Sung Dong?
These scoops...
He wasn't alone.
The cameraman who got there second.
He's currently living at a place...
that's only 20 minutes away by foot from Yeom Hwa Ran's place.
What are the police...
doing here at this hour?
"The police"?
How do you know...
who we are?
You came here with the telepathic investigator.
What brings a celebrity like you to my place?
You don't seem startled at all.
It's like you were expecting us.
Was I supposed to be startled?
Petty criminals get scared the moment they see me.
But some can be very bold...
depending on how cruel of a crime they've committed.
I knew you'd come.
How?
Stop.
I'm currently taking care of my garden.
It's to make up for not being around.
How did you know we'd come?
Because I had a dream...
a long time ago after meeting you, Detective Dong.
I knew you were a man of many talents,
but premonitions didn't seem like one of them.
It seems like you know a lot about me.
Because I also had a premonition...
about coming across a former photographer...
who kills while wearing a mask.
A killer?
Jin Jae Gyu.
There are an easy way and a hard way...
both of which will well wrap up our encounter.
- What's the easy way? - A memory scan.
- Why? - Don't you know?
You said you knew we'd meet.
I'm afraid my gift doesn't extend that far.
Your gift?
We're investigating a serial murder,
and a lot of the evidence points to you...
as the killer.
Like what?
The serial killer came out of a 20-year hiatus...
right around the time you came back to Korea.
What a coincidence.
A memory scan will clear you of all charges.
I decline.
Sure.
I bet you're guilty.
It just doesn't seem right.
So you'll choose the hard way.
If I must.
(Search and Seizure Warrant)
As of this moment, we will begin...
the search and seizure of your residence.
Enter.
As the law states, you have the right to stay...
and observe our actions.
Search the place.
(Memorist)
(Ep 7: Memory Eraser)
Why is it so dark in here?
I thought the place has been vacant for 20 years.
You may enter now.
- There's nothing here. - Right.
Not even a TV.
Did you think you were serving justice...
by killing people?
Is this part of an official interrogation?
Just consider it as a personal question.
A personal question?
Then that surprises me.
It seems like you rely on Detective Dong a lot.
That's odd since you don't seem like the type...
to believe in the supernatural powers.
The killer seems to know me well.
I guess I can say that about you too.
I only looked into your soul, that's all.
- Into my soul? - That's right.
I apologize if I made you uncomfortable.
I wonder how long you'll be able to joke around.
We're looking, but we haven't found anything solid.
People like him would never discard murder weapons.
He probably saved them like souvenirs.
Here. Let me.
Let it be. It's just the drain.
Gosh.
I'd love to have a hot bowl of soup right now.
- You had five sandwiches. - They were tiny!
What if he already got rid of the evidence?
- You think Ms. Han is wrong? - We haven't found anything.
The clever lady is barking up the wrong tree?
Sir.
Ms. Han, good job today.
The warrant expires at sundown.
Even people as old as me are pitching in,
but there he is eating his sandwiches.
Leave him be. It's better than him causing trouble.
He just doesn't know how to be considerate, does he?
Hold on. It seems like he's about to cause trouble.
That's a big chimney for a house without a furnace.
It's for a fireplace.
Am I the only one who finds this weird?
There is no fireplace on the first floor.
Then the second floor.
A fireplace should be on the first floor...
since hot air travels upward.
It hasn't even been used either.
The killings will continue.
What?
Three more will die.
One...
by one.
Brutally.
What the...
What is all of this?
Ma'am. They found a secret room.
What...
That jerk offered up the victims...
as an offering.
Several people.
Arrest him.
Yes, ma'am.
You are under arrest for serial murder.
You have the right to remain silent. You may defend yourself,
so get yourself a lawyer and keep fighting if you want.
You sick psycho. Get up.
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency)
I heard he's speaking.
- Yes, after a full day. - What did he say?
He wants to speak with Detective Dong Baek.
Tell me whose skeletal remains were in the altar.
- I'll deal with him. - No.
He says he'll tell me everything!
We'll have the forensics report soon.
We should send him in.
It'll be a headache if he loses his temper and attacks him.
I won't lose my temper!
You already did.
Then we'll make sure he can't attack him.
That should do.
What is it with the handcuffs?
My fist shoots out instinctively when I see garbage.
Good thing you became a cop.
You'd be in jail otherwise.
Don't worry about others.
But I am worried about you.
Did you have that sickening smile on your face...
when you killed people too?
Don't get worked up.
Were the murders 20 years ago also an offering to your deity?
Is that what you're talking about?
The Executioner?
Don't ask. Don't let him take the lead.
How do you know about the Executioner?
Don't you live with that strange feeling,
knowing the truth is laid out everywhere, but only you know it.
At times, it's pride, but sometimes, it's loneliness.
That endlessly strange and lonely feeling.
Can you scan memories too?
No, I'm not.
I don't have telepathy like you.
You're a shaman?
I can peek into the truth a little.
I was able to hear the deity through long prayer and penance.
You're really a shaman?
Labels aren't important.
Soothsayers, prophets, things like that don't matter.
What the deity says is what matters.
What a bunch of nonsense.
Nonsense.
I thought you of all people...
would understand.
You say you hear divine revelations, but you didn't know you'd be mocked?
I thought you wanted to know about...
the woman who was hit by a claw hammer and died 20 years ago?
Weren't all the victims from back then men?
All of them were men.
You want to know, right?
That pretty woman...
who was dying.
She was your mom, right?
Mom?
It was you.
You killed her.
It was your fault.
She died because of you.
Don't give me that nonsense.
You drew danger upon yourself.
Don't lose your cool.
- Why did you kill her? - His wrath...
You're the murderer.
- The murders will continue. - Get him out.
Was she really my mother?
More will be murdered.
Was she my mother? Tell me!
Three more will die before the month is over.
Tell me, you scumbag!
The people cursed because of you will die brutal deaths!
Stop changing the subject! Let go. Let go.
Tell me. Tell me, you jerk!
- Get him out. - No!
We have the lab results.
The skeletons were from animals.
There was no human DNA.
We'll have to detain him and investigate.
Will we get a detention warrant?
He merely went to the crime scenes as a photographer.
We'll have to try.
He mentioned the woman's death himself.
What's this about your mom?
We need to include everything so we can get the warrant.
Tell him about your childhood memory.
What do you want to put down?
I think I saw a woman die 20 years ago, and that psycho...
pretending to be a shaman knew that?
We'll assume we can't detain him and investigate accordingly.
We must have all available officers watch him closely.
Watching him is fine, but we need to find evidence.
He will kill again just as he prophesied.
- Do you believe him? - Yes, I do.
And he'll proudly kill three more people.
You don't know when he'll act. We can't just watch him forever.
He said before the month ends,
three will die.
We have 10 days left in the month.
He'll act before then.
He seemed confident.
He has a trick up his sleeve.
He's not the only one who is confident.
I have no intention of losing either.
(Criminal Department)
Thank you. It's kind of you to see me out like this.
I wanted to get rid of the stench.
We'll soon meet again.
By the way,
the stench is actually coming from something else.
What?
You're both surrounded...
by vindictive spirits.
Do you never stop talking nonsense?
Two women...
had to kill each other.
Because if they didn't, they would've gotten killed...
by the murderer.
If you're so confident, leave behind some evidence.
The vindictive spirts are warning you.
Someone's going to get murdered...
tonight.
I hope you stop it.
If you can, that is.
You will be responsible...
for that death.
- What? - You're right.
I'll be the one sending you to jail.
Tonight?
How interesting. He's crazier than expected.
He's going to do something tonight.
He just wants to play a game.
He's trying to prove...
that he's superior than us.
(Green Moving)
Don't even lose him for a second...
so we can stop him from meeting an accomplice.
Got it, ma'am.
Gosh, whatever. I don't care if we lose him.
What? There's going to be a murder tonight.
Look at the previous murders. They were brutally murdered.
He's the Executioner.
I wouldn't be surprised if someone really gets murdered tonight.
It's fine as long as we're safe.
But...
What is he doing in the dark?
Do we have infrared cameras?
No. It's not showing on the thermal image camera either.
There are dozens of cops there. He can't murder anyone.
The sun's up.
Check all the new cases.
There are a few accidental deaths...
Ms. Han.
Someone got murdered.
- "Murdered"? - Who is it?
The victim is someone you know.
I came at dawn to pack my stuff...
because I didn't want to run into him.
But when I got here...
Someone's going to get murdered...
tonight.
Rape and blackmail.
A scumbag with a hammer tattoo.
Were you guys on bad terms?
Sir, can you please protect me?
I bet I'm the next target.
What is he doing?
- He heard a sound. - "A sound"?
Do you think Jin Jae Gyu is really a shaman?
It can't be him. He was being watched by dozens of cops.
Shut it.
Maybe it was someone else.
This guy had a lot of enemies.
It's the Executioner.
He is punishing evil by becoming evil himself.
He punished him by doing exactly what he did to the victims.
Where do you think this ink came from?
How interesting.
He even recorded a video...
of beating the guy to death.
My gosh.
Who's there?
Who are you?
Wait.
No, wait.
Wait. Please don't kill me.
What did I do wrong?
Can you rewind to the part where he throws him on the ground?
I only see his feet.
Let's watch when he closes the window.
Okay.
Slowly.
Stop. Make it brighter.
As bright as possible.
- His face is black. - What is that?
Is that a ghost?
A mask.
"A mask"?
We stayed up for nothing.
He's leaving the house.
I think he's going for a walk.
Field seven. We're on him.
He stopped walking at the three-way intersection.
Do you think it was a copycat crime?
That's impossible. Only a few people in...
the investigation unit are the ones who know about the Executioner.
Then could it be an accomplice?
No, it can't be an accomplice.
He never met anyone.
- What about his call logs? - Nothing.
He didn't email or call anyone.
We checked all the cell phones in the neighborhood.
And we found nothing in particular.
Where are you going?
My gosh.
Who wants to take a photo with Hodori?
- Me! - Me!
- Who is the kid? - I don't know.
It's a boy, but they all look the same.
They all look different.
Will you hurry up? I might lose my pension.
- Me! - Me!
Here we go guys!
- It's my turn. - Me too.
- What now? - They're too thick.
- Unbelievable. - Me!
- Can I go first? - No, me first.
- Me! - No. It's my turn.
Me next.
A kid from the neighborhood?
The kid's mom used to manage Jin Jae Gyu's greenhouse.
That is how he used the kid's phone.
Did you conduct an illegal scan?
Don't get stuffy with me. That isn't the issue at the moment.
We can't use tainted evidence.
I'm not part of the team anyway.
Get a warrant based on the contact with the mother.
Head to Jin Jae Gyu's house with the kid in two hours.
Otherwise, we will have to wait for another week.
The warrant will take at least half a day.
I don't care how, but get it in two hours.
6424, please pull over.
Pull over.
It seems like you have a flat tire.
But I just had it inflated yesterday.
The engine oil is the issue.
I had that swapped out too.
Good job on that. It's crucial to keep it that way.
My wife drives too, but she never even washes her car.
(You have a new message.)
The warrant has been issued.
Begin the process.
Hello, ma'am.
It's me, the one and only telepath.
Would you like to take a photo with me?
Good.
Hi, kid. How about a photo?
Thanks.
Gosh.
Baek, why don't you hold the boy?
- Should I? - Yes.
All right, here we go.
Can you smile more?
Maybe I should come closer.
Or maybe not.
(Download, Touch OK Button)
(Secure Messenger, Downloading)
We're good. Here we go then.
1, 2, 3.
Go to Mr. Jin.
Mr. Jin!
Hi, there.
Did you have fun on the phone I gave you?
Go and play then.
(H.S.M.O.R)
(H.S.M.O.R messenger)
It's an encrypted messenger created by Russians.
It doesn't leave a trace.
That's how they've been communicating.
You can see who he's been in contact with...
by checking the app.
- What? - Hold on.
Wait. No way.
(Will you remove this app?)
He deleted the app and then rebooted the phone.
He must be onto us.
Darn it.
Is he really a shaman?
I have the call log. The ones in red are by Jin Jae Gyu.
(Call Log)
They're the same number.
Who does it belong to?
It's a corporate number. A broadcasting station.
A broadcasting station?
Customer inbound.
Can't tell if it's a regular.
How is it that you're here, Mr. Jo?
Would you like some tea?
Is there a problem?
Of course. Two accomplices of a murder case are here.
Accomplices?
What are you here for?
You have no dignity, do you?
Anyway, I received a tip.
About a murder?
No, but something just as surprising.
I heard that the cheeky young girl who came to me...
was you.
You have a right to know...
considering what you went through.
It'll make a perfect documentary.
The daughter of a murder victim joins the police seeking revenge.
How dramatic.
- This is my duty. - Then I applaud you.
So you'll knowingly receive intel from a murderer?
Saying false truths about me in front of others?
Does that count as defamation or contempt?
I wonder if you know...
that Mr. Jin obtained an astonishing gift.
He just mentioned a secret of mine that I haven't told others...
which was surprising.
I was begging him to do a special show with me.
Look at you being chummy with a killer.
Defamation it is then.
Are you truly a killer?
You see, I believe the Executioner...
to be a gutsy person.
He burns animals that the law couldn't punish.
It's like...
having one of those incinerators that people hate in my neighborhood.
If Mr. Jin is the Executioner,
I have to say it won't be so bad.
I can easily land an exclusive interview.
Who else but the Executioner has seriously questioned...
this nation's justice system?
You value ratings over people's lives?
People's lives?
Now that you mention it,
it seems like you're still in denial.
You won't admit that your father deserved it.
- Shut it. - Blood may be thicker than water,
but his life isn't worth taking revenge...
- You scumbag. - Is this how it'll be?
She's fulfilling her duty as a cop and revenge is my specialty.
Understand?
You dare lay hands of an editor-in-chief?
Sue me then. It'll go on record how you...
built your career by selling murder.
- You piece of... - Don't touch him.
Don't lay hands on other people.
- Want me to break your neck too? - Don't you get it?
What do the three that will die have in common?
You would've...
made contact with them.
What are you talking about?
Three will die?
They will die...
mercilessly.
As the moon gets fuller,
those who you have made contact with will brutally die.
One is already dead,
and two will soon follow.
Will he really kill those you have touched?
Probably.
- What if it's a trick? - It's obviously a trick.
He can't know whom I physically contacted...
unless he's a real shaman.
Then a random person... No.
That's not his style.
Naturally, he has to kill someone I came in contact with to win.
- Then... - Let's see...
just how much he knows.
We'll return your phones once the investigation is over.
Are you saying my kid's phone was used for a crime?
What crime?
We can't share the details of an ongoing investigation.
We need to know who it is.
You're saying that the suspect is near our child.
We are watching the suspect around the clock...
We can't give you the phone if you don't tell us.
Jin Jae Gyu.
Mr. Jin?
For what...
Don't go anywhere near him.
How did you end up taking care of his greenhouse?
A few months ago,
not long after he moved here, he came to me.
He wanted to buy equipment.
I run a small export business.
Which equipment?
He said he was fixing up the house.
What was it? Yes. Water pump.
Water pump?
He said his basement had flooded. I told him...
it would be cheaper to rent,
but he insisted on buying it.
I don't usually do retail.
But I made an exception since he was a neighbor.
Then he brought over a cell phone a few days later.
He said he got it as a gift,
but he liked the one he had, and gave it to our son as a gift.
That's when he saw that I ran a flower shop,
and asked me to look after his greenhouse.
Why aren't you getting in?
That's everyone I touched.
Find out which of them he'll go after.
If by chance he really is a shaman, that is.
Why am I not on this list?
I'll stay here.
I have more work to do.
- Hello? - Turn on the news right now.
It's true.
(Colleague Police Officer)
Her father was murdered because of a grudge.
She has been digging into that cold case for years.
He was a terrible human being. That's probably why he was killed.
It's very serious.
It means she was using her authority for personal reasons.
It's not only against the law for a victim to investigate...
her personal case, it is improper.
The serious abuse of authority by a victim's child...
in improperly taking revenge.
We will look into it further tomorrow.
With TVC News, this is Park Sa Myung.
The report itself is trash too, but the situation stinks as well.
The daughter of the Executioner's victim is gnashing her teeth...
after 20 years.
Gosh. But we're just sitting here shuffling papers.
You and your stupid mouth. Your mouth is the problem.
Gosh.
How's the cell phone restoration coming along?
Forensics says it'll be hard to finish today.
- Pressure them. - We are, but...
Field Nine. Two chicks entering the wild dog's vicinity.
The yellow chicks changed their feathers.
He wants us to find a water pump.
He always orders around this old man without any explanations.
Do you really not understand...
why Baek picks on you more than anyone else?
Don't say it's because I'm such a magnanimous person.
No, it's because...
you're a chump. You breed abusive people.
Are you taking after Baek?
You grumble, but you always take it. That's why he won't stop.
I have a profound reason for it.
What profound reason? To last until you retire? The pension?
Way deep down within this captain of yours,
I have a very profound reason that I can't explain.
- You're just a chump. - You punk.
- At least pretend you are working. - Okay.
What should we do?
Let them be.
Field Nine. Don't follow the chicks. Just watch them.
(Reassignment Notice)
Ma'am. You've been reassigned.
(Dismissal, New Assignment: TBD)
"To be determined"?
Operations Center. Sergeant Lee speaking.
Yes, sir. Understood.
Ma'am.
Headquarters wants you.
The first target is Han Sun Mi.
The final target is Dong Baek.
I want every reporter from every department on this...
full time.
Yes, sir. What are we trying to uncover about them?
- It does not matter. - Yes, sir.
Repeated assault is not enough.
We need something stronger and dirtier.
Find everything you can!
Should we dig into Dong Baek's private life too?
"Should we?" Why you...
Bring me everything!
You have your hidden card, right?
- A hidden card? - Yes, I laid the groundwork.
- For what? - They despise all reporters,
but I put in much effort to install a pipeline.
It's solid.
The rookie?
You'd better do a good job.
Use a recorder, a hidden camera, anything.
Bring me dirt on Dong Baek at all costs.
Your future depends on this.
Why did you do it?
Do you know much about dogs?
The ones who bark first aren't confident...
enough to bite.
The ones who are confident attack quietly without barking.
I never knew you were an expert on dogs.
The media are dogs.
They can't even look you in the eye if they see you in person,
but they bark as if they're brave before the camera and with the pen.
Why? Because they know that the more they bark,
TV, radio, and newspapers...
will become a barrier and protect them.
So? Is that why you reacted as soon as they barked?
What should you do to silence dogs?
You should crush their jaws.
That's why you're inferior.
If you kick one dog, all the dogs in the area will bark.
Why?
Because that's the survival instinct of those cowards.
You disappear...
so they quiet down immediately.
It sounds like defeat and humiliation,
only glamorized.
What humiliation?
Isn't it humiliating to fire me just because of a trashy report...
when a serial killer is within our grasp?
Who fired you?
You are still in charge of the special team.
Keep investigating.
- But... - You'll await assignment...
at most for a week. If you don't catch the killer by then,
I'll say I need you and reinstate you.
Even if you do catch the killer before then, you announce it.
You'll continue to grow as the icon of the police department...
without a scratch.
I don't need the glory.
The next few hours are critical.
Keep investigating in secret.
I told Young Soo...
that your orders will be sent out as the head of Metro.
However, don't go to the station for a week. Run it remotely.
Do you not like it?
Thank you.
You may go.
(Mr. Jo Sung Dong)
Are you close to Mr. Jo Sung Dong by any chance?
What?
I met him once at an event. Why?
I wondered if you knew each other for a while,
for example, for about 20 years?
Never mind.
(Mr. Jo Sung Dong)
(Call Logs)
I found out...
Jin Jae Gyu's trick.
I heard it's been abandoned for years.
It was owned by a foreign corporation.
But yesterday, the owner got switched to someone else.
To who?
It's a high school kid,
and it turns out he's Jo Sung Dong's son.
He's studying overseas, and his mom went with him.
So Jo Sung Dong probably bought it for him.
Old man, I want you to go meet Jo Sung Dong.
- Why? - Ask him...
why he accepted this building.
Accepted it from whom?
Jin Jae Gyu.
"Jin Jae Gyu"?
Act like you don't know that part.
Just ask him why he bought the building.
That guy is the head...
of a broadcasting station. Do you think he'll meet me?
He'll meet you if you tell him that I sent you.
By the way, when are you going to tell me your big picture?
He always hangs up once he's done talking.
Call Mr. Jo's secretary.
You're a fool who lets him treat you this way.
I should just beat that punk.
How did you find this place?
The water pump.
Oh, right. The water pump.
I couldn't find a water pump in his house.
Let's request a search warrant...
How did you find this place with just a water pump?
"Operation Anthropoid".
"Operation Anthropoid"?
A movie about assassinating a senior Nazi administrator...
during World War 2.
The soldiers succeed in assassinating their target,
but they get locked up in a church basement.
But they continue to have hope even though they get surrounded.
Why? Because they think there's a secret passage...
in the church basement.
"A secret passage"?
In the end, they failed to find the secret passage.
And when the enemies started pouring water into the basement,
they all committed suicide.
But what does that movie have anything to do with this?
It was the only movie that he owned.
How could you tell just by looking at that?
The geology books helped me guess.
I can't believe he got inspired and created an escape route.
He needed a water pump because it kept filling with water.
That's why I searched for the exit with a water pipe.
He tricked us by pretending to warn us about the murders.
- He used to create an alibi... - Wait.
It's a greenhouse.
Let's set up a trap...
- and wait for him to... - It's too late for that.
A motorcycle?
Jin Jae Gyu escaped through a secret passage.
Track his motorcycle right now.
A real-time location tracing is impossible.
We restored the cell phone,
and it looks like he searched some names.
Choi Poong Won and Prosecutor Woo Seok Do.
Darn it.
They're both people who deserve to die.
- Please move out of the way. - Out of the way.
- Conditional medical release again? - Can you tell us what happened?
- Out of the way. - Please move.
- Can you please tell us? - Please get out of the way.
He did so many bad things but continued to live a fancy life,
after requesting for a conditional medical release.
Now is not the time to...
Gosh, you jerk.
And he got in the way of the investigation and killed Ye Rim.
But he got promoted to a chief prosecutor.
Prosecutor Woo is at the golf range.
He looks fine for now.
You touched them both, but it can't be Choi Poong Won.
If it's after the full moon,
it has to be Woo Seok Do.
What's wrong?
Something doesn't feel right.
It feels too easy.
Because it's too obvious?
I feel like we missed something.
Look.
Here are the murder patterns.
Jin Jae Gyu always lured us with a hint.
He always left a hint next to the dead victims.
We know who he is now, so maybe...
No, this is very important to him.
A perfect victory requires him to stick to the game rules.
The t-shirt worn by the victim covered in plaster.
"Hammer."
Oh Yeon Tak.
Do you have photos of the crime scene?
It wasn't Woo Seok Do either.
He was also in contact with you.
- What? - Find his current location.
You heard her!
Triangulate his phone.
Pick up!
What...
Stay away from me!
Don't come closer.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Jo Sung Dong, the leader of this nation's media.
Stop right there!
Hand above your head.
Kneel.
Move and this bullet goes in your skull.
What are you doing?
Get a grip on yourself!
Get your act together!
Hold on.
Where am I?
Yes, right here...
The most crucial memory is gone.
It's as if someone carved it out.
Jin Jae Gyu has the power to erase memories.
How did you motivate your accomplice?
You're paying for sins tied to your blood.
He's the demon.
What could be his endgame?
What is the picture he's drawing for us?
Your filthy hands touched the boy.
What if the third target isn't the boy?
No!
That only leaves me.