(Yoo Seung Ho)
(Lee Se Young)
(Jo Sung Ha)
(Go Chang Suk)
(Yoon Ji On) (Jun Hyo Sung)
(Memorist)
(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
I'm on my way there.
What if the pervert hits on me?
Don't you know how rich he is? Your entire life will change.
I'll probably die before my life changes.
Life is like a jungle.
You either die or win something big.
Then why don't you live in the oratory?
"Pray for eternal life..."
What's wrong?
- What's the matter? - This is so annoying.
- Hey. - Don't ask.
This place is filled with weirdos.
I told you to come early.
I was busy studying.
You're under academic probation. Hurry up.
I really don't want to go.
He's a perverted murderer.
How dare you say that? Do you want to see me die?
The entire country knows that except for you and Dad.
That's just the evil spirits trying to slander him.
Hurry up. Take off your jacket.
(A healthy and peaceful family)
Adversity is a blessing in disguise.
- Eternal life. - Eternal life.
I'm sure...
you all asked this at least once.
"Why do you test me like this?"
- Eternal life. - Eternal life.
The creator of all beings shares our pain.
But why does he give us so many troubles?
And why does he allow me, his loyal vassal...
that has incarnated,
to go through such severe adversity?
- Eternal life. - Eternal life.
But it's all because he loves us.
You need to know this.
All the prophets we know...
were each given a hardship that they could endure.
Even normal humans were given such painful hardships.
So imagine what kind of hardship he must have in store...
for someone who has incarnated from the skies...
- Oh, gosh! - My goodness!
My gosh!
Oh, my goodness!
- What happened? - My goodness!
My goodness gracious!
My gosh, I can't believe this.
He was surrounded by 20 people, but no one knows what happened?
No, no one remembers.
Just the part where he was murdered.
The school was also surrounded by bodyguards.
You psychopathic killer.
I'm the devil that will drag you to the underworld.
Just you wait. You will soon feel what it's like to burn.
Doesn't it feel like a declaration of war?
A war against supernatural crimes.
Whoever did this wanted to attract attention.
It's like he put on a magic show.
This is interesting.
Someone else also has superpowers like me?
If that person really got rid of people's memories,
doesn't that mean that person is stronger than you?
So as of this moment, you're the usual suspect.
Are you kidding me?
I don't have the ability to erase people's memories.
But you're the only person who knows that.
Fine.
I'm already cornered as it is. Bring me a warrant.
I'd rather be investigated by someone I know anyway.
Dong Baek was home all night.
- There were tons of reporters... - Prove it.
I want you to check if he really stayed home.
Okay, I'll check.
No.
(Memorist)
(Memorist: Ep 5, Prayer for Protection)
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency)
You're here. Have a seat.
Erasing people's memories?
Is that even possible?
- Given the circumstances... - As of now...
Nothing is for sure yet.
So you don't think it was a supernatural crime?
We're going to check if it was a supernatural crime,
- or if we're being tricked. - Forget that.
Which one do you think it is?
I'm more convinced that it was a supernatural crime.
- Why? - If that's not it,
things become too complicated.
Just like Occam's Razor,
I'm going to start out by checking what's simple.
There's a second person with supernatural powers?
It might not be the second.
What do you mean?
- Are you saying... - I'll report to you...
based on the results.
How long can we hold the embargo?
The reporters are waiting, so a week at most.
You can reactivate the Special Investigation Team,
but I want an answer in three days.
I want to know if it was someone with supernatural powers...
or just a psycho.
I need to know that at least to make a public announcement.
Okay, sir.
You all need to stay alert.
Park Ki Dan was the center of attention,
and he got executed publicly.
If you fail to solve this case,
people will question the entire police force.
- We'll keep that in mind, sir. - Go and catch the culprit.
Senior Superintendent Han, you can stay.
(Sanctification)
What do you mean there might not be two people with supernatural powers?
I'm very suspicious of Detective Dong Baek.
Why is that?
The possibility of a new person with supernatural powers...
makes things a lot more complicated.
It's more far-fetched than Dong Baek erasing memories.
It's why my investigation will start with him.
Occam's Razor?
Why have you never asked...
about the reason I've been skeptical of Dong Baek?
- It's not my place to ask. - Weird, isn't it?
I have great anxieties over one telepathic inspector.
Is it because I have something to hide?
No, I'm worried about the police force.
Because Dong Baek's success...
equals to the tragedy of our offices.
People are joking about how one telepath is more competent...
than 120,000 police officers.
Him thriving will lead to budget cuts.
Our nation's leaders won't approve of us.
All I do is catch perpetrators.
I'm not telling you to make charges up.
Just be meticulous in all aspects.
There is no need to protect Dong Baek.
Do you understand?
I won't protect anyone who's guilty.
This has never seen the light of day before.
(Intelligence bureau: Top Secret)
(Confidential Personnel Record)
(Dong Baek)
(Details)
Will I find my answer in here?
No.
We know as much as the world knows about Dong Baek.
I'm handing you this file...
because this is your job now.
It's up to you to fill in the blanks.
(Dong Baek)
(Dongbaek Station)
Where do you live?
You don't seem familiar.
Are you sick, kid?
Kid? Kid!
A kid just collapsed. Hurry!
Metro isn't saying much.
They already took photos.
Of course they're not interested.
Only I know this face and composition.
So where exactly did you see this?
I'll tell you when it's time.
And when will that be?
Always so cryptic.
It was dropped off two days ago.
I doubt you deal with paintings like this here.
It's why I was going to send it back immediately,
but there wasn't a contact number.
Nothing?
There was no waybill either.
Any small detail at this point would help.
It wasn't anything weird,
but Mr. Park seemed highly satisfied with it.
He must've been satisfied with it,
considering how he looked at it for hours.
Shouldn't this be an insult to him?
Exactly. How weird.
Hold on.
What is it?
Wait a second. This seems off.
What does?
That wasn't it.
When I unwrapped it,
I saw a blade.
A long blade.
What on earth?
There was another layer.
Another layer?
The killer peeled it off.
He was found at a way station at the age of seven.
He wouldn't speak let alone say his name,
so he bounced from facilities for the disabled...
before landing in an orphanage.
He was named after Dongbaek Station where he was found.
Nothing worth noticing happened while growing up.
He revealed his abilities at the age of 20,
was offered countless jobs, but he chose to become a cop.
- Why? - There's an interview.
The justice system is the best way to catch the bad guys, right?
What a nutjob.
He turned down millions of dollars for 2,000 dollars a month.
That includes research funding from global companies.
What could it be?
Why did he choose the most illogical career path?
No one remembers him from his childhood days...
even though he's now an international celebrity.
I have the alibi video.
The news team had him under surveillance.
He peeled off the top layer.
So the one who sent this must be the perp.
Why though?
Why risk getting caught?
- The perp was challenging him. - What?
It wasn't delivered by a company truck,
so it'll take time to track down.
There aren't CCTV cameras in the area either.
- Where's that guy? - I'll bring him back.
What do you think you're doing?
You said you were done processing this place.
Hello, ma'am.
I already spoke to your husband.
Mr. Park is in this mess because of you people.
- Leave. Get out! - What?
- Leave! - Sure, we're leaving.
Let's go.
The devil's spawns.
Unbelievable. Her faith is still intact.
Have Forensics confiscate the painting.
What about the delivery truck?
I need manpower to track it down.
Why don't we let Metro take the case?
We'll be shoved aside since it's not in our jurisdiction anyway.
I saw it.
I saw the delivery truck.
Did you really see the delivery truck?
How about the license plate?
That I don't remember,
but a phone number in huge letters was written on the side.
- Really? - Really?
And the numbers?
How should I know? I wouldn't have memorized it.
What? Then what is it that you know?
You can do your thing.
The memory scan.
You shouldn't mess with grown-ups.
No, I'll do it.
On one condition.
- On one condition? - I want your phone number.
- Sure thing. 010... - She was asking for mine.
No, yours.
Who else would I want to contact?
What?
- Mind your business, old man. - Old man?
I'm two years younger than he is.
- You see... - Is that all you want?
- I'll take it the way I want. - The way you want?
Nothing's out of the ordinary.
Hold it. Check that light.
A motion sensor light in the stairway?
The one downstairs didn't turn on. Maybe it malfunctioned.
How many times did the lights in the 3rd and 4th floor go on?
Let me check. Twice.
Once at midnight and once at 4am.
Four hours from his house and back.
The rooftop.
Rooftop?
That's how he got out.
Here.
Don't be too late.
(Daeguk Deliveries)
Okay.
He could've gone anywhere without being caught on camera.
That's only if he could jump across that.
Ma'am. I really can't stand Dong Baek,
but this isn't right.
He jumped that in the middle of the night?
He'd die if he missed even slightly.
He despises murder.
I heard Occam's Razor is about eliminating complicated theories.
But this is so complicated, that I can't even imagine it.
These are the theories that we should eliminate first.
That's right.
Over there.
Hi. I have the blood test results of the witnesses.
A sleeping gas was detected in small amounts.
If they fainted due to the gas...
It wasn't the use of supernatural powers.
Then is Dong Baek removed from the list of suspects?
Hey. Why are you so happy? Aren't you enemies?
I wasn't happy.
We'll keep the option open that supernatural powers were used.
- What? - What?
Question the people in the area.
Yes, ma'am.
Based on the MRI,
we do not see any special abnormalities.
In order to determine the cause of the fainting...
Superintendent Han Sun Mi needs to talk to you.
The patient will not cooperate.
Other vitals and body index are stable.
I plan to suggest a more detailed CT scan of the brain.
I thought we were done when we spoke on the phone.
I wanted to meet you.
I had to come anyway on another matter.
Superintendent Han Sun Mi. Do you know how many doctors...
have been treating Dong Baek?
- I don't know. - 12 department chiefs.
- That's a lot. - The department of neurology alone.
There are 40 if you include other departments.
If you include the staff, add another zero.
If you include the teams abroad, add another zero.
I can see that.
You must not get it.
Dong Baek is fame and an opportunity for doctors.
I understand.
I don't think you do,
it's not just a matter of a patient's confidential data.
What doctor would risk a chance of a lifetime...
by leaking information to a cop she doesn't even know?
That's nonsense.
What if we do this?
What if I bring a warrant?
Will you still refuse to cooperate?
You must be asking because that's impossible.
Thank you for making time for me.
But...
you never asked...
why I'm willing to request a warrant to investigate him.
- Well... - Is this why?
Because you've already concluded that he may be dangerous.
Definitely not.
You were of great help.
(Dong Baek)
(Admitted into National Medical Center for unknown reasons)
Something's up.
(Han Sun Mi)
Superintendent?
Yes, ma'am. Okay.
What do you want to check?
The movements within the hospital...
from when Detective Dong Baek was admitted until his discharge.
Detective Dong Baek?
That's classified, so I can't show you that without a warrant.
(Kang Il Gook)
Mr. Kang Il Gook.
- Yes? - What law were you following...
when you shared Detective Dong's information with an outsider?
- What do you... - In Naegok-dong.
Who said that?
Won't it be a problem that the NIS investigated...
through you?
That was because the national government...
Detective Dong went missing while he was here, didn't he?
What about after that?
There aren't any cameras in the stairwells.
He was in the stairwell for an hour.
He either met someone...
Who knows?
He was alone when we found him.
Detective Dong Baek.
That's everything.
What is that?
A pen.
(Inspector Min Sung Han)
Dong Baek is on the move again.
A painting?
I delivered it two days ago.
Do you know who sent it?
I didn't see his face. He said he'd leave it outside by the door.
What's the problem?
Where was it sent from?
A villa community.
The strange thing is,
he said to make sure not to leave a trace.
He said he was donating it anonymously or something.
He wouldn't even give me the recipient's phone number,
so I had to just follow the GPS.
Okay.
He says it's Ja An Industries' villa.
- Ja An Industries? - It was in the news recently.
Where are you going? We should wait for the local police.
- Does he have a gun? - He didn't take one.
He doesn't even have a gun.
Go out back.
Be quiet.
Come here.
(Kyunghan Daily)
Her name is Yeom Hwa Ran. She's 30, not married,
and her parents live abroad.
Was she forced to drink methanol?
Someone tied her up and made her draw.
Can I have some water?
Can I please have some water?
She wasn't even allowed to drink a drop of water.
Can I have some water?
What a crazy jerk.
- She's just a weak woman. - They're not all weak.
What do you mean?
Don't you remember?
The disabled family who died due to a DUI accident.
Those kinds of accidents happen all the time.
Because of the darn law, there are tons of DUI accidents.
Don't you remember the woman who didn't even go to jail...
for having killed the family who lived off of collecting waste paper?
- It was her? - Yes.
Then do you think this was an act of revenge?
- No one survived to take revenge. - He's right.
But I'm surprised the corpse doesn't smell.
You're right.
She was dehydrated when she died,
so the decomposition process is slower than usual.
And the culprit probably covered her with embalming fluid.
- That must be Forensics. - I don't think so.
It's Metro.
Already?
Gosh, they must have eyes everywhere.
- They put a tail on me. - What are you talking about?
You both didn't know that they put a tail on me?
Why would they do that?
Think about it.
A supernatural crime occurred.
If you were in charge,
wouldn't you doubt the one person who has superpowers?
I can't believe those guys.
Do they think...
we're a bunch of pushovers?
What's their problem?
- Wait. - Let me go!
Hello, Ms. Han!
It's slippery there. Be careful.
What are you doing at an unidentified crime scene?
I was investigating what happened...
with Dong Baek and Se Hoon.
Constable Oh Se Hoon, ma'am.
How should I put this? Our cleverness and teamwork...
led us here.
We were the first ones to discover this.
Get out. We'll take over.
Yes, of course.
Just tell us what you need. I'm ready to do whatever...
It's the same person who killed Park Ki Dan.
It's a serial murder.
Does she know her?
The parents were deaf, and they died on the spot.
And their son, who was in elementary school,
also died not too long after that.
It was her third DUI accident, but she didn't even go to jail.
She got released on probation.
My gosh.
How?
They apparently settled it saying she wasn't sane...
when the accident happened.
But it was actually thanks to her lawyer.
Her lawyer was in-laws with the judge.
The problem is that after the trial, she mocked the victims...
by uploading a photo of herself celebrating with champagne.
What a crazy person.
The family member that settled...
turned out to be the parent's mother who has dementia.
The conditions aren't...
The lawyer kept his as evidence, but it just disappeared one day.
The hospital president got 10,000 dollars,
but the old lady only got 1,000 dollars.
Plus, the hospital president ended up taking that as well.
The internet blew up with people threatening to murder her.
Everyone including Yeom Hwa Ran's family,
judges, and prosecutors.
Her parents stepped down from their positions.
And Yeom Hwa Ran locked herself up at her villa.
I guess she died drinking alcohol, her favorite drink.
Unfortunately, it was toxic alcohol.
Check what the numbers mean as fast as possible.
Okay, I'm on it.
(Kyunghan Daily)
Most people come to the villas during the weekends,
so most of them were empty.
What about the villa next door?
The person who was planning to move there had a stroke.
So it's been empty for a year.
Check for witnesses.
Witnesses, my foot.
Hey.
What's your problem, you punk?
The 20 people who were right in front of Park Ki Dan...
couldn't even remember anything.
So how will you find a witness?
Would you like me to help?
That's enough.
Get out of here.
You'll regret it.
(Investigation Command Center)
Do you think it was done by some kind of a vigilance committee?
"A vigilance committee"?
Park Ki Dan and Yeom Hwa Ran both deserved to die.
- People threatened to kill them. - That's right.
Maybe someone took revenge on behalf of the public.
Don't let your prejudice get in the way.
Just focus on the crime scene.
- Yes, ma'am. - Okay, ma'am.
Can't you be nicer to her?
She may be young, but she's a senior superintendent.
Actually, she's older than you.
She's pretty much the same rank as the chief.
- You think that's funny? - Yes.
You little punk.
At least he's consistent.
He ignores everyone regardless of their age, rank, and gender.
I'm not asking you to be nice for someone else's sake.
If we solve the case together, it'll be a win-win for everyone.
Together, my foot. We're going to catch...
Actually, no. I'll be the one catching the culprit.
It'll be me and my boys.
"Boys"? I'm way older than you.
Why do you always have to be so rude?
What are you searching?
- A newspaper article. - What newspaper?
The culprit told us to look for it.
The numbers that were written on the newspaper.
People already wrote articles about that?
My gosh.
What numbers? Tell us.
Yeom Hwa Ran read English newspapers.
But there was a Korean newspaper next to the corpse.
Why? Because the culprit left that there on purpose.
- So what? - It's an inventory number.
- An inventory number? - For the newspaper.
Of when it was published?
Kyunghan Daily has over 22,000 newspapers.
What year did they publish their 16,669th newspaper?
That's around 6,000 newspapers ago.
That's 20 years ago.
October 6, 2000.
(Kyunghan Daily)
Then what's 19? It says 30 on that page.
That's the number of pages, so that doesn't matter.
- That means 19 refers to... - The page.
Bingo.
(There should be a system to support victims of crime.)
"There should be a system to support victims of crime."
My gosh.
I'm impressed.
She died due to methanol abuse.
But I also found over 300g of these in her stomach.
Rocks?
They kind of look like cement.
Why do you think she was forced to eat this?
That's your job to find out.
I was just wondering if cement accelerates...
the poisoning due to methanol.
No, I don't think so.
She was forced to eat this, so it was probably out of revenge.
Maybe it was to torture her.
Ms. Han,
you seem quite uncomfortable today. Could it be...
I have the victim's blood analysis.
The numbers were written in her blood,
but the splattered blood belongs to someone else.
Someone else? Not Park Ki Dan?
It was sprayed before Park Ki Dan even died.
That means there's another victim.
Tell the team to assemble at 8am tomorrow.
I'm calling it a day.
You act like a buffoon but you sometimes are on point.
Could you perhaps have savant syndrome?
Servant?
It's a condition where those mentally disabled...
show extraordinary abilities.
People say that it was what Isaac Newton had.
So I'm an extraordinary genius?
No, I'm saying you're a freak.
You seriously lack social skills.
That's how Newton was too. He looked down on everyone else,
picked fights with them, and cursed at them.
Being a genius is that exhausting.
I'm surrounded by idiots who can't even see what's true.
How tiresome, right?
Hasn't it occurred to you that this could be a trap,
Mr. Genius?
A trap?
Who left the evidence we're currently investigating?
The victim? No, it was the killer.
So what will this puzzle lead us too?
Would the killer be waiting for us to arrest him?
There will be a witch.
- A witch? - One that lures you with cookies.
I know that story. "Hansel and Gretel".
We'll just have to see, won't we?
Will the witch eat us or will we burn her alive instead?
This interview was released...
right around the time the newspaper article popped up.
No support is given to the victims.
Individuals shouldn't have to deal with the healing process...
all by themselves.
Dr. Nam advocates the need for a support system.
He insists that the government should be involved.
What do you think about this scream?
This crime took away her father from her.
It proves that there are more victims...
than the ones who were directly hurt.
Children especially...
suffer serious PTSD.
It's not something an individual can handle on one's own.
(Sungjung Sanatorium)
He's been with us for a few years now.
He can still communicate, right?
Well... His brain comes on and then goes off,
but you caught him on a good day.
You did come past visiting hours,
but since it's Detective Dong...
Thank you.
Everyone believes your innocence.
Those foolish assemblymen just made some stupid law.
Anyway, for our sake, please hang in there.
Okay?
Sure thing.
Doctor, you have a visitor.
Wait. Where did he go?
Doctor? Gosh, here you are.
You have visitors.
Why is the TV still on?
Goodness, you're drooling.
Are you sure he's more lucid today?
(Identity Report)
("Lambasted after Mocking Murder Victim")
("DUI Murder Only Receives Probation Yet Again")
(Kyunghan Daily)
Yes, Ms. Han.
16669 is the number of paper released.
A newspaper?
One released by Kyunghan Daily on October 6, 2000.
Find the person on page 19.
Hold on.
What was the date again?
October 6.
October 6...
(Nam Young Moon on Treating Trauma)
I'll track him down right away.
The artwork isn't the same.
It's a mirror image.
Do you not remember the interview...
you did, sir?
You should call him Doctor. He likes that.
Doctor,
do you not remember the interview you gave...
20 years ago?
He can barely remember what happened two days ago.
Can we have the contact information for his family?
That would be a breach of his privacy.
But we're the police.
Let me first ask his family...
We'd appreciate that.
- Right now? - Yes, as soon as possible.
You see, we're working on a huge case.
Shall we head outside then?
Let me ask him one last time. Detective Oh, give her a hand.
Sure. Shall we?
But I should be with him.
Your beauty must reflect your kindness.
Once you upload a photo of you and Dong Baek online,
- you'll become a star. - Really?
You're going to scan his memory?
- Stand guard. - But he has dementia.
What if you get caught?
Are you getting something?
The documentary.
Doctor. Doctor?
No support is given to the victims.
Individuals shouldn't have to deal with the healing process...
all by themselves.
Dr. Nam advocates the need for a support system.
He insists that the government should be involved.
This crime took away her father from her.
It proves that there are more victims...
than the ones who were directly hurt.
Children especially...
- Children... - suffer serious PTSD.
suffer serious...
It's not something an individual can handle on one's own.
We're setting up the cameras.
We'll start as soon as everything's ready.
This crime took away her father from her.
It proves that there are more victims...
than the ones who were directly hurt.
No.
I didn't finish coloring yet.
- Did you see something? - A drawing.
I saw the sketch from the murder scene.
Where?
The girl in the documentary drew the same thing.
- This? - The outer frame was similar.
The scene of the murder was inside a long frame.
But that girl's drawing was the same.
It was the shape of a vase.
Did the girl from 20 years ago commit the murders?
- I don't know what's... - She saw something huge.
That girl So Mi.
- Who? - Kim So Mi.
She was there when her dad was murdered.
What happened to her?
Whenever she had a panic attack,
she trembled in fear...
and recited the same prayer over and over.
A prayer?
A prayer to...
a guardian angel.
A guardian angel.
Angel of the Lord
My guardian dear
To whom
- His love commits me here - To whom His love commits me here
Ever this day be at my side
To light and guard
To rule and guide
Amen!
Let's go.
- I haven't spoken to the family... - I'm done.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you. Good night.
May I get a picture? I like you.
Why aren't they coming out?
They're coming.
Get down.
Got it.
Kim So Mi was adopted by a couple in the US after her dad's murder.
- Anything else? - It was so long ago.
I can only get the basics. We'll have to check the case file.
They store cold cases in Seoul, right?
Let's go to Metro. Give me the car key.
You have it. You drove earlier...
When did it end up here?
What is it?
Keyhole.
- What hole? - That vase shape.
It was a keyhole.
What are you talking about?
She watched her dad die through a keyhole.
- I saw that keyhole before. - Where?
I'm not sure. In the memory of someone I touched in passing.
Who?
Take the old man to Metro and stay there.
- Tell us who it was. - Later.
Where are you going? There are no cars on the road!
There is a car!
That punk always leaves out the important part.
I'll tail them. You go upstairs and find out what they were doing.
- Go home once you're done. - But...
- Must I worry about your ride? - That's not it.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hey. You jerk. - Hey.
- Hey. - Get out!
Stop the car! You punk!
You jerk!
Please, pick up!
(Officer Dong Baek)
The person you have reached is not available. Please leave...
Yes, ma'am.
Send backup to Yeom Hwa Ran's vacation house.
Operations Center. Sergeant Lee Seul Bi.
Hey, it's Dong Baek. Where's Superintendent Han?
Superintendent Han?
Locate her now. She's in danger.
She's at the murder scene. Yeom Hwa Ran's vacation house.
What?
She followed a lead and is standing by alone.
Send backup right away.
I've already sent them.
But the closest station is 15 minutes away...
Send everyone! It's a trap!
A trap?
The person who was planning to move there had a stroke.
So it's been empty for a year.
Darn it.
It's a trap.
It's a corpse.
Angel of the Lord
My guardian dear
To whom
- His love commits me here - To whom His love commits me here
Ever this day be at my side
To light and guard
- To rule and guide - To rule and guide
- Amen. - Amen.
Amen!
(Memorist)
Do you know the juvenile double jeopardy case?
Six years ago, a little girl who was an orphan died.
And the culprits turned out to be middle school girls.
An execution-style murder.
Punishing evil by becoming evil themselves.
The exact same thing is happening again.
It's just like what happened 20 years ago.
The special team has no records of it at all?
The person in charge of the investigation...
- What? - It's someone close by.
Someone who's high up.
That's pretty close by.
It's him.