(Why are you following me?)
(Episode 9)
Let me see.
Okay.
There you go.
It's yours now.
My lucky ring.
Hong Jo.
I like you.
Oh, really?
You mean you like Hong Jo, right?
You.
- What?
- Hong Jo...
likes you, too.
I guess he talks to you.
Then can you tell Hong Jo...
not to splatter the sand
in his bathroom?
Goodnight.
What was that?
My heart almost fluttered.
Gosh, I almost had a heart attack.
This wasn't here before.
Do you work here?
Yes, I own the place.
Can I have some coffee at your cafe?
We're closed already. I'm sorry.
Then maybe next time.
Hong Jo, come here.
("Cats want to come inside
if you send them outside.")
("And if you bring them inside,
they want to go outside.")
("And sometimes,
they want to do both.")
My gosh.
What?
Why isn't the hot water coming out?
Guk Bong.
Are you sleeping?
I'm sorry.
But I think the boiler is broken.
A woman?
I don't think
I can wash my hair today.
You're leaving already?
Is someone here?
Who?
I'm going to leave early
because I have a lot of work to do.
So you can relax
and enjoy your time.
Let's leave together.
I also have a part-time job.
- You're just going to leave?
- What?
Are you worried about Hong Jo?
I guess you're also a guy.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Wait up.
A skinny woman with long hair?
I thought he'd be different
from other guys.
But I guess he's just the same.
Guys all like
the same type of women.
My gosh, what am I saying?
Why do I feel so weird?
(Jae Seon)
Let's meet tonight.
Thanks.
But why did you want to see me?
I want to apologize.
I was really mean to you last time.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that?
Doo Sik told me...
that you went around
searching for the cat.
I heard you even dug up a hole.
I really had no idea.
You're not the type of person...
who'd leave the cat outside
all by himself.
You'd never do that.
But...
you did.
That's weird.
I always close the door,
but he always escapes.
- He escapes?
- Yes.
But he never goes too far away.
I think he also thinks of this place
as his turf.
Isn't it okay?
You can also
take care of Hong Jo sometimes.
No, it's too dangerous.
You should take him home.
Okay.
Wait.
If you suddenly approach him,
he'll get startled and run away.
- I'll get him for you.
- Okay.
You need to be really slow.
Just leave him be.
He'll find his way home.
No, I'll get him for you.
You should go home first.
I'll get him for you.
Hong Jo.
Where are you hiding? Come on out.
You want to play hide-and-seek?
Wait.
I found you.
I think I left some cat treats
somewhere around here.
- Mr. Bang?
- I think this is mine.
No, I don't think so.
Yes, it's mine.
It belongs to someone else.
Please give it back.
Whose is it?
I'm sorry,
but I'm a little busy right now.
Did you happen to see a cat?
He went home.
But he was here just now.
I'll ask Sol Ah.
No, don't.
It's still somewhere near.
Why do you care if he's home or not?
Just leave him alone.
He's not even your cat.
I think of him like he's mine.
I was the one who found him.
Back then,
he was just a little kitten.
He was wrapped around
in that scarf...
and abandoned out in the cold.
Does he think Sol Ah was the one
who abandoned me?
Who abandoned me?
It's all in the past.
(Take him if you want.)
(Sol Ah)
And that's how
it ended between us.
I'll take that.
The owner threw it away.
(Why are you so silent?)
Quit running away
and tell the truth.
Why can't it be me?
Why can't I mean anything to you?
Tell me.
Please, tell me so I can understand.
She abandoned you.
Am I...
the reason?
What are you looking at?
Did you decide to draw
"Beodul Love" again?
Don't look. It's not ready yet.
What if there was
a misunderstanding?
What?
Would the two be happy...
once their misunderstanding
gets resolved?
I'm not sure.
Don't you want to know
why he suddenly...
shut the door?
I used to be curious.
But not anymore.
You're the one who told me...
that he'll always keep me waiting.
The reason doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is that he kept me
waiting for 10 years.
You liked him for 10 years?
Hey, enough about me.
Let's talk about you.
You have...
a girlfriend, don't you?
You don't?
Then you did that
when you don't even like her?
You're a lot more carefree
than I thought.
But then again, this is your house,
so I guess you can do
whatever you want.
But shouldn't you at least
give me a heads up?
What are you talking about?
I told you everything about me,
but you never tell me anything.
I admit that I tend to be
a little chatty.
But...
I don't just go around
telling everyone how I feel.
I feel like you know
too much about me now.
Are you seriously not
going to tell me anything?
Then I won't let you
peek on me anymore.
To a cat, 10 years is
almost a lifetime.
Because of me,
their love could never come true.
And I'm the only one who knows
about their misunderstanding.
I should tell them that it was
a misunderstanding, right?
I should do that for Sol Ah, right?
But if I tell them the truth,
what will happen to me?
You're not the only one
who has a private life.
(Bang Guk Bong, do not enter!)
I should tell her today.
Hong Jo, where are you?
Who...
Who are you?
Did you just come out of that room?
Oh, you're her boyfriend?
Is that why...
Is that why she put up that sign?
My name is Bang Guk Bong.
The owner of this house...
is my mother.
I should go now.
I need to take a shower.
Let's eat.
I need to go to the toilet.
My gosh, darn it.
Did you sleep well?
Bang Guk Bong.
Is this yours?
Then whose is this?
Did you cook this for me?
What's the occasion?
You felt bad, didn't you?
Thanks a lot.
The water's cold again.
Bang Guk Bong.
I don't have hot water.
Is it hot upstairs?
What?
Your hair's soft.
You must've showered.
Can I use your shower?
I groom...
Hey, wait! Wait.
Why come up here?
- I need to shower too.
- No.
Why? What's wrong?
No. Don't do this.
Why? What are you doing? Get out.
My gosh. What's the matter?
What a stink.
Is this why
you didn't want me in here?
You should've said so.
I need to shower. Go away.
My goodness.
My egg yolks.
Are you going to work?
Yes.
Good, good. Get going.
- My coat.
- Your coat. I'll get it.
Your coat. Your coat.
Your coat.
You don't have to help me with it.
I can manage on my own.
Let's go.
There.
What got into you today?
It's okay. I'm not angry anymore.
Have a good day.
Okay. Bye.
- My bag.
- Your bag.
Your bag. Your bag.
Your bag.
Here you go. Anything else?
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- My lip gloss.
- Lip gloss!
Lip gloss, lip gloss. Lip gloss.
It's all done. I should
say hi today.
What are you doing?
Shouldn't you leave?
I put it on all crooked.
Get out already.
You look just fine.
You're pretty. Really pretty.
What?
You'll be late.
You should go. Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Bye. Bye!
What did I just do?
She left already?
I keep missing her.
What is your name?
Hong Jo.
Hong's your surname
and you're called Jo?
As in Joe?
Relax. I won't tell my parents.
Do you have to hide it, though?
Isn't that uncomfortable?
I didn't mean to hide it
in the beginning.
I like her...
and want to be with her.
I know.
You're hiding it
to protect something,
but if you hide too much,
you can't protect anything.
I'll stop hiding.
I'll leave.
What?
What I meant was...
Sorry for intruding.
Excuse me? Hey.
Did I leave my phone at home again?
Hello. Good morning.
Who are you?
Mirror.
What is this?
This is just insane.
What distracted you this morning?
I don't know. I left
my phone at home too.
It was buy 1 get 1 free today.
Oh? Thanks.
- Hello.
- Ji Eun.
Let's have some tea.
Oh, okay.
They went out again.
They do that too often.
Oh, you're here? Okay.
Is that ready?
Oh, yes.
Here you go.
The tone and mood
are nice and modern.
My nephew will like it. Thanks.
But now my kid's homeroom
teacher's getting married.
Just switch the names
on this wedding invitation.
Okay.
Oh, yes. But that's not my...
Oh. Yes, that's true.
Yes, don't worry. We'll do that.
Sol Ah?
Yes?
The CEO character on the landscaping
company's logo needs changing.
Oh, okay.
- This?
- Yes.
He wanted it to look just like him,
but now he says it's an insult
to the balding population.
It needs to be fixed right now
so that he won't fly into a rage.
But this project was...
Ji Eun was in charge of that.
She can't work on something...
this minor when
she's on a huge project.
Sol Ah, you do it.
I'm going out for a lunch meeting
with a client.
Wait. Ms. Park.
Ms. Park.
It was my project. Let me...
It's fine. You have something
more important to work on.
You always end up
with smaller tasks.
What kind of connection
does Ji Eun have with Ms. Park...
There she comes.
- Let's go.
I feel so bad for you.
You can't even eat lunch.
It's okay. You should go eat.
- Okay.
- See you.
How long did it take...
for you to get used to
living outdoors?
I'm hoping it won't take long...
since I also started out
as a stray cat.
I'm the one who caused
the misunderstanding,
so I should help them resolve it.
And I'm tired...
of hiding who I am.
How weird.
I'm hungry.
But why does my heart feel so empty?
Would you like some?
How weird.
My heart feels so empty.
What?
Then how would you have felt?
Your heart must've felt so empty
for 10 whole years.
Are you...
talking to me?
You must've felt so lonely.
It must've been so difficult.
Don't cry.
You're making me cry as well.
There.
Let's put a fedora on him
since there's not much time.
(Shiny and sparkly, Sunlighting)
There we go.
Is that the woman with long hair?
10 years...
is a very long time.
I'm okay.
Eun Ji Eun was the woman
with long hair?
Thanks.
But...
did you come here to give me this?
I think I should tell you.
There's something I didn't tell you.
Tell me?
What couldn't you tell me?
What is it?
I...
I'm...
not Bang Guk Bong.
What?
I'm not Bang Guk Bong.
What do you mean?
What was that about?
He just had to say
he's dating Ji Eun.
Why would he deny his existence?
I thought she was a quiet cat,
but she's dating my housemate.
She must hate me.
When did they get so close?
She already thinks
I told Ms. Park...
about her webtoon.
This meeting isn't getting anywhere.
How about a chat as an ice-breaker?
Shall we discuss the weather?
Ji Eun.
You're seeing someone, aren't you?
I hoped to discuss
fine dust particles.
I'm not.
Then do you have...
anything you want to tell me?
Well...
Not really.
You know,
like, do you have feelings
for someone I know?
Let's stop talking about...
private matters when we're at work.
It's getting more frigid
by the second.
I need to go out to breathe.
How about we be friends
away from work?
Since it came up,
how about starting today?
Can we try to get along?
We must work together on a project.
You can pick the location.
I'll meet you anywhere.
(Sonamu)
Does it have to be here?
Excuse me?
Can I have some ice?
Wait here.
Yes, of course.
Jae Seon. I'm here.
Hey. Hong Jo's here too, inside.
Hong Jo?
This...
This is...
Why is this here?
I know.
What is this doing here?
This is my scarf.
Right?
Why do you have it?
I found it.
After you threw it away.
I never threw it away.
You probably didn't know,
but that kitten you threw away.
It was Hong Jo.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
You wrapped him up in that scarf
and abandoned him.
In a garbage dump.
You must be mistaken.
I wrapped this scarf
around a boy.
You know,
the day we were supposed to meet,
he was wandering around in the cold.
I'm on my way home after work.
Oh, really?
Okay, see you later.
Even the weather is on my side.
Kid.
What are you doing here?
I needed to get him somewhere warm,
so I brought him home
so I could look for his mom.
But he suddenly vanished,
and I looked everywhere for him.
You wrapped the scarf...
around a boy?
But...
Hong Jo was found with this scarf?
What happened?
He must've been a kind boy.
He was cold too,
but he covered Hong Jo with it.
I don't know what's going on.
I think I do now.
Why you were like that to me.
The person you have reached
is unavailable. Please leave...
(Where are you? Is something wrong?)
I think I was mistaken...
No.
It's not because of that.
It's because that's who you are,
Jae Seon.
That's who you are.
You always do things alone.
You think alone,
and always draw conclusions alone.
You never ask me.
That's who you are.
And that's the way you treat me.
You mentioned the scarf before...
to test me, didn't you?
You should've just told me
the truth.
You should've gotten mad
and asked me instead.
Didn't I ask you
to please talk to me?
I didn't know I was mistaken
about this either...
Wasn't it an excuse?
You were afraid to open up to me,
and you saw an abandoned cat
in front of you.
It was the perfect excuse.
An excuse to push me away.
An excuse to be alone until the end.
You pushed away everyone near you
like that, didn't you?
In case you fell in love.
I'll take this.
Am I late?
Oh, right.
We were supposed to meet.
I don't feel like drinking coffee
right now.
Then, next time.
By any chance...
How about a drink?
He prefers to do things alone
so much,
that there's no room left for me
to squeeze into his life.
He's all alone. A total loner.
Wait.
You drank alone again?
I guess Lee Jae Seon...
is someone who thinks
on his own a lot.
Right?
I knew it. A cat knows
another cat so well!
Cheers. Cheers!
Sorry.
Still, aren't you glad to find out
he was mistaken?
I'm not sure.
Now that I know,
I feel even more dumbfounded.
That he was more alone
than I thought.
That I was totally mistaken
thinking there was...
something between us
even when he didn't say anything.
But...
why are you...
telling me this?
Do I sound so pathetic?
No.
What should I say?
Isn't it a secret?
Don't friends share secrets?
See?
We're talking comfortably now.
We're friends.
Friends...
You can really hold your liquor.
Why does it feel like
I'm the only one getting drunk?
Beer just makes me feel full.
Oh, really?
Ma'am? Can we have some soju?
Here.
Now, it's your turn
to share your secret.
What's your relationship
with Ms. Park?
It's just that people at work
seem to be mistaken about you.
I don't think that's true.
I didn't use connections
to work here.
I never mentioned
your webtoon either.
Right?
I knew it.
Then what do you two talk about
all the time?
What is it?
Well, if it's hard to tell me...
Let's talk about guys.
You like someone, don't you?
I'm kind of like you.
It's been a long time...
since I've had a crush on him.
We keep getting close
then fall apart.
For how long?
Since high school.
That long?
Then you must know
everything about him.
No.
I didn't see him after graduating...
but met him again by coincidence.
I see him almost every day lately.
But even when we're together,
it doesn't seem like I'm with him.
I understand. He comes and goes
like the wind.
So you noticed.
Actually,
I saw you two on the bench today.
On the bench?
Yes.
Oh, him?
It's not him. That guy...
I'd never met.
What?
Why would you do that to a stranger?
He seemed hungry,
so I offered him food.
You never slept over at my place?
What do you mean?
Never mind.
Then...
who is the person you like?
I did all the talking again.
We should go now.
Let's go.
Ko Doo Sik.
I like him.
You had too much to drink.
I'll hail you a cab.
- No, no. You can go first.
- No.
- Be quiet.
Trust me. I'll catch you a taxi.
No. You go home first.
Taxi!
- You go home first.
- Taxi!
- Go home.
- Don't stop here, taxi.
- Don't stop.
- Stop!
Stop, stop. There.
- You take it.
- No.
No, no. You...
Get in.
It's fine. I live nearby.
I can walk.
- Bye.
- Take care.
Sol Ah.
- This one.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing? Tell me.
- Why did it turn off?
- Sol Ah.
- Take a photo.
- Sol Ah, come here.
- I need to get the license plate.
- Sol Ah.
- Take a photo.
- What are you doing?
Take a photo.
No, no. Again.
Click. I did it!
I got a photo. Get home safely!
Driver, take her safely, please.
I can't leave you.
Sol Ah. Bye!
- Okay.
- Bye!
Okay, so now...
Now I have to get home.
I can do this. I can do this. I can.
You're doing it. You can do this.
Keep going.
Sol Ah, walk straight ahead. Okay!
Straight ahead. March.
Very nice. You're doing it.
You don't look drunk at all.
You're managing it.
Did I forget anything?
Let's see.
My wallet.
My phone.
My phone. My phone.
And... my scarf.
My scarf.
It's so warm.
Okay. I have everything!
You!
Hey! Go away!
That was crazy.
I didn't fall down.
How warm.
Perhaps I can never...
appear before you again.
I might have to...
look at you from behind.
If I stay this far behind,
will it be okay?
It was the perfect excuse.
An excuse to push me away.
An excuse to be alone until the end.
You pushed away everyone near you
like that, didn't you?
In case you fell in love.
I'm home.
It's fixed.
What's this?
Bang Guk Bong.
Bang Guk Bong!
I came to say goodbye.
I might not be able to
come by often.
Why not?
I told a lie.
Did you tell a bad lie?
Were you caught
and you're going to prison?
Does lying get you caught
and locked up?
Not always.
There are lies
that are okay to tell.
There are?
Don't you know about white lies?
Lies you tell because
you like someone...
aren't lies but good manners.
My grandma said so.
It's like that between people.
If I were a person,
- I wouldn't have to lie.
- What?
I have to lie to stay around.
Because I'm me.
That man is...
Hello.
Are you closed?
Did you just come out of that house?
Yes. I live in the house across.
My friend lives there.
Oh, a friend of yours?
Yes. Who are you?
I'm her stepbrother.
Who?
Another description would be
the landlady's son.
What...
Then are you...
Yes. I am Bang Guk Bong.
I'm glad you're friends.
I'll pay for her coffee in advance.
Tell her it's to celebrate
becoming a family.
Are you really Bang Guk Bong?
Yes.
Goodbye then.
I drank all this
and it's not enough.
Bang Guk Bong.
No.
You're not...
Bang Guk Bong, are you?
What have you done?
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry.
How could you lie to me?
I really am.
You're...
You're not Bang Guk Bong.
How could you not be Bang Guk Bong?
I wish...
- I were Bang Guk Bong.
- Don't lie!
Then why would you do this?
Who told you to change your name?
(Name changed to "Bang Cruise")
What?
I enjoyed calling your old name.
I want to keep calling you that.
Hello.
Long straight hair.
That's my taste.
It was a guy? What's going on?
Is he Bang Guk Bong's friend?
Or... are they dating?
Do you come here often?
Not often. Just sometimes.
I changed the light bulb.
I fixed the boiler too.
The water's hot now.
Why would you do all that?
I feel bad now.
You don't have to feel
so uncomfortable.
I'll stay with my girlfriend.
I was just about to leave.
You have a girlfriend.
Then he's just friends
with Bang Guk Bong?
You're way too pleased.
I am?
Tell the guy that
he doesn't have to leave.
What?
Who's leaving?
The guy you live with.
He talked about leaving.
You said you wouldn't leave.
- What?
- You got a new global name,
so you'll move abroad now?
"Bang Cruise"?
Hey.
Do you even know that's
Tom Cruise's surname, not his name?
I...
- Someone's here.
- You are...
Bang Guk Bong, whatever they say.
I am?
Can't you...
just go on...
being Bang Guk Bong?
Can I do that?
Can you...
not leave?
You.
Who are you?
(Welcome)
He's just like a cat.
He disappears and then appears.
- Didn't you find it weird?
- He gets me.
What are you really?
I would stay with Sol Ah.
Are you that close already?
How do you know this?
The first person I remember.
Will you disappear suddenly
like a cat too?
Why is it Sol Ah?
I know only one thing.
Sol Ah makes me human.