(All characters, organizations, places, entities, and events...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Please be aware of any unpleasant or unsettling content.)
What are you doing here?
It's my house.
How sick are you?
I'm just aching all over.
Nice.
- What? - You're finally resting.
This is your body telling you to slow down.
Have you eaten?
I bought some porridge, so don't worry.
At least change into something comfortable.
Did you look up at the sun on purpose again?
The duration between sneezes has gotten longer.
Maybe I can overcome this.
Don't force yourself since it'll only ruin your eyesight.
It annoys me to worry about sneezing...
every time I go from someplace dark to someplace bright.
What is it?
You've been annoyed by a lot of things these days.
Is something up?
It's just how teenagers are.
Anyway, get some sleep. I'll only drop off my book.
(It was so boring that I almost fell asleep.)
(My brain worked at full speed to figure out the perp, but failed.)
My mother might've raised me,
but my soul was enlightened by...
(My mother might've raised me, but my soul was enlightened by...)
(Episode 8)
("The Life Before Us")
(I can't tell you anything. But can you still help me?)
If...
by any chance,
something bad happens to me,
I don't ever want you to know.
Is that what you came to tell me?
You won't know unless I tell you.
I have nothing.
Same here.
Me too.
Nothing here either.
Gosh, my eyes are already killing me.
Stop whining, will you?
You'll know once you reach my age.
So what about your age?
Back in the day, I'd work for a week straight...
and recover after taking a dump...
and stretching in my seat.
Do you even know how old I am?
I look younger than my age, so I guess you might not know.
I look younger than my age. Don't take that away from me.
Sir.
Should I check the cabs...
that came to the hotel on the day of Eun Ho's accident?
Yes, go ahead.
I have Jang Ki Ho's call logs.
Since when was his cell phone turned off?
Four days before Seo Sang Won's death.
- And the location? - Nae-dong, Incheon.
That's where Jang Ki Ho lives.
Do you think his cell phone might be at his house...
just like Lee Young Sik, the guy who disappeared?
Yes, Ms. Cha.
Did you call forensics?
Okay, I'll tell him.
"Forensics"? What is it this time?
Sir, Ms. Cha went to Kevin Jung's house...
and found him dead.
What?
There are no fatal injuries.
("The Life Before Us")
If you guys had kept staying here,
you would've been able to stop this from happening.
- I'm sorry, sir. - I'm sorry, sir.
It's not their fault.
The only person at fault is the person who did this.
What's the cause of death?
I need to check something first.
How many times did he inject himself?
He took enough to kill himself.
You can take him now.
There weren't any fatal injuries on Kevin Jung's body.
Then did he die because he overdosed on meth?
And heroin.
There was white powder near his nose.
He did both?
I guess he wanted to die.
Do you die if you do them both together?
Meth stimulates your body and heroin calms you down.
If you mix and take them together,
it overstrains your heart.
Meth makes you feel invincible.
Heroin makes you feel high and hallucinate.
No one seems to have broken into his house.
And I couldn't find any signs of physical struggle on his body.
But it looked like Kevin Jung's hands were tied.
That means...
someone was involved in his death.
Isn't it obvious? I bet it was Lee Young Sik.
If Lee Young Sik was the one who killed him,
he probably gave him heroin first...
and then injected meth after he brought Kevin Jung home.
(Police)
Here's the CCTV footage of the entrance and the nearby alleys.
Thank you.
Yun Ja Young speaking.
Okay.
Lee Young Sik's place is empty.
Why was he holding the kid's bag?
What did these jerks do to him?
I want everyone back at the office. Let's have an emergency meeting.
Yes, sir.
Did you meet Ha Min Sung?
I didn't even get to talk to him.
- Why? - He got hurt.
Yes, ma'am. The doctor told me he's okay.
Oh, I see. Drive safely.
Okay, bye.
Min Sung, your mom will be here soon.
Okay.
Min Sung.
Do you still not remember what happened?
Let's go.
We'll leave you to get some rest.
He's probably shocked.
- Sun Woo. - Do you really think...
Dong Myung hurt him?
What are you talking about? You saw what happened.
I mean...
Min Sung can't remember anything.
And we didn't even ask Dong Myung.
If he didn't do anything, he would've said so already.
But he only told me one thing.
He didn't tell me that it wasn't him.
He just told me that he wants to follow the detective.
Sun Woo.
Let's not punish Min Sung for what he did.
For what he did?
You're going to stay quiet about the test leak?
The head of Administration will get disciplined.
For something else other than the test leak?
I'll make sure this doesn't happen again.
Okay?
Hello, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
Where's the student who did this?
He's getting investigated by the police.
I heard your brother's surgery went well.
- Yes. - I'll drop by pretty soon.
- It's okay. - What do you mean?
Don't let it bother you.
That means I'm also free to care.
Shall we begin?
You're okay now. I'm here for you.
Ma'am, I'm sorry to say this, but I need to go now.
Oh, right.
I'm sure you're busy with the foundation these days.
Thank you so much...
for bringing Min Sung all the way to the hospital.
Don't mention it. I only did what was right.
Min Sung, don't worry about anything and just get some good rest.
Okay. Bye, sir.
Mr. Lee, I'll leave you to take care of everything.
- Okay, sir. - Goodbye, ma'am.
I can't believe...
this happened to my son.
What do his parents do?
How could they not even come here to apologize?
Can we talk outside?
I bet he's not from a stable family.
- Mr. Lee. - Yes?
Will you please excuse us? I'd like to talk to my son.
Okay, I'll be outside.
Did he do this to you?
No?
What happened?
I took him to the science lab so we could talk about Eun Ho.
Did he follow you willingly?
No.
I dragged him there.
How?
I grabbed him by the arm.
What did you talk about once you got to the science lab?
I talked about his driver.
I told him that he was the one who hurt Eun Ho.
And I asked him if he was behind everything.
What did he say?
He acted like he was startled to hear...
that Eun Ho fell from the hotel.
Are you sure he wasn't actually startled?
I'm not sure.
He told me that Eun Ho probably fell from the hotel because of me.
Didn't Eun Ho jump because of you?
- What? - You were stealing money from him.
I saw it many times.
I would've wanted to jump...
if a hobo like you had stolen my money too.
You little...
You're right. I'm a hobo and a bully.
But...
even a guy like me has a friend.
Someone who almost died because of you.
I might continue to be a hobo,
but I'm going to stop being a bully...
so that Eun Ho doesn't get embarrassed by me.
If I could have things my way,
I'd beat you to a pulp.
But I won't.
Min Sung.
Be careful of your driver.
He's not even human.
Stop it!
I grabbed him by the collar and stopped him.
And that's when Detective Cha opened the door.
No one else would've believed me.
But Detective Cha believed it wasn't me...
without even asking me anything.
Did she?
I'll check.
You don't believe me.
The police can't make a decision based on one side of the story.
I must hear Min Sung's story too.
What if he lies?
I mean, he will lie.
No one saw us. Who would believe me?
Eun Ho himself said that he was pestering you?
That's fine. That will do.
I asked around.
He's still unconscious and his phone's missing.
Min Sung. Listen carefully.
Mix some lies in with the truth.
People suspect if you deny everything,
but with some truth mixed in, they'll believe you,
not Dong Myung's story.
It might leave a small mark,
but we can get over this.
Where will you go now?
I won't run away.
Okay. Get back safely.
My gosh. What a coincidence.
Hey.
It didn't work.
Did you follow me?
Yes, out of concern.
Why?
In case no one's on your side?
In that situation,
anyone would think you assaulted him.
But you didn't.
Who did that to him if I didn't?
There were just you two, so if it wasn't you, who would it be?
Why do you think it wasn't me?
I don't know. Your gaze and attitude?
My hunch is very accurate.
So? Am I wrong?
Am I right?
I don't care if I'm wrong.
I want to be on your side.
Being on one's side isn't about blaming someone.
It's about putting weight on...
That doesn't make sense.
You suddenly show up and say you're on my side?
You expect me to believe that?
You're Eun Ho's friend.
Should I say more?
You're also Han Sol's brother.
Dong Myung.
I would like to have...
something light to eat.
Will you come with me?
Let's go.
Come on.
(Millennium Hotel, New Life Foundation Chairman Baek Sang Ho)
(Kim Chang Su supplies food)
(Millennium)
(Murdered? Choi Dae Hoon, night-blindness)
(Kevin Jung, buyer, deceased)
(Ko Eun Ho saved Jang Ki Ho)
I'd like to be able to...
investigate the New Life Church.
I see. Okay.
Kevin Jung and Lee Young Sik's call histories.
We thoroughly checked the phone found at Kevin Jung's home.
Those are Lee Young Sik's. I emailed a copy too.
Good job.
I also have Jang Ki Ho's. Do you want it now?
Thank you.
Don't thank me. I'm doing my job.
Choi Dae Hoon.
Can we begin?
- Yes. - Yes.
How is Eun Ho?
He opens his eyes when strongly stimulated.
He should wake up soon.
Then most things should get solved.
Hey.
Don't glare at me.
I'll still work the case. Can't I even speak my mind?
Even if Eun Ho wakes up, it's likely that he won't know...
what went on around him.
For example, how would he know who killed...
Choi Dae Hoon who died after his fall?
We must find that out.
Pretend he's not here and begin.
Less than an hour after we left,
Kevin Jung and Lee Young Sik showed up.
There were heroin particles in Kevin Jung's nostrils,
and methamphetamine injection marks on his arm.
There were scabs,
so he was injected about 30 minutes before.
So he was poisoned.
An accident, suicide, or murder. Which could it be?
It looks like Lee Young Sik was drugged too.
Did they mess up while injecting each other?
What's more important is...
why they had Eun Ho's backpack.
And why was it...
left with Kevin Jung's body?
Eun Ho didn't have that bag the day he fell.
These guys were after him for a while.
They found out where the 30,000 dollars went.
That's why they took Eun Ho's bag.
But the money wasn't there.
They threatened him for the whereabouts and he fell.
Choi Dae Hoon the accomplice...
was hanged for some unknown reason.
That's a clean tie-up.
But Choi Dae Hoon could not be an accomplice.
Don't just take the pieces...
that fit your conclusion...
and use everything and see if they fit.
Yes, sir.
It's the Eunpyeong-gu Office control room.
Hello?
Eungam-dong, 11:58?
To Seodaemun-gu?
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Lee Young Sik was last seen at 11:58 in Eungam-dong.
He only got that far in all that time?
Yes. He was on foot.
To Seodaemun-gu?
Yes. They called that office's control room already.
If he stays on foot, we can follow him in real-time.
Team 1, go to Seodaemun-gu Office.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Jang Ki Ho... - Team 2 will find him.
Okay.
(Millennium Hotel)
(Chairman Baek Sang Ho supports Shinsung Middle School)
Hurry up.
What's this?
Follow me.
Why won't you get in?
What floor to, sir?
You live here alone?
What?
I share it with family-like friends.
I don't invite just anyone here.
- How is it? - It's nice.
It's large and spacious.
Isn't it a bother if the toilet's far away?
I never thought about that.
I should move.
Serve him.
Is this a light meal?
I said I'd eat light,
but you didn't say anything.
Bring that over.
Shall we dig in?
(Cup noodles)
You can start. I have to wait for three minutes.
I might as well tell you when you're smiling.
About what?
Did you meet the guy who looks after Eun Ho?
- No. - His name is Kim Tae Hyung.
He works for my foundation.
Stories of his childhood remind me a lot about you.
He was framed and kicked out of school.
He's a good kid,
but the heartless world and cruel adults...
turned him thorny and hostile.
He had no expectations for the world...
or hope in mankind,
and was just wasting his life.
I saw him for what he could be.
I knew he could change if he worked with us.
So...
how did he change?
I can trust him around Eun Ho.
Was that explanation not enough?
No. It's more than enough.
And three minutes have passed.
Don't you lie to me.
It's cooked.
You can eat. Eat up.
You were there when Eun Ho was awarded, right?
Did you hear my speech?
Yes. It was entertaining.
I didn't know it was true.
The different between human beings and animals.
Human beings protect the weak if they're stronger...
and that's why you wanted to gain power.
I didn't believe it back then.
I'm Chief Hwang In Bum,
and I'm in charge of your son and Dong Myung's case.
He must've done something terrible...
for a high-ranking officer...
to take this case.
Well, I happened to have met the boy before.
Anyway, could I please have a moment with your son?
He's also aware of the case involving Min Sung's driver.
This is just my opinion,
but Min Sung would feel more comfortable talking to him too.
Go ahead then.
Dong Myung dragged me to the science lab,
but I don't remember what happened in the lab.
You don't remember what you two talked about either?
He mentioned Eun Ho out of the blue...
saying that he fell from a hotel rooftop.
Then he accused Uncle Dae Hoon...
and spoke ill of him.
It must've made you angry...
and upset.
I don't know.
I was startled, that's all.
It seems like your driver was responsible for hurting Eun Ho.
Min Sung,
did your driver lay his hands on Eun Ho...
for your sake?
Eun Ho once told Dong Myung...
that he was making you suffer.
Is that true?
Yes, Eun Ho made me give him money...
and said nasty things.
Why...
Why did you let him?
Because Dong Myung had his back.
So that's why you told your driver.
He said he'd only scare him a little.
It must've been scary for you.
You probably had no idea...
what happened between Eun Ho and your driver.
It must've been driving you insane.
However,
you still don't seem at ease though.
Min Sung,
if you lie because it's easier...
and less scary than telling the truth...
What on earth are you saying?
I'm sorry, but I must ask this.
Telling lies because it's easier...
and less scary than telling the truth...
will make you cross a bridge...
that will only make your life harder.
Please leave.
Thank you anyway.
You too, Mr. Lee.
Until next time then.
It was me.
It wasn't Dong Myung.
I...
did this to myself.
Shut it!
Thank you for telling me.
He still didn't tell me why Eun Ho was bothering him.
Is there anything you can think of?
I'm actually the one...
who's stuck between telling an easy lie...
and saying the uncomfortable truth.
We all experience that once or twice in life.
I doubt that applies to you.
I've also told a lie to the world.
- Do you regret it? - Not at all.
The lie was to protect someone else.
I'm sure that's the case with Min Sung as well.
Then what are you protecting...
that's making you weigh the burden of the truth?
Beats me.
I don't even know that myself.
If you're fine with having an old man as a drinking buddy,
we should grab a drink sometime.
Sounds good. I'll be waiting for your call.
- I'll get going then. - Have a good day, sir.
You too.
(Hyeju Hospital)
Hold on a second.
Take this with you.
Take it. You shouldn't be empty-handed.
Thank you.
Dong Myung.
Call me whenever you want.
Not even the kindest, sweetest person in the world...
can...
replace you for him.
Eun Ho.
Eun Ho, can you hear me?
My gosh.
I don't know why I'm nervous about this.
Eun Ho.
What I wish for the most...
is for you to wake up...
and to hear you call me...
"Mom."
I've finally realized that it's a blessing...
to have someone call me that.
People don't change overnight,
but...
I'll try my best from now on.
Come in.
Your friend said he'd swing by.
Hold on.
Yes?
Are you Dong Myung?
- Yes. - Come on in.
Is that for us?
Yes.
This is too generous of you.
Chairman Baek bought it for me.
Oh, I see.
You should...
enjoy this with us when his caregiver gets here.
Sure.
Come on and have a seat.
I'd like to see Eun Ho first.
Of course.
How long have you been friends?
Last winter.
I'm sorry.
Eun Ho went through a lot because of me.
Yes, I heard.
I heard you're his best friend.
Yes.
I need to go to work now.
Can you take care of him while I'm gone?
- Sure. - Thanks.
I'll see you again.
Okay.
Min Sung purposely hurt himself today.
I feel like I'll end up taking the blame for it.
But Mr. Baek promised to help.
He's a little weird,
but he seems like a good person.
Eun Ho, I'll be back after I talk to Han Sol.
You want me to hurry?
I can't get there in a second.
I'll be right there. Just wait for a little.
Eun Ho.
You saved my life today,
and this is as precious as my life.
If you keep this for me...
until I come back for it,
I promise I'll repay you.
It won't take too long.
I promise.
Eun Ho.
Ko Eun Ho.
If you can hear me, please open your eyes.
Come on.
Lord, the healer of all illnesses.
Please take a look at this boy, Ko Eun Ho,
and heal him...
with your strength to rescue us.
Please show...
your miracles through this boy.
Isn't it tormenting to always hear someone read you a book?
Let me help you cleanse your ears.
Here it is.
It's 2:32pm, and he's heading to Seodaemun.
That's two hours ago. Where is he going?
(New Life Church)
(Kwon Jae Chun, Seo Sang Won, Im Hee Jung)
(Ko Eun Ho, Jang Ki Ho)
The more I investigate, the more it feels like I'm walking into a maze.
All mazes...
are escapable as long as you don't give up.
It wasn't that long ago when you told me to give up.
I thought you were at a dead end.
It looked like you were going around in circles...
trying to solve a case that had no way out.
Do your best as a cop.
But don't think of it as the most important task...
of your entire life.
Okay.
- Where is Dong Myung? - I sent him home.
By the way, why did you tell him...
that you knew it wasn't him before even checking anything?
I found multiple bloodstains on the wall.
Dong Myung was holding Min Sung's collar from the back.
And it's impossible to hurt him like that from there.
But still,
you can't just say that in front of the kids...
before even carrying out an investigation.
Right. I made a mistake.
Min Sung already told me that he was the one who hurt himself.
There was a scar on the back of his hand as well.
I don't think he wanted to hurt Dong Myung or anything.
Min Sung also looks like he's going through a lot.
But...
I still need to meet him in person and ask him some questions.
Yes, of course.
- Good luck. - Thanks.
Hey.
They found a total of 12 fingerprints on his bag.
Apart from yours and Eun Ho's, there were 10 fingerprints.
(National Forensic Service)
But there are only six identified people.
The rest are probably his classmates.
This was from your book.
(National Forensic Service)
(Fingerprint Identification)
There are nine in total.
But among the seven apart from me and Eun Ho,
three are missing.
They're probably his classmates as well.
Why? What's bothering you?
(Accomplice? Ha Min Sung, Min Sung's driver)
(Shinsung Middle School)
Let's not punish Min Sung for what he did.
As a cop, I'm going to find out Min Sung's secret.
I'll leave you to choose...
what you're going to do as his teacher.
It must be difficult since you guys were so close.
Who told you that?
Who told you my driver and I were close?
It wasn't Dong Myung.
I did this to myself.
Both Min Sung and I...
still have a shot.
- Who are you? - What...
are you doing here?
Do you work here?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was so late.
I was just about to leave.
Someone recently died here.
Why were you looking that way?
Do you know Choi Dae Hoon?
Who's that?
- You're a cop, aren't you? - My gosh.
I'm not a cop. I should go now.
He was waiting for me.
I didn't kill Choi Dae Hoon.
Kevin Jung was the one who killed him.
It was Kevin Jung!
Wait.
It's a great privilege to have a choice.
You choose.
Kill me with that.
Or I'll kill you.
I knew it.
Let's go outside together.
Come outside and explain...
what you meant by what you just said.
No, wait. Wait.
You're Lee Young Sik, aren't you?
Do you not have a gun?
I met the devil.
What do you mean?
Getting out alive...
could be a curse.
Don't call it in. It's just a hassle.
Lee Young Sik. You're under arrest for attempted murder on Lee Sun Woo.
You can remain silent,
refuse to give an incriminating statement,
and hire a lawyer.
Ms. Cha.
Thank you.
Do you think they arrested him by now?
No way.
Or he was shot...
for having an episode around an officer.
We should've killed him.
How long do you think Lee Young Sik will be in that state?
I promised to let him live, so I should keep my word.
When the drugs wear off...
and he thinks of what happened that night,
that's when the real fear sets in.
- Watch him carefully. - Sure.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yes.
What made you come here?
I could've died if it hadn't been for you.
You wouldn't have died even if it hadn't been for me.
They got here too.
How did you know I'd be here?
It wasn't me.
No. I followed a suspect.
He was last seen an hour ago near Baekryeonsan Park.
(Baekryeonsan Park, 3:32)
(Baekryeonsan Park)
(Shinsung Middle School)
(Hongje 1-dong)
We're following him in real-time.
He passed the school onto Mugunghwa-ro.
- Towards the derelict building. - Yes.
We're over 15 minutes away. Shall I call for backup?
No.
I'm almost there.
I was surprised to see you here.
Not as surprised as I was.
Why were you here?
Because of you.
- Pardon? - You told me to decide...
what choice to make as a teacher.
I came to find the answer.
Here?
I thought that...
if I were here, I could think only of Eun Ho and Min Sung.
Ms. Cha, we can go.
I'll get your statement tomorrow.
See a doctor.
Thank you.
And...
You're Dong Myung?
Yes.
Let's eat.
What? Is it because of Eun Ho?
I'm not hungry.
I had a hearty meal.
On which floor?
The 10th floor.
Already?
I'm jealous.
It took me a long time to get up there.
Is it just me who thinks...
we're wasting time?
You want to know what I was like.
Quit hesitating and ask away.
I used to take from the weaker kids,
steal from others,
and worked as a voice phishing transporter.
My dad's in prison,
and today I was questioned for assaulting a kid...
I didn't even touch.
What about you?
That opening makes it easier.
My life was similar to yours.
In high school, I was charged for assaulting my homeroom teacher.
I quit school.
Did you really hit your teacher?
I was beating up a kid who had framed me for stealing.
The teacher got in the way.
Are you anxious that...
someone like me is caring for Eun Ho?
- Yes. - What about you?
- Do you think he's safe with you? - What?
If you can't trust me because of my past,
others will think the same of you.
Eun Ho...
doesn't like sweet things.
But for a strange reason, he likes cakes.
Then let's give the cake to the nurses.
Okay.
- Eun Ho saved someone's life? - Yes.
Did he tell you who that person was?
No.
But that person...
wants to meet Eun Ho.
Does he? How do you know that?
An old man was waiting outside our school.
The guy couldn't come in person.
He gave me a phone number.
He asked Eun Ho to call.
A phone number?
He didn't know Eun Ho was hurt,
so I took the note.
- Do you have it now? - Yes.
Did he say why he couldn't come himself?
No.
I guess he's not well yet.
I won't be long.
(Chairman Baek Sang Ho)
(New message)
(Kim Tae Hyung)
Tae Hyung, what number is this?
Well done.
You did well.
What's the matter?
- I think I've found Jang Ki Ho. - What?
I just knew that...
he'd be trying to get to Eun Ho.
He sent someone to the school to look for the boy.
And...
he even left a phone number.
All right. Let me now call that said number.
Here we go.
0, 1, 0, 4, 0, 3...
What? Do you recognize the number?
I already have it saved on my phone.
Who does it belong to?
Goodness.
Sir.
What do you mean it's a surprise?
Friends shouldn't have a reason to call each other.
- Where are you at the moment? - The diner we last went to.
Don't you need more money for the meal?
I'm sure it's running out.
Well, I've been frugal.
My gosh.
I'll pay more than the amount I paid last time.
Really?
May you be blessed.
Anyway, have you still...
not heard from Jang Ki Ho?
I'm afraid I have no updates.
I see. All right.
Enjoy your dinner then.
(Restricted Area)
Let us check what you just said.
- We're good. - Sure.
Kevin Jung was the mastermind. Is that correct?
I want a verbal answer.
- Yes. - He didn't tell you...
how he found out that Eun Ho took the money.
He ordered you to bring back the backpack,
but after seeing that the money wasn't in it,
he ordered you to go after the boy.
Kevin Jung introduced you to Choi Dae Hoon...
and Choi Dae Hoon was hired to collect the money.
Where's the money?
Where's the 30,000 dollars?
Darn it.
Getting greedy over money already?
You punk.
I'll ask you one last time.
Where's the 30,000 dollars?
Where is it?
Tell me. Where is it?
Then Choi Dae Hoon drove his car...
and came to the derelict building?
Is that correct?
Answer me verbally.
Yes.
Things escalated,
and Kevin Jung and Choi Dae Hoon began to fight.
To calm down,
Choi Dae Hoon drank the beverage Kevin Jung brought...
and lost consciousness.
Move.
You were too high two days ago...
to know where you were.
Kevin Jung came by and you did heroin together.
Then you went to his house...
and injected him with meth per his request.
Before you knew it, Kevin Jung stopped breathing.
Is that what happened?
Yes.
What do you two think?
There's a critical error in his statement.
Yes, that Choi Dae Hoon drove his car at night.
- That's right. - So?
It seems like Choi Dae Hoon was added...
just to fit his made-up story.
He knows what basically happened,
but not the details.
So the culprit is still out there?
I don't know...
if he could take the fall.
Back at the building, he said he met the devil.
Someone could be behind all this.
Someone who knows the outlines of this case,
but not about the fact that Choi Dae Hoon has night blindness.
It seems like Choi Dae Hoon was added...
just to fit his made-up story.
"I'm the one who's making his life hard."
That's what Eun Ho said.
He said that he was the one who was making Min Sung suffer.
Min Sung,
look at me.
I'm Cha Young Jin of...
Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency's Homicide Team One.
Are you Min Sung's mother?
The detective who came by today heard everything,
so ask him.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you hurting yourself?
Just beat up others instead.
It's better than being branded as a nutcase.
Don't touch that.
Nothing went smoothly since you were born.
Do you have any idea how much we poured into your treatment?
And we're only getting started.
Say something!
I'll stop.
I really will.
Darn it!
Are you in the bathroom?
A friend of Eun Ho's brought it by.
- Sleep well then. - Thanks.
For those who believe
The Lord spoke
In a few days
We will meet after crossing the Jordan River
Ki Ho, it's me.
Open up.
Who are you? Show yourself.
It's me, Baek Sang Ho.
Gosh, I almost had a heart attack.
Why did you startle me like that?
You startled me as well.
I can't believe you were secretly hiding Jang Ki Ho here.
Wait. Let me explain.
- Take him away. - Hey, listen to me.
Ki Ho.
(Nobody Knows)
Ki Ho, it's been so long.
I was going to tell you at the right time.
You went to New Life Church for a long time, right?
I'm guessing you know Jang Ki Ho.
You should ask Sun Woo.
Why does he need to get transferred?
He did nothing wrong!
Mr. Lee!
Jang Ki Ho gave something to Eun Ho.
And his bag disappeared after that.
That means someone's looking for what Jang Ki Ho gave him.
The person who's after that is probably the one...
who's behind all this.
Poor thing.
Do you want me to kill you?
Tell me everything you know about Jang Ki Ho.
Han Sol! Han Sol!
Where are you?
Was it because of Dong Myung?
Or was there something else?