(All characters, organizations, places, entities, and events...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Please be aware of any unpleasant or unsettling content.)
Don't be scared.
I'm here to save you.
Your painful life might've made you crumble,
but my love will get you back on your feet.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Eun Ho.
I'm tired.
Thank you...
for being alive.
Young Jin.
Are you awake?
What about the plant?
Is it still alive?
Why are you crying?
Mom, what are you doing here?
Goodness.
My gosh.
Eun Ho!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Eun Ho...
Was I injured?
Don't you remember?
No.
It's all right, Eun Ho. It's fine.
I'll bring his doctor.
No, let me.
I might blurt out everything...
when I shouldn't.
Let me go instead.
I'll go.
The plant is doing fine.
It won't die just because you didn't water it once.
Once?
Then is the calendar on the wrong page?
What date...
should it be to you?
Not date, but month.
I'm missing a month from my life.
(Episode 11)
The conversation between
Inspector Cha and Seo Sang Won are still unknown.
Many speculate that Inspector Cha took out...
her personal grudge on him...
Sang Ho, Eun Ho's awake.
She could've abused her power to...
Wait here.
The ninth killing in the serial murders...
Let's see.
Can you wiggle your toes for me?
Good.
- You'll soon be going home. - Thank you.
Short-term memory loss usually resolves itself,
so don't stress too much about it.
Please let me know if anything's uncomfortable.
Of course. Thank you.
- Doctor. - Yes?
My memories...
Could they be gone forever?
I'm not sure. It's not exactly my area of expertise.
Another doctor will see you tomorrow.
Get some rest then.
Right. Thank you, doctor.
Doctor.
Yes?
You can go ahead.
Is there no particular cure for memory loss?
Amnesia isn't my area of expertise.
What I do know...
is that the patient shouldn't be asked any stressful questions.
I hear you.
Also, about what you have just told me.
Are you also going to tell Mr. Baek this?
Pardon?
Haven't you been...
reporting to him about Eun Ho's condition?
Yes, he paid for his hospital bills.
Yes, of course. He's probably dying to know.
Tell him everything about Eun Ho's condition including...
the fact that he can't recall what happened during the past month.
Tell Mr. Baek...
that Eun Ho unfortunately won't be able...
to recognize him.
Nothing got damaged, so it's probably dissociative amnesia.
There aren't any treatments for this kind of amnesia.
He could suddenly remember everything...
or slowly remember bit by bit.
Or he might never remember what happened.
(Neurologist, Park Sung Jin)
Someone's here to see me.
No problem. Okay.
You're here.
I was just about to call you.
Were you talking to someone more important than me?
It's just a friend from high school.
He can't remember what happened during the past month?
That means he can't remember Jang Ki Ho.
But Jang Ki Ho will remember him.
Chairman Yun, what brings you to call me at this hour?
Where are you right now? I'd like to meet you.
Would you like a new cup of tea?
No, it's okay.
If it's too hot, I can't gulp it down like this.
I'd either have to sip on it...
or wait for it to cool down.
I wanted to ask the kid something.
But he lost his memory.
I can't gulp it down.
(The Inspector Who Witnessed Seo Sang Won's Death...)
(Was a Friend of the Eight Victim)
(Maybe she purposely pushed him from the rooftop.)
What a darn lunatic. This is so annoying.
Hey.
- What was that for? - Shut it, will you?
This is stakeout. What do you think you're doing?
Gosh, you still didn't need to hit my mouth.
Then what? Should I have hit your neck?
- What do the comments say? - Don't even ask.
Do they think Ms. Cha purposely let Seo Sang Won die...
because she wanted to take revenge?
People say she did a good job...
and that they would've done the same thing.
- Then what's the problem? - But some lunatic...
is saying she stabbed his hands and purposely pushed him...
from the rooftop.
And people keep liking this comment.
My gosh.
We know for a fact...
that she wasn't the one who stabbed Seo Sang Won's hands.
When she got there, he was already bleeding out.
Exactly.
- What? - What?
That's it? What else?
"What else"?
No one else would know other than Ms. Cha.
Hey, there it is.
(Did She Investigate for 18 Years to Take Revenge?)
What did he say?
Why do you even ask?
It's not like you can do anything.
You guys should go home and get some rest.
Ms. Cha will end up...
facing a huge load of trouble soon.
And we might get involved as well.
Especially you, Jae Hong.
You were there when Seo Sang Won fell from the rooftop.
You guys should go.
Okay, sir.
You too, Officer Yun.
Yes, sir.
- Did Officer Yun call you? - Yes.
What is the matter with you?
You caused a mess for everyone at work,
and you still make me call you first?
I'm sorry.
Eun Ho woke up...
Even so, how could you...
Eun Ho woke up?
Yes, but he can't remember anything.
Not just the accident...
but the entire past month.
Sir...
Sir, I'll see you tomorrow at the office.
I need to deal with something more important right now.
There you are.
I just heard about Eun Ho's condition.
My gosh, I'd love to meet him.
But right now, I'm a stranger to him.
So I should hold back, right?
Yes, just hang in there.
He'll quickly get his memory back.
Of course.
Detective Cha, do you want Eun Ho...
to get his memory back?
I guess you don't.
What's so important about knowing the truth?
It's not like anything will change.
Do you really think it'd be worth the pain?
For me, yes.
No, no.
I wasn't talking about you. I was talking about Eun Ho.
Eun Ho's brain...
is trying to protect him...
from pain and danger.
Isn't that amazing?
Does that mean he'll be in danger...
once he gets his memory back?
My goodness.
You got the wrong message again.
The more he starts to remember,
the more he might remember things...
that he'd rather just forget.
And that will last forever.
Wouldn't that be like living in a nightmare?
(Special Crime Squad)
You look like you lost the country or something.
Have you ever seen anyone who's lost their country?
I'm sorry, but don't get on my nerves.
- Will you please... - I have a favor to ask.
- Go ahead. - Did you write your report...
based on exactly what you saw on the day that Seo Sang Won died?
Ms. Cha probably seemed a little suspicious that day.
But you didn't write that down.
- So what? - I want you...
to keep your statement consistent with the report you wrote.
- Aren't you angry? - About what?
That she never told us that she was friends with the victim?
If she didn't tell us,
she wouldn't have been able to be in charge of the case.
Ms. Cha should be the one telling me all this stuff.
Why must I hear all this from you?
Because Ms. Cha would feel too bad to ask you this.
I don't want to lose her.
We're finally seeing progress with Eun Ho's case.
And the same goes for the stigmata serial murders...
What do you mean? What are you talking about?
Why did you suddenly join our team?
Does Ms. Cha have something on you?
Do you really think she'd use...
my weakness against me to force me to join her team?
Who knows?
She looked at a photo of her friend's corpse with us,
but she didn't even blink.
I overheard her talk about the conversation she had...
with Seo Sang Won on the rooftop.
She couldn't write it on the report.
Seo Sang Won might've had an accomplice.
Please do me a favor.
Please stick to your report when they ask you questions.
If you refuse to do this for me, I'll just have to confess...
that I already knew everything.
Are you threatening me?
Who uses something they like to threaten someone?
- Mom. - Yes?
You should get some rest.
Are you tired? Do you want to lie down?
No, I'm okay.
Then let's stay like this for a bit longer.
Once you fall asleep, I'll...
Mom.
How did I get hurt?
I'll tell you...
once you get better.
Mom.
Did I tell you anything strange...
before I got hurt?
Hey, you're here.
Come on in.
Don't you have any questions for me?
Eun Ho.
Next time.
I actually have a lot of questions for you.
But right now, I'm only going to ask you one thing.
If you had to hide something, where would you put it?
It depends on whether...
it's a thing or a secret.
- It's a thing. - What thing?
I don't know.
What is it that I had to hide?
It's not like I'd come across a lot of money.
What if someone asked you to keep something safe for a while?
Is it related to how I got injured?
No. It happened before you got hurt.
You saved a man's life and was awarded...
It's not important to you,
but it is important to the person who left it with you.
Where do you think...
you'd have kept it?
In my apartment?
The balcony or study?
Or the kitchen.
Okay.
You should...
rest now. Lie down.
- So Yeon, you should... - Why!
Why won't anyone tell me anything?
Why won't anyone tell me how I ended up like this?
It wasn't a car crash, was it?
I can tell you what I think,
but only you know the whole truth.
Do you still want to hear?
I don't want him to regain the memory.
Losing a month of his life won't affect his future, will it?
It can't have been a good memory.
I don't want him to be scared or suffer.
You fell from a roof 10 floors high.
Young Jin!
You used the descending life line,
then halfway down, you untied yourself and fell.
That's what I know so far.
I will not stop until I know the whole truth.
But I might fail.
That's enough.
Do you mind living with an incomplete puzzle?
It might feel like living a fractured life.
Come outside.
Come outside. Right now.
Just because you did,
don't force my son to live like that.
- What does that mean? - I read the news.
The schoolgirl, the eighth victim of the stigmata serial murders.
She was your friend, right?
Did finding the culprit...
make you feel better?
She found him at last.
Um, this one.
No.
Wrap the bulgogi in lettuce.
- In lettuce? - Yes. Make a wrap.
Are your hands clean?
You didn't wash them?
Gosh, that's gross.
Wash your hands clean.
As the atmosphere becomes tense...
Hey, Du Seok.
Hey, hey. Hey!
Eat what I give you.
- What are you doing? - Then eat porridge.
The gazelle runs away at top speed.
The cheetah runs for food...
Watch it.
and the gazelle runs to live.
They're both running to survive.
Is this fun?
The animal world is...
an endless cycle of eating and being eaten.
What about humans then?
What do you mean?
We're animals too.
Memory loss.
Do you think they're lying to put us off guard?
Who?
Cha Young Jin? Lee Sun Woo?
Do you think they'd gamble with a kid?
If his memory never returns, the kid is of no use.
The best outcome is...
for Eun Ho to regain his memory,
and when Jang Ki Ho comes to reclaim what he gave Eun Ho,
we catch Ki Ho.
We'll kill the kid, right?
Let's just kill them both.
Without the kid and Jang Ki Ho,
your secret will be buried forever.
No. That's the most boring scenario.
Du Seok.
Unless we find and destroy it, it never disappears.
It exists some place I don't know.
Whenever I think of that,
I want to just blow up planet earth.
That's how annoying it is.
- Eun Ho must regain his memory. - What?
For peace on earth.
You're so witty.
It's a large piece of prey.
Eun Ho.
We're late, aren't we?
What I did was too rash.
I put myself first and didn't think of your condition.
I want to know...
what happened to me.
Of course you want to know.
You will find out.
But Eun Ho, first, you must recover.
Don't try to remember anything right now.
Don't imagine anything either.
Then I'll ask just one thing.
Why am I in such a nice room?
Now that you're awake, you'll be moved.
I want to have beef too.
You are.
This is beef too.
- What? - Do you want a beef slap?
How dare you say that?
You should offer to buy me...
What's this?
Do you still want to pass the exam to get promoted?
No.
That's why the book's stuffed in there.
Is that why you put it carefully...
where it's always within arm's reach?
How did I end up in Homicide?
There's no time to study for the exam.
So what? You'll quit?
I told you a few times.
Homicide just doesn't suit me.
Especially all these stake-outs.
Whenever I'm on a stake-out...
- Get down. Who's that? - Who's who?
Oh? Isn't that Yun Hee Seob?
Right? I didn't mistake him, did I?
Why do you think there's an accomplice?
The stigmata marks.
- On the hands? - Yes.
Before Seo Sang Won died, he said Im Hee Jung was punished,
and the other victims were blessed with resurrection.
There would be different marks for punishments and blessings?
We all know that much.
He said that Choi Su Jung didn't qualify.
She didn't qualify?
Same marks and different results.
Qualifications.
It's not the victim's qualifications.
It's the criminal's.
The one who killed Choi Su Jung...
could be someone else.
(Stigmata 8th)
(Angelic 18-year-old girl)
(Criminal Calls from 8th Victim's Phone)
(Scared schoolgirl Cha)
(Contacts)
(Detective Cha Young Jin)
Uncle.
Yes, Ji Won. What is it?
Oh? Why aren't you in bed?
Dad promised to read to me,
but he went out to work.
I see.
Come in. I'll read to you.
- What? - Your eyes look sad.
Do they?
I was reading something sad.
As sad as "The Sun and the Moon"?
Yes, as sad as "The Sun and the Moon".
This story isn't sad.
Is it not?
- I'll read for you. - Perfect.
Let's hear you read to me.
Ji Won.
Wouldn't you love to have a younger sibling?
You'd prefer a younger sibling too?
Not an older one, right?
- What do you mean? - Eun Ho...
asked me how I'd feel if I had an older brother.
Eun Ho?
The Eun Ho who visited last time?
Yes. But I said that I wanted...
a younger sibling and not an older brother.
But when I said that, Eun Ho's eyes...
became sad like yours were.
When did you talk about that?
Was it when we played soccer in the park?
No?
Then was it when we played games at home?
No. Later on, at school.
At school?
- Your school? - Yes.
Are you here about Ki Ho?
Why come here when you could call me?
Why hasn't he called me yet?
I passed the message.
After that, it's up to him.
Do you know why he's in hiding?
Beats me.
You...
- must pass on this message. - What is it?
Tell him that the Ko Eun Ho, the boy who saved his life,
is awake from his coma.
Is that all I need to tell him?
Tell him that we should go and see him together.
Sure thing. I'll tell him word for word.
Enjoy your meal then. I'll leave you to it.
He has no respect for meat, does he?
I'm dying of curiosity.
Just like me, you'll never be able to leave Homicide.
We'll see.
What the...
He's going back inside.
So there's something more important you need to say.
I need to tell him this in person.
Like I said, I'll pass the message.
If you can't trust me, look for him yourself.
Tell him that...
before it's too late, Im Hee Jung...
I'd rather you not come by so often now.
Eun Ho's doing much better and you're busy.
- I'm all right. - Well, I'm not!
This is too uncomfortable for me.
Eun Ho and I have been friends for seven years.
We care for each other and wish each other well.
(Most frequent calls)
(Detective Hwang In Bum)
- Is it okay to talk? - Yes.
You don't sound so bad.
Did the chief call you?
Yes, and I'll tell you about that later.
I have good news.
Are you alone?
Well, you're still the leader of Homicide Team 1.
- In Bum... - What is it?
Please tell her not to do anything.
Don't ask me and order that yourself.
She never listens to me.
Young Jin, don't you dare make any moves!
Just stay put.
That'll be all.
(Officer Lee Jae Hong)
(Team Leader Cha Young Jin)
Yes, Ms. Cha.
It took you a while to pick up. Where are you?
I'm in the office parking lot.
Eun Ho's awake.
What...
- Really? - Come here and stand guard.
- But Ms. Cha. - What is it?
Are you asking me for a favor?
A favor? Are you out of your mind?
I'm ordering you as your team leader.
Yes, I'll be right there.
(Special Crime Squad)
In Bum, I'm saying this out of my loyalty to you.
There's a limit to what you can do.
The organization will want to throw someone to the wolves,
and it only needs to be one person.
Why are you already thinking about sacrificing her...
instead of protecting her?
I know Young Jin didn't take out her anger on Seo Sang Won,
but I understand...
why people suspect her.
Those who sacrifice themselves...
to do what's right are the ones who get sacrificed.
And those who sit and watch by the sidelines...
doing nothing at all...
never lose anything.
I requested police protection,
so I'm asking you to stay until the officers arrive.
I thought you said it wasn't a favor.
Stand guard until they arrive.
Watch what you say since he has no recollection of the past month.
I'm asking...
Carry on then.
I'm sorry that I didn't tell you...
about Su Jung.
I just wanted...
to catch him myself.
Yes, we understand that.
I see, I have a cop on my tail.
What's he doing?
Keep going. Just keep driving.
How much longer should we wait?
- It's been long enough. - Right?
- Should we head back? - Should we?
Let's go.
Wasn't this the spot? Stop the car.
Darn it.
Unbelievable.
How did he make us out?
- What now? - What else? We should go.
"Inherit of all Im Hee Jung's rights before it's too late."
Chairman Yun said you'd understand.
Right.
I still have some time though.
Is that so?
Come and grab a bite to eat then.
That reminds me.
There's something I forgot.
That boy Eun Ho is awake.
Really?
My Lord, the Almighty,
I praise and thank you for hearing...
my prayers.
My Father.
Amen.
I should see the boy right away.
You can't.
- Why not? - The detective...
who caught Seo Sang Won came by to see me.
What?
She's looking for you.
Why is she looking for me?
She said something odd.
According to her,
the boy who saved your life almost died because of you.
Does that make any sense?
Just so you know though,
Seo Sang Won's last victim... No, that's not right.
She was the friend of Seo Sang Won's eighth victim.
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency, Special Crime Squad)
(Homicide Team 1, Team Leader, Inspector Cha Young Jin)
(Detective Cha Young Jin)
Yes, Detective.
I called too early, didn't I?
Yes, you certainly did.
Hello? I'm only kidding.
You can call me anytime, you know.
I saw the news yesterday.
Are you just hanging in there?
Actually, I forgot because something good happened.
- Good good? - Eun Ho...
is awake.
Hee Seob.
Eun Ho's awake.
But he's missing a month's worth of his memories, right?
Did you already know?
Can you set up a meeting with Eun Ho's mother today?
It's best if we tell her about Min Sung.
Why now though?
Just set an appointment with her.
Is it because he has no memory...
of having gotten harassed by Min Sung's driver?
I didn't even think that far.
There'll be an announcement about the leaking of the test this week.
Don't you think I should talk to Eun Ho's mother before I do that?
Thank you for everything.
Come in.
My goodness, Mr. Lee.
- Ms. Jung, here you go. - Thank you.
It's good to see you.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
Never mind.
Eun Ho, Mr. Lee bought you cake.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I feel a little queasy.
I just imagined eating cake.
- I'm sorry. - No, it's okay.
I'll take this outside.
- I'll take that. - But...
And stop saying you're sorry.
You're free to act like a patient.
Ms. Jung, I'll leave this outside.
No, it's okay. Can I have this with the detectives?
Of course.
I'm sure they'll love it.
You can take your time and talk to him.
Thank you.
I'll be outside, Eun Ho.
Are you okay?
It must feel really weird.
You woke up bedridden at a hospital.
And suddenly, a month has passed.
What if I never get to remember what happened?
That won't happen, so don't worry.
And even if you fail to remember,
people around you will tell you bits and pieces of what happened...
and fill up your missing memory.
But that's not my own memory.
I want to remember what happened myself.
Then why don't you try?
But let's take it slow.
First, let's travel back a month.
What's your last memory?
Of course, for you, it'd feel like yesterday.
Should we do this next time?
Well...
I went to your place.
My place?
Hurry up, Uncle!
Be careful.
Eun Ho.
So you're telling me...
that's what you think happened yesterday?
Yes.
Eun Ho asked me how I'd feel...
if I had an older brother.
Do you also remember...
what we talked about at the park?
Come on! Shoot!
- Ji Won, what's the matter? - I sneezed.
- You sneezed? - Yes.
I guess you said hello to the sun.
How do you say hello to the sun?
Every time I look at the sun,
my nose starts to itch, and I suddenly sneeze.
It's okay. The sun...
just wants to see you because it adores you so much.
That's why it tickles your nose.
It's so tiring to have everyone like me so much.
You're a snob.
- What's wrong? - I do that, too.
Sometimes, when I suddenly see the light...
after having been in the dark,
I suddenly sneeze.
Really?
Then you might also have the photic sneeze reflex.
There's no treatment for it, but it's completely harmless.
It's just a little uncomfortable.
You told me that it's harmless...
but just a little uncomfortable.
And then?
Ji Won invited me over.
So I went to your place.
And then, you woke up here at the hospital?
It must've been so hard on you.
Mr. Lee.
Did I...
- I'm here to check on him. - Okay.
Ms. Jung.
Can we talk for a moment?
- Sure. - Okay.
Chairman Yun...
wishes to talk to you in person.
If you're uneasy about it, you can turn him down and talk to me...
No, I'll meet him.
You really do sneeze.
Why do people have this kind of reflex?
Blame your parents.
- What? - It's genetic.
- You and I are the same. - You're right.
You guys are the same.
Yes.
You really came.
You begged me for help, so I even took the day off.
I expected you guys to be a bit more excited.
I'll repay you for this.
You're completely useless to our team.
The old man is a pro.
You should be careful.
I used to be in special forces.
And I used to be one of the best homicide detectives of my time.
But okay, I'll be careful.
You guys should get going. I heard Ms. Cha gathered everyone.
- Okay. - Good luck.
See you guys.
- Thank you, guys. - Good work.
It's her! Hurry!
Did you let go of his hand on purpose?
Please tell us!
Was it on purpose?
(Special Crime Squad)
Ms. Cha asked me to share something with you.
What is it?
Seo Sang Won might've had an accomplice.
"An accomplice"?
I think Jae Hong once said something similar.
He said Jang Ki Ho might've helped Seo Sang Won.
Ms. Cha's been suspicious of an accomplice...
way before she even found out about Jang Ki Ho.
What? She never told us that.
No.
She couldn't write this on the report,
but here's a conversation she had with Seo Sang Won.
(Team Leader: Cha Young Jin)
Did you gather everyone here to waste our time?
Is the article false?
No.
Are you hiding anything else other than what Jae Hong shared with us?
- No. - Okay then.
Just be yourself.
You don't even have anything to say to us.
So why are you standing there as if you do?
My gosh, will you cut it out?
Ms. Cha shouldn't have lied to us.
And I know you're her senior.
But she's still our boss, so stop being so disrespectful.
And Ms. Cha.
We're your colleagues, not your tools.
Sergeant Park.
- Yes? - I'm actually...
Sergeant Kim's senior.
My gosh, you lunatic.
How dare you talk to me that way?
Chief Hwang always told me to tell you guys...
that Su Jung and I were friends.
I didn't think it really mattered.
But now,
- I regret not having told you. - My gosh.
I'm amazed you managed to keep it a secret for this long.
Other than Chief Hwang and us, who else knows the killer called you?
Su Jung's mother.
If even that reaches the press,
then one of us is the leak.
Do you get what I mean?
The disciplinary committee meets in three days.
Be prepared.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Cha Young Jin. - Yes?
You're on standby until the committee meets.
As of this moment, you must not do anything.
- Answer me. - What about Chief Hwang?
What makes you think he could avoid this witch hunt?
(Chief Hwang In Bum)
(Daehan Daily journalist)
Come in.
Hi.
Can I have the papers I asked you to sign this morning?
Right.
Here.
So...
You're allowed to go home.
(Case Report of 8th Stigmata Serial Murder)
Attention.
From now on, you can't share any information with Ms. Cha.
- Okay? - Then who's in charge?
Who else but me?
Team 1, stay on Lee Young Sik.
Team 2, look for Jang Ki Ho.
Darn it.
Hello, Reporter Ju.
Of course. A drink?
I quit drinking.
Yes. Dinner?
I quit dinner too. You know intermittent fasting.
Tea? I quit drinking tea. I drink other things now.
I should hang up now. I'm in a meeting.
Hang up. Bye.
No thanks.
Let's go.
You two look way too stiff.
That's how you mess up and make mistakes.
Put aside your feelings of wanting to help Ms. Cha...
and go to work. Okay?
Okay.
We'll see you later.
Hey. How about we get going too?
Let's have a coffee first.
Not for me.
Hey, Jin Soo.
What number highway did we lose the old man's truck on?
Highway 48.
Then the shoulder the old man parked on.
How many minutes drive was it from Hosu Nursing Hospital?
What?
Oh, right, yes. It's 25 minutes or so away.
Do you remember how fast we were driving?
About 55km per hour?
Gosh.
You're born to be a detective.
No way.
Did you have that written down?
- Let me see. - Why would I write that down?
Other than not remembering what happened in the past month,
he's fine.
Are you crying?
I was just waiting for the day to apologize to Eun Ho.
I wanted to tell him that...
though he might not forgive me, I'm really sorry...
and that I did wrong.
I want to see Eun Ho.
Okay.
I'll write you a hall pass.
Let's go together next time.
(Hosu Nursing Hospital)
Hosu Nursing Hospital.
55km per hour.
25 minutes.
(Hosu Nursing Hospital)
Hello?
It's Cha Young Jin. Speak up.
I'm Jang Ki Ho.
I heard Eun Ho's awake.
Is he okay?
See for yourself.
I heard you're looking for me.
If I come, will you let me see him?
It's as if we met yesterday.
You haven't been in trouble?
What do you mean?
Han Sol got a transplant,
and I have a new teacher, so it's great.
Did the surgery go well?
Yes.
That's great to hear.
Who's your new teacher?
Lee Sun Woo.
Get well soon and come back to school.
I sit alone.
Who'd want to sit next to you?
Exactly.
You're the only one.
So get well soon.
Hey. Are you crying?
I've never seen you cry.
You're crazy.
Who's crying?
You are.
Darn you. I'm not crying.
I wish I could hit you.
You are crying.
Yes. I'll check when I'm inside.
I'll call you later.
I thought you'd ignore me.
Why would you say that?
That's what you said when we broke up.
That we're strangers now.
I wish we could have tea together,
but I must take care of a headache.
A headache?
Is it about the school?
How do you know that?
I gave up when I knew who the other woman was.
By now, you'd be chairman of Shinsung Foundation.
Yes.
- Why is there a headache? - So Yeon.
I'm in a rush. I have to go.
Okay. Go ahead.
It was good to see you.
Me too.
Did I make you wait?
No. I just got here.
- Let's go upstairs. - Okay.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Jung So Yeon, Ko Eun Ho's mother.
Oh, right. I'm...
Yun Hee Seob, Shinsung Foundation's chairman.
You can sit.
In my class is a boy...
who was Eun Ho's friend in elementary school...
until they drifted apart.
That boy got the answers to the school exam...
and he showed them to Eun Ho.
Didn't you say they'd drifted apart?
Yes. But the other boy...
wanted to reconcile with Eun Ho.
He thought sharing the answers would help.
It's obvious what happened.
Eun Ho wanted to tell the school.
- Yes. - A boy who was...
able to get the answer sheet?
He must be rich...
with connections to people who run the school.
- Chairman Yun. - Yes?
It must be a headache.
Ms. Jung.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
If it's okay with you, I'll give you a ride back.
Thank you.
Ms. Jung, doesn't Eun Ho...
suffer from a condition that makes him sneeze...
when he suddenly steps into a bright area?
Did you know that?
Yes, he mentioned that a while ago.
Are you like that too?
No.
Then what about Eun Ho's father?
A few months ago,
Eun Ho asked the same question.
Is Eun Ho's condition...
hereditary?
It's called photic sneeze reflex and that...
is hereditary.
So at least one of the parents...
passes it on to the child.
Drive home safely then.
- What's that? - I checked Ko Eun Ho's call logs.
After parting ways with Jang Ki Ho at the ER,
he called this diner.
I checked it before,
but I didn't check who lived there.
- Who? - Ju Dong Myung's...
- What? - His little brother.
Han Sol?
He lives there with his aunt.
The call lasted four minutes.
That means Han Sol could've heard something.
That boy sure loves to chat.
(Du Seok)
Du Seok, meet me at Han Sol's hospital room...
and buy whatever it is that kids love.
How delicious.
This is a lot. How am I supposed to carry these?
You're right.
Then just choose one to keep instead.
That's way harder!
Han Sol, did you know that Eun Ho saved a man's life?
Of course!
He called me that day...
to say that he couldn't come.
I see.
Isn't Eun Ho the kindest?
If he had saved me,
I would've given him all the presents he wanted.
He received something.
Really? What did he receive?
- A book. - A book?
What kind of book?
A gospel. Gospel of New Life.
What?
Chapter 6-6.
"When praying..."
(Gospel of New Life)
"When praying, enter the room..."
The backroom.
Again.
"Enter my backroom,"
"close the door,"
"and..."
Turn around.
"When praying, enter my backroom, close the door,"
"and pray to Father in secret."
"Father will then repay you." Father, Father, Father!
What's the map that leads to where the secrets lie?
Gospel of New Life.
Kwon Jae Chun, that jerk.
The sly old man purposely made the gospel his map...
because it was part of our everyday lives.
Memorizing it meant generous portions of food,
good clothes, and a place to rest.
But getting a single syllable wrong...
led me...
to his whip.
- Du Seok. - Yes?
Let's fetch the gospel and head to Ki Ho.
Will he willingly read us the map?
There's no need for that.
I'm just going to kill him.
I'll have him recite the gospel too.
Every time...
he gets a syllable wrong, I'll whip him.
No, wait.
Hee Dong should do the whipping.
Hee Dong,
bring me the Gospel of New Life.
Bring me the old man.
I won't say anything until I see the package.
(Gospel of New Life)
What are you doing?
Don't.
Don't do that. Stop!
What happens if this no longer exists?
Then you won't have any answers.
You'll practice your right to remain silent?
No.
Let me say that again.
Even if you figure out the truth,
there won't be anything you'll be able to do.
(Nobody Knows)
Gospel of New Life?
You said you'd find out what Ki Ho gave the kid.
I'm the one who found the truth!
Cha Young Jin must have Jang Ki Ho.
Where's my book?
What happens if this no longer exists?
There's nothing Ki Ho can do if the book no longer exists.
Are you saying that the book...
could bring Baek Sang Ho down?
We must find Jang Ki Ho and kill him.
What if we find the book first?
I saw the photo of your friend and the red cell phone.
Where did you see it?
Could Eun Ho coming by my house be a coincidence?
What is it that you want to know?
I need your help, Mr. Lee.
Eun Ho remembers Jang Ki Ho and the Gospel of New Life.