I'm sorry you had to wait for so long.
He'll be with you soon.
I wonder why Pastor Seo...
brought this young boy here.
Gosh. Here he comes.
I hear you don't even have a name.
Then I must give you one.
Sir,
I wish to share...
the name you gave me with him.
That's quite the noble idea.
Sang Won and Ki Ho.
Do you know the name of your birth mother?
Yes, Baek Young Mi.
Then your name from this moment on is Sang Ho.
Baek Sang Ho.
Bring it here.
Let the words of this gospel...
be like the blood coursing through your veins.
Then the blood within us...
will be the same.
(Gospel of New Life)
(Episode 12)
(24 hours ago)
(6:42am, November 7)
(Calls)
(Mr. Lee Sun Woo)
Eun Ho woke up.
Can I borrow your cell phone?
Why?
(Stigmata serial...)
- What are you doing? - I'm allowed to know about this.
It has nothing to do with my accident.
What are you talking about?
You told me Ms. Cha is your friend.
So how can you be okay about it?
Did a lot of people write mean comments...
because she hid the fact...
that she was friends with the last victim?
"The last victim"?
So what if people criticize her?
She still caught a murderer.
She asked me something.
She told me I saved someone's life.
Apparently, that person asked me to keep something for him.
I think she's looking for that.
Did I happen to tell you anything?
No.
I'll ask Han Sol.
You were on your way to see him that day.
Is Han Sol there?
Can I talk to him?
(Hyeju Hospital)
A book?
Did Eun Ho tell you the name of that book?
Can you say that again? "Gospel"?
- Who is it? - Han Sol.
Was it just "Gospel"? There's more, right?
Try to remember what it was.
That guy I saved...
I guess what he gave me was a book.
Just a second.
Apparently, it was some kind of a gospel.
- A gospel? - But that's all he can recall.
A gospel.
Ask him if it was "Gospel of New Life".
Han Sol, by any chance,
was it "Gospel of New Life"?
Yes, it was that.
Han Sol, I'll call you back.
What about school?
I was given permission to leave early today.
Then you can stay here a bit longer, right?
I'll see you later.
It's nice to see you guys together.
Yes, Detective Cha.
Do you have "Gospel of New Life"?
Thank you.
I'm starting to get really worried.
Give it to me.
(Gospel of New Life)
Please be careful.
Okay.
(Gospel of New Life)
Hello?
It's Cha Young Jin. Speak up.
I'm Jang Ki Ho.
I heard Eun Ho's awake.
Is he okay?
See for yourself.
I heard you're looking for me.
If I come, will you let me see him?
(Payphone, Munhwa Park)
(Officer Lee Jae Hong)
As of this moment, you must not do anything.
Yes, this is the maintenance office at Munhwa Park.
Mr. Jang Ki Ho.
Ms. Cha Young Jin has found your book.
Please call her as soon as possible.
Mr. Jang Ki Ho.
Ms. Cha Young Jin has found your book.
Where should we meet?
Where's my book?
It's in the car.
(Gospel of New Life)
What happens if this no longer exists?
Then you won't have any answers.
You'll practice your right to remain silent?
No.
Let me say that again.
Even if you figure out the truth,
there won't be anything you'll be able to do.
Now, give me that book.
I hope it's okay for the book to have a few scratches.
Is Eun Ho doing better?
Do you know how Eun Ho got hurt?
Of course.
He fell from Millennium Hotel.
Let me ask you again.
Who was chasing him and why?
Why did he have to jump from somewhere so high?
- Can you guess? - Wait a minute.
Did you just say he jumped?
Bring me the old man.
Gosh, I wonder if Ms. Cha figured anything out.
She would've called if she did, right?
Or maybe not.
She can't do anything if she tells us.
So she might not have called...
My gosh, seriously.
I'm trying to get some sleep.
Can't I even talk to myself?
Do you use honorifics when you talk to yourself?
- Yes. - What did you just say?
Okay, fine. Just talk to me like I'm your friend.
Oh, my gosh!
How could you watch an innocent civilian in this era?
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
That's enough.
Where is Jang Ki Ho?
That's what I want to ask. Where is Ki Ho?
I might as well just report him missing.
Do I need to report it to you guys?
But I'm not related to him in any way.
So I'll let it slide this once.
But if I see you guys again, I'm going to file a complaint.
(Photo frames)
On a cold day
What took you so long?
We waited ages for you.
(Gospel of New Life)
- Sun Woo. - Yes?
- Are you going to read that? - Yes.
Sun Kyung.
You read this, didn't you?
- Of course. - How was it?
Did you find it interesting or strange?
Read it for yourself and ask me again.
Yes or no?
No. I can't think of anything.
What is this about?
Though I didn't like it, it was familiar to me.
And yet I think there's so little I know about it.
(Gospel of New Life)
In one way or another,
this book has great value,
and that is what makes it dangerous.
But to those who don't know the secret,
it's just an ordinary book.
That's why you left it with Eun Ho.
Because he was good enough to save you and follow you to hospital.
You expected him to say yes despite the hassle.
I'm putting it into words, but I don't get it.
How could a person do that?
How could you give something so dangerous...
to the kid who saved your life?
That's why I wanted to leave it with him.
Because he saved my life.
Yes.
Over here!
When I returned from death and opened my eyes,
the first thing I saw was his face.
The look in his eyes...
caused a ripple in my soul.
Never in my life did I refuse anything,
or make a choice.
I lived according to the will of those better than me.
But...
For some strange reason,
I felt an affection I can't explain from that kid.
Besides, when I found out his name was Eun Ho,
I was reminded of someone who was named...
using a syllable of my name.
That was when I made up my mind.
The compensation I would gain with that book,
I would share it with that kid.
Long ago,
a nameless child was saved from near death.
The pastor named him with...
a syllable from my name.
Eventually, that child not only took my name,
but he slowly ate away at my rights.
Ki Ho.
Sang Ho.
Is that child Baek Sang Ho?
Yes.
Baek...
Sang...
Ho...
Is the "sang" from Seo Sang Won?
It is.
He took his mother's surname.
Seo Sang Won, Im Hee Jung, Jang Ki Ho, Baek Sang Ho.
You all took your mothers' surnames.
The names the pastor gave us are more important to us.
Surnames mean nothing.
Do you all...
share the same father?
If so, I have a feeling that is Pastor Kwon Jae Chun. Am I wrong?
I'm the only remaining child of Pastor Kwon's.
Baek Sang Ho isn't Kwon Jae Chun's son?
I just told you.
He was found near death.
He had no name or birth certificate.
His mother had locked him in a room...
and disappeared with the key.
If Pastor Seo hadn't saved him,
he'd have died without leaving a trace on this earth.
Do not be afraid.
You are a child that I have chosen.
I myself was chosen.
The chosen...
need not fear.
Whatever we do,
we will meet our savior in the end.
Behind you...
will always be the deity's blessing.
If you're ever in fear,
remember this passage.
God is on my side.
I will not be afraid.
What could men do to me?
I guess you overdosed him.
Is there something to wake him with?
- In the box. - Open it.
See?
Fear works better than any tool.
How long have you known that...
Seo Sang Won was a serial killer?
I told you too much already.
Until I know that book is real,
I won't say another word.
The police suspect...
Seo Sang Won had an accomplice.
You are one of the many possibilities.
Did you not cooperate with Seo Sang Won?
(Gospel of New Life)
This isn't my book.
Where is my book?
You could tell right away?
I don't know yet.
What? You don't know?
Eun Ho must've told you everything.
That must be how you thought of bringing me a fake copy.
I don't know what you'll do with me,
but I will never help you.
Eun Ho lost the memory for the past month.
He doesn't remember the pleasure...
of saving you or the fear of Baek Sang Ho chasing him.
Naturally, he doesn't remember getting your book.
You said that without the book,
I can't do anything even if the truth is revealed.
What did you mean by that?
Without proof, the truth has no power.
You mean the book has proof with which to arrest Baek Sang Ho?
No.
The book only tells you where the proof is hidden.
Even if you find the book...
and use all your manpower...
to reveal the secret, it's of no use.
Even if you have the answer, the only one who knows...
what it means is me.
Are we against the same person?
I'll find the real book and return it to you.
You said...
you'd find out what Jang Ki Ho gave the kid.
Did you find out?
I found out myself!
Darn it.
In the meantime, Ki Ho disappeared.
Do you know what that means for you?
My gosh.
Now you're pretending to be hard of hearing?
It means our deal is off, okay?
I only told you about what would happen if things worked out.
I never talked about the downside.
Okay.
I'm sorry about that.
If I'd told you,
you'd have done your job or tried to run away.
Your life, old man,
ends here.
What are you saying?
Sang Ho!
Let's hear him out.
He might know where Ki Ho is.
Do it quick. Get to it.
Detectives are watching me!
If something happens to me, they'll suspect you!
You should've said so sooner.
My gosh.
Is that so?
Yes, it's true.
I'll find Ki Ho and bring him to you.
Hee Dong!
I'll bury you well.
What's this?
This is the only phone you'll use.
I think Cha Young Jin has Jang Ki Ho.
Then they must be off to retrieve the evidence.
- Mr. Baek. - Yes?
You should hurry out of the country.
Do all copies...
of Gospel of New Life contain the map?
I doubt it.
Why do you think he came out of hiding...
just to meet Eun Ho?
Because only the copy he gave to Eun Ho...
contains the map.
However, Eun Ho still has amnesia.
That means Cha Young Jin hasn't found the book yet.
I still have an opportunity to make a choice.
Jang Ki Ho can't do anything without the book either.
All I have to do is play the game my own way.
There's no choice.
Going into hiding is your best option!
No, the choice must always be mine!
Sorry.
My body reacted before I could think.
Will you be slapping me with the water?
Clean it up.
- Is that all? - This wouldn't even make a dent.
Stop me like that again though...
and I'll smash those on you.
- Du Seok. - Yes?
Call Tae Hyung in.
Got it.
Thank you.
How has it been working at the foundation?
Good, I guess.
It seems like you're not satisfied there.
I'm still an intern, so I've only been doing...
the tasks that were given.
What do you want to do then?
I wish to help kids...
who have nothing going for themselves...
succeed in life.
Try to do a good job then. I'm expecting a lot from you.
That reminds me. You haven't been able...
to see Eun Ho since he woke up, right?
No, and I've been wanting to hear his voice.
I think they're tying Mr. Ko's accident...
with Eun Ho's incident.
Yes, I heard it from Mr. Ko.
Well, now it's even hard for me to check on Eun Ho too.
I'm dying to see how he is though.
Not just about what the doctors can tell me.
I want to know how he's feeling...
and ask if he really doesn't remember me.
Should I go instead?
They wouldn't let you in either.
I'll take Dong Myung with me.
Well, would you?
I'm sure that Eun Ho would like to see you...
once he remembers.
But I hope that he doesn't remember.
If he regains his memory of that day,
he'll never be able to forget it again.
So what if he doesn't remember me?
We can always start over.
- That was exhausting, right? - Only a little.
Then I guess you didn't do your best.
You need to work to the point where you exhaust yourself...
for a faster recovery.
Got it.
I haven't seen Tae Hyung around though.
I guess you don't know. He was your caregiver.
- Really? - He adored you like a brother...
and kept talking to you.
He even read that entire book to you.
("The Life Before Us")
(Student Records Ko Eun Ho)
(Father: Ko Jae Geun, deceased, Mother: Jung So Yeon)
Min Sung's parents would like the chance...
to pass along their sincere apologies.
What a proud moment.
Eun Ho grew up without a father...
and has a ghost for a mother.
But he grew up to be a young man who is...
as decent and honorable as any rich kid.
Maybe it's a good thing that he never...
had any parents to look up to.
(Shinsung Foundation)
How was physical therapy today?
I'd rather you didn't read this.
Have you read it before?
Not all of it, but it doesn't seem like a book for you.
I hear you asked your teacher about your sunlight allergy.
You also asked me too.
Why?
He said it was hereditary,
but I never got it from you.
I was wondering if it came from Dad.
He didn't have it either.
Just say what it is you want to say.
And stop keeping everything bottled up.
If I had always said what was on my mind,
our relationship would've been ruined.
I figured out that your blood type...
couldn't give birth to me.
When?
I was 12.
And for all these years,
you've dealt with that secret yourself?
How could you even think about keeping it to yourself?
- You should've told me. - I didn't think it mattered.
I didn't mind it being just you and me.
And there's that cool friend of yours upstairs, right?
I was scared when you got injured.
So I let my ego go and cried my eyes out.
"What do I do? What do I do now?"
But then, I came to my senses...
and I realized that I was only worried...
about losing you when you were fighting for your life.
Sometimes...
Actually, I often don't understand you.
Sometimes, you saddened me...
and left me in despair,
but I still love you, you know.
I...
was frustrated because I never knew what you were thinking.
And I always believed you thought so little of me...
and that you'd abandon me someday.
As a boy, I was always scared...
that you'd abandon me someday,
so how could I ever leave you?
That never once crossed my mind.
Didn't you say you need to go to the salon?
But your face is a mess right now.
Do I look okay?
Why did you lie when you met Eun Ho's mother?
What do you mean?
You two acted like you'd never met before.
Oh, that.
Eun Ho's mother acted like she didn't know me,
so I played alone.
When was it?
You'd dated my sister since high school...
when you married her.
It only happened a few times.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to visit Eun Ho at the hospital.
A visit from the chairman?
Me and the vice-principal is more than enough.
Do you think it was a coincidence...
that Eun Ho came by my house?
What is it you want to know?
Do you think he could be your son?
I don't know.
So what if he is?
Sun Woo, if your sister finds out...
she won't be able to handle it.
You're right.
Once she finds out, she'll kick you to the curb.
Hi, Dong Myung. What's up?
I'd like a hall pass.
- To visit Eun Ho? - Yes.
All right.
And...
I'd like to sit somewhere else.
I'm afraid I can't help you there.
- Aren't you going? - After lunch.
I haven't done it once since leaving the hospital.
Tell me if you get another urge.
- You'll do it for me? - And ruin my life?
I'll get you another part-time job.
You said physical labor helped you take your mind off things.
Are you sure you want to be friends...
when Eun Ho's awake now?
Team One, where are we?
Lee Young Sik still hasn't said anything yet.
- Team Two? - The old man made us.
Then just call him in as a witness.
Yes, sir.
Where's Ms. Cha?
I told her to do nothing.
Where on earth did she go?
Call her in immediately!
(Team Leader Cha Young Jin)
Yes?
Ms. Cha, where are you?
The office...
parking lot.
Were you sleeping?
Ms. Cha!
Ms. Cha?
Ms. Cha.
Why aren't you at work?
We saved someone who fainted due to malnutrition.
I'd say that's a job well done.
Do we have any new leads?
Yes, Team Two was made,
so the old man won't lead us to Jang Ki Ho.
All right.
- Get back to the office. - We'll stay.
I'd like to rest in peace.
You need to stay for a second IV drip.
I'm going to check.
All right.
May we help you?
I'm his caregiver.
No one told us anything about you.
I'm here with a friend.
This feels weird.
I heard you were nice to me.
You even read me a book.
I should thank you for introducing me to a good one.
Was it good?
At first, I wasn't sure if I should be reading it to you,
but I realized something after finishing the book.
Even in misery, one can be happy.
You'll understand once you read it too.
The last sentence struck me deep inside.
What was it?
You won't read it if I tell you, so check it out yourselves.
("Encounter")
Who paid for Han Sol's surgery?
Don't you remember winning the prize for good conduct?
I can't believe you forgot all the good things that happened too.
So tell me. Who paid for it?
A man spreading good in the world solved our problem.
He keeps asking Dong Myung questions hoping that they'd jog his memory.
It's safe to say...
that he really has amnesia.
Is that so?
Then I can hold off going to see him for a while.
You should head home too now.
All right.
See? Eun Ho doesn't remember.
That means Cha Young Jin...
isn't in possession of the book.
It's still too risky.
Jang Ki Ho must be killed.
What if we find the book first?
Jang Ki Ho will no longer be a threat to us.
So what if the man babbles? It hardly qualifies as evidence.
Now, what if we had the map but couldn't decipher it?
How frustrating would that be?
It's why we need Jang Ki Ho.
If it weren't for that darn old man,
he'd already be with us.
Right?
(6F, VIP Ward)
Going up.
Hold on.
Since you're here, at least say hello.
All right?
Let's go.
Hi, it's me.
Come on in. It's okay.
Shouldn't you be at the academy?
I don't care anymore.
Is there anything you'd like to eat? I'll get it for you.
Dong Myung went out to buy it himself.
Is he still here?
- Hey, you're here. - Hi.
Have you been well, Mr. Lee?
It's been a while.
He's the teacher I told you about.
We should talk outside.
I wanted to call after hearing about you,
but things were too hectic that day.
That's how you've always been.
You think you care, but you never take action.
Right.
So how did you meet Chairman Baek?
He helped me when I actually landed in prison...
as the guilty one.
It's funny since no one cared when I was innocent.
I apologize.
Whatever. Just be good to your current students.
Especially Dong Myung.
But if you're just pitying him...
and going to abandon him later on,
just stop caring about him right now.
I won't make the same mistake.
You call that a mistake?
Tell the guys that I left.
Tae Hyung.
Don't trust...
Chairman Baek too much.
Who do you think I'd trust more? The person who helped me...
or my teacher...
who never believed me?
You should listen to Mr. Lee.
When I doubted Dong Myung,
he still trusted that he was innocent.
And that's because...
of what happened with you.
Mr. Lee.
- You can pick. - Was Mr. Lee...
Tae Hyung's homeroom teacher as well?
I guess so.
They seemed a little awkward with each other.
Don't let it bother you.
Did you come with Mr. Lee?
No, I just ran into him.
I'll be off now.
Thank you for coming.
What's the matter?
You should go. You were on your way out.
- It's all my fault. - Stop it.
You got hurt because of me.
And my uncle died, too.
What are you talking about?
Say you won't tell anyone.
Please don't do this.
Eun Ho, are you okay?
Eun Ho.
Don't touch me.
I just remembered.
You asked me to meet you there.
But you weren't there.
Why did you do that to me?
Why? Why did you do that?
- I don't want that. - Aren't you tired?
The tranquilizer will help you get some sleep.
No.
If it's unnecessary, let's just skip it.
Okay, but don't stress yourself.
Okay.
You know why Min Sung did that to me, don't you?
Tell me everything. Don't leave anything out.
But that won't be the full story.
They're just assumptions...
that were made based on Min Sung's story.
I don't care.
Did you figure out the truth by catching the culprit?
You didn't.
You could only rely on the culprit's story.
You knew that,
but you started anyway.
I don't care about the full story.
You're not Su Jung.
You're still alive.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
On my way here,
I only cared about your memory.
You mean "Gospel of New Life"?
It's the only thing you asked me about after I woke up.
You were going to show me that, weren't you?
I think we both need...
some tranquilizers.
Show me.
I don't know where I saw this.
But I remember seeing a photo of your friend...
and a red cell phone.
You went into the small room.
I thought my brain was making things up.
See? It's just a matter of time.
Just show it to me.
(Gospel of New Life)
You're right. It's a matter of time. You'll remember it one day.
But you don't have much time.
I should remember it as soon as I can.
Do you have a photo of that man?
Let me see it.
You saved my life today, and this is as precious as my life.
If you keep this for me until I come back for it,
I promise I'll repay you.
I remember reading it in a room.
Your room?
Yes.
Then I put it in my bag.
- Your gym bag? - No.
The bag I normally use.
Didn't you take this to school the next day?
(Gospel of New Life)
My locker.
I put it in my locker.
- When? - Right before I left school.
That's enough for today.
What would you like to drink?
Dong Myung bought me juice.
- Is that enough? - Yes.
What's the matter?
You remember things that happened more than a month ago, right?
You drew an angel...
with six wings on your notebook.
Where did you see that?
I'm sorry.
A regular came unannounced, so I finished late today.
You're here, so I'll get going now.
Thanks.
You should get some rest.
- I'll see you. - Bye.
See you.
I need your help, Mr. Lee.
Sure. I'll help.
You don't even know what I'm going to ask.
Because I have...
full trust in you.
Are you sure?
It's possible that I killed a man.
However hard I think,
I don't think I'm bad enough to deserve to be killed.
So even if I'm around you,
I have nothing to worry.
So, how can I help you?
Eun Ho remembered Jang Ki Ho and the Gospel of New Life.
He put it in before leaving school, but it wasn't there when we checked.
That means someone took it some time in-between.
Baek Sang Ho and Oh Du Seok were here,
but it disappeared before then.
That's why Oh Du Seok didn't find it in this locker.
And...
Min Sung saw him,
so he couldn't check Eun Ho's backpack.
Afterwards, he stole Eun Ho's backpack,
but he didn't find what he wanted inside.
So he kidnapped Eun Ho.
Not knowing the book disappeared in the school.
The copy that Baek Sang Ho wants so desperately,
we must find it first.
Why? Is something wrong?
You just said "we".
It's nice to hear.
You could get into trouble.
Don't worry.
If things get too hairy for me, I'll just bail out.
Why are you giving me that look?
So far...
you've had many chances to bail out.
If you miss the chance, you might never get out.
I don't know about that.
But I want both you...
and Eun Ho to be safe.
If someone must get hurt,
I think it better be me.
Thank you, but...
I protect myself.
But Eun Ho...
Protect him for me.
Okay. I'll do that.
Let's go.
Detective Cha.
The angel drawing in Eun Ho's notebook...
Did you ask him about it?
I did.
The angel with six wings that you drew in your notebook.
Where did you see it?
Eun Ho.
Does it matter where I saw it?
It's a symbol related to the stigmata killer.
We tracked the killer with an angel doll...
the killer had given to...
the first victim's younger sister.
I saw it in Mr. Lee's house.
- What? - When I visited his place,
Ji Won showed me her dolls.
She showed me the angel doll...
and said the others are younger than her,
but that one was much older than her.
I drew it because I remembered how it had six wings.
Who is Ji Won?
Mr. Lee's niece.
Why do you think Eun Ho was in your neighborhood?
He must've had business there.
That business...
Could he have gone to your house?
Why do you think so?
When Eun Ho described that day,
it wasn't as if he was remembering.
It was as if he missed it.
- What's wrong? - I can't sleep.
I want to read that book.
Okay.
Here you go.
(The Life Before Us)
Hey.
Are you at home?
No, at my office.
At this hour?
I was reading something.
I have something to tell you. Shall we meet up?
(Stigmata serial murder victims)
I went through Su Jung's files again,
and thought of when I said I'd taken the call that you did.
The lie I told to protect you from...
the public's curiosity.
If it hadn't been for that,
the media would've torn you apart.
If that had happened,
you wouldn't have been able to hide...
that you were Su Jung's friend to investigate.
Why are you saying all this?
You said that once you solve the stigmata case,
you'll quit the police force.
Yes.
That means that until you do,
you must remain here at all costs.
Are you thinking of...
leaving instead of me?
Don't wonder whether...
you have more to lose or I do.
Let's think...
who can do more by remaining.
Everyone around me,
in one way or another,
becomes unhappy.
No, it's just misfortune.
That's not your responsibility.
Those unfortunate people have someone like you...
who embraces their misfortune.
Isn't that what prevents the misfortune...
from turning to unhappiness?
I'm so glad that...
I met you.
I bet that...
Eun Ho thinks he's glad he met you.
(8th victim, Choi Su Jung)
(Ko Eun Ho, friends with Ju Dong Myung)
Let's start the day...
with some good news.
What is it?
I think Eun Ho will recover soon.
Can we visit him?
He's still being treated. Let's give him a bit more time.
Eun Ho said he lost a book...
at school that he was given as a gift.
What's the title?
I don't remember the title,
but I think he said it has a blue cover.
I'll ask for more details and let you know, okay?
- Okay. - Okay.
Okay, then.
I'm sorry.
It was a prank.
We meant to return it soon.
I see.
But then Eun Ho got hurt,
and you couldn't talk to him.
I'm sorry.
I was going to scold you, but now I'm grateful.
That you came forward instead of keeping it a secret.
Since you meant to return the book,
you must still have it.
- No. - Then what?
- It's in the library. - The school library?
- Yes. - Yes.
(200. Religion)
(Gospel of New Life)
They said they left it in the library, so I checked.
There are three more copies.
(Gospel of New Life)
Compare page 120.
The one different from the others is the real copy.
Page 120.
(Page 120)
Let's see.
(Gospel of New Life)
- I found it. - We need one more.
I'll copy it right away.
Please do.
(Jang Ki Ho is calling.)
It's Jang Ki Ho.
My book. Did you find it?
No. But we found a lead.
Don't make me wait too long.
I had to walk a long way down to get a signal.
I'll come to you soon.
Make sure to stay hidden.
Hello?
What on earth?
(Team Leader Cha Young Jin)
Did you find anything?
Detective,
I think some of the content is in special ink.
It doesn't show up on photos...
or on a photocopy.
Then the only option is to compare them manually and write them down.
I'll head to you right now.
No, let me compare them.
If the book contains some sort of code,
then I should do it.
(Gospel of New Life)
I'm the only remaining child...
of Pastor Kwon's.
Baek Sang Ho.
Who were you to these people?
I don't know where I saw this.
But I remember seeing a photo of your friend...
and a red cell phone.
(One must love.)
You said you saw a photo of my friend and a red cell phone.
Yes.
Was the cell phone in a photo too?
No.
What's wrong?
I remember...
where I saw it.
(Nobody Knows)
(If the culprit dies, so does the case.)
(The beginning meets the end.)
A sacred wound and the blessing of agony.
Thanks to me, you will now be reborn.