Don't worry. You'll go down slowly.
I don't want to do it.
Why? Are you scared?
You still need to do it.
Are you not going to do this
in case of an emergency?
I can't do this.
Fine.
Make sure you remember
everything you learned today.
Okay.
- Please let her go.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
- Hyun Jung.
Yes?
If you want to survive, do it.
If you want to live.
Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Good job. Please help her out.
- Okay.
You just saved Hyun Jung.
It's not time to be proud.
It's your turn.
Get ready. All right.
It looks scary.
- Watch and learn.
- Okay!
Be careful.
Get ready and step forward.
(Episode 10)
Mr. Lee.
What in the world
are you doing here?
Eun Ho...
What about him?
He didn't get pushed by someone.
To live...
To survive,
he jumped off himself.
He knew it wouldn't reach
the ground.
Although he knew it,
he wanted to live.
That's why he jumped off.
What on earth was chasing him?
He's just a 15-year-old kid.
Your nails got longer.
Ko Eun Ho...
We should kill him
once he opens his eyes, right?
That boy jumped off from this height
to live.
Of course,
he's too young to be killed.
Still,
he's out of my control,
and he's the result
made by Ms. Cha Young Jin.
- Don't you think so?
- Sang Ho.
Things are getting messy.
We shouldn't have kept him alive
in the first place.
Is that when things started
to go wrong?
Or...
(New Life Church)
Gosh. Mr. Jang.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I heard...
you've been away for a few days
recently.
Where have you been?
You went somewhere nice all alone?
How have you been?
If you lock the doors like that,
how will you get out?
Don't worry. I already have a way.
Have you been well?
Yes.
You look well.
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
We haven't met for a long time.
We need to talk.
Let's save it for later.
You'll only get hurt if you run
in a rush at your age!
See you later.
Mr. Jang.
Mr. Jang!
Doo Seok.
I lost him.
Me?
I'm locked in.
Yes.
What's his name?
Ko Eun Ho?
Ko Eun Ho.
Go after that boy.
If he has the stuff, Ki Ho will
have to come see him again.
Why don't you let them go?
They've had enough.
Were you still here?
What should I do with the boy?
He saved someone's life,
so he deserves an award.
Here at the Shinsung Middle School,
I've seen light and darkness today.
(Ko Eun Ho)
It's not here.
Good job.
("The Life Before Us")
"I stood
before a mirror several times..."
"and imagined how I would change..."
"if life tramples over me."
"I put my fingers in my mouth..."
"and opened my mouth to the sides,
grimacing my face and thought,"
"would I look like this?"
It looks quite fun.
("We should love.")
Come on, Mr. author!
You can't close the book this way.
He shot himself to death...
He had such a vain hope.
No wonder he ended your life
that way.
This is how I would have written it.
"I must save them."
((I can't tell you.
But please help me.)
(But please help me.)
He's quite daring.
Hee Dong, where do you think
it went wrong?
Well,
if I didn't lose Ki Ho...
You scumbag.
If you got the bag as soon
as Eun Ho left the emergency room,
it would have been over by now!
What's wrong was...
Eun Ho's mind.
His kindness ruined our plan.
If I were to go back in time,
I'd tell little Eun Ho...
that ill will always comes back
as ill will,
but goodwill doesn't always
come back as goodwill.
Being evil is clear,
but being good is...
complicated...
and it often betrays you.
Come in.
Hello.
Thank you.
When is your brother leaving
the hospital?
In two weeks.
Come and get a haircut later.
I won't charge you.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For being friends with Eun Ho.
Was it when he was seven years old?
He helped an old man
collecting waste paper.
I didn't like it, but I let him
because I thought he'd quit soon.
Then that old man...
kept bringing Eun Ho around
to make him work.
My mother was pretty insignificant.
This is what she always said.
"Everyone will look down on you
if you're kind. Be spiteful."
But she's right.
They look down on you if you're kind
and you'll suffer losses.
Although Eun Ho did suffer losses,
at least he's got a friend.
I'm sorry.
I should be...
sorry for Eun Ho...
for being his mother.
He had never spoken ill of you.
I'm sure he never said
good words about me.
I'm sorry.
My gosh.
He jumped off on his own.
Do you think Eun Ho rappelled down?
When I first heard
that he fell from here,
I thought it was a miracle...
that he was still alive.
But if you fall from this height,
it's like a car crashing head-on
into a cement wall...
at 95 km per hour...
without a seat belt or an airbag!
But since it was that high,
he must've thought
he had a chance of surviving,
so he untied his belt.
But even at that height...
Mr. Lee.
- Yes.
- If he rappelled down,
it couldn't have been
this life line.
Why would there be a life line
that's far shorter than the height?
Right.
You're right.
Even if the rope was cut,
this rope must've been tied here...
when the employees of the hotel
found him, right?
It must've been impossible
to unfasten the safety rope...
without leaving a trace after
he fell and before he was found.
That means he didn't fall
because the life line was defective.
I'm sure
the culprit didn't expect...
Eun Ho would
use the life line to go down.
There's no reason for them to place
a life line that's too short...
for this building
in the first place.
It was replaced after the incident.
To destroy evidence,
the culprit replaced the life line.
But he made a mistake of replacing
it with a shorter one.
Then do you think...
there's another criminal...
among the insiders of the hotel?
If the criminal was working
in the hotel,
that explains why he had to bring
him from the abandoned building...
to the hotel.
That's why it's strange.
Why would he commit a crime...
at his workplace?
And this is a hotel.
Ms. Cha.
If you're hiding something from me,
please be honest and tell me.
There's more, isn't there?
This case didn't begin...
because of the 30,000 dollars
that Eun Ho acquired.
It happened because he saved Ki Ho.
I checked the security cameras
in the emergency room.
Ki Ho handed something to Eun Ho.
And he put it in his bag.
After that,
his bag went missing, he fell,
and his bag reappeared.
The person who stole Eun Ho's bag...
to get what Ki Ho gave him.
That's the criminal.
The criminal wasn't...
trying to harm Eun Ho.
Then...
he moved from the abandoned building
to the hotel because...
He saved Eun Ho from Dae Hoon.
Because Eun Ho had
what Ki Ho gave him,
and he was valuable.
But...
there weren't any particular wounds
on Dae Hoon's body.
Eun Ho and Dae Hoon both followed
without resisting.
That means they know the person.
Who was it...
that Eun Ho willingly followed?
His friend told him to meet
at an abandoned building,
and he went there
just as he was told...
although he was anxious.
He must have trusted his friend.
But you're betrayed
only when you trust someone.
If I were 15 years old like him...
You shouldn't have done anything
there.
Should I have stopped
in that situation?
Hey.
How dare you threaten my Min Sung?
Yes.
Get up.
You know what?
I'll teach you what real friends
do for each other today.
Say it.
Say that you'll keep
your mouth shut.
Stop it.
So say it now.
Please don't kill me.
You're supposed to press harder!
Children grow...
even if you force them down.
You don't understand, do you?
Darn it.
Come here.
Come on.
Children become...
adults in the end
as long as they're alive.
You're...
the guy at the school gate
last morning, right?
I am.
His name is...
Ha Min Sung,
right?
I can explain this.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Should I take you to a hospital?
I don't think it's that bad.
Okay. Then,
should I call the police?
- Eun Ho.
- Don't.
What do you want to do?
Fine.
Let the adults have a talk alone.
Why don't you wait in my car
with that guy?
- Do you want me to be with you?
- No thank you.
Well, my backpack and my phone...
I'll bring them for you.
Get some rest here.
Have you heard who I am?
Yes.
You're the chairman
of One Life Foundation.
Min Sung...
must've been upset
because of my prank.
- Well, about earlier...
- No.
Me first.
I'm not a suspicious person,
so listen at ease.
Confucius said that...
a father is bound
to hide his son's mistake.
It seems...
you care about Ha Min Sung
like he's your son.
I mean, I was mistaken...
you for his father.
All right.
In that sense,
I'll let you choose.
Choose?
One.
Follow the world
and call the police.
- Well...
- Two.
Follow my way.
What is your way?
There's nothing much to it.
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth.
You'll feel the same fear
that Eun Ho must've felt.
Don't worry.
You'll neither be harmed nor die.
You didn't plan
to harm or kill Eun Ho either.
You only tried to scare him.
I'll do the same.
All right.
What's your choice?
Okay.
I'll follow your way.
("The Life Before Us")
Are you okay?
If you don't mind,
why don't you go to my hotel?
My room has a killer view.
Let's go have your wounds treated
and eat some delicious food.
We can have a talk too.
From the way I see it,
you need to calm down a bit
before going home. That's why.
If your mom sees you now,
she might be worried.
Don't you agree?
- Okay.
- Good. Let's go.
Where's my backpack?
Mr. Oh.
That guy took it.
He'll bring it to my room.
Is he not going with us?
We're moving in two cars.
Who was it
that Eun Ho willingly followed?
Someone from inside the hotel.
Eun Ho knows him,
and he knows Jang Ki Ho.
- It's Mr. Baek.
- No.
No, it can't be him.
If it hadn't been for Sang Ho,
Eun Ho wouldn't have been
able to have surgery that soon.
He even provided a VIP ward
and a caregiver too.
He needed Eun Ho to survive...
because he had
important information.
He got a VIP ward for Eun Ho,
and the caregiver is his person.
It's perfect
to keep watch on the kid.
All right, let's say he did it.
Then why...
did Eun Ho make
a drastic decision...
to jump off this building?
He's just a kid.
If Sang Ho wanted something
from him,
he could've just given it to him.
I'm going to find that out.
Why he had to make such a decision.
Yes, Ms. Cha.
- Where are you?
- I'm at Lee Young Sik's ward.
(Restricted Area)
Yes.
He's becoming more determined
to stay silent.
It almost...
looks like he's a monk
practicing silence.
We haven't been able to confirm
his sister's address yet.
- Her number...
- Ask the support team for help.
You two should go straight
to Eun Ho's ward now.
Stay with him until I get there.
Don't let anyone in the ward
except the medical staff or his mom.
Not even his caregiver.
I found a new clue at the hotel.
I'll tell you the details later.
Okay.
Eun Ho fell off...
about an hour
after he arrived at the hotel.
I thought he was in the car...
with the culprits
before he moved to the rooftop.
Perhaps,
he was in Mr. Baek's room.
Have you ever been to his room?
No.
Don't you want to go?
Dong Myung went there too.
I wonder what he ate, saw,
and talked about there.
Hi, Sang Ho.
Are you busy?
Why don't we have dinner together?
With Ms. Cha.
Why not? Where though?
Here?
Fine.
Not now. After an hour.
Okay. See you later.
We're meeting in an hour.
Thank you.
It must not be him.
It's true he's eccentric,
but he isn't the type of person...
who would cause harm to children.
When I was little,
I met him at church.
He was staying
at the church orphanage.
He was really nice to other kids.
Even now, a lot of children...
are getting benefits thanks to him.
What about Seo Sang Won?
Until his true face was revealed,
he was known to be
affectionate to children.
A scale of justice...
can be tipped over one evil deed...
even if you've done good deeds
countless times.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not saying he's the culprit.
It seems Ms. Cha isn't fond
of the story we made.
But that's what I like about her.
It's a bit tiring though.
Sang Ho.
We need to come up with a plan.
She has started to suspect us.
And Eun Ho will wake up soon.
Must we kill him?
I want to keep him alive,
have him by my side,
and change him little by little.
Aren't you curious...
if malice is innate or acquired?
Do you think that's possible?
You earn people's trust
by treating their biggest pain.
To him, you're the biggest pain.
What a shame.
We shouldn't have brought him here.
We wouldn't have to kill him then.
Right.
That was the worst move
which we hadn't expect.
Do you like sweets?
Yes.
So you don't.
Bring something else.
I like that one.
I'll eat it.
You've got to eat this much
as you're still growing.
You're smiling now.
- Are you feeling better now?
- Yes.
Thank you for helping me.
I just happened
to be there at a perfect time.
I was meaning to see you anyway.
- Why?
- The person you saved.
He's a close acquaintance of mine.
- Really?
- Yes.
He's Jang Ki Ho.
He goes to the same church as me.
- What a funny coincidence, right?
- Yes.
- Are you guys close?
He's still recovering,
so I went to see you to thank you.
Hey, I'm relieved you're all right.
Eat up. Drink some tea too.
When I was young,
however loudly I cried and screamed,
nobody came to help me.
So I ended up giving up.
On that day,
I neither cried nor screamed.
But someone came to my rescue.
Like me?
Yes.
I slept really well that night.
And I didn't feel lonely.
I have a similar experience.
Ki Ho told me...
he left something with you.
- Yes.
- Do you want me to give it to him?
No.
He said he'd come for it,
so I'll wait.
Okay. Right.
Sure.
Make sure you don't lose it.
- I kept it in a safe place.
- Really?
Good boy.
Eun Ho.
I want to give you a present.
Wait.
Pick anything you like.
I think it may take a while.
Take your time.
Do you want me to take it out
for you?
Yes.
("Drawdown")
Why? Don't you like it?
- It's too heavy.
- It's for display purposes.
Hold on.
This is a book I want to recommend.
What do you think? Have you read it?
("The Life Before Us")
- I bought this today.
- Did you buy one again already?
I'm going to go now.
Aren't you going to pick one?
I'm a bit tired.
Can I come and pick one next time?
I'll make sure to pick one then.
Of course.
Come back anytime.
Eun Ho.
(Restricted area)
I'm going to go this way.
On the tenth floor,
nothing will open up
without our fingerprints.
I'll take you home.
I just want to take a walk.
All right, then.
- Get home safely.
- Thank you.
- Are you going home?
- Yes.
Did he just let you go?
- What?
- Didn't he say he'd drive you home?
He did, but I just wanted to go
by myself.
- All right.
- Goodbye.
You should take your cake.
- It's fine.
- No one will have it except you.
- Take it and have it with your mom.
- Okay.
("The Life Before Us")
Why are you back so early?
What about Eun Ho?
- He said he'd take a taxi.
- Is that so?
- Did I do something wrong?
- No.
I...
This is a book I want to recommend.
Have you read it?
- I bought this today.
- Did you buy one again already?
How can that be a mistake?
He never told us
about his bag being snatched.
But I asked him if he bought it
again when he said he bought one.
He's a smart kid.
He would've picked it up.
Let's hurry.
Goodness, that brat.
Doo Seok.
He ran up to the rooftop.
Hey.
Hey, kid.
If you're a guardian of Ko Eun Ho
of Shinsung Middle School,
please come to the front desk
immediately.
I repeat.
If you're a guardian of Ko Eun Ho
of Shinsung Middle School,
please come to the front desk
immediately.
You must save him no matter what.
Hello?
Yes, this is the Millennium Hotel.
There was an accident.
Please hurry.
- Is he alive?
- Yes. Hurry up.
He's the chairman of this hotel.
You can go.
Hurry!
(Hyeju Medical Center)
(Operating room)
Darn it.
Lord of salvation.
I entrust the soul of your child,
Choi Dae Hoon, with you.
I pray in the name of Jesus.
Amen.
It's a miracle, isn't it?
What do you think the opposite
of a miracle is?
- Guess.
- Common sense.
The occurrence of a miracle is
against common sense.
You look like you were expecting
a different answer.
It's doubt.
All doubts are erased
when you want a miracle to happen.
Detective Cha didn't doubt
the miracle at that moment...
because she felt relieved...
that the boy survived that fall.
The problem is
that she strongly doubts us now.
- What?
- She's with Sun Woo on the rooftop.
- And?
- And there is...
a pulley for the life line hanging
on the rooftop...
which is medium length.
Sang Ho,
I was in a hurry that day,
so I forgot to consider the length.
- The length was...
- It's all right.
It's all right.
- Let me see your hands.
- What for?
Turn them.
It must have hurt a lot.
It's okay. They're only chafed.
It's going to hurt a bit more.
(Descending Life Line)
Attention! I need to use
the kitchen for a while.
Our appointment is soon.
We should go.
It'll be rude to get there late.
Excuse me.
(Baek Sang Ho)
Yes, Sang Ho.
What?
You need something sweet.
Chocolates were sold out,
and this was all they had left.
I'm fine.
Your brain needs sugar to work.
I always...
crave something sweet
when I'm tired.
And I miss my family.
What about you?
I endure it.
I wish you'd stop looking at me
that way.
I think I should
keep looking at you.
You know what?
When I go back home,
I can have delicious dinner,
have a conversation,
make jokes, and watch television...
with my family that I love
That makes me feel better.
But you'll be left alone...
to think about the case,
the victims, and the perpetrator.
How do you always endure it in life?
Since my friend was
brutally murdered,
I've been living that way.
You should go now.
There's nothing you can do
from now on.
Let me say hello to Eun Ho first.
Bye.
Yes, Sun Kyung.
No, I'm having dinner at home
with you.
Yes.
Wait for me. Okay.
Have you...
You must be hungry.
Do you want to go and eat?
I'm fine.
I need to talk to Mr. Ko Hee Dong.
He needs some rest.
He's severely burned,
but above all, he's in shock.
I found out that the life line was
replaced after Eun Ho fell.
I need the persons concerned
including you to testify.
Sure. I'll cooperate
as much as I can.
We'll give you a call
when we're ready.
Are you going to let her leave?
I don't want to hurt her.
But I won't have a choice.
I still want to see her in torment.
Let's go eat.
- Wait outside.
- Yes.
What's going on?
Mr. Lee also dropped by.
Let's have a seat and talk.
Aren't you going to tell me
what's going on?
You still hate me, right?
- Why would you bring that up now?
- But you still trust me, right?
You know that Eun Ho is my friend,
and I'd do anything to protect him.
I trust you.
And I don't hate you.
But I also don't like you.
You're the most reliable person
I have now.
Then listen to what I say.
Stay close to him for a while.
- I will.
- And...
don't trust anyone...
but me.
He was probably rappelling down,
and someone caught the rope.
So he must have been pulled back up.
That's why he untied his belt.
Our initial investigation was not
enough because of Dae Hoon's body.
You two will go to the hotel,
meet the first reporter,
and find out
if they found anything strange.
Okay.
Didn't you get the call
to stay away from here?
I didn't hear it
from Eun Ho's mother.
- I want to hear her say it.
- Just leave.
Are my records the problem?
Did Sun Woo tell you?
There must be a misunderstanding.
This whole situation has nothing
to do with you.
It's a measure I took
as the investigation made progress.
Is it turning out bad for Eun Ho?
Have you reported what happened
in the hospital to Mr. Baek?
Yes, because he was curious
about Eun Ho's condition.
Did something happen to Mr. Baek?
Just go.
Let me see Eun Ho's face
before I go.
Not now.
Aren't you curious
about my relationship...
with Lee Sun Woo?
He was my homeroom teacher
in high school.
I smashed him with a chair.
Whatever this is about,
I believe you have to talk...
to Mr. Lee, not me.
Are you the one who witnessed
the accident and reported it first?
That's right.
Did you go outside
right after you heard the sound?
Yes. I heard the sound and went
to the site of the accident.
It must've taken two minutes
at the most.
I called 911 right away.
Was there anyone around the site?
No, but...
when I called and told them
the name of the hotel,
they said
the ambulance already took off.
We're having a sumptuous feast
now that your brother is here.
What did you put in here?
Uncle.
Don't be distracted,
and eat your food.
Okay.
You seem to have gotten lean.
Don't skip meals already.
- Really?
- No, you look great now.
- It's perfect.
- What do you mean?
His cheeks are drawn.
Oh, right. Ji Won.
Who will you save
if your dad and uncle are drowning?
How can a child save an adult?
Let's say you are a grownup.
Uncle.
- Why?
- You're bigger and stronger.
Is that right?
Is that why?
Ji Won, listen carefully.
Your dad can't swim.
But your uncle is good at swimming.
He's good at running and kendo too.
Then I'll save Dad.
Are you brainwashing her
to save your husband or what?
Make sure you save me.
- I'll save you both.
- Both of us?
You better eat a lot
and grow up faster then.
Eat up.
- Is it tasty?
- Yes.
Good.
Dong Myung.
- Don't act like we're close.
- It's late.
- Where are you going?
- To earn money.
To work part-time?
Right, to work part-time?
Are you good now?
A convenience store?
A delivery center? A gas station?
Are you okay?
No. I want to harm myself.
Be careful already.
Move the boxes quickly.
Do you want to work all night long?
What are you doing?
- Hello, ma'am.
- Min Sung is missing!
When?
You two violated another law.
Min Sung, you aren't allowed to work
because you don't have permission.
Minors are not allowed to work
after ten o'clock at night.
Didn't you know?
I know,
but he needs money to survive.
What time do you finish work?
- Six.
- Can you handle it?
- Yes.
- I'll wait in the car.
- Let's have breakfast later.
- Okay.
That's the situation up until now.
And one more.
- Ms. Yoon.
- Okay.
Someone already made a report
before the first witness did it.
The reporter had the voice
of a young woman,
but the number was
under the name of a man in his 50s.
Once the kid survives,
he'll be a dangerous witness,
but they saved him without a hitch.
Because the kid has to be alive
for them to get the thing.
It fits perfectly
with Ms. Cha's assumption...
that the one behind everything
must be...
the one that is after
what Jang Ki Ho gave to Eun Ho.
If this map is right,
it means one of them is the demon
that Lee Young Sik met.
What on earth are they looking for
that they're causing all this mess?
I'm curious like crazy.
Mr. Han.
Why aren't you saying anything?
That's who I am.
I'm taciturn and introverted.
This will be a difficult fight.
Our chief wanted
to close the stigmata case...
and make it his achievement
before he retires.
But Lim Hee Jung is involved
in another case.
His superintendent position must be
higher than he expected.
- Just follow our convictions.
- What, you punk?
The case has gotten big,
so let's resolve it nicely
and make it our achievement.
And about the chief,
he's going to leave soon anyway.
That makes sense.
Ms. Cha. Continue.
No.
I'll do it.
How much do we know
about Jang Ki Ho's whereabouts?
Byung Hee and I are checking
security camera footage.
He left the hospital
and moved to Chueui-dong.
Didn't Seo Sang Won use to live
in that neighborhood?
Check the footage in the periphery
captured during the incident.
Okay.
For now, the only way
we can use against the hotel...
is violating the fire law.
We need a search warrant,
but under what ground...
That is why we must find Jang Ki Ho.
And Lee Young Sik too.
We must make him speak.
We also need Ko Eun Ho.
If he wakes up, we wouldn't even
need a warrant to arrest them.
He's just a kid.
How did he make such a choice
in that situation?
I wouldn't have been able
to do anything if it were me.
He's smart unlike kids these days.
I think I know who influenced him.
The investigation will become
complicated from now on.
Do they look alike?
They have a similar aura.
Their faces look
somewhat similar too.
That sounds about right.
Could it be their personalities too?
It'd be too bad for him then.
Eun Ho is not like me.
He's sweet and thoughtful.
That is why we could be friends
for a long time.
(Ko Eun Ho)
We enjoyed the food a lot.
- Thank you.
Your grandsons all look handsome.
They should be actors.
Either one of you should sit
in the passenger seat.
- Mr. Hwang.
- Yes?
Can I go buy some beverages?
Okay.
The man Eun Ho saved.
What about him?
Maybe he isn't all better yet.
He sent his acquaintance
to school to meet Eun Ho.
- Did you tell him about Eun Ho?
- No.
I didn't want to surprise him,
so I just took his number.
Do you have it with you?
- Yes.
- Give it to me.
- Did you get the number?
- Yes.
It's the man
who's in touch with Jang Ki Ho.
I met him...
on the day Seo Sang Won died.
We haven't been in touch since then.
If he wasn't going to see you,
why did he ask you to meet the boy?
He left your number, not his.
I don't know anything
about his intention.
Why are you
looking for Ki Ho though?
If he calls you, tell him...
that the boy who saved his life
almost died because of him.
(Baek Sang Ho)
Did you sense anything?
I told him
that Eun Ho almost died,
but he wasn't surprised
nor did he ask me what happened.
Tail him.
Hi.
Track his locations on the day
Eun Ho saved Jang Ki Ho...
and the day after he had
his backpack snatched.
Why?
They took his backpack, but couldn't
find the thing and showed up to him.
That means Eun Ho put the thing
somewhere else...
- in those two days.
- Okay.
It won't take long. Go to a cafe
for a cup of tea or something.
I already did. Do it within the time
I finish drinking water.
Let's do a round of sparring
after the case ends.
I'm going to beat you up to a pulp.
I'm not like how I used to be.
- Hello?
- I emailed it to you.
Unless the kid didn't have
his phone with him,
it's just the vicinity of the school
and his house.
Thanks.
- Yes.
- Hurry up and turn on the news.
- Why?
- They're talking about you.
This is an exclusive report.
Detective Cha, who was at the site
of stigmata murderer's suicide,
has turned out to have been
a close friend of the eighth victim.
If the reason why she didn't give up
on catching the killer...
for nearly 20 years was
for personal reasons,
not a sense of duty
as a police officer,
we need to reconsider the situation
of that day.
She's been known to have watched
the last of Seo Sang Won...
who committed suicide during
an arrest attempt on the 30th.
Detective Cha of the SCS of
Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency...
has been known to have the last
conversation with Seo Sang Won...
on the day of the incident,
but the police briefing to inform...
Eun Ho.
I found out quite a lot.
But seriously,
were you fearless or brave?
How did you think of jumping off...
of such a high building?
How did you think of unbuckling
the belt?
Good job...
for getting away from those thugs.
No.
Thank you for being alive.
Ms. Cha.
You...
Did you wake up?
What about the flower pots?
What?
Are they fine?
Eun Ho.
(Nobody Knows)
Should Eun Ho know the truth...
when nothing will change
even if he does?
Does it mean he'll be in danger
if Eun Ho's memory comes back?
Pray to Father.
The Father who comes in secret
will pay back.
Father, Father.
How come no one tells me
why I became like this?
I wish he doesn't remember it
like now.
You fell from a ten-story building.
Young Jin.
What do you mean
I should save Jang Ki Ho's life?
Ko Eun Ho woke up.
Is that true?
Is it true you let him go
on purpose?
The disciplinary committee
will be held in three days.
Before that, you're on standby.
You can't do anything from now on.
This is Cha Young Jin. Go on.
I'm Jang Ki Ho.