(Episode 9)
What are you doing
in someone else's house?
It's someone else's place
for you too.
I called you many times
to see you.
Do you remember me?
We met at school earlier today.
Sorry I touched it
without any permission.
I did it because I wanted
to talk to you alone.
It must be hard...
by the thought that your friend died
because of you.
Why is it because of me?
It's not like I told him to die.
If you think so,
that makes me feel relieved.
Let's talk for a few minutes.
Are you really Eun Ho's friend?
Yes.
Like you and Choi Dae Hoon.
You look comfortable
in the photo I found in his phone.
I heard everything
from Detective Hwang.
He said...
he'd scare him a bit. That's all.
I believe you.
But I don't believe
that Eun Ho extorted money.
Because you're on Eun Ho's side.
I thought he was a boy who couldn't
tell a lie or do bad things.
But I was wrong.
He could do anything
if he wanted to.
However, I realized one thing
for sure.
He has neither told a lie
nor done a bad thing...
just for himself.
Doesn't it hurt?
- Of course, it does.
- But does it...
lessen your sadness?
The better your condition gets,
the less you'll hurt yourself.
How do I get better?
Eun Ho got injured and Dae Hoon died
because of me.
How would I ever feel better?
One of my friends...
was killed by a murderer...
when she was 18.
She called me three times
before she was killed,
but I was just lazy
and didn't answer them.
I'd thought she died
because of me for a long time.
But that's an awful idea.
Whether I'd answered her calls
or not,
murder must've not been committed
in the first place.
It's the murderer that's thoroughly
responsible for my friend's death.
It's the same for you.
Eun Ho's fall and Dae Hoon's death
aren't your faults.
Your fault is...
that you neglected the violence
Eun Ho was about to fall victim to.
That's all.
What happened after that...
has nothing to do with you.
It's not your fault.
Uncle Dae Hoon.
Ki Ho.
It's been a while.
Who are you?
Oh, well.
Don't you go to New Life Church?
- What?
- I...
just saw the picture of it,
so I came in.
That was on it even before I brought
that scrap here.
Get out.
I'm sorry. I'm leaving now.
I'm sorry.
Goodness.
I don't know where to start
to resolve this misunderstanding.
I wish I could show you
everything in my mind.
We can help you do so.
Sang Ho.
Chairman Baek.
Chairman Baek Sang Ho.
That's nice to hear.
You should live long...
so that I can hear that longer.
I was going to tell you
at the right time.
Ki Ho said he had something
to get back from a boy,
so I just waited until he gets it.
Do you know what it was
that he needed to get back?
Well...
I thought he'd keep his my shut
if I'd been too nosy.
Darn it.
Sorry, I interrupted you.
I have to lift my head...
to talk to you, and you know,
my neck hurts.
This is way better now.
I like this place.
There's nothing around here,
so no one would know
what happens here, right?
I've had wrong thoughts
about you so far.
If I'd known what kind person
you are,
I wouldn't have used petty tricks
for that chicken feed.
What you need isn't just Ki Ho.
You need what the boy has.
But only Ki Ho knows what it is.
Am I wrong?
- Go on.
- I'm offering you a deal.
I'll talk Ki Ho into saying
what the boy is keeping.
Drink it.
You've lost this much water
already while crying.
I'm sorry but I need you
to check something for me.
- What is it?
- I'll show you some photos.
Just tell me if you recognize
anyone from the photos.
Will it be all right?
Yes.
I don't know him.
I don't know this guy.
It's late. Let's go home.
These guys...
You showed the photos
because of Dae Hoon, right?
Did he do wrongdoings with them?
I don't know yet. I'm checking
all the possibilities.
I know Dae Hoon isn't a good guy.
Still,
he has sympathized with me
and been nice to me.
He was the only one...
that I didn't have to pretend
to be fine.
Did he know...
that you habitually hurt yourself?
Yes.
Did you know
about his night blindness?
There are too many light sensors
in his place.
I also checked his medical record.
You two really knew
almost everything about each other.
I also thought...
I knew everything about Eun Ho.
I'll come back again.
We should see often,
and call me anytime.
Make sure you don't ignore my calls.
Okay. Bye.
(Mr. Lee Sun Woo)
Min Sung.
Dong Myung.
Why did you do it?
I was on the phone
with Eun Ho's mother,
and I've been waiting
after I heard you were here.
How did you get hurt?
I tripped myself hard this time.
Why didn't you take my call?
I had a lot to think about.
You're a hypocrite.
I told you to stop bothering me
and stop worrying about it.
But...
you ignored me, kept poking me,
and threw me off guard.
When he said one lie,
the first thing you said to me was,
"Why did you do it?"
Before you asked me
if I really did it,
you said: "Why did you do it?"
I'm sorry.
Your friend must...
still have the habit of stealing.
Hello?
Yes.
Are you on your way home?
- Yes.
- Go straight home.
Hurry up.
- I will.
- I'm hanging up.
I'll get going.
Are you going
to your brother's hospital?
I'll take you there.
No thanks.
Min Sung said that he hurt himself.
I'll fill you in on the way.
Let's go.
(Chairman Baek Sang Ho,
Manager Oh Doo Seok)
Did he tell you why he did it
to Eun Ho?
Not yet.
His chauffeur is the perpetrator,
right?
They're still investigating that
too.
He is.
That's why Min Sung went all crazy.
Dong Myung.
About Min Sung's chauffeur...
What?
He's dead.
How?
Kevin Jung killed Choi Dae Hoon.
Mr. Lee.
I don't have the details yet.
And...
I'm sorry,
but I can't tell you even if I did.
I told Min Sung
to beware of his chauffeur.
I told him that he's bad.
You didn't know.
Even if he's dead,
he's still a bad person.
Min Sung is...
also a bad person.
Though he's bad,
since someone close to him died,
it must have been sad
and hard for him.
I was in the same class with Eun Ho
in second year in elementary school.
But it's so delicious.
- And?
- I feel bad about the people...
- who can't eat it.
- Like who?
One of my classmates.
You shouldn't have brought it up
if you weren't going to tell me.
It was a long time ago.
I was very little at the time.
- It sounds fun.
- Forget it.
Gosh.
So...
we were in the same class
in second year in elementary school.
He asked me why I didn't have
a father.
So I told him:
"He died because he had
too many shrimps."
Did you know your friend was
allergic to shrimp?
That's why I said that to him.
That's so mean.
What did he say?
He kept crying.
So I told him that my father died...
because he was too full
after eating all the shrimps.
He started following me since then,
so I hung out with him.
Then he started ignoring me
overnight.
His mother told him not to hang out
with poor friends.
I was a poor boy with no father.
Does he...
still ignore you?
I met his eyes,
and I ignored him
when he waved at me.
Well done.
Min Sung,
are you allergic to shrimp?
- How did you know?
- Eun Ho once told me about you.
I should have asked him your name.
I sent...
the answers for the midterm exam
to his cell phone.
I didn't tell him they were
for the midterm exam, though.
I wanted to be friends with him
again.
My grades went up, but he said...
that he couldn't write the answers
because he already knew.
Did Eun Ho tell you to confess?
I begged him,
but he wasn't going to let it go.
He said that he'd tell the school
if I didn't.
So that's what you meant when you
said he gave you a hard time.
Yes.
My mother...
is going to prison, right?
Maybe.
But you shouldn't blame yourself.
You're only responsible
for your own wrongdoing.
Was Dae Hoon ever
going after Eun Ho's bag?
To destroy evidence on his phone.
I've never thought about that.
But someone must have opened
Eun Ho's locker.
Do you know who it was?
But I saw a man.
Here at the Shinsung Middle School,
I've seen light and darkness today.
Everyone, do you know what
differentiates humans from animals?
After that,
Eun Ho asked me
if I had opened his locker.
Was it one of the guys
in the photos earlier?
Then I would have said
I've seen them.
If we find this man,
will you be able to verify it?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
The things you told me today are
a great help.
- Really?
- Yes.
Call me if you want to talk to me.
(Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin)
I've told you everything.
You can talk to me about anything.
- Okay.
- We should go.
They'll be worried
when they find out you're missing.
Go inside.
Goodbye.
Dong Myung.
Can I see your brother before I go?
He's probably asleep.
You're right.
Good night.
- Yes, Mr. Lee.
- Yes.
You sound tired.
- Were you sleeping?
- That's what I'm about to do.
I see.
I'm sorry. You should go to bed.
Why did you call me?
What do you mean?
I just wanted to hear your voice.
Good night.
- Why did he call?
- He just...
wanted to hear my voice.
He must have been worried about you.
Goodbye.
Min Sung.
Now I'm going to worry about you...
if you're sleeping well,
eating well,
or getting yourself together.
- Eun Ho won't like it.
- Well, I don't think that's true.
Even so, I'll still worry about you.
Can I?
Well,
- I'll think about it.
- Sure.
Think about it and call me.
If we're to make a deal,
there needs to be trust
or at least security.
But...
you only have that sly tongue.
"Look,"
"I am coming soon."
"My reward is with me,"
"and I will give to each person
according to what..."
"they have done."
Ki Ho promised that he'd reward me.
Then he asked me to find a boy...
named Eun Ho.
It means I'm the only one...
he can rely on right now.
I don't trust people.
I trust what they have...
in their pocket.
This whole time,
I've been so wrong about you.
I had no idea...
you were this gutsy.
Let me get this straight.
So...
even when your life is at risk,
you're running that tongue of yours.
This is me, Ki Ho.
Hello?
Is that you, Ki Ho?
- Yes.
- Where are you?
I was startled
because you weren't here.
Well, I had something to check.
Stay there. I'll go get you.
If I can't cut your hands off,
I guess I'll have to join hands
with you.
Look.
If I tell you
I'd become your tool...
without asking anything in return,
you won't be able
to trust me, right?
- I'm listening.
- Well,
you said you liked this place.
Buy it at a price 20 times higher
than the market value.
- Ki Ho is waiting.
- Fine.
I'll buy this place.
Sang Ho.
Was he also like that in the past?
I thought he was
just a foolish geezer,
but it's like he was raising
dozens of snakes in his stomach.
Are you really going
to buy this place?
- It's useless.
- Why is it useless?
It's not bad as a graveyard.
Good thinking, Doo Seok.
Let's bury him
at a nice place later.
Okay.
Not bad, Doo Seok.
(Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin)
Someone must have opened
Eun Ho's locker.
He didn't take anything out.
He put something in.
What did Jang Ki Ho give to Eun Ho?
You're here.
I've been so busy.
How did you like Dong Myung?
- He's cute.
- Like you in the past?
When I met you, I was 18.
Look at you.
Then again,
a three-year age difference...
is huge for kids around that age.
And I've become...
a totally different person
from that time too.
Let's sit down.
Take out the voice recorder.
Tae Hyung, the voice recorder.
Oh, okay.
It's not here.
What are you talking about?
Move.
What happened?
Was there any time
Dong Myung was here alone?
No.
Wait.
Yes, what is it?
Ki Ho went to see Eun Ho today.
I see.
Please keep up the good work.
Forget about the recorder.
Sit down.
Isn't it suffocating
to stay in this room?
It's better than the beginning.
- I've gotten attached to him too.
- As expected.
I guess having had you
guard Eun Ho was the right choice.
Well, are Dong Myung and Eun Ho...
- in the same class?
- I don't think so. Why do you ask?
- It's nothing.
- You silly.
I guess Mr. Baek is inside.
That's right.
Are you always with him?
- Mostly, I am.
- What is your name?
(Manager Oh Doo Seok)
On October 30, Mr. Baek went...
to Shinsung Middle School to present
a good conduct award, didn't he?
- That's right.
- I'm sure you were with him.
Right.
I see you aren't curious...
about why I'm asking you
these questions.
I rarely do anything useless.
I know you won't tell me
even if I ask.
My gosh, we've run into each other
twice a day in this wide world.
- Will you give me some time?
- Sure.
- Mr. Oh, you can leave first.
- Just a moment is enough.
Just go home and rest.
- See you again.
- Goodbye.
This afternoon, you asked me...
which one I'd choose if I had to.
Oh, the drug dealing?
Did you find the culprits?
And you said you desired
for salvation instead of justice.
Which side is justice?
And which side is salvation?
Gosh, you got me wrong.
An act of choosing itself...
is salvation.
You didn't choose.
Justice would...
punish them both, but salvation
would give them a chance...
without telling good from evil.
I mean,
I heard they were both missing,
which gave me a bad omen.
I wished at least
one of them would be alive.
I babbled on...
with that in mind.
I didn't know you'd be
bothered by it this much.
Didn't you go to New Life Church
for a long time?
Frequenting there for a long time
should be the right way to put it.
Whatever the case is,
you must know well...
about Lim Hee Jung
and Jang Ki Ho, correct?
They've devoted all their lives
to the church.
Why do you ask about them two?
It's our job...
to ask and listen
even without any reason.
That's right. But whatever you ask,
ask Chairman Yoon Hee Seob... No.
It should be faster to ask Sun Woo.
Mr. Lee Sun Woo?
Yes, he must've seen
and heard things since childhood.
Wait.
Did you not know?
You didn't know...
Sun Woo is the actual heir
of the Shinsung Foundation.
Gosh, what do I do?
I made a mistake.
You scared me!
It hurts.
What are you doing in here?
I didn't want to stay in my room.
Gosh. You gave me a fright.
What's wrong with you?
What happened to your face?
I got into a fight with a drunkard
on my way home.
But he was taken away by the police.
Seriously.
You learned taekwondo
and kendo when you were young.
Aren't you going to use that?
How can I use that?
The other person will get hurt.
Don't hit them. Get punched
and then avoid it.
All right. I get it, so get out.
Get out.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Did you have an argument
with Hee Seob?
No. I left the room
because I felt like...
we'd start arguing if I stayed.
He's super sensitive right now.
Did something happen at school?
There is always something at school.
But he shouldn't bring it home...
and worry his family.
I knew it.
What are siblings for?
Really? Tell me honestly.
If Hee Seob and I fell in the water,
who would you save first?
You can be childish at times.
I've always been childish,
so hurry up and tell me.
Sorry.
See? I told you so.
You just abandoned your brother.
Hee Seob is Ji Won's dad.
Goodness, I'm Ji Won's uncle
and your little brother.
That's not about being siblings.
It's about relationships.
If Hee Seob
and one of your students...
fell in the water,
who are you going to save?
Sorry.
Don't just lie down.
Wash up and go to sleep.
Okay.
Goodnight.
- Yes, goodnight.
- Right.
"A person..."
"can't live without love."
"But..."
"I can't promise you anything."
"I have to wait and see."
"I..."
"loved Madam Rosa."
"And I'll continue to miss her."
I'll stay for a little bit.
You can stay for a long time.
I'll go get some fresh air.
All right.
("The Life Before Us")
I found your bag.
You read the book.
I like the last verse
of the last chapter.
Soo Jung complained...
she couldn't understand it
when she was reading it.
But she also said
she came to like the book...
because of the last verse.
However, for me,
the last verse of this book
has changed.
"I can't tell you."
"But..."
"please help me."
Eun Ho.
Was it because of Dong Myung...
or Min Sung?
Or was there something else?
There isn't such a world
where no one gets hurt.
So I chose
a side of not getting hurt.
But I don't know
if you will get a chance to choose.
Eun Ho, make sure you wake up.
Then I will...
Sang Ho. Go inside and sleep.
Sang Ho.
Sorry.
It's cold out here,
so I was telling you...
to go inside and sleep. Sorry.
Thank you, Hee Dong.
What?
I was having a nightmare.
What was it about?
I went back to when I was a kid.
You poor thing.
You must be getting hassled
in your dream too.
Young Sik.
Wasn't it so horrible and painful
yesterday?
You'll be tormented
in the future too.
Shall I kill you?
So that it doesn't hurt anymore.
(Woosung Hospital)
- Thank you for the food.
- You're welcome.
What? Hey!
Did the sun rise
from the east today?
Well, the sun actually rises
from the east.
It was a joke.
The sun rises from the west
in Venus.
Was that a joke?
Which part of that was funny?
- The reason why it rises...
- Hey, did you guys only buy yours?
- Do you want it? I didn't touch it.
- Is it sweet?
I only go for sweets.
It's Americano. You can have it.
- What's this?
- Caramel macchiato.
- Macchiato?
- Gosh, I'm going to die.
I really am going to die.
I just got here,
and I want to leave now.
- Don't I look bad?
- I can't tell.
You always look bad.
- Do you have a huge worry at home?
- No, I don't.
Then why did you decide to live
as if there's no tomorrow?
- Do you have a death wish?
- Sir.
When you're tired,
sweet coffee is the best.
It's caramel macchiato.
You should live a long life.
Caramel goes best with macchiatos.
I feel younger already.
Let's get to work.
Good morning.
You're all here early.
Detective Kim got here first.
When you reach my age, you'll find
yourself waking up early.
You're talking about age again.
I slept like an infant
when I was your age.
Let's start our meeting
so that I can get to work.
Let's begin.
As Eun Ho fell, Dae Hoon drove to
the abandoned building by himself.
Then he got in a fight with Kevin.
Kevin gave him a drink to calm down,
and then he blacked out.
Under Kevin's directions,
he hung Dae Hoon's body.
- What do you think?
- We need more details.
Why did they get in a fight?
What were they talking about?
He was a bit unstable.
Apart from that, he's lying.
You said Dae Hoon drove
by himself, right?
He drove through those dark roads
with the headlights off...
when he had night blindness.
He wouldn't have been able to see
anything.
He already admitted his crime
with Kevin.
Why would he lie about that?
First of all, he doesn't know
that Dae Hoon had night blindness.
Secondly, there could have been
another accomplice.
When he said he met the demon,
he could have meant the person
behind it, not because he was high.
This is getting more interesting.
We need to find the weak spots
of Young Sik...
that made him follow
such ridiculous instructions.
- Team One will take care of it.
- Yes.
- What about Hee Jung's funds?
- We're still waiting for a warrant.
Even when we have the warrant,
we'll need more information...
to check all her accounts.
We need more teams on this.
- I'll call for backup.
- Yes.
And...
Can I speak first?
- Yes.
- You've gotten nicer.
I found something.
Shinsung Foundation purchased lands
to build a university.
But it turns out
that Lim Hee Jung...
invested in the construction company
several times.
How much?
A total of 15 million dollars.
Where did she get all this money?
Is this also from the church?
If an unregistered investor dies,
- what happens?
- It'll be troublesome.
How did you find out about this?
I could have bought a house
with the money I paid...
- to treat my sources.
- You're still arrogant.
Find the source of the 15 million
dollars when you get the warrant.
Okay.
I found a lead
from Min Sung last night.
On the day Eun Ho received
the good conduct award,
he saw a young man
walking down an empty hallway.
After that, Eun Ho asked him
if he'd opened Eun Ho's locker.
He's still asleep.
- Doo Seok, how long are you...
- Just leave him.
Why? Is he sick?
He's been busy day and night
in the last few days.
- He must be tired.
- What?
Say it so that I can understand.
It means I worked hard
thanks to someone.
Thanks to whom? What kind of...
- Me?
- You have quick wits.
- What did I do?
- You have the body...
that leaves a strong impression
everywhere you go.
And I have to do all your work.
Doo Seok.
When you speak so kindly to me,
I feel like I could give you
my liver and gall bladder.
I don't need
your liver and gall bladder.
When you die,
you can give me your kidney.
It looks so healthy.
You look thin and pale.
Get some more sleep.
That crazy freak.
You're okay, right?
Sure.
Sang Ho said
he got me the best one...
so that I can use it
for a long time.
Ki Ho gave something to Eun Ho,
and then his bag went missing.
Someone is looking for the thing
that Ki Ho gave him.
That someone might be behind this...
chain of events.
(Millennium Hotel,
One Life Foundation, Baek Sang Ho)
The parents are complaining.
I have no idea how they all
found out in a day.
They don't even want to summon
the school violence committee.
They want him expelled
or transferred.
Can't we just be honest with them?
That's the problem. We can't.
- What do you mean?
- Tell him, Ms. Kim.
If we reveal the truth,
people will know
that Min Sung hurts himself.
How would he be able to bear
all that?
Kids think Dong Myung is accused
of something he hasn't done.
And Min Sung...
should be protected
for what he's done?
To be honest,
we don't really need Dong Myung
in our school.
Min Sung's mother said
that she had an idea.
It could also be...
a good opportunity for Dong Myung.
Did you tell him about this?
Yes, roughly.
Where is he?
He left without a pass.
Let's quit if we're going to run
the school this way.
Mr. Lee?
I don't care
if it was my father's will.
Calm yourself down.
You're a teacher.
Don't call me a teacher.
It makes me feel sick.
Look over there.
- What?
- Look over there.
Ms. Cha.
You seem very upset.
What are you doing here?
She has some questions
about Jang Ki Ho and Lim Hee Jung.
The reference interview?
Didn't two male detectives come here
last time for that?
I needed more information.
Can I stay here?
Sure. You're family.
- Did you tell her?
- I heard from Mr. Baek yesterday.
Have you heard about the source
of Hee Jung's 15 million dollars?
It's Chairman Baek as far as I know.
Does that give him the right
to invest for Hee Jung?
Does that...
have to do with the fact that
she was murdered by Seo Sang Won?
Wait.
Why are you investigating
Sang Won's case?
It's my case.
You didn't tell me that.
Should I have told you?
Until now, we've been...
She's the detective that was there
when he died.
One last question.
Please tell me everything you know
about Ki Ho.
Not you.
You couldn't even remember his name.
I need the security camera footage
and the list of visitors...
of the day Eun Ho received
the award.
I can help.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of help.
Chairman Baek must know well
about Ki Ho.
Does he?
Did you not know?
You didn't know...
Sun Woo is the actual heir
of the Shinsung Foundation.
It feels like it'll be difficult...
to find the people who know Ki Ho
let alone himself.
When you find him,
please give me a call.
I can't promise you that. Goodbye.
Sun Woo.
You're still a teacher,
and I'm the chairman...
yet.
I'm sorry. It was...
a mistake.
We'll talk later.
Let's go.
He hasn't said a word
for three hours.
He even refuses to tell us his name.
Are you also remaining silent?
- Something's been bothering me.
- What is it?
- He looks different.
- What?
He looked like he gave up everything
last night. But today,
he looks determined.
Do you think something happened
overnight?
You'll feel safer
during the time you're here.
Then you'll want to tell them
the truth.
The chairman is certain
that you won't,
but I need to make sure.
You're good-for-nothing,
but your older sister is
a hard-working person.
Your nephews are adorable too.
Stay still.
You could hurt yourself.
We don't care about those kind
and adorable people. Why?
Because they aren't ours.
Young Sik, if you put us in danger,
we will destroy yours...
in a way that will make
them wish to die.
Don't cry.
If you keep your promise,
good things will happen
to your family.
If you behave,
you'll be released soon too.
Okay?
Ms. Cha.
Here. I put what you asked in here.
- Okay.
- Are you just going to leave?
I'm the victim
of what happened yesterday.
- Right.
- Well,
I guess the assault against me
isn't that important to you.
I'm sorry. I'll get back to you
as soon as possible.
Do you suddenly feel uncomfortable
around me?
Why do you think so?
This is the first time...
you came to school
without calling me beforehand.
Is that right?
Should I've told you sooner...
that my brother-in-law is
the chairman of this school?
Are you assuming
that I hid it on purpose...
and followed you around?
I don't, but it's better we behave
more carefully from now on.
I'll call you later.
Did you find Min Sung's weakness
that only Eun Ho might've known?
Did you...
find out about Min Sung's secret?
You're answering my question
with another question.
I think...
I've missed the chance.
Where's Han Sol?
I don't know.
He hasn't been around for a while.
Han Sol.
Joo Han Sol!
(Detective Hwang In Beom)
- Mr. Hwang, Han Sol is...
- Dong Myung, it's me.
Dong Myung, when are you coming?
Put Mr. Hwang on the phone.
Mr. Hwang, he wants to talk to you.
Hi, Dong Myung.
Where are you?
Dong Myung!
Joo Han Sol, come down there.
I want to stay a little longer.
Come down!
Why would you yell
at a sick kid?
I'm sick too.
I'm rotting inside.
Because of that punk,
I might be forced to transfer.
Why?
I don't know.
Why me, not you?
How could you...
bring my brother here?
We met at the convenience store.
He bought me ice cream,
and I asked if I could come here.
All right.
Have it your way, then.
Let go...
- if you don't want a beating.
- You said you quit being a thug.
Why must you transfer because of me?
If I tell you,
- will that make any difference?
- I...
took the exam with the answer sheet
which my mom sneaked away.
I'm going to tell the school.
Was Eun Ho aware of this?
Do you want to come in?
Do you have snacks?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Here.
Let's continue with the meeting.
Joo Dong Myung is
killing me, seriously.
I should submit a leave of absence
or something.
I'll be in charge of Dong Myung.
I'm requesting...
that he moves to my class.
We're considering the school
transfer option at the moment...
Why must he be transferred
when he did nothing wrong?
Mr. Lee! Keep your voice down.
It's true what happened
to Min Sung is unfortunate,
but Dong Myung shouldn't
be punished for this.
Min Sung and Dong Myung's picture is
up on the online school noticeboard.
- What do you mean?
- Min Sung wrote a posting.
(Min Sung would've smashed
the wall in the science room...)
(with his forehead
if it hadn't been for Dong Myung.)
(Detective Hwang In Beom)
Hello, Mr. Hwang.
Did you see the noticeboard?
Dong Myung didn't make a smile
any bigger than that.
Was that you?
No, it was Min Sung's idea.
I only persuaded Dong Myung.
I wonder if it'll be effective.
Of course.
Kids are way better than grownups.
Tell Dong Myung
that he's in my class from today on,
and he can no longer cut school.
Okay.
Did you hear that?
He said it so loud.
(Manager Oh Doo Seok)
Mr. Oh?
Could we meet for a moment?
I think it's this man.
Are you sure it's him?
I think he's similar,
but I'm not sure.
I see.
Thank you. You need to rest up now.
- Ms. Cha.
- Yes?
Dong Myung and I
might be in the same class soon.
- Is that possible?
- I don't know.
That's what Mr. Lee said.
I need the security camera footage
and the list of visitors...
of the day Eun Ho received
the award.
(Good conduct award ceremony)
(Emergency management training)
A descending life line is
used to escape from a building...
lower than ten stories
in an emergency situation.
Several people can use it in a row.
It consists of a support fixed
to a wall and a descending tool.
Eun Ho.
Focus on the video.
You'll practice this later.
Okay.
(Descending Life Line)
Why did you leave the gym
and go to the main building?
To go to the bathroom.
Isn't there any bathroom in the gym?
It was crowded.
There's one on the first floor
of the main building.
Must I tell you why I didn't want
to use the one on the first floor?
I'd like to hear about it.
I'll tell him on his behalf.
No, it's okay.
Mr. Oh had a kidney transplant.
He decides the amount of water
to drink based on his daily urine.
It's important to check
the amount of his urine.
As you can see, he's very sensitive.
He prefers quiet bathrooms.
Excuse me.
It can't be helped.
It's detectives' job...
to ask and listen
without any reason.
(Descending Life Line)
(Length: 30 m)
Mr. Lee.
What in the world
are you doing here?
Eun Ho...
What about him?
He didn't get pushed by someone.
To live...
To survive,
he jumped off himself.
(Nobody Knows)
He's just a 15-year-old kid.
What on earth was chasing him?
The culprit wasn't trying
to hurt Eun Ho.
Ko Eun Ho...
We better kill him, right?
Because he's the result
made by Ms. Cha Young Jin.
Don't you want to go
to Mr. Baek's room?
Ms. Cha, you need to watch
this news report.
Exclusive news. Detective Cha
of the stigmata murder case...
has turned out to have been
a close friend of the eighth victim.