Ma'am, stay awake.
Hang in there. We're almost there.
You need to stay awake, okay? Yes, stay awake.
Please stay focused. Okay, let's do this. Now, push!
That's great! Good!
You need to breathe. One more time. Push!
Give me a long one. Push!
Gosh, how adorable.
Look at you.
How are you so adorable? My goodness gracious.
Ha Ri, your baby is so cute. Do you want to see?
Come on. Let's go to your mommy, my dear.
There's your mommy.
Mommy. Mommy.
That's your mommy.
Mom!
"Hello, I'm 39 years old, and I'm single."
"I was single yesterday, and I'm single today."
"So I'll probably be single tomorrow as well."
"I haven't been able to meet a guy for a very long time."
"And now, love is like a miracle that might never occur to me."
"But I still have hope, so can you please show me..."
"a small miracle by sending me some snacks?"
Ms. Jang Ha Ri, I can totally relate.
But let me tell you that the small miracle...
you've desperately hoped for has come true.
You won the draw, so you will be given...
a box of snacks!
Your name is Jang Ha Ri. You're 39.
And you're single.
You've had sex before, right?
Yes.
It was in 2010 during the Vancouver Winter Olympics.
It was 10 years ago? So you didn't have sex recently?
I did go on blind dates but...
When did you finish your period?
A month ago.
It's time I have my next one.
Recently, I started having very bad period cramps.
Last month, I almost fainted due to the pain.
I even had to go to the ER once.
Then why didn't you get it checked?
Well, I was too busy working day and night.
I don't have much time today either, so I just want some painkillers...
and go home after I take the AMH test.
That means I just need to take a blood test, right?
Your hormone levels will tell us the age of your ovaries...
and how many eggs you have left.
Do you plan to have babies?
When are you getting married?
I don't know when I'll get married.
I'm more urgent to get pregnant than to get married.
So I'd like to freeze my eggs.
I want to freeze...
a few of my healthiest eggs until I finally meet the one.
Excuse me.
Me?
Yes?
Is there a pharmacy nearby?
A pharmacy?
It's over there.
Hey! I'm going to call the cops.
Stay right there! Hey!
My gosh. Hey!
Hello?
Help!
There's a pervert here! Please help!
- Hey! - He's over there!
- Stop right there! - Is this the police?
- Let's go. - Take him.
(Episode 1: You Want to Know Why I Can't Get Married?)
Ha Ri.
Are you really going to freeze your eggs?
Why do you want kids? I get sick of them just by looking at them.
How is it possible to hate kids?
I fall in love just by looking at them.
It's hard to come across a woman like you.
Who has babies these days?
I wouldn't have married if my husband...
insisted on having a child.
How can you marry a man who doesn't want kids?
There they are.
Which one's better?
- This one. - Okay.
Nice.
Why ask for my opinion then?
- We're here. Hi, everyone. - Hello.
- Welcome. - Hi, guys.
You're here.
Hi, Pororo.
I see you're with a friend.
You've been loved for 13 years now since your debut in 2003.
What's your secret?
Could you tell us why people find you so charming?
Is there a reason why your goggles always stay on?
I found him.
Mr. Nam!
Sang Hee, please don't run.
- Mr. Nam! - My gosh.
- I found him. - You did?
He's on Outstagram.
It's him, isn't it?
Yes, it is Han I Sang.
I see he's back in Korea.
What on earth has he been up to though?
(Posts 13, Followers 4, Following 0)
(Following 0)
My first time on Outstagram.
My first time doing embroidery.
My first time running a marathon.
My first time being in a human slingshot!
Unbelievable.
He not only has money but a lot of time on his hands.
Life must be fun.
Then I guess I'm happy for him.
Just don't mention him to Ms. Jang though.
Why not?
Because I value my life.
Hello.
Gosh, you're here.
- Hello. - Hi, there.
My goodness. How have you been?
You like that?
Can I really come back?
Ha Ri scares me, you know.
She'll throw a fit once she finds out you're back.
But what can she do?
It's my house, not hers.
Don't worry about her and do whatever you want.
I wish you luck. Sure thing.
What a good day to wreak havoc.
(Fun Dance Aerobics)
1, 2, and disco. 1 and 2.
1, 2, and disco. 1, 2, and disco.
You've had it hard enough.
It's about time you lived a decent life.
Eat food that's above average...
and wear clean clothes.
Do Ah, it's Daddy!
Do Ah, I'll hire you the best nanny ever.
Thank you for hanging in there, my daughter.
Gosh, you're adorable.
Do you like this?
How adorable.
Will our model fall asleep now that her stomach's full?
Sweet Ji Yul laughs and smiles when she's not hungry anymore.
Isn't that right, Ms. Smiley?
How cute.
She won't nap because she wants to play.
Her daily routine is play, eat, and then sleep.
It's best for her to eat, play, and sleep though.
I bet you fall asleep while breastfeeding.
How did you know?
That's common among babies who play, eat, and then sleep.
Also, I see you drinking coffee.
You don't nurse frequently enough, and it's keeping you up at night.
What are you, Sherlock?
You scare me now.
I really need to stop nursing her at night though.
Keeping a journal of her daily routine...
will show you what changes are needed.
Feed her for an hour, let her play for two,
and have her nap for two hours.
Follow that for a few days, and it'll come naturally for her.
You should get married soon and have one of your own.
Nice house.
Magazines and advertising agencies have been calling nonstop...
now that they know you're back.
Are you forcing me back to work...
when I'm not done taking a break?
Three years is more than enough.
Would you seriously turn down a photo shoot with an A-lister?
Yes, I would.
- Why? - Because you suggested it.
What are you, a moody teen?
Must you be like that when I'm here helping you move?
You're making me uncomfortable so put that down.
This is my way of kissing up to you.
Sign with my agency.
What do you say?
No thanks.
You have time for a marathon but not to call me?
You have time to fly but not sit down with me?
You have time to go to an amusement park...
but not contact me?
You have time to sew but not return any of my texts?
Auntie!
I can't believe I responded to that.
Did he seriously just call you Auntie?
Apparently, I'm the same age as his youngest aunt.
Unbelievable. Does he not know that this is a workplace?
Why haven't you said anything?
How can I?
I practically encouraged him myself.
I can't suddenly blame it on the fact that I was drunk.
If he's not too daft, he'll change his ways.
Are you back from your interview?
Well, I'm coming back from a meeting.
I can hold my own in one now.
I'm proud of you.
- What's wrong? - Menstrual cramps.
I've been running errands for my mom when she's on her period.
She taught me that menstruation is nothing to be ashamed of.
Is it severe?
I can't get you any water right now.
It's all right. Let me help.
This way.
Excuse me, but she has menstrual cramps.
Could you hold the elevator for us?
I'm sorry about this, but she has menstrual cramps. Be careful.
Please let her cut in line. She has menstrual cramps.
Careful.
Are you all right? Is it bad?
Can you hold your head up?
Are you sure you're all right?
What now?
The elevator is here.
Auntie, come on. We need to move.
Sorry about this.
Going up.
Just hang in there, all right?
- What the... - What did my mom say again?
She described the pain as excruciating.
Ms. Jang, hang in there.
What do you do for menstrual cramps?
- Auntie, we're here. - Move! Out of my way.
Unbelievable.
The pain must've been unbearable.
Who is she?
Oh, she's Deputy Manager Jang Ha Ri of "The Baby".
He can't take a hint at all, can he?
I'm afraid Ha Ri will be stuck being called Auntie.
(Use a wet towelllllllllll)
(Recruitment Qualifications)
Hyo Joo, come here for a second.
- Hyo Joo. - Yes?
What is this?
"Infertility can be treated with herbal tonics."
Is this what they wanted?
Dr. Ko said he's getting a patent for herbal tonic treatments,
and asked us to stress it.
Still, you can't write down whatever they say.
Let's not get sued.
We're already the ugly duckling in the company.
What choice do we have? It's Advertising's page.
I'm too nice to fight.
So Yoon.
Sir.
You scared me.
What? You're scaring me.
Must we write Dr. Ko's advertisement piece like this?
It's good.
"It has an excellent effect on treating infertility."
That's how they wanted it written.
There you go again. Just because your name won't be on it.
If people complain,
the reporter whose name is on it must take responsibility.
Seriously. Stop being so inflexible.
They wanted to stop advertising with us. I worked really hard...
to get this.
Work with me.
Some readers know these advertisement pieces are ads,
but some believe the articles and go to them.
And it's about infertility. Imagine how desperate they must be.
Will you be accountable if this is all a lie?
- Why should I be accountable? - Exactly, so I won't print it.
I really don't want to do this, but we'll lose the advertisement fee,
so I'll report this to the higher-ups.
Go ahead.
Come in.
Ms. Jang wants to take out the ad.
- What? - The ad on herbal tonics...
Ms. Jang.
Ms. Jang, get up. Get up.
Please get up.
Ms. Jang.
I know I adore you, but you can't do this.
That's why I'm doing this.
You impinge on my editing authority thoughtlessly,
so I'm going to lie here thoughtlessly as well.
Strictly put, you're not the editor-in-chief.
You're only the acting editor-in-chief.
That's why I'm lying here in Ms. Shim's place.
Do you miss her? Shall I call her in?
No, no, no, no.
Why would you call in someone who's resting after having a baby?
Ms. Jang.
This is why you can't get married.
Oh, my gosh. Again.
You need to watch what you say before I make you pay.
Fine. I get it, so get up. Let's talk.
I'll remove the article.
Fine, but since Editing took it out,
Editing must take responsibility.
Yes, sir. We will.
Since it affects our department's income.
Are you done?
Yes, sir.
Ms. Jang. Stay and chat with me.
I don't want to date you.
You punk. I'm married with kids.
It's been so long since I saw you. I'm happy, that's all.
I even prepared your favorite liquor.
You haven't been to our studio in a while, right? Want a tour?
- I looked around already. - Okay.
I assume your trip was nice.
You'll get back to work, right?
- What? - Just because.
I'm sure you'll get a lot of job offers...
although you took a long break.
So I figure you'll need a studio as soon as possible.
It'll be really hard to find a studio.
Rent shot up.
You need all new equipment too.
I'm just thinking of you.
Things are bad overall,
so I thought...
it would be good to share the studio...
with me.
No.
Isn't Jang Ha Ri working at "The Baby"?
My gosh. You even remember her name.
So Yoon, what happened to the story about the kid who picks his nose?
I'm still picking at it.
Stop picking at it, and give it to me.
Hyo Joo, what are you working on?
- Breast pumps. - Stop squeezing it out. Finish it.
Yeon Ho?
I'm almost done with the constipation piece.
Sure. It's time to stop going.
Ha Ri, can we take a break?
I'm starving.
Should we have a snack?
- Yes. - Thank goodness.
Was there anything else?
Like jewelry or clothes?
You know I made my personal woes public...
just to feed you guys.
They must have really pitied you if they chose your story.
So Yoon, you have unparalleled skill in hurting people's feelings.
Don't be so sensitive.
Why don't you have a boyfriend?
You're attractive and successful.
Are you too picky?
Hey. What do you take her for?
She may not look it,
but she falls in love easily.
She falls for any old schmoe.
She's easy.
That's right. I'm super easy, but still, right?
That one was the best.
She fell for a guy in front of the studio in three seconds.
Just how hot was he?
Hey.
He wasn't hot.
He was crying.
I never saw a guy cry before.
They say a man's tears...
make the heart cry.
I thought she was a total psycho.
Psycho? She's not that bad.
You didn't see the look in her eyes.
And I don't want to.
I don't like aggressive girls.
So? Did you hit on him?
He was a psycho.
Forget men. I need to have kids.
What should I do? I'm turning 40 next year.
You can get married quickly and have a baby right away.
With whom? Where and how will she meet him?
Sign up for a matchmaking service.
I used to be a VVIP at Get Married because I was "marriage material".
Now, I get calls from second marriage services.
Girls. Stop saying useless things.
Find a good-looking rich guy.
Good-looking rich guys will never date old women.
Agreed.
- Not a chance. - Choi Hyo Joo.
Yes?
You don't know the half of it.
It's hard to even date a normal guy.
The only decent guy I can date at my age is either already married...
or dead.
Who gets married these days?
You should just stay single all your life.
What?
She... She's right. My friend doesn't date either.
She thinks it's pathetic to be obsessed with dating and marriage.
Then am I going against the current trend?
I guess you could say that.
It looks like Generation Z has a hard time understanding you.
- Right? - Yes.
I hate her the most.
The problem might be...
that you're too obsessed with marriage and having babies.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
I'm so exhausted.
Should I tell you guys a scary story?
I'm your future.
How is she my future?
Why would I end up like her?
You guys are in big trouble.
Let's see.
Is the new editor-in-chief single?
You say you understand women who just became mothers.
But I can easily tell you're not married.
What does a single woman know about childcare?
Is a single woman allowed to write articles about childcare?
A mother can't be a journalist.
The job requires too much overtime work,
and you can barely even go home.
What they say in magazines are all true.
But it's hard to do what they say when you actually become a mother.
Reading about childcare is different from actual childcare.
But you wouldn't know since you're not a mother.
Ms. Jang, why don't you move to "Unique" or "The House"?
You've been working at "The Baby" for way too long.
It'll be hard to get promoted once Ms. Shim returns.
And even if the position for editor-in-chief becomes vacant,
you won't be able to get the position.
You know...
single women can't become the editor-in-chief of "The Baby".
It's not like I'll never get married.
- What? - I want to have a baby.
Once I start dating, I'll get pregnant before the wedding.
And when is that going to be?
Don't stay at a place where there's a slim chance for you to grow.
Go to a place where you could become an editor-in-chief.
I'm telling you this for your own sake.
Ha Ri rarely even comes by.
She's a deputy manager, so you guys won't even meet.
My gosh.
Did you find a place to live?
I moved in today. It's near the park in Hangang-dong.
"Hangang-dong"? "The park"?
Why does it have to be Ha Ri's neighborhood?
- Hello. - Hey, welcome.
I'm glad you're here.
- Have you been well? - Yes, of course.
(Menu: Today's Anything, Whatever the Owner Serves)
What's "Whatever the Owner Serves"?
That's today's new menu.
The Pacific saury gratin. It doesn't taste that fishy.
- You should try it. - Sure.
I'll get you a new pair of chopsticks.
It sounds delicious.
- How did it taste? - It... It was delicious.
- Thank you for the food. - No problem.
(Jo Jo's Restaurant)
(Interview with Pororo)
- Here's the Pacific saury gratin. - Thanks.
- Enjoy. - Okay. Thank you.
My goodness.
Oh, gosh.
If you drink this, it means we're going out.
What if I don't drink it?
Then we won't ever meet again.
I'm jealous.
There you are.
No! Please!
Mom?
Hey!
- Hey, you're here. - My gosh.
What are you doing here?
I moved here yesterday.
Move where?
- You moved into our house? - Yes.
Why? Why would you move into our house?
I'm a resident here.
That's absurd.
Hey, did my mom let you rent this place?
She was the one who offered to let me live here.
She never told me anything about his.
You must be tired. Let's eat breakfast.
No, it's okay. I don't need to...
Hey!
Are you joking with me? Get out.
I have nowhere to go.
Did you lose the house to Jeong Won?
What's your problem?
Why would I lose the house? We got divorced because of her.
She even paid back the money she borrowed as alimony.
At least she had some conscience.
- That nasty brat. - Yes, she's a nasty brat.
How could she do that to me?
But you have no conscience.
You show up in five years and have the guts to chat with me?
How could you look at me like nothing ever happened?
Then I won't look at you.
My gosh.
To be honest,
I just can't seem to raise my daughter all by myself.
My parents want me to live with them in the States.
But how can I?
My friend, you're the only one I can trust and rely on.
After all this time?
Jeong Won hated my guts,
so you didn't think twice about cutting me from your life.
But now that she has left you,
you come back to me pretending like nothing happened?
My daughter Do Ah is in the other room.
Talk to me again once you've said hello.
Unbelievable.
You must be Do Ah.
Gosh, you're a sweetheart.
Do you not wash your own kid?
Babies are supposed to be messy like this.
This is practically normal.
Why is her bottle so small?
At eight months, she should be having at least 240ml.
How did you know...
that Do Ah's eight months old?
You drew a short straw when it comes to Dads.
Gosh, you poor thing.
I feel bad for you, Do Ah.
She's adorable, isn't she?
Yes, and that's why I'm giving you a day.
You have until tomorrow to leave.
Really? When she's this adorable?
When she's only eight months old?
When we have nowhere else to go?
All right. I have a deadline to meet, so I'll be back at 2am.
Leave the baby and move out.
Give her back or I'll call the police.
She was scary, wasn't she?
Nasty lady!
Please don't cry.
You're actually Jae Young's mom, aren't you?
It killed me...
to see him go from dandy to scruffy.
We'll make room for him at mealtime...
and see if he's feeding his daughter properly.
He's also been drowning himself in alcohol, so we can stop that.
Why is that so difficult?
He got divorced, not terminally ill.
Why do we need to take care of him?
Okay, fine. He can leave, but I'm kicking you out too.
What? Why?
It's my house, not yours.
I let you live there rent-free, but you're acting like the owner.
Who are you to dictate whom I give my room out to?
You're really his mom, aren't you? Only that would make sense.
I actually wouldn't mind swapping kids.
Now, hang up. I need to get back to my workout.
The stage of childbirth?
The government is supporting more infertile couples now,
so I thought we could choose an infertile couple,
have the government pay for the procedure,
and write an in-depth piece until they give birth.
Sounds great.
You know the program where one experiences pregnancy?
My superior actually suggested something new.
Should you accept it,
pitching your idea would become easier.
What's this new idea?
Fathers-to-be experiencing pregnancy is getting old.
My superior quietly suggested...
how fresh it'd be for a journalist to write an in-depth piece...
on how it is to be pregnant.
Goodness.
Why me though?
Are you going to smile or not?
Must I go this far to bring in money for advertisement?
I'll make sure that everyone knows of your sacrifice.
Let's think of the bundle of joy in your oven and smile.
Smile!
- Its name is Unexpected. - My goodness.
That's a scary name for an unborn baby.
It's because the baby came to me unexpectedly.
Since that's the case, give me an unexpected smile.
Over here.
- All right. - Hurry.
- Smile! - Ha Ri, you look great.
- Over here. - Smile!
- Let's smile. - Ha Ri, smile.
- Smile. - That's the spirit.
- Do we have the shot? - Let's look.
How does it look?
It's good, right?
- Do we have it? We got it. - The one before is better.
Why not?
Leave it on. I'll wear it on my way home.
I'd rather have the full experience.
Are things all right at the studio?
It seems like he can barely hire you.
He's sharing the space to keep up with the rent.
- I heard I Sang's name. - Who?
Why? How do you two know each other?
- I don't know him. - They went on a blind date.
You two were set up on a date?
That's not the case.
He cursed her, you know.
He put a nail right through her heart.
What?
I truly believe that it's the reason why...
you haven't been able to date.
Must he really be mentioned at this moment?
I'm exhausted as it is, you know.
Just a second. Let's pose here.
I saw him once before, and he seemed okay.
He's a lunatic in disguise.
That's the guy?
Han I Sang. He's one of the hottest photographers right now,
and he's two years older than you.
How should I put this?
It seems like he has a story to tell.
Is that a deal-breaker?
It'll be odd not to have one at that age.
No wonder my radar spotted him.
- Are you sure about this? - Not everyone is perfect.
All that matters is that he's sane.
Hold on a second then. I haven't talked to him...
- since he got back from overseas. - Sure.
- Stay right here. - Got it.
I see you came ready for business.
Will you finally be getting married next year?
Well, if he's the right guy, then I'll sink my teeth in him.
Remember the woman I mentioned? She's right there.
What's wrong with her?
She's just shy, that's all.
I promised to set her up with a dashing bachelor.
I'm not interested in marriage.
Since when?
- This moment. - Why?
I should date him for a year before tying the knot, right?
You haven't even met him yet.
Exactly. We'll meet today, date for a year,
and get married next year.
Why must one get married?
Because it gets lonely.
Being single is easier.
How can you live without family?
I'd like a husband who I can call my best friend...
and have 2 sons and 2 daughters.
Since I'm too old though, I'll settle for two kids.
I'm not interested in a nagging wife.
I'd rather earn enough money for myself,
be clear of children invading my life,
and stick to having the TV to myself.
I hear you, so look into his eyes and have his gaze locked on you.
You know how an audience is like.
"Really? My goodness." Be excited about what he says.
While you do that,
touch him gently and subtly.
Touch him when we just met?
Ha Ri, touching is Flirting 101.
One lingering touch...
led to my first kiss with my husband.
A kiss?
But we're not even in love yet.
Why do people value marriage as a priority?
It's not just old-fashioned but despicable.
Are we cavemen trying to preserve our species?
Fine. Unbelievable.
I get it.
Let's not talk about it anymore, okay?
Goodness, your biceps.
You must like the snow.
I do.
Me too.
- Mr. Nam... - Soo Chul...
I heard you're college alums with Mr. Nam.
I am.
I'm Jang Ha Ri. I'm a reporter with "The Baby".
It's nice to meet you.
I see. It's nice for you. Same here.
One lingering touch led to my first kiss with my husband.
I hear you're a great photographer.
Is your expertise in magazine advertisements?
What are you doing?
You made a big impression on me when I first saw you.
What's your deal?
- Pardon? - You have no fear.
What if I'm a bad guy?
You're not a bad guy.
You don't look like one.
I can tell.
Are you saying you can tell, so you fell in love at first sight?
If you felt like destiny was drawing you to me...
That's even sillier.
Excuse me. All I did was introduce myself.
Who introduces themselves so aggressively?
If you felt anything for me, it's desire triggered by hormones.
So don't hypnotize yourself with some romantic fantasy.
Wait, so...
are you saying I gave you...
a look filled with desire inviting you to do something?
You're not all that.
Ms. Jang Ha Ri. I know we just met, but let me give you some advice.
If you're lonely,
get a dog.
I realized...
he was a real psycho.
Do you have one with two stripes...
right around here?
No, that's the only design.
It would be nice if the fabric had a sheen...
and some embroidery around here.
Do you have something like that?
- No, we don't. - I see.
You don't have much.
- That narcissistic pig. - Seriously.
Don't worry.
He's so popular, he's getting his own studio.
Thank goodness.
Even if I run into him and by chance he recognizes me,
I'll pretend I don't.
Darn it. I lost my timing to avoid him.
Get a dog.
Long time...
I almost said, "Long time no see."
(Moai Stone Family Limited Release Pre-sale)
What did he say? Did he recognize you?
I ignored him first.
I thought you said something...
- Hey. - Stop faking it.
No...
Again? Does it hurt a lot?
Go ahead.
I'll take some meds and head to the office.
Give me that.
Goodness.
What's wrong with her?
Menstrual cramps.
- Let's go. - But...
Darn it.
It's okay. Go on.
Gosh.
It was on sale.
That was a good buy.
Oh, my gosh. I think her water broke!
Oh, no! You need to get to the hospital!
That's not it.
She must be having contractions!
Should we call you an ambulance?
She should go to the hospital where her doctor is.
The baby won't come right away. It's your first, right?
- No. That's not it... - Is it your second baby?
- Don't they come faster? - They do.
No, it's not a baby...
It's her third!
Oh, my gosh! She's so tough! She's a real patriot!
- You need to get to a hospital. - No.
- Let's go. To the elevator. - No. That's not it.
- Elevator. - Elevator. Hurry!
- That's not it. - Why is it so slow?
- Let's take the escalator. - That's not it.
We should take the elevator.
But it isn't coming!
- Move! She's having a baby! - Out of the way!
- Are you okay? - We're almost there.
Oh, no.
- Mister! Just a minute! - I'm not preg...
Mister! She's having contractions. Sorry.
Are you okay?
Okay, good. Excuse us.
Okay.
"Mister"? I'm not that old.
- Hang in there. - I'm okay.
- You are not. - I'm fine.
- Oh, no. - Listen to me.
- My gosh. - Let me go.
- Please let go. - Where's our car?
I'm telling you, it's definitely that way!
No, it's over here.
Where is it?
Where? Hey. Where is it?
- I'm telling you, it's this way. - That's not it.
- Hang on. - Listen to me.
They all look the same.
- Where is it? - That's not it.
Excuse me. Let me help.
Thank you!
That's great.
Good luck. Be strong!
- Where's your hospital? - Why are they doing this to me?
Don't worry. I'll take you there.
No, I'm okay.
- Good luck! - Good luck!
My gosh.
My gosh. It hurts.
Are you okay? Where should I take you?
Drop me off at any pharmacy.
I don't think I should.
I'll take you to the nearest hospital.
No, I'm okay. I'm really...
Please... Please slow down.
My gosh, please let go!
That hurts!
Gosh, let go of my hair!
My goodness.
Wait! Just a second!
Her water broke!
I told you I'm fine.
Gosh, okay. I'm sorry. I apologize.
Isn't she about to give birth any minute?
The doctor will be here soon.
My gosh, please let me go!
When did you start having contractions?
Gosh, I can't believe this.
- Let me check. - My gosh.
No. No.
Ma'am, you need to cooperate.
No. Don't.
- My gosh, it hurts. - My goodness.
Gosh, it hurts so much.
Is she going to have the baby soon?
Get an ultrasound scanner ready.
"An ultrasound"? Why?
May I talk to her guardian?
"Guardian"? I'm not her guardian.
I need to talk to you about...
Ms. Jang!
Where are you going?
Ms. Jang.
Ms. Jang, are you okay?
- Check her blood pressure. - Okay.
Gosh, what's on your face?
Why aren't there any burp cloths?
There's one.
Do Ah, I'll be right back. Wait right here.
I won't take long.
- What? - It looks like...
you have endometriosis.
If you take a look, these big bumps...
are signs of endometriosis.
And that's what caused the severe pain.
Why did you just endure the pain?
Is it something really bad?
No, you'll be fine once you get surgery.
You also took the AMH test so you could freeze your eggs.
The test says your ovaries...
are 40 years old.
To be honest, once you're past 35,
your ovaries aren't in the best condition.
So I honestly don't recommend you to freeze your eggs.
You should've done it in your 20s or in your early 30s.
But you're 39, and it's too late.
So is it impossible?
In your case, it's going to be hard...
to collect an egg that's healthy and is in its best condition.
Even if we manage to freeze it,
the egg could get damaged when it defrosts...
and gets fertilized.
Is there no way?
The chance for you to get naturally get pregnant...
is below seven percent.
Once you reach your 40s, it goes down to five percent.
And once you're over 43 years old, the success rate for IVF...
drops low to less than 10 percent.
There's a 90 percent chance...
that you could have a miscarriage before you're 10 weeks pregnant.
Does that mean I won't ever be able to have a baby?
Is it impossible for me?
It's already hard for you to get pregnant.
But if you get an endometriosis surgery,
you can't get pregnant for a year since you'll be taking drugs.
You lose eggs every month, so what will happen after a year?
Your chance of getting pregnant will get even lower.
The pharmacy.
I need to go to the pharmacy.
- Hello? - Where are you?
Why aren't you back yet?
I'm...
I don't know where I am.
I'm sure she brought some clothes from work.
Here... It should be here.
(Shoes that will take my baby to only the best places)
(A baby bottle that will help my baby grow tall)
(Write down what you want to be when you grow up.)
Enjoy your food.
- Okay. - Okay.
You can be rich and extremely smart,
but no one can ever beat someone who's happy.
That's because being happy is the hardest thing in the world.
But I hope you'll be able to achieve that, Ha Ri.
(Mom)
"Mom"?
You're the happiest person in the world.
You always smile every time you see a baby.
Every kid likes their mom.
My dream is to become a mom.
(Mom)
Ms. Jang, what are you doing here?
I'm... I'm looking for a pharmacy.
This can't be the end.
But why does it feel like it's all over?
No, it can't be.
Do you want to marry me?
(Oh My Baby)
I'm about to turn 40.
And I learned that it takes effort to date and get married.
Jae Young, try to spend some time with her.
Then you guys might grow feelings for each other.
- Hey! - I don't think this will work.
That's just our fate.
Should I set you up with someone in return for the gift?
We're all destined to meet someone. Don't search too far away.
- Find someone nearby. - Ha Ri!
You told me I'll fall for you.