(Dahan Hospital OB-GYN)
Excuse me, sir.
The patient left this behind.
She left? All by herself?
Yes.
Gosh.
A seven-percent probability to get naturally pregnant...
doesn't mean it's entirely impossible to have a baby.
But your fecundity will continue to decrease.
If you plan to get pregnant any time soon,
you can postpone the endometriosis surgery.
What would you like to do?
Do you want to get the surgery or get ready for pregnancy?
Then let's do a follow-up in six months.
If you still haven't gotten better, let's do the surgery then.
"Six months"?
Ms. Jang.
What are you doing here?
I'm... I'm looking for a pharmacy.
A pharmacy...
Do you not feel well?
No, I...
Why does it feel like it's all over?
This can't be the end.
Do you want to marry me?
It looks like something happened.
So I won't ask.
What?
I don't get what you're talking about.
I'm not interested in getting married.
- With whom? - With you.
Why would you marry me?
Do you want to marry me?
It was my way of thanking you.
I felt grateful enough to even propose to you.
Just consider it as a polite way of saying thanks.
You get that, right?
No, not really.
I see.
You don't get it.
I guess I should've gone with the common route then.
Anyway, I'm grateful.
I'd even be more grateful...
if you could forget about everything that just happened as well.
But...
You don't seem to be thinking clearly.
Can I give you a lift?
No, I'm good. I'm back to normal, so you can go.
- Ms. Jang... - I'm fine, so...
You're a polite one, aren't you?
That's enough.
Get back down here and let me do it.
Unbelievable.
I know how to replace a light bulb, you know.
Why would I let you have the pleasure?
Go back to watching the baby.
I find you cool either way,
so let me do the grunt work around here.
That's not why I asked you to come live with us.
The women in this family managed without a man for over 30 years.
Don't even think about being our handyman.
How can I not when I'm the only guy...
around the house?
The cutlery is what you'll grab.
That's how it is at your mother-in-law's.
My mother-in-law?
I'm just saying we're as close as that.
And have Ha Ri help raise Do Ah.
She'll do a good job.
Why would I ask her that?
As a stepmother...
"A stepmother"?
- We're a family again, aren't we? - Right.
Anyway, she just adores kids.
She's great at babysitting them too.
I know that, but why would I...
Here. Drink this.
Gosh, thank you. You didn't have to.
You need to go back to how you were.
It's herbal medicine.
You should've lived a good life, not come back as a scruffy dog.
Mom!
- Say goodbye. - Bye!
Really?
(My mom Ms. Ok Ran)
Yes, Mom?
Are you busy?
Not really.
Can you make it to Eun Joo's wedding this weekend?
I have a deadline to meet.
You'll be done by then.
Swing by if you can. Your aunt will be devastated.
I'll see what I can do.
You'll do what?
Did you know that you always use your deadline as an excuse?
Even your aunt knows that...
you're deliberately skipping weddings and kids' birthday parties.
It serves you right for letting...
your younger cousins get married first.
Missing family events like this only make them pity you more.
You should attend them with your head held up high.
- I... - Got it?
I didn't commit a crime, you know.
Why do you think I'd feel ashamed?
Can I only hold my head up high if I'm married with kids?
Okay, fine.
Mom, I...
What was that?
I'll have dinner ready, so don't be late.
Whatever. I'm hanging up.
Ha Ri!
What took you so long?
Ms. Shim is shooting lasers out of her eyes.
Right, of course.
Sure.
Ms. Shim, you're back.
I thought you had another week off.
How can I stay home when this is happening?
But the issue was solved.
Leave the Advertising Department to solve their own problems.
Why did you agree to wear the fake pregnant belly?
Still, it led to a deal.
Then take care of the Eggo photo shoot too.
Sorry?
Eggo said they wouldn't be renewing their contract,
so it's up to you to get them to sign with us again.
Send Ha Ri the related materials.
What? But I worked hard casting Na Eun as the model for this.
Why would that fall on my lap?
Why do you keep throwing projects at me?
I'm not in the Advertising Department...
If you want to patronize...
and order subordinates around, be the editor-in-chief yourself.
I didn't cut my baby's breastfeeding short...
just to hear you talk back at me!
I'll call it a day for now and get begging tomorrow.
Back to work, guys.
Gyeong Jin's getting married next month.
Tell me about it.
Everyone's finally getting married one by one.
Myeong Sook's son...
- got into Sehan University. - I know.
Is your daughter...
- a high school senior this year? - That's right.
- Gosh, time sure flies. - Tell me about it.
(Episode 2: Am I on the Right Path?)
Is she asleep? Why are all the lights off?
Gosh.
What on earth?
What are you up to?
You just can't be normal, can you?
Unbelievable. Here you go.
It's for you.
Your cousin's getting married.
It seems to be easy for everyone else.
That must be why you seem a little depressed.
Not really.
In my 20s, I thought marriage would happen to me naturally.
When I reached my 30s though, it became a test.
I needed to study about men, how to date them,
and go on blind dates that felt like interviews.
I'm about to turn 40 now,
and I learned that my efforts won't take me down the aisle.
What do I do?
What else? You can just give up.
If life happens as we want it to, no one would have a crappy life.
I might be in a different place...
if I had put in a little more effort though.
Well...
Anyway, I'm regretting my yesterdays...
and hoping that I don't lose my chance tomorrow.
Your life isn't so bad...
Forget it.
So what's up with your belly?
Gosh, get that out of there.
Let it be.
This is what I regret and what I might lose tomorrow.
I'd rather mope around like this a little more.
Sure, whatever.
Good luck then.
Unbelievable.
Gosh.
I came by to ask for a favor,
but you're in no position to help me.
What kind of a favor is it?
Ha Ri might grow old all alone at this rate.
She doesn't seem to want to get married.
All she cares about is her job now.
What if she lives a lonely life forever?
She wouldn't be lonely.
She'll find someone and live happily ever after.
Jae Young. Stay by her side...
and be with her.
You need to live with people to find new people.
If you two grow on each other, you can settle down together.
How could you say something so frightening?
- Is Ha Ri frightening? - Come on.
Think about it.
She and I are like brother and sister.
Exactly. I'm saying...
be close like you're brother and sister.
Darn it.
Seriously. She keeps worrying me.
Hey, get up. Let's have some soju.
Get up!
Get off.
Fine, you have beer.
Why you little...
What are you doing? Slapstick? Your face is funny enough.
Hey.
Take this and go. Don't come back.
What is this?
Do Ah's pajamas. It's a parting gift.
Bye. Let's never meet again. Go.
Why did you buy this?
I bought you that, so leave. I don't want to look at you.
Go.
I don't think it'll work with me. That's our destiny.
What are you babbling about? Go.
Since you gave me a gift,
should I set you up with a guy?
When did I say I needed a guy?
Do you really not?
You seemed to be kicking yourself for not trying hard enough.
Well...
I think it may be too soon to give up, but...
So? Should I set you up?
It's okay.
There's no guarantee that I'll meet a nice guy just because I try.
Well, if you know someone...
who looks nice,
is a good person,
and has a good sense of humor...
I don't care about looks, so an average guy will do.
But you wouldn't know anyone like that.
What was that? Is that a yes or no?
Are you saying yes if I know someone like that?
If you do, you can try setting me up.
There are too many voices inside of you, right?
Just stick to one.
Thanks for the pajamas.
Brush your teeth and go to sleep.
A seven-percent probability to get naturally pregnant...
doesn't mean it's entirely impossible to have a baby.
But your fecundity will continue to decrease.
Good. You're doing good.
Let me take a picture.
"Because I've never tried wall climbing."
(Share)
(This is The Baby!)
(Followers)
They're all pictures of babies.
Do Ah, where's Daddy?
Do Ah.
Daddy's gone.
Here's Daddy.
You didn't have to come. You could've just called.
- You jerk. - Why you...
Why did you come here? It's so sad.
There aren't many kids' zones.
You've been out for five months, right?
How about expenses?
I sold my house.
Aren't you going to work again?
I don't know. It's too hard finding someone to watch a baby.
Gosh. What is this?
Jeong Won asked me to give you her child support payment.
She abandoned her own baby. Tell her to stay out of our lives.
It's hard to become strangers even if you get a divorce.
Although I accomplished it.
Hey.
Want to meet a girl?
What's this? How annoying.
Mr. Nam.
I saw that guy. Han I Sang.
He's the one that said he didn't like me.
Why is he liking my post?
Was it wrong to like it?
What's going on? What are you doing here?
You follow people and like their posts.
Isn't that how you do social media?
Are we close?
Do you do that only with people you're close to?
People follow people they don't know.
I only follow people I'm close to.
- Then cut me out. - I didn't accept it. You cancel it.
Fine.
Are you two childhood friends? You seem very close.
Continue to be close going forward.
I feel like I should be angry right now.
You said I wouldn't run into her.
I tried.
But you two met before I was ready. This is very awkward for me.
You seem to hate me today.
You said you were so grateful, you could propose to me.
It was my way of thanking you.
I felt grateful enough to even propose to you.
I Sang.
No, Mr. Han.
Let's have a proper conversation.
Just us.
You won't keep using the studio, will you?
Why?
I'll set my schedule to avoid the times you're there.
Aren't you uncomfortable with me? I'm very uncomfortable.
I'm fine.
Are you still uncomfortable with me?
It would be weird if I were comfortable.
You told me to just get a dog when we first met.
If you look at it that way,
I'm the one who should've been more offended.
- About what? - Don't you remember?
What would offend...
Hey.
Hey. Where are you going?
What's wrong with you?
Sit down. Sit.
Do you despise women?
- What? - You said,
if a woman shows interest,
it was because of this and that.
Isn't that the same thing?
How did you develop such a twisted prejudice?
I'm about to develop a prejudice.
Do you think I don't understand because I'm drunk?
You're saying you don't like me.
I don't like you either.
Had I known you were a psycho, I wouldn't have mustered up courage.
You read me correctly.
I'm not the guy you're looking for.
What if you fall for me?
I swear you'll fall for me.
Who gets drunk enough to say something like that?
You told me I'd fall for you.
- So did you fall for me? - No.
- Do you plan to? - No.
Then what's your point?
Why are you taking it out on me?
You're the one who guaranteed it.
Anyway, I'll do my best to avoid you so things don't get awkward.
- I expect you to cooperate as well. - Sure.
Let's try our best not to run into each other.
- Okay. - That was nice and easy.
Here. This is for my drink.
What do you mean the photographer isn't here?
I have an interview with Yeon Ho.
Why isn't anyone here yet?
They're coming.
It's going to take over an hour to set things up and do the shoot.
Yeon Ho is interviewing a famous photographer from abroad.
I can't do both.
It's a cover shoot.
I can't postpone it. We also need to do a video shoot.
I had a really hard time casting Na Eun.
You know how popular she is these days.
- Aunt. - Did you hear that? Even guys...
I must be crazy.
Hello, I'm Choi Kang Eu Ddeum from the Advertising Team.
You were an idol star, weren't you?
You seem very familiar.
No, my last name is made up with both of my parents' last names.
You have two last names?
Eu Ddeum, what are you doing here?
Mr. Kim told me it's a very important client...
and that I should help you get a contract renewal.
He sent you here to deal with an important client?
I didn't know he trusted me so much either.
I promise I'll do my best to help.
Ha Ri, I don't have time. You need to make a choice.
No, I don't want to.
You don't want to?
That means you still can.
Can you help us just this once?
You do your job, and I'll do mine.
I'm only here to share your working space.
This is a great part-time job.
You can make money, get good practice,
and get the hang of it again.
Why would he practice with our cover shoot?
It's just a figure of speech.
Forget it. That's enough.
We're stooping too low.
I'm sorry for asking you a favor when I promised to avoid you.
But did you have to make us talk facing your back?
It's not like you have a really broad back anyway.
Gosh.
Hey, you're here. You came a long way.
- Hi. - Hello.
Gosh, they're here. My goodness.
Hey, give me the draft.
We don't have time.
Na Eun, you can stand right here.
Hurry up. We don't have time.
There's not much time, so I'll make it quick.
This is harmless to humans, so kids can suck on it.
Hey, don't put it in your mouth. It's dirty.
It's filthy.
Gosh, how dirty.
Is there anything else you'd like us to emphasize?
Right. And let's see.
It's very durable.
Kids sometimes throw stuff,
but it doesn't break that easily.
This is so weak.
And... And what else is there?
I have to urgently go somewhere.
Can you assemble everything back together?
Yes, of course. I can do it with my eyes closed.
- Don't worry. - Okay, thank you in advance.
- Sure. You should go. - Okay.
Bye.
How much time do we have left?
Seung Ho. Seung Ho, wake up!
What time is it?
- 3:50pm. - We have 10 minutes left.
- Gosh, my hands are shaking. - We can do it.
My goodness.
Aunt, is this how you do it?
I'm really busy right now. Will you please leave me alone?
Ha Ri.
I think you should take a look.
Is this how you do it?
You look adorable.
No, I can't do this. There's no time.
What are you doing?
I really need to go to Yeon Ho's interview on time.
If I'm late to this one, it'll be an international embarrassment.
What are you talking about?
- I can't... - We can't postpone this one.
- Please. - I have to go.
Please just take a couple of photos.
Give me the draft.
I don't like babies.
So you can be the one to make her smile.
What do I need to do?
She's a baby model, so make sure she smiles.
And the toys need to show.
The draft is right here. Do me a favor.
I'm sorry. Thank you, I Sang.
Sorry!
You're adorable! Look over here!
Na Eun, raise your hand! Smile!
Hey, can you smile a little?
She'll cry because of you.
Does my back still look small to you?
It kind of looks broader now.
Na Eun, let me join you!
Hey, look. Na Eun, look at the bubbles.
Look how pretty the bubbles are!
What about Mr. Kim in the Publishing Team?
People say he's gay.
What about Mr. Oh in the Monthly Fashion Team?
He's already dating someone.
What are we going to do with Ha Ri?
I can't believe there's no one...
to introduce to her.
If you date a colleague, you'll have a lot in common,
and it's also great because they understand your hardships.
But it's hard to actually date someone in the first place.
Would you date a colleague?
Gosh, no way. Our company sucks.
See? She works here,
but she wants to date someone who works at a better company.
You normally badmouth your colleagues, not fall in love.
Actually, I'm dating Seung Ho in the Camera Team.
- Since when? - Since when?
I asked him out the day Ha Ri said we'll end up just like her.
- You're amazing. - Thanks.
Anyway, there's a reason why people don't date their colleagues.
But if she fails to find someone outside of work,
we'll have to keep watching her live a sad life.
I know you'll be at the beauty salon.
I'm going to Gangnam for business.
I can easily drop by.
Okay. Bye.
Ha Ri, are you going on a blind date?
No.
Oh, I see. But still, you can't carry everything dressed like that.
It's the weekend, so there won't be a lot of empty cabs either.
Hey, you should give her a lift. You're also heading to Gangnam.
- No, I'm not. - You're not?
Forget it.
I'll see you.
But I'm sure that's heavy.
Or maybe not.
Hey.
I lied earlier. I'm heading that way, so I'll give you a lift.
- No thanks. - I wouldn't mind the company.
Well, I would.
I'll park here until you hop in.
We should stay clear of each other, so I'll get in the back.
Thanks.
Okay.
Thanks. Have a good day.
You said you're off to a wedding.
I can drop you off, so hop in.
Must I get the door for you too?
Thanks.
My cousin is getting married today.
You gave me a ride, so why don't you stay for a meal?
- No thanks. - The snow crabs are to die for.
I'll treat you to a meal next time then. Thanks.
Snow crabs?
- Auntie, congratulations. - Thanks, Ha Ri.
You made time out of your busy schedule?
It's true that I've been busy.
Anyway, head that way.
- Hello. - I'm so glad you came.
Gosh, thank you.
- Ok Ran! - My goodness.
The traffic was awful on my way here.
I can't believe you look prettier than the bride today.
Exactly. She should've known better.
Anyway, congratulations. You must be ecstatic.
Ha Ri said she couldn't come because of a deadline.
You have no idea how sorry she is.
What are you talking about?
Ha Ri's already here.
She's over there.
Gosh, congratulations.
You look stunning.
I sense the tears coming.
One might think you raised me.
You said you couldn't come.
It wasn't easy to free up my schedule.
Anyway, I even got you a huge gift.
As in what?
You should've told me that you were coming.
How can I cover for you when you don't tell me things?
Come to think of it, this is where my best shot lies.
Quite a number of bachelors will be here...
and watching the ceremony will plant the idea of marriage.
What on earth are you saying?
Stop shaking your legs.
I'm nervous, that's all.
Why would you be when it's not your wedding?
Next, we have a guest performer...
who will like to present...
a nuptial song to wish the couple's happiness.
It's none other than the bride's...
- cousin. - Where are you going?
Could you join us up here?
- What... - Ha Ri?
- Honey, goodness. - My gosh.
Hello, I'm Eun Joo's older cousin,
Jang Ha Ri.
I know I look young to be older than her, but still.
I'm only slightly older than her.
My singing isn't nowhere near perfect,
but I hope you enjoy it...
and consider it as...
my way of wishing her...
a happy marriage.
Cue, music.
Fill me with your love
I guess my love needs to be recharged
I can't live without you, I really can't
You're my battery that charges my love
I don't care if you're not super handsome
I don't care if you don't have the fittest body
But you who will care for me dearly
You are the man of my dreams
Hug me once more
Embrace me in your arms until my heart bursts
I guess my love needs to be recharged
That's why you're the one I need
Fill me with your love
I guess my love needs to be recharged
I can't live without you, I really can't
You're my battery that charges my love
Ms. Jang...
What on earth?
Why are you getting in people's way?
I'm not blocking anyone's path.
But because of you...
Why are you here?
My meal ticket.
I haven't had snow crabs before.
Only blue crabs.
Thank you.
The dining hall is this way.
I was just about to get lucky.
Ha Ri, that's enough. You look desperate.
If you know what I'm doing, start looking too.
How old is Eun Joo's husband again? 32?
Does he have an older brother? A young uncle wouldn't be so bad.
Don't embarrass yourself and just eat your meal.
Mom, can you keep an eye on him?
- Sure. - I need to go to the restroom.
- Go ahead. - Come to Grandma.
What would you like?
- Good boy. - Look at him eat.
My sweet little puppy.
Your singing was amazing.
Ha Ri, you've got a successful career,
so stick to living alone.
You haven't been able to get married or have a child,
so living alone would be more comfortable.
Who cares if you're a little lonely?
Just earn enough money to live in a retirement home.
Did you hear about the old people there...
getting beat up these days?
Only animals would do such a thing.
Tell me about it.
Dig in.
I'm going to get married.
My mom should be congratulated too, you know.
Please set me up with anyone decent you know.
Auntie, set a blind date if you find anyone.
Got it? Is everyone on board? Good.
Goodness, the snow crabs have been served.
- What? - Hold on.
- The snow crabs? - Auntie, wait.
Auntie?
Crabs...
They care more about the snow crabs than you.
Your aunt already set you up with numerous men.
Who would she have left for someone who's close to 40?
No one's been interested in you for a few years now!
Anyway, who gets married at a young age these days.
A lot of women marry at your age.
Don't think you're running out of time.
The man that's meant to be will turn up.
I thought it was my bad luck that kept me from marriage,
but you're having it tough because of me too.
You can't enjoy having a son-in-law and grandchildren.
What can't I enjoy? That's not all that great.
I enjoy myself just fine.
And...
don't look in strange places.
Look close by.
Don't you know?
The bluebird is in the small room in your house.
Why is that there?
(Han I Sang)
Why did you go to Gangnam?
I said I'd come here.
I went to watch a dance for a bit.
- A dance? - Yes.
Jang Ha Ri.
Here's the dancer.
Dancer? Where?
- Where? - Never mind.
- Hello. It's nice to meet you. - Hello.
It's dinner time. Why don't we go eat?
I ordered already.
What would you like?
Iced Americano.
- Pardon? - Just a minute.
Shall we go?
I want to have some more coffee. Their coffee is good.
Hot Americano.
- Yes. - Mine is iced.
Jae Young told you about me, right?
He said you were married briefly.
You must've been hesitant about meeting a divorcee.
Not at all. I get so much judgment for not being married.
There are times when I think being divorced is better.
I got married when I was 40 too.
You never imagined you'd still be single at this age, right?
No.
It gets harder to meet people the older you get.
To be honest, there's a lot of pressure.
I realized from being married,
that the couple's families must adjust as well as the couple.
It isn't easy.
Dating and marriage...
are all so hard.
Even if...
it takes a while,
why don't we get closer slowly?
If you say a while and slowly... How long?
It'll be hard to have kids if I wait too long.
Kids...
You can have kids when you're 60 if you have the money.
Even Trump had a son when he was 60.
A woman can't have kids in their 60s.
So, saying I have 10 years until menopause,
12 times a year for 10 years is 120.
I only have 120 chances at getting pregnant.
How many of those do you think will make it...
when I couldn't do it for 10 years? I don't have a guy.
I don't know when I'll get married.
And that's only when you have many eggs...
So my point is...
I envy men.
What's wrong, Do Ah?
Oh no. Did you wake up?
It's okay.
(Galaxy Cafe on the Hills of Montmartre)
Let's get yummies for our Do Ah.
Yummies.
Well...
Yummies for Do Ah's daddy.
For Do Ah's daddy.
Let's go.
Do you live nearby?
I live here.
I didn't think that guy would share an umbrella with you,
so I ran out and bought one.
Let's share.
Is this amusing to you?
You watched on purpose.
Don't be mad.
Don't you know how you apologize?
Why do you always show up during my most humiliating moments?
You're so... Every time...
Don't follow me!
But... I didn't think much of it...
and watched.
I didn't mean to humiliate you. I'm sorry.
Ha Ri. Wait. Ha Ri.
Ha Ri.
What...
Why did that...
My suit...
Oh no.
Ha Ri!
What is he doing?
What is it?
- Ha Ri, are you okay? - My suit...
What do you think you're doing?
- Let go of me! - What's wrong with you?
- Where did you come from? - Who are you?
Are you a mugger? A pervert?
What do you do for a living?
How do I look like a pervert or mugger to you?
You're more suspicious because you look normal!
And you shouldn't fall for it just because a guy talks to you.
What... What are you babbling about?
Let go!
Seriously.
- What? - You punk.
This is so embarrassing!
Stop it.
What?
Let go.
Darn it.
Oh no!
Stop it.
Jae Young, stop it already!
- Hey! Let go. - Wait.
Stop it!
Let go!
I'm so cold.
Anyway. Sorry about that.
I didn't know you were her colleague.
He isn't my colleague.
Ha Ri and I are like siblings.
And I thought she was in danger.
You punk.
You should get along with your colleague.
Why would you have a fight in the middle of the street?
- We're not colleagues. - We're not colleagues.
What about your blind date?
What were you doing outside...
with your jacket all ripped apart?
Did you get rejected again?
I didn't get rejected.
Do you think I get rejected all the time?
What's your problem?
Watch how you talk to me.
You're so mean.
You should do something about your nasty temper.
I was there.
She didn't get rejected.
I mean, she didn't exactly get rejected by him.
Anyway, they weren't meant for each other.
No one did anything wrong.
Gosh, what's the point of trying so hard?
Love only left me with heartaches...
and hardships.
Go. Just leave.
No! I can't break up with you!
We've done enough!
Why do we need to break up?
Nothing's ever worked out after I met you.
I'm sick of you!
It becomes meaningless once time passes by.
No matter how much you loved each other.
Put it back on.
I'm going to live a happy life.
So don't waste your time hating me.
I hope you become happy, too.
All break-ups are painful and horrible.
It leaves you with a heartache or a broken memory.
Or even both.
It just ruins you.
(Divorce Registration)
I'll take the furniture I bought.
I'll see you in court.
Gosh, that wench.
Yes, you're right.
Drink up. You poor punk.
Drink up.
Judging by the look on our faces,
no one here is in love.
I never once felt happy because of a guy.
So I wonder why I was so obsessed with getting married.
People talk as if I'm too old to get married anyway.
I'd rather be single and happy than become miserable...
just so I could get married.
This is nice.
Here.
(Eun Young)
My gosh.
What took you so long to come? Your deadline was over ages ago.
I thought you were a ghost. What's that on your forehead?
Why are you guys always so clingy?
"You guys"?
Jae Young moved into our place.
My mom let him move in.
"Yoon Jae Young"?
Hey, why would you let that traitor...
move into your place?
What a shameless jerk.
Why would you let him move in with you? Why?
You guys, say hello to Aunt Ha Ri.
Bow!
- Hello. - Hello.
Hey, you cutie pies. Have you been well? Here you go.
Hey!
You should get counseling. Your temper is getting worse.
Hey, take a look at me.
How do you expect me to be sane?
You need to come over and spend time with the kids...
if you want me to stay sane.
What? What's wrong?
Why are they so quiet?
Hey! Get over here!
- Run! - Hey!
Hey! You guys!
I told you not to touch the rice! Open the door!
They really drive me crazy.
I know you can't live without your kids.
Yes, of course. I can live without my husband but not my kids.
But that's only because I'm a mom, but it's better not to have kids.
Hey, don't get married.
It's so tiring to live as a mother.
I mean...
You always meet adorable kids...
and interview moms who are rich.
That's why you think it looks nice to be a mom.
But look around you. Do you envy this?
You'll realize how precious your current life is...
once you don't have time to buy coffee for yourself.
Eun Young, I can't have kids.
How can I have kids when I can't even get married?
My gosh. Hey.
I told you not to run.
This isn't your house. At least ring the bell before you...
- Here. - What's wrong?
Can you sleep with her tonight?
My friend's father passed away, so I need to help at the funeral.
What's wrong with you guys?
Did you do this, Do Ah?
Was it you?
My goodness, really?
You need to sleep now.
It's time for bed, Do Ah. You're burning.
Do Ah.
Are you okay? Why are you so hot?
What... What do I need to do?
Let me see.
Do Ah!
Do Ah.
Why won't he pick up?
My gosh.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with her?
She has a fever.
- Gosh, she does. - It's okay.
- Should I get a fever reducer? - No, it's okay.
I just need the baby diary. I'll take her to the ER.
Okay. Call me if you need something.
Okay. It's not a big deal. You can go to bed.
My goodness, poor baby. Oh, gosh.
Don't skip your meals, and get good sleep.
Thank you.
You should eat if things aren't awkward between you and Jae Young.
We're good.
It's not because of Jae Young.
I need to go because I have to help Professor Park with his thesis.
You guys don't even keep in touch?
Doesn't she ever call? You guys have a baby together.
Hey. Hello.
Okay, you should go.
She didn't come by to say hello. She's unbelievable.
But I guess that's how she became an assistant professor so quickly.
Good for her.
(Crazy Ha Ri)
She has bronchitis.
You should know that as her mom.
Actually, I'm not her mom.
Her father...
He's getting drunk somewhere and isn't picking up my calls.
That piece of garbage.
So you're babysitting the daughter of a piece of garbage.
I'll prescribe three days' worth of medicine,
so make sure she takes it all.
If she vomits in her sleep, it could block her airway,
- so have her sleep on her side. - Sure.
Gosh, thank you.
Do you have any idea how scared I was?
Look at you all better and playing on your own.
I'm sure the fever was no joke,
but you did good. How sweet of you.
My gosh. Did you just smile at me?
You're laughing after scaring me like that last night?
I'm not cut out for this at all.
How on earth would I raise such a pain in the neck?
It'll be all right.
There's nothing you can do when something you want...
will just never happen.
Right?
- The latest issue is out. - Right.
Thanks.
("When I ever become a mom...")
(Dahan Hospital OB-GYN)
Did you finally choose to have the surgery?
The surgery could lead to infertility, right?
There's a high possibility.
I'll have a baby first and then do the surgery.
Are you getting married?
I could get married at 50 or 60 if I want,
but this is my last chance to get pregnant.
I'm not getting married.
I just want to have a baby.
("When I ever become a mom...")
(Oh My Baby)
Marriage? I'd love for fate to bring someone to me,
but my reality is, I'm being called an old lady.
You've never been good at dating.
Zip it...
or you'll taste my foot in your mouth.
Ms. Jang, are you still embarrassed to see me?
No, I couldn't be more comfortable.
Eu Ddeum, no aunt of yours works here.
How about a little practice round by helping us out?
- Do you want me? - Can I have you if I do?
Don't hate me so much.
It's harder to hate someone than to like someone.