I'll go back to university.
- What?
University? What university?
I'll study and transfer to
a four-year university.
Mom. Dad.
It's been my dream
to study child psychology,
so that's what I'll do.
I'll get my diploma,
become a certified psychologist,
and do what I love...
while being someone who's needed.
That's the only way
for me to love myself too.
Do you even know how difficult
it is to transfer schools?
You're being ridiculous.
Consider your age too.
Your brain won't be able to keep up.
Besides, you weren't
a smart kid in school...
I mean, your grades
were slightly below average.
Da Hee, it doesn't seem like
you're thinking rationally.
This isn't the right way
to deal with the shock...
from your annulment.
You're practically throwing
another grenade at us.
We're dying here.
Just remember that
this is our last shelter.
He's right!
I know that.
I also know that it's absurd
and that I'm not very smart.
But that's why
I'm going to give it my all.
Please believe in me this one time.
I won't ask you to pay
for any of my classes.
I'll get a part-time job
and pay for them myself.
I just think...
it's my last time
to take this chance.
So please...
Da Hee,
I understand how you feel,
but your siblings are right.
You know how difficult
transfer exams are.
Money isn't the issue. The timing...
Go for it.
Go ahead.
If other people can do it,
so can you.
Na Hee is proof that
cleverness runs in the family...
and her grades...
were better than Joon Seon's anyway.
So just give it a go.
We'll consider it as something...
we should've made her do
10 years ago.
Mom...
It's just like you said.
Consider this as your last chance...
and do your very best.
So make a life for yourself...
that won't be
looked down on by others.
You can do it too.
My gosh, Ok Boon.
You couldn't be more encouraging.
Thanks, Mom!
I'll study my butt off...
and I'll show you
that it can be done.
Honey, what has gotten into you?
What do you mean?
That wasn't like you at all.
"Cut the nonsense."
"First an annulment
and now a new career?"
The old you would've
discouraged her immediately.
I don't always
discourage our kids, you know.
It said on the news
that it's easier...
to change your nationality
than your level of education.
That's just how the world is.
Da Hee must've been
frustrated with it all too.
Is that really the only reason?
What other reason can there be?
Am I not allowed
to encourage her now?
Well, if that's the case...
I'm just sorry,
that's all.
Every child will frustrate you
in the same amount.
Ok Ja calls it the principle
of trouble conservation.
Out of all our children,
Da Hee has caused the least trouble.
She had to clean up
after her siblings...
and tend to Na Hee
while she studied.
We've never done anything
for her directly.
Our lack of expectancy...
could be the reason
why she never aimed high.
I don't want...
to see her be discouraged anymore.
I want to believe in her
and let her do what she wants to do.
I'll encourage her
just like I should've years ago.
Sure. Let's do exactly that.
I guess parenting
keeps teaching us new things.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
I'd wish I could stop
being taught new lessons though.
- Turn off the light, will you?
- Sure thing.
(Cohabitation Contract)
Okay, good. That's easily readable.
Since this is my space,
I can move around the furniture.
Sure thing.
Just memorize
the contract by heart...
so that we don't get
in each other's hair.
I'm more worried about you,
you know.
From now on, we both have
to clean and do laundry.
And we both know
you're terrible at housekeeping.
Worry about yourself
and mind your own business.
That's right.
Why would I even worry about you?
Can you now go back
to your space then?
I'd like to get changed
and go to bed.
Yes. Sure thing.
Unbelievable!
You've got to be kidding me.
Hey! What... Why didn't you knock?
Don't invade my privacy.
We're not married now, you know.
Sorry. I left my phone out here.
What am I supposed to do then?
I need to use the bathroom
and the kitchen too.
Then at least knock.
I graciously let you
have the bedroom, didn't I?
Okay, noted.
As if there's anything
I'd actually like to see.
What do you mean by that?
Na Hee, what do you mean?
Is it salty?
Gosh, it's perfect.
I see you're awake.
You see, skipping breakfast
has been leading...
to stomachaches.
As if I asked.
Rolled eggs.
How soft.
The kimchi looks super crunchy too.
I could eat seconds and thirds.
Is what you're having good?
Yes, you know how
I enjoy light breakfasts.
It helps me focus more
in the mornings.
Well, you have
liked the American style.
It must keep
your stomach at ease though.
Na Hee!
That's the milk I bought.
Clause three of
the Cohabitation Code.
You never touch
your housemate's belongings.
When caught, you will have to pay
three times the price.
Read the Cohabitation Code again.
What? Oh, my gosh.
I should've hung these
out to dry yesterday.
There.
Wait, stop.
Isn't it Thursday today?
Clause five of
the Cohabitation Code.
Yoon does his laundry on
Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays...
while Song does hers on Tuesdays,
Thursdays, and Saturdays.
Who does it on Sundays
will be up for debate.
Did you not memorize that clause?
But I still need something
to wear to work.
- It's wet.
- That's your problem.
Darn it.
I'll just dry them myself.
Hold it!
I bought the dryer,
so don't even think about it.
Good morning...
Hi, guys.
I see you're all here early.
What on earth are you wearing?
I just wanted to wear it today.
There's no...
particular dress code
for doctors, right?
The government has been promoting
shorts at the office too.
You should wear something
like this too.
Of course,
you can wear whatever you want.
I actually find it stylish even.
Didn't we agree to go over
the research paper for the fall?
Where's the material?
In front of you.
- Good job today.
- You all did great.
Have a good day.
Gyu Jin!
What took you so long?
What a nutjob.
How can she be this evil?
No, vicious describes her better.
What?
What are you mumbling about?
Why couldn't you have come earlier?
I said I had a meeting this morning.
I came earlier than usual.
You woke me up
yelling that you needed a shirt.
Don't you have one at home?
I told you that none were dry.
The others are at the dry cleaner's.
But you have a dryer at home.
I can't use it today though.
What do you mean? Is it not working?
Don't ask.
Why do you want to know
about my personal life?
What's with the temper?
Did you and Na Hee argue?
I told you not to ask!
Will you look for
an academy to study at today?
Yes, I'll register at the academy...
and look for a part-time job
while I'm out.
Auntie, it's admirable.
I wish you the best.
Your words couldn't
be more encouraging.
Thanks.
Then eat up.
You can't study
unless you're fit enough.
Look at you,
receiving special treatment now.
Good for you, Last One.
You're right. Maybe I should
go back to school too.
Is there an age limit
to studying at college?
Ga Hee and Joon Seon.
Don't call me Last One anymore.
- What?
The Last One is no longer...
and I've been born anew.
I'd appreciate it
if you didn't call me...
by any nicknames that belittle me.
Why are you guys laughing?
Because you sounded so serious.
"Don't call me Last One anymore."
"I've been born anew."
But we're so used to it.
Can't we keep calling you that?
Shut it and do as she wants.
I don't like hearing you
call her that either.
You'll be banned from meals
if you call her that again.
Mom, you're overreacting.
Why can't we call her that
when it's who she is?
Listen to your mom, you punks.
What if I called you
Loafer 1 and Loafer 2?
Gosh, no.
Got it, Dad.
Tell Mr. Yang to bring by...
a kilogram of pork on his way over.
Why? Is it for Da Hee?
At this rate, we might have
an Ivy Leaguer on our hands.
I don't know if we should
let her get this part-time job.
Shouldn't she devote all her time
to her studies?
Can't you pay
for her classes instead?
But this is what she wants,
so just let her...
follow her own plans for now.
But still...
You said you wanted to
believe in her and encourage her.
I'm sure that Da Hee
will do a good job.
She gets her tenaciousness
from me, remember?
Come on. Is that really the reason?
Maybe you think
it's a waste of money.
Must you put it like that?
Am I really one to be that cruel
to my kids?
My goodness, we're late.
Ok Ja will be angry.
Gosh.
Where are you going?
I thought we were running late.
Be quiet.
My gosh.
Hello! Yes, I'd like some.
Gosh!
Why is she even here?
I can't believe this.
She's not a friend
but the bane of my existence.
My darn life.
I'm here to register
for the morning classes.
Please fill out this form.
None of these jobs seem fairly easy.
All I need are the evening shifts.
(Looking for a part-timer,
from 5 p.m. to closing)
The work is never done.
I posted a job opening long ago,
but I didn't get a single call.
Did I even post it right?
My goodness.
I can't believe this.
She wants to transfer
to a university after all this time?
Da Hee is unbelievable.
She didn't study when she had to.
How would she do that now?
I don't think it's a good idea.
That's my other line, Ga Hee.
(Mother-in-law)
Never mind.
Go on. I don't have to answer it.
Na Hee.
Hang on. What?
You know there is a welcome party
for me after work, right?
You have to come.
I really don't like team dinners.
Can't we meet some other time?
I know you don't like it,
but it's a welcome party for me.
If you don't come, I'll be upset.
I'll see you later, okay?
All right.
I'd like to welcome
Dr. Yoon Jae Seok.
Cheers, everyone.
- Cheers.
Drink up.
Thank you.
I'm watching you.
Dr. Song, over here.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Gosh.
I guess you do care
about your broth-in-law.
It's surprising to see Dr. Song
at a team dinner.
Please come and have a seat.
What would you like to drink?
You don't like drinking, do you?
I don't really like alcohol.
I'll just drink soda.
Why?
Now that you're here,
you should drink with us.
Here.
We already had two rounds each.
Dr. Song, go ahead...
and drink this up.
I really don't want
to drink this up.
I will just take my time
and drink it slowly.
You can't do that.
You came late,
so you need to catch up.
Drink up.
Bottoms up.
- Bottoms up.
Sir, I will drink it for her.
- Give it to me.
- Hey.
Why would you step up?
If someone is to drink for her,
it should be Dr. Yoon.
- Me?
- Sure.
Well... I don't mind
drinking it for her.
But I'm not sure if Dr. Song
wants me to.
Forget it. I'll drink it myself.
You scratch my back
and I will scratch yours.
Sir.
It looks great.
Good.
One more.
All right.
- One more.
- Again?
That's good.
All right.
Wait, Na Hee.
You're drinking too much.
Na Hee.
Here.
Again?
I can't.
I can't drink anymore.
- You hypocrite.
- What did you say?
It's romantic when I do it,
but an affair when others do it.
When you offer a drink
it's just for socializing,
but when I do it, it's being pushy
and causing a stir, right?
Just stop forcing everyone to drink.
It's already hard enough
to work at the hospital.
I don't want to be stressed out
from a team dinner.
When...
When did I force you guys to drink?
Just stay quiet.
My gosh.
Na Hee.
Dr. Song.
That's enough for the basic steps.
Now let's practice...
the moves with your arms.
- Okay.
You should pair up
with partners first.
Married couples can be partners.
Do I have to do this with my wife?
I want to dance with
someone else... No, I can't.
You fool.
I'm sorry, but it seems
I don't have a say in this.
For the rest of you...
You two are partners.
And you two.
Excuse me.
I don't want to be his partner.
I'm here to relieve stress,
not to get more.
My gosh. I feel the same way.
I'd rather dance alone.
Why don't you just give it a shot?
If it doesn't work for you,
I'll change your partners.
Let's begin.
Stand facing each other.
Ladies, put your hand
on your partner's shoulder.
Gentlemen, put your hand
on your partner's waist.
And hold the other hand.
Look into your partner's
eyes passionately.
1 and 2. 2 and...
- Don't laugh.
- Three. Cha-cha.
- One.
- Ma'am.
What should I do when her nostrils
are bigger than her eyes?
What? You fool.
Look. They are even bigger now.
Just keep your mouth shut.
Get off. Let go of me.
I'm not drunk.
I can walk straight.
Why did you drink so much
when you can't hold your liquor?
Go on ahead.
Look who it is.
You're my ex-husband.
Are you happy that you got divorced?
Are you?
Hey, will you stay quiet?
You're the one
who asked for a divorce.
You punk!
Don't live like that.
How can love change?
You sly jerk.
We got divorced
because you live like that...
Gyu Jin, your taxi is here.
Hey. My goodness.
Gosh. Hey.
Darn it.
Gosh. I didn't do this
even before we got divorced.
Darn it. My back is killing me.
You lunatic.
She even falls off the bed.
What a sight to see.
Look at her.
She gets up herself now.
My gosh. This is unbelievable.
Goodnight.
Gosh, it hurts.
Mom, I'm going out.
Aren't you eating breakfast?
I'm cooking now.
I don't have time.
Training begins today.
This movie has
a lot of great scenes.
I'll be on camera many times.
If this thing goes well,
I might be paid a lot...
for this movie.
I'll get you a mink coat then.
Forget about a mink coat.
Just earn your own keep.
Mom, I'm going out.
I'm attending classes
starting today.
You should eat breakfast.
You can't study on an empty stomach.
I'll eat something
before I head into class.
I'm leaving.
Grandma, I have class duty today
so I should leave early.
See you.
They should've told me
that they're leaving early.
I always eat rice for breakfast.
Just eat it. I should get to
take it easy from time to time.
It feels like
I'm chewing rice stalks.
I said just eat.
- Eat.
- Okay.
Good morning.
- Hello.
- 1 and 2.
- Hey.
Jeong Bong, that's a good punch.
- Is Mr. Jang in his office?
- Yes.
He's upstairs with Byung Heon.
Okay. Keep practicing. Stay at it!
- Okay!
Joon Seon really gets on my nerves.
Why is he so dim-witted?
Why does he act like a senior
when he's not even that good?
Is he the CEO?
Is he the martial arts director?
I wish he'd act his age.
Or get wise and quit.
You know how innocent he can be.
That's not being innocent.
It's being stupid.
Let's be honest. Do you think
it's easy for me to keep him around?
He's old,
has a bad back
and is choosy about his stunts.
To be honest, the kids
feel uncomfortable around him.
And he's so nosy,
he gets in all their business too.
I wish he'd just fend for himself.
- Byung Heon, don't put up with it.
- What?
Speak up if you must.
- Mr. Jang!
- Hey, Joon Seon.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I have something to say.
I'm really sorry,
but I need to quit.
What? Why so suddenly?
Every dog has its day, I guess.
Someone offered to invest in me.
It's this producer from Hong Kong.
Apparently, he's really big
in the industry.
He saw some of the stunts I did...
and said I was awesome.
How can I refuse
when he offered to invest?
I should give it a go, shouldn't I?
I see. Who is this investor?
What?
There's someone called Tteok Hua.
Tteok Hua?
There's someone. Tteok Hua.
Anyway, I'm really sorry that...
I have to quit like this.
I'll buy you a drink
when things are sorted out.
Let's stay in touch, okay?
- Okay...
- Good. See you.
- Bye.
- Take care.
I wonder how much he'll offer.
I have no idea.
Look up Tteok Hua.
- Joon Seon!
What do you two want?
We'll come with you!
We don't care for Action Art
if you leave!
- Joon Seon!
- What, Mom?
- You took your sweet time.
Do you know how many times
I called yesterday?
Sorry. We had
a team dinner yesterday.
What about your wife?
Did her dinner start at midday?
She totally ignored my calls.
She must've been busy then.
What? Is something wrong?
The part-timer suddenly quit.
I had a terrible time
running the cafe on my own.
I wanted to ask for help
and couldn't reach either of you.
What's wrong with your wife?
Shouldn't she have called me today
at least?
What does she think of
her mother-in-law?
I'll really do something
if she keeps this up.
Mom, I'll...
Mom, I have a long line of
patients waiting.
I will, I'll come over
when I'm free.
Mom, I'll call you back. Bye, Mom.
It looks like things are
about to get real bad.
You must feel okay.
No thanks to someone,
my back and shoulder still hurt.
You should've left me alone.
Why take me home?
I regret doing so right now.
Don't you go and get drunk anywhere.
You're the type that could
get into trouble.
Don't worry. I'll fend for myself.
As if you can.
You almost spilled the beans.
Wait.
Mom called yesterday?
Yes. She did.
Couldn't you have just taken it?
What for? Am I obligated to?
She must've called
to make us come over.
Clause seven. Both parties
must attend family occasions...
like birthdays, national holidays,
or ancestral rites.
For other occasions,
prior notice must be given.
And they are attended
by mutual consent only. Right?
No, no, wait.
Even so...
Come with me.
Let's just talk. Come with me.
Let go of me.
Song Na Hee.
Let's amend a clause.
This might make my life crazy.
Amend how?
You know my mom hates it
when you ignore her calls.
Will you help me out here?
Take a minimum number of her calls.
Why should I? The stress
she caused was terrifying.
Okay. Then how about this?
We'll count the calls you take.
When we sell our apartment
and split the profit,
I'll pay you more per call.
You're getting such great ideas.
How much will you give me?
About 100 dollars per call?
That's robbery.
I don't want to take her calls.
You sort out your own mom.
Wait, wait.
Do you think I'm doing this
just for my sake?
I'm not.
If you ignore her calls,
who do you think Mom will go to?
To us? No.
She'll go to your innocent mom.
What will you tell her?
"We got divorced and I have
no duty to take her calls, Mom."
You got divorced?
- My gosh.
- Divorced?
When affixed with "to",
what was a verb...
is still a verb, yes or no? No.
It's no longer a verb now.
In English, what always
comes after the subject?
I called because I saw
you're looking for a part-timer.
You hired someone already? I see.
Okay, I understand. Thank you.
Oh, dear. It's not easy
to find part-time work.
Oh? Ms. Choi.
- Hi.
- Give me that.
- My gosh.
- I'll help you.
Thanks so much.
My part-timer suddenly quit.
This looks too heavy for you.
I have nothing but strength.
Yes.
Shall I put them here?
No, around the corner.
There are a few more inside...
I'm done. Is that all?
Thank you so much.
By the way, Da Hee.
Since you're helping out,
could I ask for a favor?
- Sure.
- I'm out of bananas.
Could you watch the cafe
while I get some?
Okay.
If someone comes in,
don't take an order.
Just say fruit juices
are available today.
Shall I get the bananas then?
No, no. I have to buy
other things too.
I won't be long. Help me out, okay?
Okay. Don't worry then.
- See you.
- Bye.
An americano
and a vanilla latte, please.
An americano and a vanilla latte?
That's 9 dollars 50. Thanks.
Take a seat
and I'll bring those over.
Da Hee.
You're back.
A customer was
really craving a coffee.
I worked at another cafe
for over a year.
Shall I make you one? Hot?
My gosh. How did you manage to...
transform the cafe
in just a short while?
I just cleaned up
a few things I noticed.
So, are you all right?
I mean, we experience...
all sorts of things in life,
but there must be some aftereffects.
I'm fine.
Thanks for your concern, Ms. Choi.
Sure. What about work?
Are you still on holiday?
No. I quit my job too.
I want to transfer to a university.
Transfer? My goodness.
Won't your mom complain?
She might freak out.
No. I have her full support.
But at my age, I can't ask
my parents to support me,
so I'll work part-time
while taking classes.
Did you find work already then?
No.
I can only work in the evenings
because I study during the day,
and I can't find anything suitable.
You can't?
Well, seeing how I need
a part-timer right now,
and you live nearby,
we can arrange a schedule.
Would you care to work here?
Here? Really?
Yes.
You fools.
Why did you quit with me?
I lied about the investor.
I quit because I couldn't
hang in there any longer.
I really have nothing at all.
We know that.
But Joon Seon,
you are too important to us.
That's right.
When no one would pay us,
saying it was about the experience,
you shared your pay saying...
we needed to make a living too.
Hey. That was only natural
because we worked and deserve pay.
No.
You're the only person
who thought that's natural.
Forget about that.
So, what'll you do now?
You ate and slept at
the action school.
Where will you live?
Do you have a plan?
Joon Seon.
When did we ever plan things
before causing trouble?
We'll think of something
while staying at a sauna.
You two are unbelievable.
Here's your sweet and sour chicken.
Yes, thank you for coming.
We sold all the chicken in stock,
so let's call it a night.
It's been a while since we
had that many customers.
We should have days like this too.
Who says we always
have to have bad days?
Mom, Dad, Auntie!
Da Hee, it's you.
Why are you here?
To go home with you two.
- Shouldn't you be closing up?
- Right.
Wait a few minutes.
- I'll go pay for the peanuts.
- Sure.
I hear you enrolled
at an academy today.
Go for it when you can.
Get into a better university
than Na Hee did...
and make her eat her words.
Yes, ma'am!
Mom, I even got myself
a part-time job.
It's close by
and the hours are perfect.
Is that so? Where is it?
Won't it interfere
with your studies?
Of course not.
It's at Ms. Choi's cafe.
- I'll be taking the evening shifts.
- What?
At Yun Jeong's cafe?
Are you insane?
Why would you work for her?
Why not? It fits my schedule
and the pay isn't bad.
I'm more than grateful.
That's out of the question!
This is a joke.
Did she actually ask you
to work for her?
Yes, I met her on my way here...
and she was looking
for a part-timer.
She said she'd rather
give me the job than...
She'd give you the job?
Don't you know how cruel she is?
A few days ago, she...
Anyway, my answer is no.
Don't you work there.
I don't approve.
Aren't they friends?
Why does she hate her?
They've been...
at each other's throats
since high school.
I guess you can call them rivals.
Being the jealous type,
Yun Jeong has always been
mean to your mom.
There's bad blood between them.
You...
stay put.
I'll deal with her myself.
(Episode 8)
I felt bad after hearing
Da Hee's story.
It really was a punch to the heart.
Why would I waste money
on someone else?
I'd rather Da Hee
pick up the paycheck instead.
- Ms. Choi...
- Gosh, don't be like that.
It's just the two of us,
so let's not be formal.
Okay. Fine, Yun Jeong.
Thank you for
looking out for Da Hee,
but she won't be working here.
What? Why not?
I know we're friends,
but we're also in-laws.
There's a certain wall between us.
And just like you said,
I'm also worried that
bad luck will...
rub off her.
Hold on.
Did I say such a thing?
Yes, you did.
It was quite recent.
Did you already forget that?
Well...
Oh, that?
I was only worried
about you, you know.
Anyway, I'll let Da Hee know myself.
Consider that this never happened.
All right then.
Ok Boon!
Okay, fine. Let me be
a little more generous then.
I'll give her a 20 percent raise.
My gosh! This trash can
needs to be emptied.
Fine then!
Things are urgent for me too,
so please help me out.
So this isn't you being generous?
No, this is me pleading.
I really need the extra help.
You said you'll give her
a 20 percent raise.
Yes.
How dare she try to play me?
Did you and Na Hee
really get divorced?
When? How?
Isn't it obvious?
We signed the papers
and submitted them.
It took less than five minutes.
I'm in shock.
This is the most shocking news
I heard lately.
Your actions are more shocking,
you know.
I can't believe you slept there.
Anyway, don't tell Mom
or the people at the hospital.
Keep your mouth shut.
That's not the hard part.
But are you sure about this?
You got divorced in secret
but are still living together.
Is this the Hollywood style?
I'm not sure if this is
sophisticated or reckless.
We couldn't lose out
on 100,000 dollars though.
Gyu Jin,
are you sure you won't regret this?
Na Hee is a great person.
This isn't because she's not great.
Two great people can marry...
but still have problems.
You either overcome them...
or call it quits.
Your sister-in-law and I...
I mean, your former sister-in-law.
Well, we called it quits.
Former sister-in-law?
Must you be that cruel?
This is why you shouldn't marry
so quickly after falling in love.
Take your time
and weigh your options.
Well, it's not my goal to marry.
Is that so? Why?
Managing my own life is hard enough.
I can't be responsible for
someone else's too. It's scary.
To be honest, I'm scared
that I'll change my mind...
like you and Na Hee.
Even if I live happily with my wife,
one of us will end up dying first.
The one left will wallow in sorrow.
Like Mom.
Marriage can only end
in pain if you ask me.
That's what I believe.
You're not wrong.
Why didn't you tell me that
before I got married?
Would you have listened?
You and Na Hee were
head over heels for each other.
Gosh, thank you, sir.
Gyu Jin, are you all right?
Can you make it home by yourself?
Of course. I'm not drunk, you know.
Who do you think I am? Na Hee?
Must you speak ill of her like that?
Head home then. Catch.
Jae Seok.
Na Hee.
Wait, should I not be
so casual anymore?
It's hard for a third party
to know about someone's marriage,
so it's not my place
to say anything.
Still, I'm upset.
I really like the both of you,
you know.
I'm sorry...
for making you witness this
the second you came back to Korea.
I'd like nothing more
than to ask what happened,
but I won't since
I wouldn't understand anyway.
Can I still call you
my sister-in-law though?
That won't change
even though you get divorced.
It doesn't matter.
We need to keep up the act
for the time being anyway.
Me being back in Korea
is a secret...
and so is Gyu Jin getting a divorce.
We're the secret-harboring brothers.
I know and I'm sorry for
playing a part in that.
When you said you were
marrying Gyu Jin,
I promised to always
be on your side.
My arm...
Something's wrong with my arm.
Why? Do you have a cramp?
Unlike others,
the blood in me
isn't thicker than water.
I'll always be on your side.
Call me when you're lonely,
when you need a friend,
or when you need
someone to eat with.
I hear that you're an outcast
at the hospital.
An outcast?
Didn't you know?
Everyone says that you only
have Gyu Jin to eat with.
Me?
So you'll let Da Hee work at...
Gyu Jin's mother's cafe?
Why not?
She needs a part-time job anyway.
Besides, you love money, right?
She offered a 20 percent raise.
Money isn't the issue here.
Wouldn't it be uncomfortable?
Whatever.
She seemed urgent,
so I doubt she'll be
a menace to Da Hee.
Well, Da Hee isn't the type
to do anything wrong.
Exactly.
My gosh.
Is it already that time of year?
Will you be going there tomorrow?
Of course.
Let me come with you this time.
It's okay.
I'll just go there myself.
All right.
Leave the store to me...
and make sure to be careful.
I'll cook some food
in the morning...
and pack some fruit for you.
(Song Young Suk)
Is that where he went
early this morning?
Yes.
Then he won't be back
until after sundown.
I wonder how long he's
going to keep this up.
Probably until the day he dies.
I guess the pain
won't go away easily.
He had to bury his sister
in his heart.
It's a miracle that he met you
and was able to settle down.
Gosh, but still...
He lived his whole life
blaming himself.
It's about time
he lets himself off the hook.
He can be too cruel
on himself at times.
Don't you want some, Young Dal?
I already ate.
You can have it all.
Young Suk.
Don't you miss Mom?
Should I sing her song?
With my eyes closed, I walk
With my eyes open
My cousin in Cheongdo
suggested it actually.
A family who owns an orchard needs
someone to babysit and do chores.
I heard that age isn't an issue.
I'm talking about your sister.
Why don't you send her there?
How much can you earn
polishing shoes anyway?
She'll only starve by your side.
If she works there,
she'll at least get enough meals.
They might even send her to school.
What do you say?
No, I won't go!
If you go there,
you can eat your favorite snack
every day.
I don't want it.
I want to live with you instead.
Young Suk, look at me.
This isn't goodbye forever.
I'll earn enough money...
and come back for you.
I'll come to you before you see
100 full moons.
I promise.
Really?
Yes.
So stay strong
and wait for me, okay?
Also,
don't you ever skip your meals.
Whatever food they give you,
you will eat it deliciously.
Got it?
Here is Mom's handkerchief.
Whenever you want to see us,
you'll look at this instead.
Understood?
Promise you'll come back for me.
Of course.
No one lives there anymore.
The orchard went bankrupt.
They took off half a year ago.
Sorry?
Creditors came by
and smashed everything in there.
It was a nightmare.
Then what about the people
who worked here?
There was a young housekeeper.
The young girl they hired
as a babysitter...
who had a round face and puppy eyes?
Yes, that's her.
She died.
Was it last year?
She had a high fever.
I saw one of the workers...
carrying her body
to bury her someplace.
I don't know
where they buried her though.
You're still five...
while I'm over 60 now.
Young Suk.
I'm sorry.
I'm terribly sorry.
I really must be an outcast.
Why though?
What did I ever do to them?
- Are you leaving?
- Yes.
- I guess I'll see you next year.
- Of course.
Yes, Chi Su.
Young Dal, where are you?
I had an errand to run,
and now I'm on my way back. Why?
It's the day of the year
when you're most miserable.
Don't give your wife a hard time
and spend the day with me today.
I'll shut down my store.
That's not necessary.
Just listen to your friend.
I'll treat you
to something special today.
It won't be just soju again.
There's a place
I've had my eyes on.
But...
Unbelievable.
Mr. Shin, don't bother.
It's on me today.
I want to go out with her.
How much will that be?
- Me?
- Yes.
Sir, we don't do second rounds.
Did you not see that
at the entrance?
This isn't a place like that.
No, I didn't see it.
You're belittling me, aren't you?
Where's the hostess?
Get the hostess!
The hostess is right here.
How may I help you?
Are you the hostess?
Are you?
Yes, I'm the hostess here.
What's the matter?
The thing is,
this cutie says she doesn't want to
go out with me.
Sure. That's true, sir.
We don't do second rounds.
I've been in the liquor business
for 15 years...
with my own principles.
I never water down liquor.
I never overcharge customers.
And I never let my employees
go out for second rounds.
You've got to be kidding me.
If you run your business like this,
you'll never get regulars.
Do you know who I am?
There are a lot of bars...
that ask me to come.
Is that so?
I'm sorry,
but we still can't do that.
Darn it.
You just don't seem to get it.
If you keep being like this...
- I said no. Just go.
- What?
Gosh, I said it three times.
You should get it by now.
I don't know who you are,
and I can make my living
without regulars like you.
So go take your business
somewhere else, okay?
You crazy wench.
Do you have a death wish?
Shut your mouth.
It's my principle
that I never skip a meal.
I just finished serving customers
drinking in broad daylight.
I had to sing 14 songs
without having a meal.
So I'm starving now.
Do you know what it means?
What are you talking about,
you lunatic?
It means you guys are dead meat.
Do you understand?
Darn it.
I'm going to kill you.
My goodness.
I'm telling you.
He started throwing a tantrum,
so she had no choice.
She didn't do anything wrong.
- It's okay. Stop it.
- Cho Yeon.
You know I don't
like to make excuses.
I'll pay if I did something wrong.
Otherwise, I'll be released.
Let's go, guys.
- Cho Yeon.
Wait. Gosh.
- Cho Yeon!
Here's your Americano.
Do you want a carrier?
Yes, please.
I'm glad that I swallowed my pride
and begged her.
Thank you. Please come again.
Bye.
Da Hee.
Would you turn the volume up?
Yes, Ms. Choi.
I'm not feeling well.
I will go get a massage
and have dinner.
Take good care of the store
while I am away.
And wipe the frame over there.
Yes, ma'am.
She's nothing like her sister.
I wish they were
mixed half and half.
I've missed this acrid fine dust.
One must have freedom,
first and foremost.
(Jungang Police)
- Cho Yeon.
Cho Yeon!
- Hey, guys.
Stop making a fuss.
This is embarrassing.
Cho Yeon, here. I got you some tofu.
This is ridiculous.
It's not like I was in jail.
Where's the sauce?
It comes with a sauce.
What was I thinking?
Ga Yeon, you always make
mistakes like this.
Pull yourself together?
How could you forget it?
Stop it. I can eat it without sauce.
It's hard to open it.
It tastes so good.
So how did you reach
a settlement with them?
Well... It's...
Ga Yeon closed her savings account.
We couldn't let you end up in jail.
To us, you are like
a real sister and mom.
I'm not your sister or mom.
I'm not even married.
I'll pay you back within this month.
Open up another savings account.
Okay. Just eat it.
Okay.
It tastes good.
Hey. You guys should go on ahead.
- I have a place to stop by.
- Where are you going?
Don't even ask.
I'll just meet my boyfriend
and get some money from him. Okay?
Here. See you.
Bye.
She's going there, right?
Isn't it obvious?
Dad!
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
What brings you here?
You didn't even call.
I just came by because I missed you.
The trees have grown a lot.
Dad, what fertilizer do you use
to make them grow so big?
It's like magic.
I use something else
besides fertilizer.
It's my sincerity.
Dad, give me that.
- Okay.
- Let me sweep.
Is your business going well?
Well...
There's a new talking bar
next to my store.
Apparently, the barmaids there are
young and slim.
I lost all my regulars to them.
I've given them
a lot of free fruit over the years.
How disloyal they are.
Dad. I should probably
lose some weight.
Like I always say,
appearance doesn't matter.
Those who visit your bar
are hungry for emotion,
not for bodies.
So you should try to fill
the void in their hearts.
- It's...
- The teachings of Buddha,
so I should work hard with pride?
My gosh.
What kind of father...
tells his daughter to work hard
running a karaoke bar?
All occupations are
equally honorable.
You should just live a life
that you're not ashamed of.
So what's the matter?
I guess you're here
because you have a lot on your mind.
Are you a mind-reader or what?
How did you know
that I have a lot on my mind?
I've raised you since you were six.
In the small temple in Mount Daeun.
Gosh, I know that.
If it weren't for you,
I would've already been long gone.
I was abandoned with a fever,
but you fed me herbal medicine
for 10 days and saved my life.
And you took me in when I was
a fool who didn't remember anything.
You even let me call you Dad.
That's why I can tell everything
from your face.
So Cho Yeon is distracted
with worries again.
Dad.
Monk.
Maybe I should quit running the bar.
Why? You said
the work is cut out for you.
I just said that because
I had nothing else to do...
as a woman without parents
nor a decent education.
I'm just sick of dealing with
drunk customers.
I want to live an ordinary life...
like normal women do.
I think it's time.
What time?
Time to move on.
Time to change your life.
Time to get closer to the truth.
Gosh. You're just saying things.
I'm just sick of living like this.
So what do you want to do
to make a living now?
Dr. Song.
I'm sorry. My work ended late.
Shall we begin now?
- Yes.
First, we organized the list...
of patients under age 18
with pneumococcus as you asked.
Hang on. Didn't I ask
Han Gi Yeong to do that?
Where is he, by the way?
Is he late?
What? What's going on?
Well... Did you not hear that?
Gi Yeong transferred
to Dr. Yoon's team.
What? Whose team?
I thought he told you.
Get data on antibiotic sensitivity
with the samples on page 29.
- Shin Hye Jeong.
- Yes?
Up to December of 2019...
What is it, Dr. Song?
Don't you see we're in a meeting?
I see that.
I also see one of my team members
is here without telling me.
- Hey, Han Gi Yeong.
- Yes?
What are you doing here?
Well, the thing is...
Han Gi Yeong.
Didn't you say
you talked to Dr. Song?
Well...
I sent her an email...
which she hasn't read yet.
What? An email?
That's a notification,
not a discussion.
Come with me. Let's chat.
Dr. Song.
We're in a meeting right now.
Can you...
Stay out of it, Dr. Yoon.
Hey. Follow me.
Don't be like this, Dr. Song.
Calm down. I'll talk to him later...
Stay out of it, Yoon Gyu Jin!
Did you have to do that
in front of our juniors?
You insulted me. Do you know that?
Should I do nothing when someone
takes one of my team members...
a week before the conference?
I'll say it again.
I didn't take him. He came to me.
All he did for you was research
and data input in Excel sheets.
If that's all he had to do
when there are younger residents,
how would he feel?
That's why all the juniors...
Treat me as an outcast?
I know. But what does that
have to do with you taking Gi Yeong?
I didn't take him!
I thought he cleared it with you.
Is it over if he says it is?
You should've come to me.
You know my team is
a member short without him.
I assumed
you'd gotten someone else.
Really? Weren't you just
trying to mess with me?
What do you think of me?
Am I like you?
You're not.
You and I are
fundamentally different.
I'm not as crafty as you.
You're always like this.
You say you didn't know...
and stay neutral
without taking sides.
That is why I don't like you.
At work and between me and your mom.
You're always like that.
That's why I divorced you.
Because you're crafty!
Anyone listening would think
you split up with me!
He wanted to eat dinner
and now he's not picking up?
Did he go home?
Why didn't you say so first?
I wanted to divorce you
for a long time!
Honestly, these two...
They swore me to secrecy
and now this?
Are they broadcasting
they got divorced?
Yes, it's me.
It will be rush hour soon.
I'll have dinner with my son
and come over in the evening.
Who cares?
What's wrong with you?
What crazy timing is this?
It'll be bad if Mom hears.
No, it's someone else.
- This friend is weak.
- No.
Who cares? She'll kill me
if she sees me here.
No, wait.
Don't act like you're
the best in the world.
No. I must live.
Okay. See you later.
Mom!
What...
Are you Jae Seok?
What on earth...
Why are you in a white gown?
Mom. I'm sorry.
I love you!
You fool.
What happened?
Come here!
Stop right there!
I got you.
You little rat.
You're calling a son
you haven't seen in a while a rat?
Isn't this too lavish a welcome?
What?
Mother. How have you been?
How do you think I am
now that I saw you here?
That hurt.
You must be really healthy.
Your punches are more painful.
Are you on something? Ginseng?
Ginseng? You idiot.
Don't try to talk your way out.
What happened? Why are you here?
What's this white gown?
Why ask? Can't you put
2 and 2 together?
I'm back and I work here,
and you found out. The end.
Isn't that simple?
What?
You scumbag. You jerk.
Come here.
Let's talk at home. Come with me!
- Mom, wait.
- Come with me!
- Walk!
- Wait.
Can I at least change first?
I'll talk to Gi Yeong
about this situation.
He won't talk to you.
He's too scared right now.
Forget it.
What good is such a timid kid?
You keep him.
Okay. It would look bad
to send him back.
That's why you should
treat your juniors better.
Honestly, you...
(Mother)
- Mom.
- Yoon Gyu Jin!
What's wrong with you?
Why? What is it, Mom?
"What is it, Mom?"
You knew Jae Seok was back?
And you didn't tell me?
When you work at the same hospital?
You and your wife!
Come over right now.
- Even if the skies fall, okay?
- Mom, we...
- I'll come alone. Na Hee...
- Bring her too!
Mom knows Jae Seok is back.
She wants to see us.
Leave me out.
I have no reason to go there.
I can't do that.
You're the one who
wants to keep us a secret.
You should cooperate
to keep our cover.
Don't you remember
Clause seven of our contract?
That hurts, Mom. Mom.
That really hurts.
Grab the other ear.
The other ear, please.
Just let go. I won't run away.
How can I trust you when
you lied about being in Turkey?
Come in!
Okay, Mom, okay.
Mom. Mom.
Stop glaring. You're scaring me.
Tell the truth.
When did you come back, you brat?
Do you have to curse?
Not long ago.
I want a date. When did you return?
What time on what day?
Saturday. Last Saturday.
Last Saturday.
That was a week ago.
It's been a week.
And you started work without
telling me, you ungrateful brat?
"Ungrateful"?
You have no idea
what a noble sacrifice I'm making.
I deserve a Nobel Peace Prize.
What are you talking about?
- You scumbag.
- Mom.
- Mom, talk it out.
- You idiot.
Don't resort to violence.
That could become a habit!
- How dare you?
- Mom.
- What?
You...
What?
Mom, we're here.
Mother, we're...
What?
Da Hee.
Why are you here?
Na Hee.
You!
What?
(Once Again)
What on earth did I tell
my brother-in-law's brother?
That really was not me.
I didn't say it was just us.
I said we had drinks.
What?
Do you think you'll never
need to ask me for a favor?
I wasn't blessed with
a good husband or great kids,
but I was blessed with
a great son-in-law.
What, what? What is it?
- For real?
I'm going to quit
and do something else.
Something ordinary.