Let's get divorced.
What?
Let's get a divorce.
But under one condition.
As you know,
my mom is still traumatized...
over Da Hee's annulled marriage.
She said that I'm her only hope
and that I should make mine work.
The timing is rotten,
so let's not tell our parents
for a while.
We will...
once the time seems right.
I asked around
and selling the house...
will each give us enough
to rent a studio apartment.
So until then,
let's not tell our families...
Hold on a second.
What are you doing?
Are you truly asking for a divorce?
You want to sever our marriage?
We're only going back
to how things were.
That's not what I mean...
Is this because you're upset
about what I said the other day?
If that's the case,
I'll admit that I was wrong, but...
Gyu Jin.
It wasn't a mistake.
You were just finally
speaking the truth.
Of course not. Don't be ridiculous.
Don't deny it.
We drifted apart...
and became
no better than strangers...
since that day.
I felt guilty...
and you resented me.
But we kept those feelings
bottled up inside...
and found other ways
to be at each other's throats.
I thought you'd
forever be on my side...
and a place for me to rest,
but that has changed.
When...
was the last time
we enjoyed each other's company?
A year ago? Two years ago?
Na Hee...
That's not all.
Your mother is egotistical...
and you put on a show
as Son of the Year.
I'm sick and tired...
of putting up an act too.
She's egotistical?
Watch what you're saying
or you'll regret it later.
I can't take it anymore.
Your mother...
is too much.
Hey.
Why do you keep acting
like the victim here?
Living with you
hasn't been merry for me too.
You're just as odd
as my mom, you know.
You think you're the law,
you don't consider others' feelings,
and you grill people
when you think they're wrong.
It's like I've been living
with a bomb on my waist.
That's why I'm saying
we should get a divorce.
I know I can be weird.
It's why we're both miserable
in our own ways.
So why must we stay together?
Whom does that benefit?
Fine, let's end it.
We'll get a divorce. Happy now?
Don't say that out of spite.
Can't you see that I'm dead serious?
I'm just as serious too,
so let's get a divorce.
Living with you
hasn't been merry for me too.
It's like I've been living
with a bomb on my waist.
A divorce?
Is it that easy for you?
How can she...
How can you make
a mistake like that?
What have I constantly
been reminding you to check?
Typos, dates, and passport numbers.
You should never mess those up.
What have you learned
over the past year?
What if you found out
on the day of departure?
The next flight
was fully booked too.
I double-checked,
but I had so much work that week...
I'm sorry, sir.
She was only helping me out,
so it's my fault.
Of course, you should be sorry.
You insisted on getting married...
during our busiest season
of the year...
only to get an annulment?
What a joke.
This is where lack of education
truly shows.
It's too obvious.
Have Ji Hye and Tae Hoon
ever made a mistake like this?
It's why they were promoted
to full-time employees...
even though you were hired first.
If I could, I'd love
nothing more than to...
fire you both.
But the boss wants to promote
one of you to full-time status.
Until our Monday meeting,
prepare a nine-day
package vacation to Spain.
We'll decide after
seeing your presentations.
- What?
- A full-time employee?
The spot will only go to one of you.
This is your last chance
so do your best. Got it?
Out of the way.
It's great that we weren't
reprimanded in any way.
Right, I guess.
If you'd like, I can send you...
the Eastern Europe
package deal format for reference.
It's all right. I have it too.
I see.
Yes?
What's this?
Isn't it obvious?
What other documents
must we be exchanging?
I already signed them,
so let me know when you do.
We'll hand them in.
We have until 6 p.m.
I'd rather you not take too long.
Hold on.
Wait right there.
What's there to think about?
I'll just sign them too.
(Yoon Gyu Jin)
(Application of Divorce
by Mutual Consent)
Are we good?
We're good.
When would you like to go to court?
I don't really care.
Today seems fine.
Today?
Yes, today seems great.
Yes, this must be a fine day.
A fine day to get divorced.
We'll go straight after work.
Sure! I can't remember
when it was...
that we agreed on
something like this.
You're right. Talk about teamwork.
It's the best.
Yes?
I see you two are here together.
The director called everyone down.
All right.
We have a new doctor joining
our Department of General Dentistry.
Please welcome Dr. Yoon Jae Seok.
He studied dental prosthesis
in Turkey.
I'm sure you know...
that Turkey is known
to be the best in the field.
The dissertation he wrote there
one the excellence award...
I won the top excellence award, sir.
Right.
Anyway, he's a talented doctor
who won the top excellence award,
so I look forward to him...
doing his best
for our young patients.
- Dr. Yoon?
- Yes, sir.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Yoon Jae Seok.
I'm still adjusting after
returning to Korea a few days ago,
but I'm the type to...
pick up on things easily,
so please don't hesitate
to show me guidance. Thank you.
You sure are a friendly one,
aren't you?
Does it run in the family?
Just so you know, he and Dr. Yoon
of Internal Medicine...
are brothers.
Keep that in mind...
so that you don't
speak ill of the other.
- Should we head to lunch?
- Sounds good.
You surprised me.
When did you get back?
Didn't Gyu Jin tell you?
We had dinner together.
I see you two are having
communication issues.
Don't you two talk?
You said it was a secret.
Only to Mom.
Na Hee can know
since she's on my side.
You won't tell her, right?
She and I don't get along anyway.
And again Na Hee speaks bluntly.
I don't know why
I find this so charming.
Will you be able
to keep this a secret though?
Your mom knows everything
that goes on around here.
I'll have to tough it out.
Just so you know, I'm able
to smell her from a mile away.
Don't get too cocky.
She's always
a few steps ahead of us.
Beware of Mom.
Don't be relieved
even if she walks out the door.
An annulment? Goodness.
What a joke her kids are.
Just thinking about it
sends shivers up my spine.
She'll have to tell everyone...
that came to the wedding that day.
How humiliating.
Ok Boon, how mortifying.
Ok Boon? Ok Boon!
Ok Boon.
How can you just walk past...
your friend's store like that?
Well, you're never around.
It's always just your employee.
Well, come inside for a beverage.
What?
Come on.
What? Hold on.
I heard about
your youngest daughter.
Oh, I see. Did Gyu Jin tell you?
No, he's not the type
to say those things.
I heard at the market.
You should've told me
if something like that had happened.
We're not strangers.
We've been friends for 50 years...
and our kids are married.
Things were hectic
and it wasn't worth mentioning.
It's not a divorce but an annulment.
How is that not a big deal?
You're declaring that
the wedding never happened.
You have no idea how shocked I was.
My heart was pounding like crazy,
so I can imagine how you felt.
Actually, I'm fine.
That's the spirit. Pretend to be
okay with it in front of others.
But there's no need
to be like that with me.
I'm not kidding. I really am fine.
Divorce is trending anyway.
Don't be so old-fashioned.
Okay, good for you.
Keep thinking that way.
Just think that your kids
are only on-trend.
We shouldn't be worrying
too much at our age anyway.
Not when we don't
have many years left to live.
My gosh.
You must be the unluckiest person
on earth.
Two got divorced
and one got an annulment.
It sounds like the title of a movie.
"2 Divorces and 1 Annulment".
"2D and 1A".
You!
I...
I should move
to another neighborhood.
Honey, what's wrong?
Did someone say something again?
That cow. How dare she.
What's wrong?
Are you hyperventilating?
Ok Ja, grab a plastic bag.
Right, of course.
- Here you go.
- Hurry.
Here.
Forget it. I don't need it.
Don't shock me like that.
Who on earth did you
meet on your way here?
I take it back.
Where's the plastic bag?
- Here!
- Give me that.
Honey, just a second. Come here.
- 1, 2...
- It hurts.
It hurts!
- What...
- It hurts.
Darn it.
I wonder why she didn't
finish her juice. What a waste.
I thought the freshly made juice
would cool her down a bit.
How delicious.
Hold on.
I wonder what time it is in Turkey.
It'd be nice to hear
from my younger son.
It's true.
In Turkey,
this is how the horses are.
Like that.
- Really?
- No way.
It's the truth!
If it isn't,
I'll change my last name to Yu.
You can call me Yu Jae Seok.
Unbelievable.
Gosh.
I should've taken a few new photos
in Turkey just to throw Mom off.
We should go to Turkey
sometime together.
When do you take your vacation?
- Thank you, Doctor.
- Thanks.
I'm heading out.
See you outside the court.
She's really going there?
Unbelievable.
How did she live with me
until this moment?
(Integrated Care Center)
Dr. Yoon.
I see you're heading home.
Have a good day, then.
Hold on. What is it?
What's going on?
A patient came in with a cut...
and I'd like some help.
But I can always ask Ji Yeon.
She has experience
with patients like this too.
No! Let me.
She seemed tired, so let's go.
Let's go, my fellow doctor.
But we should be going that way.
Yes, of course.
That's where I was going.
Let's go.
(Yoon Gyu Jin)
(Divorce by Mutual Consent)
The person you called
is unavailable...
Yes, this is Song Na Hee,
Is Dr. Yoon Gyu Jin
still at the hospital?
An emergency patient?
Okay. Thanks for letting me know.
Seriously? I waited
outside the court for half an hour.
I was just about to leave...
when an emergency patient came in.
The kid was crying his head off
with chips of glass in his leg.
Things were too hectic
and I forgot to call.
Is that so?
Wasn't there an on-call doctor?
Yes, Gi Yeong was on standby,
but he needed help.
Our personal lives are important,
but I'm a doctor first and foremost.
I couldn't let a patient suffer...
and turn a blind eye
when a junior doctor needed help.
What? Why?
Make sure you show up tomorrow then.
Don't make me wait for you.
Don't you worry!
Even if the world ends tomorrow,
I'll make it there!
Darn it.
(European Route)
Goodnight, everyone.
I see you're working late.
How's the project coming along?
(The Stadium of Dreams: Camp Nou)
A tour of Camp Nou
during peak season?
It sounds good.
They can experience
the history and tradition...
of the soccer team
in the form of a quiz.
Then they can have free time
during the rest of the trip.
This is the map I made.
Look.
Do you like it?
(The following file already exists.
Do you want to replace it?)
(Spain trip project)
Are you done?
Do you want to have some udon
at the cart bar around here?
No. I'm tired. I should get going.
Okay. Bye.
It's okay. Well done.
Good job.
(American Route, European Route)
- Hello.
Hello. Good morning.
What?
I'm sure I saved the file yesterday.
Where is it?
What happened? Why...
What happened?
Where did it go?
What's wrong?
What should I do?
I told you not to send the dishes.
Why do you keep sending them?
There's no room for the dishes
in the fridge.
I don't want you to be tired.
Okay.
Did you get the money I sent?
No, that's not all.
I have some money for myself.
So did you pay Dad's hospital bill?
Okay. Yes.
Don't just make do
with instant noodles.
Mom.
I might become
a full-time employee this time.
So just hang in there until then.
Okay?
Yes.
Take good care of your health.
Okay.
Let's begin.
- Mom.
- Okay. All right.
Please excuse me.
Gosh, Sang Hyuk.
This is a robot
from a cartoon, right?
What was the name?
It's Mega Bad Racer.
Right. Bad Racer?
It's the strongest one, right?
It goes like this.
Sang Hyuk, how many...
heroes and villains
are in the cartoon?
Are there about 20?
Can you tell me how many there are?
Yes, I can.
Gosh. Go ahead.
Sang Hyuk, can you count them
with your mouth open?
What are you talking about?
The file is gone?
It's not like the file has legs.
Aren't you just making excuses
because you didn't finish it?
That's not true.
I'm telling you I finished it.
She's right.
I saw it before I left yesterday.
The idea sounded trendy,
so I liked it.
How did that happen?
Did you not save the file?
It's not like that.
Yes. I guess I forgot
to save the file.
It's my mistake.
I'm so sorry, sir.
The file is gone,
but I still remember the content.
Please let me give
a verbal presentation.
Forget it. This isn't
some kind of school project.
How would you give a presentation
to the director without a file?
Please give me a chance.
I said no.
Why are you so clumsy?
See one and you've seen them all.
This is why I care about
educational background.
Your work says everything.
Da Hee, you don't seem desperate.
You just stroll around
with no thought.
And you just do what you're told to.
That's why you're still
serving your internship...
like an amateur at your age.
You know that?
I should've picked someone
from a four-year college.
Those who are incompetent
always lack tenacity.
This is so frustrating.
I guess that's why her husband
broke off their marriage.
How do you know that?
What?
Whether it was me or the groom
who broke off the marriage.
How would you know that?
Why?
An intern from a two-year college
must have been dumped, right?
What is she talking about?
I just strolled around doing
what I was told to do?
That's true.
I was busy going around
and meeting our clients.
I was always running short on time
doing odd jobs for you.
So I'm an amateur?
That's also true.
I didn't even have a chance
to learn real work doing all that.
You had no intention to teach me
real work in the first place.
Look here, Ms. Song.
You know what? You did graduate...
from a college in Seoul,
but it's not even
a major university.
You always talk about
educational background.
Isn't that just because
of your own inferiority complex?
What? How dare you say that?
I'm not finished.
I'm the second most treasured...
I mean, I'm the most treasured
daughter to my parents.
You have no right to insult me
and yell at me like that.
If you're the boss, you should
lead the team with your ability...
instead of watching porn
during office hours.
Hey, you... Get out!
Yes. I'm leaving.
It's not that you're firing me.
I quit. Got it?
When your precious son grows up
and starts working,
I hope he will meet a boss
just like you.
He will be mistreated
and work overtime every night.
I hope he will be treated
just like me.
What is that lunatic talking about?
Gosh, I can't believe this.
Da Hee.
Da Hee!
You know, right?
You know the whole thing.
But why...
I didn't do it for you.
Your mom sent me some potatoes
she grew herself one time.
I'm just paying it back.
Da Hee.
I'm sorry, Da Hee.
I just had no choice.
No.
You always have a choice, Song Yi.
This is your choice.
It's your choice
that you want to survive this way.
And it is my choice
that I'm quitting like this.
I ended up getting fired,
but I'm not ashamed of myself.
What about you?
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Thank you, Doctor.
- Yes.
- That was the last patient.
Already?
Why does work finish
on time these days?
Why do we not
have many patients here?
I always said we should promote
our hospital better.
You're finished, aren't you?
What? Jeong Hun?
How serious is it?
Okay. I'll be right there.
Okay. Wait for me.
Oh, hi. My friend just got injured
in a three-way collision.
Gosh, this is serious.
I'm sorry,
but I can't make it today.
I will talk to you later.
I'm sorry. I have no choice.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Where do I go now?
(Yongju Traditional Market
Merchant Association)
And one more thing.
Since the spring event,
we all have...
worked really hard together.
Like I always say...
Where did you get your hair dyed?
It looks good.
At the shop behind the drug store.
It's only 15 dollars.
Really? That's great.
Just pretend to listen to him.
It won't end otherwise.
Anyway, on the agenda
at the previous meeting...
was a program for
our members' health and welfare.
Research showed that...
most of you were interested in
learning dance sports.
Starting next week,
we'll hire an instructor...
to teach us in
the afternoon or evening.
I'd like you all to
attend if possible.
Listen. Just to
give us a demonstration,
the instructor agreed to
come by today.
Anyone who wishes to take part
can come to the lounge.
Especially you men.
Make sure to be there.
Okay.
Will the president
and his wife be present?
No, not me.
We're both terrible at
anything physical.
The president and wife
should be a good example.
You want people to attend.
Exactly. The president
should be there...
so other men can join. Am I wrong?
- No.
Well, that is true, but I'm not...
- He said yes!
- Applause!
Sirs and madams,
it's lovely to meet you.
Let's see how supple you are...
by learning the basic step.
Look at us.
In 7, 8.
1, 2, cha, cha, 1.
2, 3, cha, cha, 1.
Keep going. 2, 3, cha, cha, 1.
Wow. This mother here is so good.
You're our ace.
Hey, I'm not a mother. I'm a miss.
Oh, I see. I apologize.
She's just saying what she thought.
It's your fault
for not looking single.
Stop it.
Miss, is this right?
Is this how to dance?
Is this it? It is, isn't it?
Yes. Not bad.
Ma'am, shall I help you?
No, I'm fine. I can manage.
Go on. Get his help.
- Why me?
- Why not?
Go on.
Don't be silly.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
I love it.
Korean beer is just my taste.
- It's so good.
- Is it?
You said you'd live in Istanbul
and play golf and gaze at the sea.
Hey. Great views
only last you for a while.
I looked at so much green
that my eyesight improved.
I was hoping to visit
while you were there.
You should've stayed a while longer.
Why did you come back?
Didn't I tell you to visit soon?
Pil Jae got to visit, didn't he?
Attention. One o'clock.
Why? What? How pretty is she?
I'm looking right now.
You don't have a decent job
and you aren't that pretty.
Your family isn't that great either.
We're done.
Our marriage is void, okay?
She looks like something
definitely happened to her.
What do you think that is?
Was she dumped?
Was she conned?
Did she lose the deposit
to her lease to a pyramid scheme?
No. You're all wrong.
On the day of their wedding,
she witnessed
her fiance cheating on her.
And the guy had the gall
to void the wedding, I think?
Perhaps?
That's detailed.
Have you been watching
Korean dramas in Turkey?
Not in Turkey.
The day I returned,
I saw something killer.
- What?
- What did you see?
Hey, wait here.
I drank a whole pitcher
and I'm even not drunk.
Nothing in the world
goes how I want it to.
My gosh.
Hey. Excuse me.
Is this yours?
Thank you. I appreciate it. Thanks.
You're welcome. Get home safely.
You seem drunk.
What?
I'm not. I'm not drunk at all.
You're wrong. You look very drunk.
Never mind, then.
Wait!
You brought me my belongings,
and I'm eternally grateful.
Would you like to get
just one drink with me?
I really want to get drunk.
I really, really do.
Yes?
What kind of drunk antic is this?
Slowly. Slow down.
Don't you worry. I'm not drunk.
The more I drink,
the more sober I feel.
Hey.
Why do you think
I asked you to drink with me?
I don't know.
Because I'm handsome?
You're really funny, mister.
What, "mister"?
It's clear that
we're only 4 or 5 years apart.
I asked you to drink with me...
because I don't know you.
What?
I feel so frustrated.
If I were to just go home like this,
I think I'd grab my parents
and wail my heart out.
I want to get things off my chest,
but I can't talk to a friend
or someone I know.
I don't want them to
see me at my lowest,
and it hurts my pride.
Hey.
I have no idea
what you're going through,
but you can't get
over a man like this.
He wasn't even worth this...
I don't think.
Pretend you stepped on a turd.
It happens to all of us
once in our lifetime.
It was just a bad day.
- Yes, we step in turds.
- Right.
When it gets in a tiny crease
in the sole, that's darn annoying.
You know the feeling.
The truth is,
my marriage was voided
on the day of the wedding.
I won't say why
because that's privacy.
But then today, I even lost my job.
Don't you think that
life is just crazy?
Here.
My nickname is Last One.
It's only because
I'm the youngest child,
but is that why?
I've been the last at everything
my whole life.
The oldest, my brother,
is great at sports.
My oldest sister is pretty.
My second sister is amazingly smart.
I feel as if my older siblings
took all the good traits,
and I'm the one that got made
with the leftovers from them.
Thinking about that made me sad.
I wish I had just one good trait.
You're too hard on yourself.
All human beings...
have value just by existing.
Why cut yourself down
by comparing yourself to others?
"Just be myself."
You don't know that phrase?
Just... Just be what?
You just live as yourself.
Be yourself.
That's way cool.
That's a huge dignity boost.
Did you go to a good school?
Why does that matter?
That's a prejudice too.
Is your IQ over 100?
Yours isn't?
I feel a bit tipsy now. I should go.
Okay. Hang on.
Wait. What are you doing?
I invited you for a drink.
I should buy.
What do you take me for?
I don't mind paying. Okay then.
Hang on.
How much do I owe you?
- Wait.
- Just a moment. Hello?
It's 96 dollars.
What?
Nine?
Did you say 90?
Yes.
Let me see...
We had a lot.
What's this?
I'm sorry. Lend me 64 dollars.
This means I'm paying.
My gosh.
What is this?
What has gotten into you?
It's not like you to call first.
Tell me about it.
So how have you all been these days?
Must you ask when
I'm a father of twins?
I'm either at work
or watching my kids.
I feed them, change their diapers,
and put them to sleep.
Then the cycle repeats.
- So he's saying he's happy.
- How did you know?
You look good too.
How's divorce treating you?
Good. So what?
Is it really nice?
In what way?
You know how...
my ex-wife and I constantly argued.
When I was still married to her,
I didn't mind Mondays.
Going to work was better
than staying at home.
One day, I stood outside my house
after coming home from work.
It felt like a rock
was pressing on my heart.
I just didn't want to go inside.
So I decided to wait
until she fell asleep...
and walked toward the bench.
And there was my wife.
She had the same idea.
So we signed the papers
the next day and went to court.
You made the right choice.
You both have a right...
to live comfortably.
Anyway, it's been great.
My ex-wife agrees.
I feel like we were wrong
to hold onto our marriage...
and deprive ourselves of happiness.
Relationships can be weird.
There was a time when we had fun...
just sharing an ice cream.
Let me join you for that drink.
My goodness.
Don't deny it.
We drifted apart...
and became
no better than strangers...
since that day.
I felt guilty...
and you resented me.
This is my first time making soup,
but I think I did better
than my mom.
You need to eat well
at times like this, okay?
Please eat even though
you don't feel like it.
Sorry.
I don't want to.
I'll get to it later.
Shouldn't you be resting some more?
I got your favorite...
Did you throw them away?
Yes.
They just seemed to be taking space.
We could buy new ones
when we need them.
Who gave you the right
to throw them all away?
You should've discussed it with me!
Good for you...
for being able to move on so easily.
Na Hee...
An anonymous donation
was made through an acquaintance...
Aren't you tired?
Should we go to bed?
Sure thing.
What's that?
- No way.
- Gyu Jin?
My son?
There you are.
I bought trotters, your favorite.
It's just for you, my son.
- Mom, you're wasted.
- My sweet boy.
Gyu Jin?
Where are you?
Gosh, I'm wasted.
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
My shift just ended. How about you?
I still have a few things to do.
You should head home first.
Sure. Got it.
Gyu Jin, look over here. 1, 2...
Wait, I pressed the record button.
- You did that on purpose, right?
- Of course not.
Try some of this.
Gyu Jin, say a few words.
We're here to eat patbingsu.
Here you go.
- Isn't it good?
- It's so good.
Are you going
to keep recording this?
Oh, right.
Na Hee.
Do you remember
the snack diner we used...
to go to?
They sold tteokbokki
and patbingsu there.
We used to love their patbingsu.
Why don't we go there
for old times' sake?
It shut down two years ago.
Also,
I don't like patbingsu anymore.
Da Hee, breakfast is ready!
My gosh.
Gosh, it reeks of alcohol.
Why does it smell
like an old man lives here?
Last One.
Wake up.
You should get ready for work.
Mom cooked
dried pollack soup for you.
Wake up already.
Let me be.
I'm not going to work today.
Why not?
Are you still drunk?
I don't have to.
- I'm taking the day off.
- What?
Can interns do that?
What if you get fired for this?
So what if I'm an intern?
Aren't interns
allowed vacation days?
I'm going back to bed, so leave.
Get out of here!
My gosh. All right.
There's no need to throw a fit.
Go back to bed.
Unbelievable.
Da Hee has adopted
quite the temper these days.
Isn't she getting up?
She's taking the day off from work.
She even raised her voice
and threw a fit.
That's not like her.
I'm guessing she's still
not over the annulment.
She had a team dinner last night,
so I'm sure she's tired.
Just let her get enough sleep.
Sure thing, Father.
That workplace of hers...
constantly has team dinners
and eats late at night.
If only they'd pay her enough.
What do you expect
when she's only an intern?
It's not easy earning money
from other people, you know.
You're saying that as if
you're out there making a living.
Of course, I am.
I'm receiving child support.
Unbelievable.
Keep it down...
- and go back to your meal.
- Got it.
Are you taking Ji Hun
to his father today?
Yes, he said he was busy,
but I guess he made time.
- Really, Mom?
- Of course.
He'll pick you up from school,
so come straight out.
Yes, Mom.
I'll get ready for school then.
Thank you for the meal.
You should eat some more!
He sure is young, isn't he?
He's thrilled to see his dad.
Just so you know,
I have work today.
- No one asked.
- Got it.
Get in. Let's go to work together.
Forget it. I'll just take a cab.
There's really no need for that.
Hop in.
Let's do it.
Let's get divorced.
We'll head to the court together
after work.
I'll stop by your office.
All right.
I got it. I said I wouldn't be late.
- Dad!
- I'll call you back.
Ji Hun, how have you been?
- Have you been well too?
- Of course.
Bring him home by 10 p.m.
He has homework to do.
Got it.
Wait, did you dye your hair?
Right, that color
definitely suits you.
Meanwhile, you're losing your hair.
You should watch out
since you're dating someone young.
Is that so?
Is it bad?
I've been applying
some ointment these days.
Whatever you do
is none of my business,
so just bring him back on time.
Ji Hun, I'll see you later.
Do you think I lost a lot of hair?
- No, you look great.
- Right?
That's my boy.
Why did she have
to annoy me like that?
Have you been well?
I said I won't be late.
Must you buy it today of all days?
I have to, at least once a month.
You know that.
What's up with you today?
Hold on a second...
Hello? Unbelievable.
Go ahead. Dig in.
- Dad.
- Yes?
- I'm going to the restroom.
- Sure.
Go ahead.
How can you hang up on me like that?
Must I go with you to buy that?
Mom...
Make the swings bigger like so.
That's right.
Jun Yeong, you can't be like this.
You agreed to film
the motorcycle scene yourself.
I don't think I'm in
the perfect condition though.
Have one of my boys do the scene.
Out of the blue?
Would it be all right?
It's what we're paid to do.
- Jeong Bong, let's talk.
- Sure.
You're closest to
his height and build.
You'll be filming
a motorcycle scene.
A motorcycle?
That's not really my specialty.
As if that's important.
You probably know
how to ride one though.
Come on, Mr. Jang.
You can't make him film the scene
without giving him a heads-up.
It's nothing too difficult,
so he'll be fine.
I'll teach you the route...
A stunt shouldn't be performed
just because it can be done.
Out on the field,
accidents happen...
even when all precautions are taken.
You can't keep accepting
requests like this.
We only have one life, you know.
Tell him it can't be done
unless you'll be doing it yourself.
What?
Mr. Jang, come on over.
We'll cut out the motorcycle scene
and save some time.
Sure thing.
Guys, stretch out your limbs.
Taller ones to the back,
shorter ones to the front.
Look at her handwriting.
Oddly enough, she's a funny one.
You never know,
so I'll keep it as a lucky charm.
Mom, must you be this relentless?
Hi, Mom.
Jae Seok, where on earth are you?
I'm in Turkey, of course.
I just woke up.
Are you kidding me?
Why do you keep dodging my calls?
Why won't you call back?
- I'm sorry.
- Did you call Dr. Kim?
Yes, just a second ago.
Wait. What was that?
I think I heard Korean just now.
- Right?
- Mom,
it was Korean TV.
I fell asleep while watching it.
I guess it kept going all night.
I'm running late,
so I should get ready.
I'll call you when I can.
Don't skip your meals
and know that I love you.
Come in.
Your shift is over, right?
- We should go.
- Sure.
Dr. Yoon!
Gosh, I'm glad.
You're still here.
I'm sorry, but can you
help me with a patient?
Gi Yeong,
I'm sorry but not today.
You should ask Dr. Park.
She's still in her office.
Let's go.
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
It's okay. I'll get it.
Even when it's over,
you still won't let me do anything.
Fine. Let's get going.
(Seoul Family Court)
- Are you Yoon Gyu Jin?
- Yes, that's me.
- Song Na Hee?
- That's me.
Your application has been received.
You have a cooling-off period
of one month to rethink things.
The final decision
will be made on April 10.
Your presence is requested
in Court 301 at 11:30 a.m.
A notification will be sent to you.
- Sure.
- Got it.
You're done then.
Sorry?
- Is that it?
- Yes, the application is all set.
Next!
Gosh, sorry.
It sure is easy
to apply for a divorce.
Tell me about it.
Coming to this decision wasn't easy,
but it sure is to get divorced.
How about we grab a bite?
As if I'd have an appetite for that.
Let's take a walk instead.
Let's be cool.
Congratulations.
On getting away from me and my mom.
We still have a cooling-off period.
Let's not make
a big deal out it though.
It's not like we did it
in a fit of rage after a big fight.
What's the point of having
a cooling-off period of a month?
Okay. I agree.
Anyway, congratulations to you too
for escaping from this life.
Thank you.
I finally get to take a walk
with you after a long time.
But I didn't want it
to be like this.
I'm a little sad.
Don't be.
It's not like we're losers.
We just made a different choice.
You think?
Sure.
You know the condition, right?
Make sure to keep it a secret from
our families for the time being.
If your mom finds out
that I asked for a divorce,
- she will...
- Hang on.
What do you mean
that you asked for a divorce?
This is a divorce
by mutual agreement.
Okay. Let's just say that it is.
It's not that we say that.
It's true.
I think you're mistaken.
It's not like I'm getting a divorce
for you against my will.
I made my decision
after much deliberation.
- Do you understand?
- Okay. I get it.
I wondered why things were
so peaceful between you and me.
That's what I was going to say.
I thought it was awkward.
What will you do with our house?
Will you put it up for sale?
Of course.
We will sell it and split it in half
so we can each get a studio.
Okay. We should call a realtor then.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- All right.
We should do it now.
We don't have to wait.
- Let's go.
- Okay. Let's do that.
Let's go then.
You should go that way.
- We'd like to sell urgently.
Well... This isn't the right time.
We don't know how
the real estate policy will change.
And the housing price
has hit the bottom.
I don't care.
I don't mind losing money.
Just put it up for sale.
Right. Let us sell the house
as soon as possible.
Really? All right then.
If you want to sell it urgently,
you should lower the price
by about 100,000 dollars.
- 100,000 dollars?
Seo Jin, you're still here.
Where's Joon Seon?
He went to the shoot.
Aren't you hungry?
How could you sleep all day?
Gosh, Seo Jin.
You're good at drawing.
You're even better than me.
Seo Jin.
Do you want me to buy you ice cream?
Shall we go out?
(Young Mart)
Seo Jin, you have a white mustache.
Are you a grandma?
Do you like it?
I'm glad
that I bought you ice cream.
Seo Jin, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
Right.
You have no idea at your age.
Actually, there was something
I wanted to learn.
I want to heal angels
with wounded hearts like you.
But if I were to do that,
I had to study a lot
and go to a good college.
Unfortunately, I wasn't
so good at studying.
So I just gave up.
"I'll just go to a two-year college
and get a job."
"If I work hard, I can succeed."
Or so I thought.
But life is quite tough.
I want to start all over again.
Do you think I can do that?
Can I be brave and start afresh?
I can't? Is it too late?
What? Is it a yes or a no?
Seo Jin.
How did you know we were here?
Ga Hee said
you two went out together.
Seo Jin, your mom couldn't
come to pick you up.
So she asked me to take you home.
Do you want to go home with me?
Let's go. All right.
I'll take Seo Jin home.
Okay. See you.
Bye, Seo Jin.
Just be myself.
She fell asleep on the way here.
All right. I'm sorry.
The bathroom is leaking,
but the plumber says he has no time.
So did he fix it already?
No, he said he'd come right away,
but he hasn't come yet.
- I'll call him again.
- I'll do it.
I guess it's a plumbing problem.
Do you have a toolbox?
It's okay. He'll come soon.
You shouldn't let a stranger
into a house full of women.
It won't take long.
Get me a toolbox.
Wait.
It will be done soon.
Is it doenjang jjigae?
It smells amazing.
Is it done?
Yes. The pipes got loose.
It tastes good with a lot of tofu.
Get going if you're done. It's late.
Thank you.
What?
Okay. I should go.
Gosh.
Bye.
I'm home. Dad!
Hello, sweetheart. You're home late.
I had an extra class.
What are you doing here?
Are you sleeping over?
What?
Are you two living together now?
It's not like that.
He just dropped by
to bring Seo Jin home.
Is that it? I see.
All right.
I should get going then. Bye.
Make sure to turn off the tap.
If the toilet leaks again, call me.
Okay. Thank you.
- Bye, Dad. I'll text you.
- Okay.
Why? What?
I smell food. You should've let him
stay for dinner.
Dad likes your doenjang jjigae.
Don't be silly. Just go wash up.
And wake Seo Jin up.
Mom.
I read an article on the Internet.
A child from a divorced family...
might suffer from a sense of loss,
anxiety, and fear.
So I'd like you to try...
to get back together with Dad...
for my sake. Okay?
You took an exam
at the academy today, didn't you?
Seo Jin. Wake up, Seo Jin. I'm home.
It must be delicious.
Hyun Gyung makes
really good doenjang jjigae.
What do you want?
Shall we sell the house?
We should.
We can't get a new place...
unless we sell this house.
I know. I guess you're right.
But I heard the house price
might bounce back in a few months.
It's not a few months.
It might happen in a few weeks.
It has just hit bottom.
And we have to lower
the price by 100,000 dollars.
That's a huge loss.
I guess an expert
dissuades us for a reason.
Okay.
My point.
So let's be honest with each other.
Let's not be emotional.
We should think reasonably.
Do you think 100,000 dollars
is little money?
No. We've worked really hard
to save that money.
We've gone through our internship
and residency training...
in so many operating rooms
to save that money.
I know.
That's how hard we've worked.
We can't lose that money
in the heat of the moment.
We're not that foolish.
We are intellectual people.
I don't know about you, but I am.
Let's not put it up for sale
so urgently.
Even if it takes time, we should
receive a reasonable price. Okay?
Good. Until then,
we stay here together.
Okay, although it doesn't
mean anything.
We're just sharing the house.
We're like housemates.
Housemates sound good. Okay.
But we should respect
each other's privacy.
Of course.
I will be at the hospital all day
and just sleep here anyway.
I'll sleep in the bedroom,
and you'll sleep in the living room.
Okay.
So we will share this house
for the time being.
Deal. Why don't we have
a written contract then?
Deal.
(Cohabitation)
Cohabitation Contract.
One. Song Na Hee
occupies the bedroom...
and Yoon Gyu Jin occupies
the living room.
Article 1, Clause 1. Cleaning
and interior design are left...
to the owner's discretion.
Two. The rest of the house
is owned communally.
So it should be cleaned
by both parties.
Article 2, Clause 1.
Every Sunday at 9 a.m.,
there should be
a general house cleaning.
The kitchen is cleaned by Song
and the bathroom is cleaned by Yoon.
Seven. Both parties must attend
family occasions...
like birthdays, national holidays,
or ancestral rites.
For other occasions,
prior notice must be given.
And they are attended
by mutual consent only.
Eight. This agreement shall not be
disclosed to anyone.
The one who discloses it
takes full responsibility...
and moves out,
forfeiting all shares in the house.
Is there anything you want to add?
No. It's perfect.
This is the most important clause.
"The one who discloses it
takes full responsibility..."
"and moves out,
forfeiting all shares in the house."
You bet.
Say we're living together
when we're divorced.
Our parents would all faint.
What about at work?
We don't have to lie to them.
We can't tell for a while.
Once the director finds out,
it's only time until Mom does.
You're right. We shouldn't tell
our colleagues for a while too.
Let's print the contract.
Okay.
Are you home?
How much fun did you have
that you're sleepy already?
Was it that much fun?
Yes. I had fun.
Hey, I get jealous
if you have too much fun.
Tell the truth.
If Mom and Dad are drowning,
who will you save first?
I can't swim.
Don't try to talk your way out.
Who will you save first?
Who will you save?
- Who will you save?
- That tickles.
- Stop it.
- I won't.
Ji Hun wants to sleep.
He must be tired
after hanging out with his dad.
Do you still have half the melon?
Give him some when he wakes.
This was expensive.
You're showing off
with a melon you got on sale?
It's still an expensive melon.
Okay, fine. I get it.
Why do you keep
looking at the front door?
Why is that?
Are you hopeful because
Joon Seon went to Hyun Gyung's?
I'm not hopeful.
Don't you make things up.
As if.
You're just looking for an excuse
to get them back together.
- Right?
- You're right.
- I'm home!
- That's him.
How come we're having melon?
Why are you back so late?
Did Hyun Gyung make you dinner?
No. I fixed something for her.
And then?
I left because she told me to.
Is that it?
Darn it. And I thought...
She denied it, but look at her
looking all disappointed.
I know. It's too obvious.
It shows.
- Cut them into smaller pieces.
- Joon Seon.
- Okay.
- You can't eat them all.
Wasn't it for me?
Make sure the skin is thin.
Okay!
Da Hee, come over here.
Have some fruit.
Here. We got it for cheap,
but it's really sweet.
Listen, Mom, Dad.
I have something to say.
Why are you suddenly being
so awkward and polite?
You're not getting back with...
No, right?
I...
What do you want to say
that you're so serious? Just say it.
Yes. We're used to getting
shocking news,
so nothing's bad anymore. Say it.
I quit my job.
Why? Why did you quit?
Did you quit or get fired?
Half and half.
And there's one more thing.
There's more?
The contract stands
until this apartment is sold.
Any objections, Ms. Song Na Hee?
No. No objections.
Then...
(Yoon Gyu Jin)
(Song Na Hee)
There.
I hope we get along, housemate.
Same here.
I'll...
I'll go back to university.
- What?
University? What university?
I'll study and transfer to
a four-year university.
Mom. Dad.
(Once Again)
Na Hee!
Clause three of
the Cohabitation Code.
You never touch
your housemate's belongings.
Wait, stop.
Clause five of
the Cohabitation Code.
Did you not memorize that one?
- Darn it.
- Why are you so annoyed?
Did you and Na Hee fight again?
Why do you want to know
what goes on in my private life?
You got divorced?
Divorced?
You're belittling me, aren't you?
Get the hostess!
The hostess is right here.
What's the problem?