Let's all raise a glass
to Da Hee's happiness.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
- Here comes more food.
- Great.
Make some room.
Mom.
Ouch! That's so hot!
Save me!
- Oh, dear.
- Are you okay?
(Episode 3)
My gosh,
what on earth just happened?
All except 1 of their 4 kids
have failed marriages?
Maybe this house is cursed.
Should I suggest
some sort of exorcism?
Why though?
You...
got married just several hours ago.
We waved you off
as you set out for your honeymoon.
Now you want an annulment?
Why on earth
would you bring this up?
Mom, it's...
Did you and Young Hoon
get into a fight?
Is that why...
you suddenly want to call it quits?
Stop interrupting her
and let her speak.
How can I when I'm this angry
and frustrated?
I don't think I can do this.
I don't think
I can live with him forever.
What?
Are you kidding me right now?
Marriage isn't a game, you know.
You can't say that
after walking down the aisle.
My gosh. This must be a joke.
I thought she was the sweet one,
but look at what she has done.
Is she seriously throwing a tantrum?
Honey, keep it down!
There's no need to
yell at her like that.
How can I not raise my voice?
Whatever.
If this happened
because of an argument,
go back to him and apologize.
Ask for his forgiveness
and calm him down.
No.
What?
This isn't because I'm angry.
It's over for us, Mom.
What will you do
if it really is over?
The food we ate at the wedding
hasn't even been digested, you brat.
What about our guests
who came to the wedding?
What about our relatives?
Da Hee, look.
I say this from experience.
This is how marriage is.
You argue...
and consider calling it quits,
but you still keep going.
Quarrels between married couples
never last.
I'm sure that Young Hoon
is waiting for you to call.
Why don't we get him
on the phone first?
Yes, that sounds like a good idea.
I'll try to appease his anger,
so talk to him and...
No.
I'm done, Mom.
But Da Hee.
What do you mean, you're done?
What will you do now?
What are you going to do, you brat?
Just what...
- Mom, no!
- Stop hitting her.
- Mom, don't.
- Let go!
How dare you humiliate us like this?
- Mom...
- How dare you!
- Don't get physical, Mom.
- How dare you.
It's not like I'm asking for much.
All I want is for you
to have an ordinary life.
Is that really so hard to do
for all of you?
Is it nice to see
your brother and sister...
live back at home
after failing their marriages?
Is that why you're
following in their footsteps?
Honey, please.
Kids, take her outside.
Here. Da Hee, get up.
Take her outside.
Come on. Let's go.
- I...
- My gosh.
Darn it!
No wonder I had...
this odd feeling in my stomach
during the ceremony.
How could she do this to me too?
Three of my kids
hammered a nail into my chest.
One after one, again and again!
What did I ever do to deserve this?
What did I even do wrong?
What...
- Mom?
- Mom!
Dad, something is wrong with mom.
Are you all right?
Honey, look at me.
My gosh, hold on.
Mom...
- Dad, hurry.
- Hurry!
Here you go. Now breathe.
Come on, 1, 2...
How can you cause this mess
on the day of your wedding?
Na Hee, I'd rather talk tomorrow.
I want to get some rest.
How does this even make sense?
I'd have the same reaction
as Mom as well.
Aren't you old enough
to know what's important?
Where's your
sense of responsibility?
Is this a joke to you?
Are you insane?
Gosh, how stupid are you?
That's right. I'm a fool, okay?
I caused this mess because
I'm not as smart as you.
It's why I voiced
my uncertainty at first.
I didn't know if I loved him...
and marriage seemed
like a hasty decision.
But Mom said I should marry him
before he changes his mind.
Then you should've been adamant
about what you want.
In the end, this was your choice.
Why say otherwise
when you went along with it?
Take responsibility
for your own actions...
and don't be a fool!
You're right. I'm a fool.
I hate that about myself too,
you know.
Everything you said is true,
so please stop yelling at me.
How dare you yell at me
when you're the one to blame?
Da Hee, come on.
Must you be like that
when she's obviously in pain?
- Get out.
- But I'm not done yet.
Shut up and leave!
This is why they say
it's better not to have kids.
No wonder why I don't want to marry.
What? I can't let it go to waste.
It'll cost more money
to throw out all the food.
Go ahead. Someone should eat this.
- Sorry?
- Here you go.
Oh, right. Sure.
Get out here.
Unbelievable.
Is Da Hee all right?
This is how
it's going to be all night.
You should head home
and leave this to us.
Don't you have work tomorrow?
I wonder if your mom
will be all right.
She seemed more than shocked.
Da Hee can be quite odd sometimes.
Your brother and older sister
are usually loud anyway,
but Da Hee is more the quiet type.
An annulment?
I guess...
the quieter ones
do cause bigger issues though.
They usually keep all their emotions
bottled up inside...
so when that bottle
finally pops open... Bang!
Gyu Jin, come on.
What?
Keep it down, will you?
I have enough of a headache.
Right, I understand.
I need water.
Ga Hee, it's me. How's Mom?
Is she lying down?
Will she even
be able to sleep tonight?
How's Da Hee?
No sane person...
- would be able to sleep.
- Soccer...
I'm upset, that's why.
- Pass!
- Gosh, this is bad.
Ga Hee, hold on.
Can't you see that I'm on the phone?
- What?
- Turn it off.
- Right, of course.
- Son Heung Min passes the ball.
- Son Heung Min makes a run.
- Right.
To the inside.
- Son Heung Min shoots.
- Shoot!
- Ga Hee, I'll call you back.
- Unbelievable.
You call that a pass?
It hit the goal post...
What on earth are you doing?
Son Heung Min was playing.
That's what I should be asking.
Your sister-in-law
came home on her wedding night,
and you're watching soccer?
You say you're family too.
That's what you say to my mom.
What am I supposed to do?
Should I dive under my covers
and cry like Da Hee too?
Or maybe I should
get down on my knees...
and pray for everything
to get better.
I don't appreciate your sarcasm.
And I know you look down
on my family.
I know what you think
about Joon Seon and Ga Hee.
You think less of them
because they're divorced, don't you?
Why must you get
all sensitive like this?
It's not like your family
is any better.
Look at today for instance.
What on earth is wrong
with your mother?
If she's running late,
she could've sent you over first.
Why can't your mom
take a taxi like a normal person?
Unbelievable. Must you be so crude?
No one talks like that
about their mother-in-law.
Why not? It's not like
she's my mother, is she?
Fine, whatever.
Talking to you is too exhausting.
Let's just drop it.
You're going to watch soccer,
aren't you?
As if. I won't, okay?
Take the remote control with you
if you want to.
I won't turn it on. Go ahead.
It doesn't mean that
you should really take it with you!
Gosh, she can be so
so catty sometimes.
Darn him.
(Da Hee's wedding,
ovulation)
Shoot!
However, it hit the goal post.
Wash up.
Forget it. Let me be.
- Go and wash up.
- Stop it.
Do I need your permission
to wash up and shower now?
Are you my mom?
Should I call you that, Mom?
Fine, then just
take off your clothes.
What?
What did you just say?
I've started to ovulate.
I already knew this morning,
but forgot because
of the mess Da Hee caused.
Still, I'm glad you didn't drink.
Are you serious?
We were arguing
just about a second ago.
It's a temporary truce
due to an emergency situation.
We don't have time,
so let's get this over with.
Hold on. Wait a second.
You may be able
to control your emotions like that,
but I can't. I really can't.
Let's not be like amateurs.
No one said anything about emotions.
This is only physical.
Wait, don't come any closer.
How can you say that
without batting an eye?
Have you no shame at all?
This isn't homework, you know.
Just shut it, okay?
I'm just letting you know of
your physiological duty to perform.
Just come here.
Like you said,
just think of it as doing homework.
Hang on.
I'm going to shout. Don't do that.
Stop it.
Don't do this to me.
We're doing it anyway.
Don't waste your energy.
Stop it. Don't do that.
Hey! Stop right there, Gyu Jin.
Gyu Jin, open it.
Aren't you going to open it?
I will never open it.
You're so... You know what?
I have my own principles.
I'm not opening it.
Come on out while I'm being nice
unless you want to see blood.
Hey, just give up.
You'll never lay
a finger on me tonight.
We don't have time.
Just open the door.
Hey, Gyu Jin!
Open up before I count to three.
Otherwise, I'll smash down the door.
One.
Two.
Hey, have it your way.
There's no way I'm opening it.
I'll never open the door.
Mom. Mom!
Mom.
Come and take a look at this.
Hurry and come on out.
Gosh, that was quick.
It's as if he was afraid
she'd want to get back together.
Gosh, it hurts.
I guess he's just
trying to scare her.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to work.
My colleague is taking care
of my work now.
I should go.
Are you going to work? Now?
You.
Come with me.
Mom, I have to go.
I got a text message that we have
an issue with a group tour.
Just come with me before I have you
erased from our family register.
Mom, please.
Gosh, that naive fool.
I'm so tired.
You're out of your mind.
How can you go to work
at a time like this?
Why not just go around
and tell people...
that you called off your marriage?
No one is that interested
in me anyway.
And people will find out eventually.
Do you seriously want a beating
or something?
Madam Jang. Why use violence?
This isn't like you.
He's right. Let's talk it out
like cultured people.
Da Hee. You're not seriously
going to work, are you?
You just said that because
you were frustrated, right?
See? Mom, silence means yes.
She was just frustrated.
Calm down and have a seat.
Please. You have
high blood pressure.
I'm afraid you might collapse.
Let go of me.
Don't play the hypocrite.
You are the ones who raised
my blood pressure.
I'm going out for a moment.
You guys make sure
that she stays in her room.
If she gets out of her room,
I'll kick you guys out of the house.
Gosh, Mom. Why would you say
such scary things?
Okay, Mom.
- Where are you going, by the way?
- See you, Mom.
Don't worry about Da Hee.
How could you miss that game?
It kept going back and forth,
and Son Heung Min
scored a volley...
despite his injury
during the injury time.
It was beautiful.
I can imagine...
What now? What do you want?
Clear your schedule after work.
I made an appointment at a clinic.
A clinic? What clinic?
What clinic do you think?
It's a fertility clinic.
Checking the ovulation day
with an ob-gyn isn't enough.
We should go to a clinic together
and get a test to do things right.
Na Hee, how could you do
such a thing without telling me?
Na Hee, let's just take our time
and do things naturally.
We're not that old yet.
Naturally how?
You just go into a panic
when I touch you.
It's not that I go into a panic.
I was like that
because it wasn't the right time.
When is the right time then?
Have we even had
the right time recently?
What's wrong between us?
Then do you think nothing is wrong
between us?
Are you serious?
Make sure to be there on time.
It's at six o'clock.
Hanbit Fertility Clinic.
Hey. What...
Gosh, this is crazy.
(My Youngest Son-in-law)
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be directed to voicemail.
Please leave
a message after the beep.
- You startled me.
- Hey.
I don't feel right about this.
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
I'm supposed to console
my heartbroken sister.
But I'm watching her instead.
What kind of brother is that?
I am so ashamed as the firstborn son
of this family and her brother.
There you go again.
Joon Seon, come and have a seat.
Why? What?
Joon Seon, listen carefully to me.
Did you see Mom's eyes
when she said,
"I'll kick you guys out
of this house"?
If things go wrong,
the three of us will be doomed.
So?
That cheesy sentiment,
sympathy, and brotherliness.
Forget all that.
Even if we take her side now,
it won't help her.
It will just put us in trouble.
You're so silly.
So?
What's so hard to understand?
Just shut it and do as you're told.
You shouldn't lose Mom's favor.
- My gosh.
- I see.
But still,
it must be stuffy to be cooped up
in that room all day.
She must be hungry too.
I know, right?
She must be hungry, right?
She hasn't eaten since last night.
Shall I make her some food?
I mean Mom didn't say
we weren't allowed to give her food.
She didn't.
I'm sure she didn't say that.
Isn't she Ok Boon?
- Ok Boon.
Ok Boon.
I didn't see you there.
Were you going somewhere?
We went to a sauna.
Where did you go
at this time of day?
I was just out in the neighborhood.
By the way,
when are you going to buy us a meal?
You said you'd treat us big
after your daughter's wedding.
Don't tell me that you're done
after the rice cakes you got us.
Gosh, no.
Now that we're here,
why don't you buy us a meal now?
We just had a bath,
so we're very hungry now.
- Ok Boon.
(Korean beef and rib course,
65 dollars)
The Korean beef tastes really good.
It melts in my mouth.
The portions are too small though.
Shall we order two more servings?
Can we?
Hey, why do you even ask?
She has sons-in-law who are
a doctor and a municipal official.
She can buy us even more.
Am I right?
Sure. Of course.
Please get us two more servings.
Ok Boon, I want some raw beef too.
- Raw beef?
- Yes.
Well...
We will have raw beef too.
You're so cool, Ok Boon.
Look. This is a big one.
I'm just eating this because of you.
I can't let you throw this away.
I know that.
Do you want another fried egg?
Okay. Wait a second.
Ga Hee, I want one.
Make it medium well-done.
Forget it.
Gosh.
Hello, it's me.
How are things going?
Is it still serious?
Well... It's not so good.
Mother must be frustrated.
Okay.
Seo Jin is staying with my friend.
Don't worry about her.
You have to come to
her art therapy session tomorrow.
You didn't forget, did you?
Of course. Why would I forget it?
You know I'm actually quite smart...
Hey, it's Mom. Mom is here.
Hurry.
Go to your room.
Mom, you're home.
Hey.
Mom, you're back.
You were out for a while.
Oh, sorry.
We were hungry,
so Joon Seon and I ate.
Where did you go, Mom?
Dad called to ask how you were.
Don't ask any questions.
Hey. I smell meat.
What meat did you eat, Mom?
I said don't ask any questions.
Don't ask if I ate meat
or a bunch of leaves.
- What is wrong with you?
- What?
I'm going to lie down.
Figure out dinner on your own.
Let Da Hee finish her meal.
Gosh, she's almost a psychic.
We can never hoodwink her.
You're right.
She hates Da Hee's guts
but still wants her to eat.
Why isn't he here yet?
He must be off work by now.
Do I really have to be there?
This is crazy.
- Mom.
- Hello?
Are you the son of
this phone's owner?
Oh, are you Gyu Jin?
Yes, it's me, Mom.
- My dear son.
- Will you stop this, Mom?
My goodness.
- Oh, dear.
- Darn you.
Put me down a little softly.
- That hurt.
- What is wrong with you?
You promised me
you wouldn't drink again!
You startled me.
I'm not deaf, you fool.
Why are you yelling at me?
How many times must you do this?
If you drink, can you
at least stop at your limit?
Mom, I'm a married man
with a family of my own.
You call me drunk
to pick you up all the time.
What daughter-in-law
would accept that?
Will you take me back
if I get divorced?
If she can't accept it,
she can call it quits.
I don't need any of you.
Mom, please.
Don't you mind me!
Since when did you
ever care about me?
Darling.
Why did you leave me all alone?
I feel so lonely, darling.
You're at it again.
Mom, why are you crying now?
- Go to bed, okay?
- No.
You be quiet!
Don't give orders. I hate you!
I'll do what I want!
- Darling.
- What mom...
kicks her son? Mom?
Where are you going?
That's not your bed.
Mom, that's not your bedcover.
What are you doing?
Where are you lying down?
Get out from under there.
Hush.
I feel sleepy. I'm going to sleep.
You won't leave, will you, Gyu Jin?
I have to go.
I might get killed because of you.
Don't go, Gyu Jin.
Mom doesn't want to be alone.
Her insides will hurt
in the morning.
(Yongju Traditional Market)
- Good job. See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
So what? Is your youngest
still stuck in her room?
Her husband hasn't called yet?
I don't think
they'll get back together.
I thought she was the mildest...
and least trouble of the four.
She must feel terrible
after causing this mess.
Hey. Don't feel too bad.
They say raising kids
is the hardest thing in life.
Not even a king
can control his kids.
Drink up.
You need to slow down.
You could pass out real quick.
Hey, Chi Su.
Do you know what's
the worst part of raising kids?
How dare you ask that
to a widowed man with no kids?
So, what is the worst part?
When your kids are hurting.
That's when you feel the worst.
Kids cause you lots of pain.
It's so painful.
My goodness. Hey.
You really startled me.
What are you doing there?
Weren't you in bed?
Why?
Why not come home in the morning?
Or not come home at all.
What happened was...
Yes, I get that you're angry, but...
I wanted to come over
right after work.
- But...
- But what?
Were you abducted or something?
Do you know how miserable I felt,
sitting alone in the waiting room?
I didn't mean for that to happen.
I was leaving when Mom called and...
It's your mom again?
Someone else called me
on Mom's phone.
She was so drunk...
So what?
What show did she put on
to call you over?
What? A show?
Did you call it a show?
Yes, I did. It's not the first time
she put on a show like that.
"I'm in pain."
"I'm too drunk to move."
"I can't hail a taxi."
"I'm locked out of the house."
She calls you over
for so many reasons.
What is all that if not a show?
Yes. My mom is
obsessed with her kids.
It's true she is eccentric,
I admit that.
But how can you say that
your mother-in-law puts on a show?
That's just fact. Am I wrong?
No. You're right.
You always state the correct facts.
You always focus on the facts.
Do you know how sickening that is?
"Is this woman really my wife?"
"Does she even
consider my mom family?"
Then do something
to make me feel we're a family.
We always suffer
because of your mom.
No, don't say that we suffer.
You're the one who suffers.
You're the only one
who has an issue with this.
What do you mean?
Are you saying...
I keep trying
when you're not interested?
Do you think I'm doing this
because I'm besotted with you?
I'll hit rock bottom
if I don't even do this.
I'm fighting to at least
do something.
Don't you get that?
Do you even want to
maintain this marriage?
Na Hee. Must we do this
to maintain our marriage?
At the cost of forcing
and embarrassing each other?
That's how desperate I am.
You're not as desperate as me.
Don't be silly.
If you were that desperate,
you'd have listened to me
and not worked too hard.
Do you think doing this
will erase the past?
- What?
- What did I tell you?
I told you to skip the conference
and rest or you could miscarry.
But what did you say?
"I never come in second in my life.
I won't give up on the conference."
It was you who gave up on our baby!
No, I mean...
What I was trying to say was...
So,
you resented me all along.
No.
Is that why you avoided me?
No, Na Hee, listen to me.
I get it.
I'm sorry.
I forced you not even knowing that.
Please, Na Hee. Na Hee.
You idiot. How could you say that
then and there?
Da Hee, are you sleeping?
I know you're not asleep.
Fine.
I'll talk to myself.
You just listen.
One day,
your mom told me that...
out of all four kids she bore,
Na Hee scares her the most.
You know your sister has
a crazy temper.
She talks back to her own parents
if she's displeased with something.
She's such a nasty brat.
But you know, Da Hee,
even more so than
Na Hee's temper,
you scare me the most, Da Hee.
All your life,
you were sweet and obedient.
But there were times...
when you'd become the most
stubborn person on earth.
Every single time though,
I'd learn that
you had a good enough reason.
That was the case when you...
wanted to switch schools
in middle school...
and when you...
insisted on working part-time...
during your senior year
in high school.
That's right.
I'm sure you have
a good reason this time too.
I'm sure of it.
Still,
know this though.
It will pass.
Once time passes,
what seemed serious
will turn out not to be.
It's true.
Life is a marathon.
You know,
sometimes you cry,
sometimes you laugh.
So what if you have
to shed tears this time?
You have your mom and dad...
and also your siblings.
You have so many people
in your corner.
Dad!
It's all right. It's okay, Da Hee.
Look at the facial features
of our baby.
You must take after your dad.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's not big enough
to have facial features.
Well, they're visible to me.
Shouldn't we tell my mom
and your parents though?
I will once I get back
from this seminar.
Na Hee,
shouldn't you go to sleep?
It's past 1 a.m.
Go to sleep without me.
I need to wrap this up first.
This is why I told you
not to attend this seminar.
Mi Jin said you should be careful...
since you have
a thin uterine lining.
She's only trying to scare me.
You know what she's like.
Still.
Honey,
I need to wrap this up quickly.
If you want to help,
go to sleep first.
Don't take too long.
Blood.
That's odd.
I stopped all the bleeding.
Did you get hurt anywhere else?
You're the one who's bleeding.
Na Hee, what's wrong?
Hurry. Call an ambulance. Na Hee!
(Episode 4)
Gosh.
Yes, Mom.
Gyu Jin, I called to get an earful.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I was only going to drink
some from my own bottle.
But you know how I am.
- I can't help myself...
- And you still drank?
Mom, you shouldn't
have taken the first sip.
Why is that?
Did your wife say something?
Did you argue because of me?
No, of course not.
- Did you have breakfast?
- Yes.
I see you made bean sprout soup.
It wasn't well-seasoned though.
I found it bland.
You're unbelievable, Mom.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Doctor!
My gosh, Yoon Hoo.
It's good to see you.
What's this?
Look at how well your arm is.
Are you all good now?
- Yes.
- Me too!
Si Yoon, yes, of course.
Why don't I take you
on a plane ride?
Guys,
we'll meet again
when you're even better.
- All right.
- Good.
Bye, Si Yoon.
- Bye.
Bye, guys.
Bye!
Tteokbokki, again?
We'll go once we finish this.
Let's go then...
Let me check my schedule first.
We were once like that too.
We were happy to just be together
and so in love.
The good days.
Let's sit here.
I can't. Dr. Jung just called.
I need to go.
I have something to give you.
Ta-da!
You said you were exhausted...
because you couldn't get
much sleep in the past few days.
But you also said
that sugar gives you energy.
Gyu Jin, I'm touched.
What if other people see us?
Are you sure we can be this bold?
I'd like them to see us...
so that we can get caught.
Why? Am I too sexy?
Having trouble staying away?
Wait, someone saw us!
What? Gosh, you startled me.
I nearly had a heart attack!
You have no idea how shocked I was.
The light,
the heat, the ticklish sensations...
I wonder where they all went.
Hit the big drum
Tap on the small drum
Play the xylophone
Nice!
Seo Jin, would you like
to try the guitar this time?
Na Hee.
Hi, Hyun Gyung.
Oh, you must be here
for Seo Jin's play therapy.
Yes, her dad is
playing with her today.
I came out here
to get something to drink.
I see.
Could I perhaps buy you that drink?
Sorry?
Mother must be going crazy.
Because of Da Hee, I mean.
Right.
My mom just has
terrible luck with her kids.
I wasn't referring to
you and Joon Seon,
so please don't get the wrong idea.
We did hurt her in many ways.
That much is true.
I bet it's hard
teaching kids to write essays.
It's not easy going
from house to house either.
You have no idea.
When I have back to back classes,
I barely have time
to go to the bathroom let alone eat.
My stomach is never at ease
and my bladder is suffering.
This is a surprise though.
You're not the type
to play hooky like this.
You caught me off guard.
Is that so?
Hyun Gyung,
could I ask you something?
Of course,
there was a reason behind this.
Go ahead and ask.
Why did you...
divorce my brother?
Was it because he lost the house?
I guess that made me
pull the trigger,
but...
I guess I was unhappy.
You know how sweet your brother is.
While we were dating,
that was what I loved about him.
After marriage though,
that also became
what I didn't like about him.
He would lend his friends money
and guarantee others' debts.
That was hard enough,
but then he'd often
come home injured.
He had major surgery
after Seo Young was born,
and I couldn't stop worrying.
I lost my parents
at such an early age...
and I didn't want to lose
someone else close to me.
Do you know what I loved the most
after getting divorced?
I didn't have to hate him anymore.
That feeling was the best.
Why did you suddenly
ask me that though?
The person you called
is unavailable.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
- Extra fees...
- Got it.
Sure thing.
I'll see you later tonight, Yeo Jin.
Young Hoon!
Goodness. What's going on?
You have no idea
how shocked I was...
to see Da Hee come home.
It was as if I saw a ghost
and I couldn't believe my eyes.
I've been shaking like a tree.
Didn't Da Hee tell you?
She won't say why.
All she said is that
you two decided to call it quits.
What kind of parent...
would be able to accept this?
You know?
I see.
Of course.
Marriage isn't easy.
There are many things to
worry about and it's exhausting.
I hear that...
many couples fight
on their honeymoons...
due to all the pent-up stress.
Still,
you should try to
talk it out between you.
This is just wrong.
An annulment is out of the question.
Mother.
Yes, of course.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry for talking too much.
You go ahead.
Please don't try too hard.
We're just not compatible
in many ways.
All marriages
get off to a rocky start.
You're supposed
to build marriages too.
I know that Da Hee is indecisive
and foolishly kind.
She even frustrates me too,
you know.
She's quite stubborn too.
Yes, she is.
Don't I know it.
She's tactless too.
She seemed awkward around my mother,
so I took her home
so that they can bond.
But...
Unbelievable.
Instead of trying
to get along with my mom,
she spent the entire day
washing the dishes in the kitchen.
You have no idea
how frustrating it was.
Right.
Gosh, really?
Also, let's be honest here.
You know she lacks in many ways.
She didn't even graduate
from a decent school.
I was going to
let all of that slide,
but she wouldn't swallow her pride.
She could at least
try to learn a decent skill...
or try to be more charming
as a woman.
Are you going to the restroom?
No, I'm going home,
you punk.
You little brat.
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
What? She lacks in many ways?
What does she lack?
There aren't many women
who are as sweet as my Da Hee.
Also,
how dare you take
my precious daughter home...
and make her wash dishes
before she's even married?
I didn't make her. She...
Shut it.
Forget it.
Now that I think about it,
my Da Hee...
is too precious...
to let you have her.
You can beg all you want.
I won't give her to you.
Never!
You, uncross your legs.
How dare you cross your legs
in front of your elders?
Is it a civil service exam
you passed?
So what if you did?
You're a snobby brat
who doesn't respect people.
Who does she think she is?
This is unbelievable.
Just leave it.
I'll do it once I'm done.
Forget it. Mom would
probably end up doing it...
and she's already upset
because of me.
Gosh. Trying to be
Daughter of the Year now?
That's rich considering
what you did.
What did I tell you?
I said you'd get caught.
Stay for all your classes.
Your mom is probably home.
All right. Got it, Seo Young. Bye.
You startled me.
I thought you were Mom.
Are you all right, Da Hee?
Mom seems to be less angry now.
And so what if you're out here.
It's not like you did
something terribly wrong.
It's all right.
Mom, you're here.
Da Hee just got out of her room.
She says it just feels too stuffy.
Who told you to do the dishes?
Why are you doing this?
Do you think we have
no one else to do the dishes?
Mom.
From this time forth,
never do the dishes, okay?
What was that?
Why did she take it out
on the dishes?
I don't know.
She's different than usual.
Hello, it's me.
Thank you for attending
the wedding ceremony.
But can you tell me
your account number?
No. I'd like to give
your gift money back.
My daughter is getting an annulment.
It just happened.
No, it's not a divorce.
Just an annulment.
Sure. They didn't
register the marriage.
They didn't even go on a honeymoon,
so it's not a divorce.
Right.
I said it's an annulment.
Why do you keep calling it divorce?
Yes.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Do you want to eat out tonight?
(Na Hee)
I'll stop by at my parents'
after work.
Yes.
Can I get treatment now?
I didn't make an appointment though.
Hey, Jae Seok.
When did you come back?
Gyu Jin!
You should've called home
as soon as you got back.
You didn't even tell us
that you're back.
And what's this about
staying at a hotel?
This is why Mom is upset with you.
You know that?
I do. That's why I didn't call her.
I went to Turkey to avoid Mom,
but she kept calling me.
What if she finds out that I'm back?
You know I'm always
at odds with Mom.
I need to be prepared
before I reunite with her.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why did you come back then?
You should've just settled down
and lived there.
I was going to,
but I just couldn't live
in a foreign country for life.
I can't eat pork there.
The day I returned,
I had pork belly
and soju with a friend.
It felt like paradise.
You oddball.
So what's your plan?
I should work.
I signed a contract today.
I'll start working right away.
I guess you found a job
before you came back.
Where is it?
Is it a university hospital?
No, it's your hospital.
Hey.
How could you decide it
without telling me?
Gyu Jin. It will be fun, right?
You, your wife, and I.
The three of us will work together.
Well...
I'm a big fan of your wife.
She's smart and clumsy
at the same time.
She's so funny.
She hasn't changed, has she?
I don't know. Did she not change?
It feels like she did.
Am I the one who has changed?
Mom, I'm here.
What's all this?
I bet she's not
in the mood for cooking.
Is she in her room?
Hey. Don't go in there.
She passed out
after making 200 phone calls.
"Hey, it's not a divorce.
It's an annulment."
She said that thousands of times.
It still rings in my ears.
"Divorce, annulment."
What about Da Hee?
Da Hee, what are you doing alone?
It's chilly out here.
You're drinking without snacks.
Na Hee brought
your favorite trotters.
Let's eat.
What are you doing?
Are you making rice
at this late hour?
I'm making sikhye.
Da Hee likes sikhye.
Ga Hee told me.
Good. I'm glad
that you wrapped things up.
We can't get our way
even with our own lives.
There's nothing we can do
about our children.
Our children aren't any better
or worse than others.
It just happened
because we weren't lucky.
We just have to get through it.
Okay?
Da Hee,
don't beat yourself up too much.
Mom will get over it soon.
I guess it will be a week at most.
I agree. She's used to things
like this because of us.
I'm sure this is
no big deal for her.
It's not that you divorced after
losing your house like Joon Seon.
And you didn't come back home
with a child like I did.
She's right. An annulment?
You're no match for us.
It's no big deal.
I know.
Are you guys trying to console her?
Joon Seon, Ga Hee, and Na Hee.
- Yes?
- Yes. Go ahead.
Actually, Young Hoon has
been seeing someone else.
A girl from the training institute.
- What?
Just sit down.
Are you saying Cha Young Hoon
has been two-timing you?
Yes.
- That jerk...
He said he broke up with her,
but I don't think so.
The girl did seem smart though.
To be honest,
I couldn't understand a word...
his colleagues were saying.
It made me feel sad.
But what's worse is...
that Young Hoon didn't
marry me for love.
His mom said he should marry
a slightly dimwitted woman.
That's why.
- Because I'm too nice.
- What?
That crazy idiot.
I'm going to kill him.
Stop it.
How could I stay calm?
Above all things,
I just can't forgive...
a guy who cheats on his woman.
I will make him
lose his social standing.
Of course.
We should never let this slide.
The three of us should take
revenge on him.
We should go
tear his two-timing legs apart.
How could you say such a thing?
She's right. That's disgusting.
How would you tear his legs apart?
That sounds terrible.
No, even that isn't
good enough for me.
How could he look down on you...
just because he is well educated?
It's okay.
I think I'm better off this way.
To be honest, I wasn't sure
Young Hoon was the right guy.
I just married him for
his background like a snob.
I think I'm getting another chance.
You're right.
This is better for you.
Sure. You could do better.
Of course.
But there is one thing I do regret.
I should've slapped him
in the face when we broke up.
Other than that, everything's fine.
I will just focus on my work now.
I'll become a full-time employee
for sure.
Good. You will. Good for you.
Hey, we're always on your side.
Am I right?
Sure.
Are you?
Forget it. It sounds so lame.
You always spoil the mood like that.
You're condescending as always.
My point. Na Hee is smart,
but she's quite condescending.
I know.
My gosh.
- Gosh.
- What are you?
- Hey.
- Why...
Da Hee.
Come here. Eat this.
Let's drink together.
Okay.
- Cheers.
Did you spill it?
The door is open.
I'm here to settle things.
Don't live like that.
And you should never get married
and just die alone.
How dare you do that to my sister?
I'll tear your legs apart.
Well...
What was that?
I heard you two-timed
between my sister and another girl.
Gosh. Well... It's just...
Is that a yes or a no?
So you punched me back.
I should've taken off the ring.
It hurts so bad.
You know, I was going to
tear your legs apart, but I won't.
- Do you get it?
- Yes.
- Behave yourself.
- Okay.
Aren't you getting off?
I'm leaving.
Gosh, are they gangsters or what?
Why do they all
want to tear my legs apart?
(You scumbag)
What?
What's this?
What happened to my new car?
(I'll rip your
two-timing legs apart!)
What's this?
No. No!
No!
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
Ok Boon. Ok Boon.
- Hi.
- Ok Boon.
What on earth happened?
We had no idea what had happened...
and made you buy us
expensive Korean beef.
I feel terrible.
I can treat friends to a meal.
You must be so upset.
Even we feel terrible.
Exactly.
Why not take a few days off?
Why are you coming to work?
No, no, I'm fine.
An annulment is no big deal.
How is that not a big deal?
It's impossible to sell
a chipped plate.
This is just unbelievable.
Should we find a good shaman
and do an exorcism?
Maybe we should.
When I look at you,
I'm even more positive that
it was best I had no kids.
Divorce doesn't run in the blood,
so why did
three of your kids split up?
Kids are such a pain.
Two got divorced
but one is an annulment!
Darn it.
Where are you going?
Aren't you going to work?
She seemed angry.
Did we just pour gas
onto a burning fire?
It's not like I made things up.
It's all true.
Getting divorced is a big deal,
but splitting up on the day
of the wedding is rare too.
- It is, right?
- Yes.
Whose marriage was annulled?
Was her youngest daughter's
marriage annulled?
My goodness. I don't believe it.
Poor Ok Boon.
So what if her husband is alive?
Her kids are cursed.
She's a bit too greedy
for her own sake.
She had four kids thinking
they'd all be good to her.
The poor woman.
She must be writhing in turmoil.
Four!
Really? What time did she leave?
Okay, then. Bye.
Ok Boon left saying
she's going to work.
Really? When?
A little over an hour ago,
they think.
That's enough time
to make 10 round trips.
Where did she get to?
- I don't know.
- What a nuisance.
- The receiver cannot...
- She's not picking up.
Oh, dear. No, it can't be.
Young Dal.
You don't think Ok Boon got
any terrible ideas, do you?
There you go again.
You're going way too far.
It's not that. I mustn't be that.
Oh, dear, Young Dal.
I can't live without my sister.
Will you please calm down, Ok Ja?
Don't you know your sister
is not that kind of person?
Don't be silly.
(8 dollars 60 cents, Seoul Taxi)
What's this?
It looks like she took a taxi.
A taxi?
Did she go to the Han River?
(Electronic Civil Service)
(Divorce by Mutual Consent)
Do you know what I loved the most
after getting divorced?
I didn't have to hate him anymore.
That feeling was the best.
(Madam Jang Ok Boon)
Hi, Mom.
By the hospital?
Slow down, Mom.
It's like a fire is
burning inside me.
What is it now?
You said you ended it well.
I didn't end it well at all.
Of course, it's a good thing
she broke up with that jerk.
It's more than a good thing.
But why is it always me?
Why is it always my kids?
Do I ask for a lot?
I just want you to live
ordinary and simple lives.
Is that so much to ask for?
- Mom.
- My gosh.
You don't know.
I'd rather something happen to me.
My kids splitting up...
It's so upsetting and pitiful.
I get all sorts of ideas.
Did I raise you poorly?
Were your dad and I poor examples?
Mom, that's not it. Never, ever.
It's not just me.
I can't bear to face
people in the market.
If they speak like that to my face,
what do you think they're saying
behind my back?
This will last at least a month.
Should I go on a trip somewhere?
Will you send me abroad?
Shall I?
Shall we go somewhere together?
No, I can't take you.
What about Gyu Jin?
- Listen, Mom.
- Na Hee.
You are my only hope now.
You must live happily, okay?
I'm a married woman
and there's not much to being happy.
Bear with
and accommodate each other.
Then you grow on each other.
Don't you betray me.
Show me that you're happy.
If something were to happen to you,
I'll bite my tongue and kill myself.
That won't happen, would it?
- Guess.
- Wait.
Are you usually like this?
You should've noticed in 20 minutes.
I did notice.
When you're not with me,
you still laugh and joke.
Hey, hi.
Where are you? Still at work?
In the parking lot.
- I'm going home.
- Are you?
Then instead of going home,
shall we meet there?
The bakery we often went to.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
The traffic was terrible.
You wanted bread?
You could've told me to get some.
Do you want something?
You like the bread here.
Not today.
I had spaghetti for lunch
and I can still taste the grease.
Can you?
I was at work today
and guess who I met?
I was in my office...
Let's get divorced.
What?
Let's get a divorce.
But under one condition.
(Once Again)
Fine, let's get a divorce!
We'll get a divorce. Happy now?
Look at that.
What a fine day to get a divorce.
Ok Boon!
It sounds like the title of a movie.
"2 Divorces and 1 Annulment".
That annoying cow!
There's only a position
for one of you.
This is your last chance,
so show me what you can do.
I have something to tell you.