ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 4
Gi-beom.
-Where's Hwang Deuk-gu?
-He got away.
What?
The police car.
-The police car?
-Yes.
The police aren't on our side, either.
Some of them are helping Argos.
-Gi-beom.
-Kang Gi-beom.
Gi-beom, it's him.
Are you a defect as well?
Did you find the police car
that took Hwang Deuk-gu?
Not yet.
We should've followed
Gi-beom's decision, then.
You should have killed him back then.
Mi-na.
Don't let your emotions get in the way.
I didn't let it.
I'm being loyal to our cause.
You brought us here because we are loyal.
Don't lose focus.
We must bring down Argos.
Not just Hwang Deuk-gu.
Why did you shut down Gi-beom eyes?
Once he's out of control,
he's just a subject we must subdue.
You're not dealing with a robot here.
The situations we were inserted in
were always uncontrollable.
Does it mean we must crumble
and let those bastards get away?
-I'm sure you already knew it.
-I'm angry.
Because we lost Hwang?
Or because you pity Gi-beom?
If it's neither,
is this insubordination against me?
Because of those bastards,
the pain we
must face infuriates me.
-What is it?
-We failed to track him down.
The police said that no police officers
went on a patrol to that area.
Do you want to blame me, too?
No. The responsibility of a failed
operation and an insubordinate member
falls upon the team leader, myself.
Is that all you want to say?
I only follow orders.
Making decisions for the team
isn't my job.
It's just that
shutting down his artificial eyes
was a punishment enough for his actions.
I'm sure Gi-beom
reflected on his actions, too.
It's been long enough, too.
Please let him out.
We tried to get the best subjects,
but this is all they amount to.
It's a waste to just throw them away.
Can't we recycle them?
If I stop their brain activities,
I can delay necrosis.
You risked your life
for a promise of a better future.
I bet you don't want to die yet.
You ought to
go out with a bang.
Your memory of the pain
will disappear soon.
Don't worry.
When will you take care
of those moles in the police?
We'll scare them away
if we're not careful.
Wait until the time is right.
I'm being treated
like an incompetent chief.
Do you even care about that?
One cannot attain glory without suffering.
In many circumstances,
if we don't kill, we will be killed.
Grant my team
a license to kill.
You strongly argued
that you could keep your team, Rugal,
under control in such situations.
I still stand by it. I just want
to raise the degree of our defense.
As they are turning more vicious,
we need a sure way to shut them down.
Just make do what you can do.
This may be a covert operation,
but this is still a national project.
I'd like to get official permission.
Guarantee us legal immunity.
I will
try again to persuade him.
You're pretty good.
What's this?
Having a chat may be too much for you.
Are you talking to me?
One hundred percent.
What is happening?
Gi-beom, you're free to come out--
What's wrong with him?
-Hey, are you all right?
-Yes.
I'm fine, but I can't seem to move.
There's nothing wrong with the program.
I didn't detect any errors
with his artificial eyes, either.
Was there anything unusual
or uncomfortable?
I don't know.
I saw something for a split second,
and it disappeared again.
That's odd.
Things were weird
when the streaming was turned off.
Is it just a simple malfunction?
I'll reset it for now.
I can't live my life in anxiety.
Can you inspect this more thoroughly?
Observing you makes us more anxious.
Looking at your vitals,
your heart is beating slightly faster.
Any other unusual changes?
So far, it's still in the normal range.
Let's run a physical checkup first.
Look.
The maximum rate of oxygen consumption
went up by 170 percent.
No way.
A significant portion of that
is an innate quality.
It won't go up that easily.
Is he back to his original condition?
Yes, for now.
Shutting his eyes down was a risky move.
You should have been more careful
when executing that.
Explain to me.
How was he able
to stop streaming on his own?
That kind of process doesn't exist.
Is that so?
Then, I need you to examine
the error more thoroughly.
We must find out
if it was a bug in the algorithm
or if it was an improvement of
the artificial eyes that resembled a bug.
Okay. I will look into it.
Look at his muscles.
They are improving as he exercises.
I don't believe this.
You're perfectly competent.
You have the guts to make bold decisions
and have incredible physical attributes.
You're like a double-edged sword.
You're a threat
to the foundation of Rugal.
This is your second strike.
I apologize.
But I don't think I was wrong.
I did take an extreme measure,
but I don't plan on giving you my excuses.
To tell you the truth,
it's very hard for me to conceal my anger.
We have a lot of responsibilities,
but we don't have the rights.
All of the injustices originate
from this imbalance.
If we show them our accomplishments,
we may be able to balance this.
Then, I will earn privileges for Rugal.
Since you've recovered, you no longer
have to stay in the solitary cell.
Sir.
Don't trust me.
Keep me under your control.
Are you aware of
what that entails for you?
But in exchange,
grant me freedom
within the realm of your control.
Freedom?
Freedom to build teamwork.
-What are you doing?
-Damn it. Come on!
It's really nice to see you.
Are you playing with food?
You said you like your food neat.
Was that for me?
I appreciate the thought.
I've been eating all the meals
given to me. I'm stuffed.
Mi-na and Tae-woong gave me food.
Eat.
You must eat to survive.
They were tempting the agent
who went on a hunger strike.
Darn it.
Why would I do that? I'd starve.
It's bad for my health.
-What?
-This is good, though.
Are you feeling better? How are your eyes?
-You're out.
-But still, I prepared this for you.
One at a time. Can you take turns?
Besides,
I can't believe you got me snacks.
Hey, I was the first one
to ask you a question.
I'm fine. I'm good.
Anyway, I want to treat you to a meal
for all the trouble I caused.
-Full-course meal.
-A killer meal.
Come on. You should hang with us.
You're spoiling the mood.
See you out front.
He likes free food, I guess.
Let's do this.
-Rock-paper-scissors.
Here I go.
Wow. Nice shot.
Damn it. That was a mistake.
Number nine.
-Tae-woong, the pink ball.
-Be quiet.
Raise it at a 45-degree angle.
-What was that?
-You need more than
just your strength to play pool. You know?
-My gosh.
-You need techniques.
Don't be so angry.
Try again. I'll give you one more chance.
When will that stop? We need to play, too.
Nice!
Come on. Try to lighten up.
I can't play when you scare me like that.
We don't have time to go out and eat.
Let's order Chinese.
No, I'll buy you a nice meal.
It's almost over. Let's go out.
Don't you dare move an inch.
What are you doing? That's cheating.
The ball...
Unbelievable.
Is she your golden goose?
Or does she have ambitions?
Why? Does she remind you of your old self?
I don't care who I used to be.
Why don't we talk about the kind of person
I will be in the future?
I take that you can't really communicate
with Hwang Deuk-gu?
We worked very well
like a well-oiled machine.
If you want to reminisce about your past
and run an entertainment company
with girls like her,
I won't stop you.
Why did you go after Bong Man-cheol?
That wasn't me.
You'll get swept away with that attitude.
Choi Yong is crazy about money.
He'll take it out on someone.
Will you be the victim
or set someone up for the fall?
I'm dying to find out
what you will choose.
Have you heard anything
about someone named Gu Won-bong?
Gu Won-bong?
All I did was follow this beautiful voice.
Seeing a beautiful sight is a bonus.
You should have told me
that you were coming.
We haven't opened yet.
You're too generous with your compliment.
No. I didn't mean her.
I meant the two of you.
Everyone is at each other's throat.
It's so nice to see you getting along
like a family.
I wonder if Chairman Ko can see
this romantic sight from the other side.
If you're that concerned about him,
you should go visit him and report back.
You're right.
He must have a lot of questions for us.
Don't you agree?
You must be busy setting up
your new business.
There will be a good show
in a couple of days.
Come and enjoy yourself.
A show?
Discuss your new business
while watching the show. It might help.
You seem to have
a lot of interest in me.
This is nothing for my family.
That sounds fun.
I'll make sure I stop by.
By the way, why did you all take my side?
Come on.
I wouldn't call that taking your side.
I wasn't taking your side.
I would have done the same thing.
If we were together, we could've caught
Hwang Deuk-gu or anyone that may be.
"Together"?
We banded together based on
our loneliness and tragedies.
I don't want to be part of it
on a deep level like that.
But it was nice to hang out with people.
It's been a long while.
Until when do you think
our mission will continue?
Until we completely destroy
those bastards, Argos.
Will that day come?
When that day comes,
we won't be
needed, right?
Then,
we exist to disappear in the end.
My goodness, stop with your sob story.
We didn't even start yet.
What are you talking about?
Listen. Before this gets too depressing,
let do everyone a favor.
Everyone, tell me your wish.
I'll make it come true.
-A wish?
-Why? You don't want to?
In that case, I'll pass Mi-na.
Gwang-cheol.
I want...
Don't think. Tell me one now.
-Three, two--
-A cell phone?
You have a cell phone.
YOUR RESERVATION IS COMPLETE
"Jazz night"? What is this?
-"Jazz night"?
-Yes.
What's that?
A jazz show? Did we all get the tickets?
Hold on.
It doesn't exist.
It means the ticket wasn't purchased
on proper channels.
This message is from Chief Choi.
-It's a mission.
-Darn it.
Gi-beom.
My wish is that
you come with me to this mission.
Sure. Let's do that.
Cheers to our mission.
-Cheers.
Excuse me!
This.
I'd appreciate it
if you can open the door for me, too.
You seem to be having a great time.
Come on. I need to de-stress too.
Even if those bastards show up,
we have to lay low.
Chief Choi is right though.
He wants to find out the scope
of their reach and raid them in one blow.
Don't they have team dinners?
It'd be amazing if they all got together.
I want to run into that bastard,
Hwang Deuk-gu.
I'm going to knock him out and whack him.
Thank goodness I let him go in one piece.
Now, you have a chance too.
Are you saying you went easy on him?
Of course. If I wanted to,
I could've whacked him right off the bat.
Is that so?
I have to say, he put up a good fight.
He didn't chicken out.
That makes me want to run into him
even more.
By the way, doesn't this place
look like a neutral zone of some sort?
I heard Seol Min-jun is different
from other Argos members because
he's a showbiz management specialist.
Really? That's a little disappointing.
Gosh, I wonder if Gwang-cheol
will bring some prey home.
SEOL MIN-JUN AGE 43
OWNS A JAZZ BAR
That's Seol Min-jun.
Calling Tae-woong, over.
Calling team leader Han Tae-woong, over.
What is it?
Tae-woong,
are you just going to leave me here alone?
The other two are there with you.
-Jazz isn't my thing.
-And that place isn't fit for me.
Someone might remember me.
Tae-woong,
I think this place is totally safe.
Let's just have some fun today.
-I'm busy at the moment.
-Come hang out with me...
You don't need to worry.
Just do what you were told to do.
Report everything to me.
Yes, sir.
You have a nice voice.
Is this like your side job?
Yes, I help out occasionally
when they're busy.
I'm quite busy at the moment myself.
Can I ask you a favor?
Pardon?
It's nothing hard.
There's a briefcase
in the front passenger seat of my car.
Can you go bring it?
That's all?
There's something sensitive inside,
so don't open it.
Okay.
Mr. Seol.
-We'll take care of this.
-Hey.
Hands off.
Dal-ho, this is our turf.
I don't want to cause trouble.
You rude jerk.
Hey, does "not causing trouble"
make a problem go away?
-We'll just take this briefcase.
-Don't even touch that briefcase.
If you do,
I'll make you regret it big-time.
Hey!
-Do you need a hand again?
-Run!
-Guys, get them!
-What the hell?
Hey!
Mr. Bong, what brings you here?
There was that misunderstanding
because of my guys.
Also, I haven't given you my answer
as to whose side I will take.
I'm headed to Mr. Seol's show,
so I don't have time for this.
Then when will you have some time?
I'm not sure.
I'll have to think about whether
I'll summon you or visit you myself.
It won't be easy
even if we bend over backward.
Obviously. I mean, look at her living
at Chairman Ko's house even after he died.
What the hell are you doing?
Shouldn't you have better manners
as someone who owns a jazz bar?
Knock before coming in.
What the hell are you trying to do
at my place of business?
Hey, Seol Min-jun.
Do you think no one's above you
now that you run this swanky business?
Go do your work.
And it is your job to make
ugly things look nice.
It was so hard
to improve Argos' public image
to what it is now.
Don't turn something little
into a big problem.
You look like you're about to beat me up.
Why are you standing there?
Go sort out the mess.
Thank you.
We'll be back
after the intermission.
Oh, hello.
-What the hell?
-Gosh!
-Gi-beom.
-Wait outside, Mi-na.
-I'll go with you.
-I'll figure out
the situation and call you.
Make sure everyone evacuates.
Okay.
This way, please.
We're closing up due to
-an unexpected disturbance.
-This way.
-Hurry!
-Please follow the security guards
-and leave immediately.
-Shit!
We will be contacting you individually
regarding your ticket refund.
This way.
-What's going on?
-Argos got attacked.
What? By who?
They were strange.
Gi-beom is still inside.
Please help him out.
Okay.
By the way, where's Gwang-cheol?
I thought he was with you.
Gwang-cheol. Lee Gwang-cheol.
Answer me.
Gwang-cheol.
Freeze them and grind them up!
If we can't get out,
will we die?
Don't say things like that.
I'll call people who can help us.
Damn it.
Hey, you three. Stop.
What the hell?
What's wrong with these guys?
Who are you guys?
I asked you a question,
so you should answer it.
Jeez, I guess talking is useless.
Come at me, then.
Oh, wait.
I'll come.
Tae-woong, how long can he last
without the batteries?
Go start the car.
I'll bring Gi-beom.
Okay.
What was that about? My gosh.
-I have no idea.
-That was crazy.
Let's just get out of here.
Hey, who booked this bar for our show?
Some weirdos showed up and...
-Damn it.
-Hey, get him!
No idea. I nearly died.
I was terrified, so I ran out of there.
Can you come and--
What the hell? Who are you guys?
Gosh, who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Just come with us.
Gosh.
Do not tell anyone about what happened
and what you saw today.
Okay.
And about me as well.
Okay, of course.
Did you guys kidnap Gu Won-bong?
Who the hell are you?
What are you curious about?
What the hell are you trying to do?
You seem very curious, and I just wish
that you had asked me directly.
Be gentle, will you?
We need them in good condition.
I'm the chairwoman of Argos. Step aside.
It's too dangerous now.
You should get out of here.
I must find out who caused this commotion.
Take me there.
Please open it.
To tell you the truth,
I've always been fond of you
since we first met.
There are two kinds of people for me.
Enemy and prey.
Most people get eaten up
of their own accord.
But from time to time,
I meet stubborn fools who rebel.
That totally excites me.
When that happens,
I have dreams every day.
"How should I smother them?
How should I rip them to pieces?"
It's so exciting.
Just admit that you were afraid of me!
Don't cut me off.
You kept
doubting me and vying for
the opportunity to beat me.
I was totally waiting for you
to start a war.
But instead of launching a frontal attack,
you decided to join hands with Choi Ye-won
and hide behind her.
You don't even know
what Choi Ye-won is capable of.
Now, we're talking.
Give me something useful,
and I'll spare your life.
You psycho.
You traitor.
Bravo!
You get better at stuff like this
every time I see you.
What?
Look.
I spent a lot of money to get that photo
from the National Police Agency's server.
They certainly hid it
very well.
Ye-won.
I'll explain everything.
This is...
Don't you dare call my name.
I wondered why you were fishing
for information about Gu Won-bong.
I finished Ko Yong-deok nice and clean
with a gun.
For you, I should use something classy.
This would be good.
Right?
Do you want to play it?
-Enough.
-Let go.
Revenge
is for those who have something to avenge.
We can't kill him.
I need him for something.
What will you do?
Just trust me.
As always,
I promise you it'll be fun.
Hey, you guys don't even feel pain?
What the hell did they do to you?
Actually, this is good.
There's something
I've always wanted to test.
Activate physical manual control.
Manual control error.
They use people
and discard them like this?
These crazy bastards.
Kang Gi-beom.
Hwang Deuk-gu?
Gi-beom.
These bastards are seriously crazy.
What's going on?
Oh, boy. There are many of them.
This will take a while.
You have to grant me a wish.
Here? All of a sudden?
-Yes.
-What is it?
-I'll handle them alone.
-What?
I don't have time
to worry about going easy on them.
Okay.
You can't take this back and say
this doesn't count as a wish.
You piece of...
Let's go.
Gwang-cheol is gone.
-We lost connections with Gwang-cheol.
-Maybe his battery died.
You said Gwang-cheol's brainwaves
are connected to the drone.
That's right.
I'll try to locate his last GPS signal.
Take the highway. After 1.4km,
take the second exit.
Okay, got it.
I believed that it'd find me one day.
What people call an opportunity.
I was so close
to finally singing on stage.
I know I could've done well.
It must've been a dream of yours
to become a vocalist.
Yes.
Did you also have a dream?
I think I did,
but it probably died alongside my body.
Then I'll let go of mine too
since I'm going to die anyway.
They say it's easier if you let go,
but that's a lie.
Do you know why?
It's because you never can.
You're only fooling yourself.
I want to live.
I don't want to die.
Not like this.
This is close to
where his signal last pinged.
Wait.
Has it been activated?
Gwang-cheol?
Mi-na, open the window.
Sure.
Good. Now follow it.
Got it.
What are you doing?
No...
No!
Get rid of him too.
Is she really dead?
Mi-na, she might live
if she's rushed to the hospital.
Call an ambulance.
We must save her. We must!
She must live!
Carry him.
Gwang-cheol.
It gets chilly in the evening,
so I was warming up your seat.
Just take it from me
if you want it that badly.
I know how people like you are.
You think you can take it
at any given time.
You're enjoying this.
Not really.
As if.
I can take it from you whenever I want to.
Who desires something they already have?
If it's not what you desire,
then at least assist me
so that I can fully take control.
Not until you prove that you can
bear the weight of the crown.
I feel like I won't wake up
if I close my eyes this time.
Cut the crap and
focus on receiving your surgery well.
How did you cope with it?
Even though I only exchanged
a few words with her,
she'll be embedded
in my memories for a while.
There's nothing we can't do
once we put our minds to it.
Just hang in there, all right?
Please watch over me
until my surgery is over.
Sure.
I'll make sure to keep an eye on you,
so don't worry.
Have you ever contacted Seol Min-jun?
You see,
I sometimes come across information
that I wasn't searching for.
Not even you
can have access
to all sensitive information.
It was my mistake this time
due to urgency.
What's your relationship with him?
He's one of mine who's deep undercover.
I see.
It didn't seem like
a power struggle within the organization.
Could his cover be blown?
I haven't been able
to reach him since yesterday.
Let me look into it.
I'd appreciate it
if we kept this between us.
Sure thing.
Did Hwang Deuk-gu send you?
I knew it.
He was there.
Choi Ye-won.
HWANG DEUK-GU, SEOL MIN-JUN, CHOI YE-WON
Would you like to converse?
What is this?
Please be clear with your order.
Activate him.
Why don't we forget
about our failed projects
and move on to phase two?
The prototype is almost ready.
Install everything you have in him.
There are a few more things I need.
Which are?
I need a subject that I can
collect data from.
Well,
I have just the right person for that.
We'll finally meet again.
Find everything about Hwang Deuk-gu.
HWANG DEUK-GU AGE 51
ARGOS VICE-PRESIDENT
I'm coming for you
in my own way.
Subtitle translation by Won-hyang Son
They probably hid everything here.
This is a message.
-Choose your side.
-Eyes cannot lie.
What is it that you want?
How many have they killed?
He has been playing with me all along.
We don't have much time to enjoy.
-Why are you doing all this for?
-He is trying to freeze us.
You can take me, or you can save them.