RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Let's take photos.
Someday, we'll consider them as assets.
Is that a wedding gift?
You rarely kiss me like that.
Don't be ridiculous.
I kiss you all the time.
No, you don't.
-Around 11 p.m., a police officer...
-Killed his wife...
-Stabbed his eyes...
-An unprecedented case...
As an officer sworn
to protect the public...
This case is a disgrace to the police...
The suspect
is a highly decorated officer...
And solved many high-profile cases.
Meanwhile, his risky methods
were reprimanded numerous times.
Both eyes were stabbed
with a sharp instrument.
He has a severe ocular penetrating injury.
Vitals. BP 138 over 92,
heart rate at 92, massive bleeding.
ETA, five minutes.
I'm here at the entrance
of National Police Hospital.
The suspect of this grotesque crime
was found at the scene alive
and is being transported here.
The public is raising concern
over the crimes
committed by members of the police force
and is criticizing
for bringing the suspect to the NPH
since it could seem
like a cover-up is in motion.
Even though his prints and blood
at the scene
point to him as the perpetrator,
word has it that
the suspect is denying all charges.
NATIONAL POLICE HOSPITAL
EXAMINATION ROOM 1
Let go of me!
We combed the scene
as you wished us to do,
but none of the evidence
points to your wife being killed by Argos.
The same goes for your eyes.
So dead, I'll be a lunatic.
And alive, I'll be a murderer?
-Kang Gi-beom--
-This isn't the first time
the organization has fucked
with the police.
Don't identify your case
with that of the police force.
The criminal organization
deals in murders, kidnappings,
tax evasion, assault and battery,
bribery, and embezzlement!
There are over ten cases against them.
If we had been able
to show our evidence in court
and had our witnesses
properly stand trial,
Ko Yong-deok would've
at least gotten 20 years.
But what happened to those witnesses
and the officers protecting them?
TWO MONTHS AGO
-Hello?
-How are things?
I thought I'd be finally
taking all the credit,
but you just had to follow me out.
Gi-beom, we can protect the witnesses
by ourselves just fine.
Also, working overtime
on your wedding anniversary
will only lead to a war back at home.
It's not like I'm trying
to slack off or anything.
You made a big mistake
if you volunteered alone today
just so that I could be with my wife.
Stop thinking of her as a caught fish
because you'll regret it.
What did you just say?
It's almost time for court.
Get the witnesses ready.
Sure thing.
Just don't let word get out
that I keep bothering my seniors.
I'm hanging up.
What's wrong?
Officer Kim, behind you. Officer Kim!
Be quiet.
I...
You see,
I need to talk to them.
So keep it down.
Fuck.
The police are the ones giving us hassle,
but we come out looking like the bad guys.
Please don't kill me.
My daughter just celebrated
her first birthday.
Please...
Damn it.
You're all be behind bars
one way or another!
Goodness.
So we have a feisty one.
How though?
You don't have any evidence
and your only witness is dead.
Also, the trial should've already begun.
WITNESS
PROSECUTOR
Prosecutor,
did you have confirmation
of your witness attending court today?
Yes, I had confirmation but...
Killing us won't keep you out of court.
How's that?
Many in Argos
are ready to testify against you.
Rats like Officer Kim here?
He sure does love his kids.
But he doesn't seem to care about
other people's kids.
Officer Kim!
Assistant Inspector Mun?
Assistant Inspector Mun...
No...
-Clean this up.
-Yes, sir.
You bastard!
Let go of me! Let go!
I'll kill you all!
Let go!
Move! Get out of the way.
Clean it up.
Yes, sir.
POLICE MEMORIAL PARK
MAY THE FALLEN REST IN PEACE
SONG MI-NA
Due to recurring gun-related cases
and unsolved kidnapping
and missing persons' cases,
I feel responsible as it is my duty
to protect the welfare of our people.
It is why I am stepping down
as Commissioner-General.
How does it feel
to be exonerated from all charges?
I'm glad that the truth
has finally been revealed.
It's true that there were some setbacks,
but I will put that behind me
and move forward.
What's your opinion on the police claims
regarding the disappearance
of key witnesses?
It all sounds like a lousy exit plan.
Even the Commissioner-General
stepped down.
I guess we'll see who has the last laugh.
I have one more question.
Is it true you're considering
running for the Assembly?
Did you predict today's outcome in court?
-I'd like an answer.
-This way.
-Are you running?
-When will you address the rumors?
-Please say a few words.
-Any words?
MAY THE FALLEN REST IN PEACE
SONG MI-NA
Be happy.
-Thank you.
-The pleasure was mine.
-Congratulations, Mr. Park.
-Hello.
I'm glad the court ruled in your favor.
I only have you to thank.
Only good things will follow,
so don't worry too much.
Thank you.
There's a rumor about you
running for the Assembly.
Is this true?
Assemblyman Park is here
and he's the man of the hour.
Excuse me.
ASSEMBLYMAN PARK NO-SIK'S
BOOK LAUNCHING EVENT
Excuse me for crashing the party.
Carry on though.
Is someone running for Assembly?
How does this make any sense?
Someone who secretly beats people to death
is begging for their votes now?
What the fuck is this?
Disgusting, that's what it is.
-You...
-Admit to your crimes
or at least give us back their bodies,
you bastard.
-Bastard!
-Sir, are you all right?
Who the hell is he?
Step aside.
Get out of the way--
And who the hell are you?
Don't just stand there. Get rid of him.
Damn it.
EAST BUILDING
COP ASSAULTS ARGOS'S CHAIRMAN
A detective on the case assaults
an innocent man
in front of all those reporters?
It's nothing compared
to what those bastards do.
That attitude of yours
dragged our reputation in the mud.
You are to catch the criminal,
not become one.
-Whose side are you people on?
-What?
You're still only speaking
on their behalf.
What about our fallen officers?
Innocent until proven guilty.
Argos is one of Korea's
most honest companies.
An honest company?
The whole world knows that the enterprise
was formed by The Red Ants.
How much did the police help
to clean their names?
Inspector Kang,
watch what you're saying.
Don't you know what this hearing is for?
This is bullshit.
Wait, hold on.
Could I perhaps still buy some flowers?
-Sure. Come in.
-Thank you.
FLOWERS
-Yes, honey?
-Where are you?
1ST ANNIVERSARY GI-BEOM AND JIN
I'm really sorry.
I'm at the flower shop
picking up your favorite.
I know I'm running late,
but we should still celebrate.
Just hurry home. I miss you terribly.
Yes, ma'am, will do.
-Excuse me. Could I take this?
-Yes?
That?
-And this.
-Okay.
Also...
-I'll take every bouquet in here.
-Sure thing.
Why did she leave the door open?
Jin?
Jin!
Can you hear me?
Jin, get up.
Jin...
Because of you, your wife had to suffer.
You picked the wrong person to mess with.
Who are you bastards?
Who are you?
You rarely kiss me like that.
Give me a kiss back.
Who are you bastards?
You bastards...
I could look at you all day.
-Wait. What was that?
-I love you.
-Is this a hoax?
-Hey.
Hold him still.
Make it above your head.
I can't lift my arms right now.
-You lost too much weight.
-Hold him still!
I should get you some food.
I starved for two days
to fit into this dress.
I should've died that day.
Being alive is a disgrace.
Once you're imprisoned after the trial,
many will come for your life.
We can't let you just die like that.
What are you saying?
Consider this as a gift.
-What's this?
-I wish you
the best of luck.
Wait.
Hold on.
Enter!
At a week from today at 1 p.m.,
wait by the wall
at the north side of the yard.
Don't do anything too conspicuous.
No one will think that of me
since I'm blind.
And don't stand in such a stiff mannerism.
So you have eyes on me?
Does this look natural enough for you?
Can you introduce yourself
before you give orders?
Whether you follow my orders or not
is up to you.
That's bold.
Starting today, you will train
how to take even strides.
How so? Why should I trust you?
If you'd rather get beaten up,
then so be it.
What a thirsty man needs
is water, not words.
If you can see me, don't just watch and--
What is this?
A rope?
Tie the string around your ankles
and practice until you feel comfortable.
Imagine that you're doing
a three-legged race.
Once I think you're ready,
I'll let you receive ambulatory care.
SIX MONTHS LATER
BRIGHT LIFESTYLE
We have an injured inmate.
He needs ambulatory care.
RESTRICTED AREA
Who are you?
A doctor.
Gi-beom, escape.
Who are you?
Kang Gi-beom!
KANG, K BEOM
Hey, you're not supposed to come out.
I have to go to the toilet.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, but could you let me loose?
-It's that way. Be quick.
-Yes, sir.
Stop there.
Turn right and go straight.
You'll find the stairway
to the emergency exit.
STAIRWAY
One.
Two.
Three.
The floor.
You have no time. Stop crying and get up.
It's the real deal from now on.
You must not make any mistakes.
Just tell me where to go.
Hey!
Shit.
Take six steps forward
and seven steps to your right.
There's an ATM machine to your right.
Turn to your left.
Take 19 steps forward.
There's an automatic door to your right.
Walk through the door.
Take five steps, and you'll be outside.
Turn to your right and run!
Damn it.
An inmate has run away. He's blind.
You can't run far.
You're dead meat.
There's a change of plans.
I'll switch to plan B.
We need to get him out of there
at all costs.
Yes, sir.
You're the only one
who has survived for this long
after screwing us over.
It's a shame I can't see you.
But it's nice to meet you.
Don't, Gi-beom. Just run!
Stop right there!
Stop. Run to your left.
If you get caught right now,
you won't be able to escape again.
I won't get caught.
He has no eyes.
I'm grateful that you're keeping me safe,
but you can't just ask me to perform
a secret operation.
You're still here
despite everything you've gone through,
so it can't be helped.
He won't be receiving the surgery,
will he?
If he wants, then sure.
Artificial eye surgery is still dangerous.
It's practically an act of suicide.
I promise to find
the abducted hospital staff members.
Even if the surgery is a success,
I'm not sure what kinds of side effects--
Despite losing both of his eyes,
there are people
who still want to kill him.
He needs this.
Gi-beom, are you awake?
Mr. Earphone?
That's me.
Great job escaping.
I haven't introduced myself.
I'm Police Chief Commissioner
Choi Geun-cheol.
Mr. Choi.
Where am I?
This is K Hospital.
The medical staff disappeared
into thin air,
and the hospital shut down.
I'm sure they're still alive
since they're useful.
Perhaps.
However, you're different.
As long as you're a target,
Argos will continue to look for you.
I'm sure you've come up
with some measures.
Of course.
After all, I'm the one who decided
not to clear your name
regarding the murder.
-What?
-Had you not been incarcerated,
you would've died several times already.
I take pride in saying that
this was the best way to protect you.
I may be lying down like this,
but you'll need to be honest with me.
Why did you ruin my entire life
without my consent?
To give your eyes back.
I'll be able to see again?
Yes, if the surgery is a success.
And you'll have to become my agent.
And then?
Bring down Argos.
Isn't that what we all desire?
Will I truly be able to see again?
If you accept my offer,
you'll be declared dead
at 9 p.m. tonight.
And then, you'll be born again.
Where do we begin?
I know you can't see,
but let me introduce the staff.
This is Susan who's in charge
of bio parts.
She studied medicine, but she's excellent
at programming as well.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
And this is Bradley.
He's a mechanic.
I have nothing else to say
but that he's a genius.
That's true.
Thank you for doing this.
We've been through
countless trials and errors.
As a result, we've created
much advanced artificial eyes.
And you're our first test subject.
Could you address me as something else
other than "test subject"?
You'll become a cutting-edge,
integrated AI
that can be weaponized as well.
In other words,
you'll become a human weapon.
Human weapon?
That's not bad.
Let's begin.
This hurts so much.
Is anyone there?
Gi-beom, you need to relax.
-Hello, sir.
We need to kill him at all costs.
Thanks to your men's incompetence,
he got away twice.
Once from his house
and once from the penitentiary.
I want solid proof.
My men picked this up
from the place where he was found dead.
-Did you see it?
-Sorry?
What do you mean?
Did you see his body with your own eyes?
I...
I didn't.
But he was declared dead
at 9 p.m. that night.
-Are you sure?
-I'm positive.
Excuse us, sir.
Where's Hwang Deuk-gu?
The future of our organization
is taking place here.
So where the hell is he?
I'm here.
I'm not late either.
Do you think the rest of them
have nothing to do?
Bring me some wine.
I don't have much of an appetite.
This baby is excellent.
This is to celebrate your entering
into the political world.
You always need to stand out, don't you?
I was scared of him
and felt reluctant
about going into politics.
I can't believe
the most powerful individual
is afraid of something.
That can't be.
Hierarchy exists for a reason.
I'm afraid that loutish son of a bitch
might cause trouble.
Reputation is everything in politics.
Everything I do is for you.
All right.
Listen up.
There's legislation, jurisdiction,
and administration.
On top of them, I'm going to place Argos.
From now on, I'm going to define
what's good or bad
and what's filthy or clean.
That is right. You are truly amazing.
You have to take control over Argos
for as long as possible.
We don't need no successor.
He's right.
We will always have a place for you.
In two weeks,
Ye-won and I will get married.
A remarried politician is better
than a divorced one.
It looks hopeful. Don't you think so?
Of course.
Everything I do is for you.
You know that, right?
Jin.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry, Gi-beom.
There's no point in crying.
It's already too late.
Jin.
Gi-beom.
Are you okay?
Get rid of that knife.
I don't want to see it.
I really can see.
Hey, do you work here?
You opened your eyes.
Do you know me?
We're on the same team.
What do you mean?
I'm in charge of Gi-beom.
Watch out.
It's been a while.
Mi-na.
Is it really you?
You thought I died, right?
Is it truly you?
Or am I suffering from aftereffects
of the surgery?
No, you're not.
I even went to your funeral.
Chief Choi saved me that day.
I still go by the same name,
but my identity is completely different.
I'm relieved.
I'm truly happy that you're still alive.
Do you really think so?
What?
I remember his blood-curdling voice
every single day.
But that day,
I didn't get to see his face.
Even when my colleagues
were getting killed,
I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't do anything either,
so this is where I've ended up.
You couldn't do anything?
You're right.
We were like that.
But how about now?
Are you still in pain
every time you think of Jin?
Do you still feel the horror
of when your eyes were gauged out?
It's tough.
But I need to pull through.
I want to see you prove it.
Whether it's truly a relief
that you're still alive
or if it would've been better
had you just died.
Prove it.
Oh, God. Please give us some water.
Please give us some water.
Please!
Just once!
-We're sorry!
-Just once.
-How long have they been starving?
-Please.
-Water, please.
-It's been about a week.
Please give us some water.
Go on.
-We're thirsty.
-Please give us some water.
-It's mine!
-Give it to me!
Give it to me!
Which one of you
is Director Gu Won-bong of K Hospital?
It's me.
It's me, sir.
Please spare me. Please.
Today,
I wore my favorite suit.
Do you know what this means?
Let's not have
any bloodshed today, all right?
Yes, sir.
All right, then.
Let's talk about business.
How dare you sit down?
You won't have any problems
looking for investigation data.
All of this data
will be stored in my eyes?
Not only the official reports,
but original copies and security data
will be stored as well.
That's not bad.
Sure. Seeing gruesome clips
all the time is just wonderful.
What?
Oh, did you hear me? I'm sorry.
I'll begin the uploading.
Okay.
He doesn't have a strong stomach.
No.
Why do these errors keep happening?
It's because you remember
the anger and pain.
Do something. It's making me sick.
You could erase some parts of his memory.
They're visual data,
so I can't erase them permanently.
Hurry up!
I'll stop uploading for now.
PSYCHOPATHIC DETECTIVE MURDERS HIS WIFE
I won't allow it.
Let me catch Jin's murderers myself.
As long as you're part of Rugal,
you need to work as a team.
You know why I want to do this.
Let's say the true culprit's identity
is revealed.
What will happen to me
who risked everything
in order to get you out?
They'll be caught anyway.
You need to adapt first.
You'll eventually cross paths with them.
You still can't see properly.
Don't act rashly.
Focus on your training.
Excuse me.
Let me ask you something.
Sure, go on.
Whom do I need to beat
in order to be acknowledged around here?
Probably Han Tae-woong, our team leader.
Why do you ask?
Han Tae-woong?
-Han Tae-woong.
-Hey, hey.
There's one hurdle you must overcome
before that.
What is it?
Let's spar
like the old days.
Like the old days?
Bring it on.
You still got it.
All right, then.
I'll raise the difficulty level.
Get rid of that knife.
Get rid of it.
So this is your weakness.
As your colleague,
I can't turn a blind eye to your distress.
This is your first and final warning.
Your training will be tough,
and we're running out of time.
We have no time to tend
to a spoiled newbie!
So wake up, you asshole.
This blow training will help you
take blows better.
Let me down first.
Don't be absurd.
Getting hit will help you
throw punches better.
What?
Then at least, don't use the word "blow"--
Why does it hurt so much?
These gloves have improved power.
-Get up right now.
-What is it this time?
Your wounds shouldn't get infected.
It'll help your immune system.
Are you giving me the carrot and stick?
God, you startled me.
I didn't know you were there.
Hold on.
I think we've met before.
Haven't we?
You'll be coming here often.
It's a crucial place for those
who have artificial parts.
You too?
Where?
He's not even looking at me.
Maybe it was because you used to be
part of an elite police,
you held out well.
I heard you'll be combating
with our team leader tomorrow.
Right?
Remember.
If you act emotionally,
you'll lose much more than you expected.
But then again,
it may sound ridiculous to someone
who's already lost everything.
You have a stunning body.
It's an inverted triangle.
Judging by the vibe I'm getting,
this must be a death match.
Gi-beom won't succumb to anyone.
He won't stop until he wins.
But still, I can't imagine
our team leader losing.
Me neither.
I think there's a problem.
Don't try to beat him by strength.
I'm not patronizing you.
His arm is his weapon.
You had warned me not to act emotionally.
That's right.
But I disagree.
There's one thing I learned
during my years in the police.
In order to catch the bad guys,
I need to be far more vicious than them.
You'll have to be
extremely vicious to beat me.
It's all over once he grabs me.
If I can't beat him by strength,
I'll damage him little by little.
I got you.
You don't know
how to properly use
your newly-acquired power.
You fail to understand
your opponent's capabilities
or use the space around you.
Train properly before challenging me.
Hey.
Come here.
I'm not done yet.
Jin.
You assholes.
I can see well now.
Subtitle translation by Soo-ji Kim
A disturbance?
I won't lose again. Never. In any fight.
The truck with the cash has been stolen.
The guy who pointed a gun at me
is already dead.
The devil we have been chasing
is someone else.
I killed your wife with a knife.
There are two kinds of people for me.
Enemy and prey.
They are the ones who killed Jin.
How was I supposed to just let him go?
Would you look at that.
I have something that I need to finish.