ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
What happened?
He blew himself up.
-Shall we move him to the HQ?
-No, they might be tracking him.
-Let's take him to K Hospital.
-Okay.
Where's Dr. Oh's number?
It's a transcranial
direct-current stimulation device.
-What is that?
-The method is called "brain doping."
An electric current
is sent through the brain
to abnormally stimulate
the bodily functions.
How dangerous is it?
Planting this inside someone's brain
is crazy enough.
A high-voltage current
was sent through this.
It's enough to blow up most people's
brains, except for rare cases.
-Hello.
-Hey, Bradley.
-Take a look at this.
-Okay.
It can be turned on and off remotely.
There's a pressure sensor, which means
he was able to control the voltage.
By pressing this spot right here
like this.
People have disappeared,
and so have the evidence.
Maybe the reason for kidnapping
is something worse
than destroying everything.
But don't worry too much.
It's clumsily made.
It is?
We're looking at a failure right here.
He would've died anyway
even if his brain hadn't blown up.
What do you mean?
The planting procedure itself must've
damaged his central nervous system.
I'm sure he experienced severe pain
and even paralysis.
-So this is a failed attempt?
-The technology was ruled out
during Rugal's early days
because of such adverse effects.
Perhaps, this is
connected to the kidnapping
of Director Gu.
I should go express
my sincere condolences.
EPISODE 3
You made a wise decision, Director Gu.
We can be pretty rough,
but we care.
Once we accept someone into the family,
we stay loyal forever.
I trust that you'll keep your promise.
I don't have time for this.
Just tell me what you need.
It used to be supported
by the government. It'll cost a lot--
I have too much money,
so don't worry. What else?
I need healthy experimental bodies.
A lot of them.
That will be a piece of cake for me.
I'll get you men and women
from all countries.
I'll keep them coming
like meat hanging in a butcher shop.
Do a good job.
ARGOS' MAIN BOSSES
Unless they're idiots,
there must be a reason why they are
interested in this technology.
Argos committing crimes
with that kind of goal?
That's unheard of.
It's not groundless speculation.
The victims of a number of unsolved
kidnapping cases were former athletes.
They're likely to be physically superior
to ordinary people.
Kim Dae-sik was a rising marathon star
back in school.
Everything will be answered
once we find out who "he" is.
Agreed.
However, we'll wrap it up here
and wait for further instructions.
Sir.
I gave you plenty of chances
to make up for your mistake.
-When can we expect further instructions?
-Not sure.
Rugal is a national agency
with a strict command structure.
We'll wait to find out who's responsible
and what the outcome is.
An internal feud will break out
inside Argos.
The widow, Choi Ye-won,
who took over Ko Yong-deok's position.
And the mid-bosses
who are after the throne.
Their internal feud will be
a golden opportunity for us.
Let's just watch
how they fight amongst themselves.
Is this because of me?
Are we reducing our action radius
due to the risk of exposure?
Don't overreact.
Even if that was the case,
we only got you out
because we can handle this much.
I'll assign each of you to a mid-boss.
Find out what they're up to.
Gi-beom, you'll just support the others
for the time being.
I have a special task for you.
The security screening at Argos'
main buildings are on par with airports.
Look.
There are times
when you can't be a machine.
This is just a temporary solution.
You can be back in three hours, right?
Of course.
Shall we make some popcorn later?
Watching people fight is so entertaining.
Do you not have a brain or what?
Think, will you?
Then what about nachos and hot dogs?
You should go with him.
Yes, I will.
What? Are you avoiding me?
Yes.
Okay.
Why did I get it on my nail?
It can trick metal detectors
while also capturing images.
This is so cool.
Gwang-cheol, can I also...
This is really cool.
Hey.
Oh, right. Tae-woong. I have a question.
I've been wanting to ask you this.
Fire away.
Everyone knows my story.
What's your story?
Why did you leave Argos?
I guess you think
we're friends or something
just because we had a meal together.
Just focus on your task.
If you make another mistake,
I'll teach you a lesson.
Please continue to help us out.
-Well done.
-Thank you.
Let's go.
Get back to work.
Sly and crude. It's obviously Argos.
You're an exception, of course.
You've turned over a new leaf.
I didn't say anything.
My stomach still gets upset
whenever I come to places like this.
Did you and Gi-beom
cross paths in the past?
You cut him off
when he asked you about your past earlier.
He arrested me.
That's like a movie.
Enemies meet again as allies.
Isn't that your story?
You know it's a secret.
If Mi-na finds out
that you were arrested for petty crimes,
are you going to be okay?
Of course not. I certainly won't be okay.
She'll make my life hell.
Tae-woong.
You see, that's actually her charm.
What? Giving you a hard time?
She's tough. She's dependable.
They're all leaving.
Did you get the money's location?
Of course.
RESTRICTED AREA
-Let's begin.
-Okay.
Name, Choi Yong.
He's in charge of construction projects.
He's one of the founding members
of The Red Ants.
He used to bribe politicians like crazy
with Ko Yong-deok.
Who's this guy that has
a strategic alliance with Choi Yong?
Name, Bong Man-cheol.
He used to be a loan shark in Myeong-dong.
When Argos became a corporation,
he was in charge of money laundering.
He used to be known as the Money Expert.
He solidified his position in
the financial institutions,
but he still misses his loan shark days.
He owns
multiple private lending businesses.
And the members of the gang
transport all the cash themselves.
-So how will we get in?
-That...
Get through that checkpoint,
and you're halfway there.
TRUSTWORTHY LOANS FOR EVERYONE
It's been delivered safe and sound.
BONG MAN-CHEOL AGE 58
ARGOS MOPIN CREDIT BANK CEO
Delivery complete.
I will wait at a nearby rooftop.
CHOI YE-WON AGE 32
CURRENT CHAIRWOMAN OF ARGOS
Mr. Bong is inside, right?
Please come with me.
If you show up announced
at a sensitive time like this,
it'll only cause misunderstandings.
Is that a bad thing?
Right.
You are little kids getting hurt
in a big kids' fight.
I know it'll be a nuisance,
but we'll have to check.
SIDE DISH
My gosh, Ms. Choi.
It's nice to hear from you.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
We're supposed to meet today,
but there are so many roadblocks
between us.
We're still not on good terms,
so I didn't think you meant it.
You're actually here?
We'll be total strangers soon
at this rate.
Will you be okay with that?
We don't share a single drop of blood.
So technically, we are strangers.
Mr. Bong Man-cheol.
Choose your side wisely.
Hey, tell her nicely
whose turf she's on now.
I won't see you off.
I'm busy, so let's get this done quickly.
What are you looking at? Get lost.
Go!
Thank you.
I'd like to repay you for helping me.
I must look like a mess now.
Well, just a little.
ARGOS
Call me, and we'll exchange names.
I heard you try not to go out
after sundown.
You can usually get everything done
during the day.
If you can't,
that means you're incompetent.
What is it that you want to say?
The tens of billions of won
Assemblyman Park was trying to embezzle.
What's your thought on that?
From what I've heard, we still don't know
who's responsible for it.
We don't know where the money is.
Isn't that a bigger problem?
It's not my money. Why should I care?
I'm sure you need a reliable handler
whom you can trust.
The cops, who have caught the whiff
of cash, are keeping their eyes peeled.
And some in politics are saying
they no longer want to work with Argos.
I asked you if you need such help.
How could I trust a company
filled with thieves?
I'll take care of this.
-It's easier said than done.
-This is
my specialty.
Just remember this one thing.
I never use my expertise for free.
-What do you want?
-The tens of billions of won that's gone.
I want half of it.
What a lunatic.
Why don't you keep this lunatic
by your side
so that you can live without worries?
It wouldn't be a bad idea.
"I am more than capable
of taking Chairman Ko's head."
Is that what you mean?
Go take care of it, then.
Whether it's a political connection
or your life,
I will be sure to save it.
-Hello, sir.
What is this?
Gosh! You scared the crap out of me.
Hey, do you have no manners or what?
Do you now think everyone is under you?
Don't you know how to knock? Knock, knock!
The losses
from the new city development project...
How did you make up for it?
Let's hear it.
MOPIN CREDIT BANK CEO BONG MAN-CHEOL
That's none of your business, okay?
Let's keep out of each other's turfs.
Of course.
I should be more respectful of your turfs.
So why is it that you're shitting on mine?
What?
Fuck!
Damn you.
Wait...
-Shit!
-Stop!
It's like I told you.
It wasn't me. I seriously don't know
anything about this.
There was a loss,
but I never embezzled any money.
Do you know how it feels to be patronized?
-What?
-It's most fucking annoying
when what they're saying is true.
This moment never existed.
The money, this car, and even you.
I'll erase anything from that building.
I'm telling you. It wasn't me!
Sir, really. It wasn't me...
-Choi Ye-won.
-What?
She came by this afternoon.
-Choi Ye-won?
-Yes?
Ask my boys if you want.
I was only going to scare her off,
but some punk started
to beat the shit out of my boys.
They were beaten to a pulp.
Some punk?
They were in on it together.
I'm sure of it.
Right.
Finally, I'm seeing the bigger picture.
Choi Ye-won tried to take
the money for herself,
but she's blaming me
now that her plan's gone south.
Shut up.
Sir, I'm right about this. Hear me out.
This was her doing! My gosh.
Let go. Let go of me!
Fucking hell. Sir!
Choi Ye-won?
Have you not operated a dashcam before?
Why didn't you turn on the audio?
Just watch.
Still, we made them
turn against each other.
That's right. It's a small win.
And what's with the camera angle?
Enough with the attitude.
They're the ones who stepped out of view.
Why are you getting worked up?
Anyone can make mistakes.
At least get the facts straight.
I positioned the camera perfectly.
That's enough, Gi-beom.
Sure thing. Let me apologize.
Everything is my fault.
This one thing is for sure though.
We're meant to use our brains.
There's no need to
drain our physical energy.
Hey, you.
-Can zoom in?
-Sure.
HWANG DEUK-GU,
KO YONG-DEOK'S SECRETARY
The Hwang Deuk-gu I remember
was never in charge of a business himself.
However, he packs a mean punch.
It's why the picky Ko Yong-deok
let him be his secretary.
Still, it all seems too fast.
From secretary to vice-chairman?
I agree it's quite unusual.
Vice-chairman or not,
since you have become an Argos,
you will be finished.
Okay, we're good.
There.
You know,
I didn't know if I should say this
to an old man who doesn't know
how to properly operate a dashcam but...
-An old man?
-That's right. An old man.
Don't get cheeky with me
and focus on your job.
Right.
Your eyes have a few secret functions.
Ones...
that even Mr. Oh doesn't know about.
Here's one that I only I know about,
so hold onto your socks.
Wait. Is what I'm seeing
being displayed on the monitor?
Yes. Nice, right?
It's a streaming service.
We can see what
you see in real-time, old man.
-That's amazing.
-Right.
I told you not to call me that.
You seem way younger than me too,
so have some respect.
Sure.
Hold on.
-Come closer.
-Why?
Your eyes are dry, right?
It eats up a lot of resources,
but I can't allocate as much as I want.
Have you spied on me with this?
I'm not interested in men.
Have you?
I have, just once, to test it.
-When?
-Well,
the pretty lady...
What? Who?
What was her name again? Choi Ye-won?
Have you told anyone that I met her?
Don't deals begin with
sharing secret information?
-A deal?
-Yes, a deal.
So let's...
Gosh, what a grip.
Anyway, I won't tell anyone you met her
and give you more intel on her as a bonus.
Forget it.
I don't need any of it,
so tell people if you want.
Okay, fine. I'll add another.
-And what's that?
-I'll help you practice
turning the streaming feature off and on.
You said it's a feature
only you know about
so what good would it do
for me learn that?
Chief Choi knows
that a certain feature exists.
So you'll help me learn
how to control it myself?
On one condition though.
Why is everything so complicated with you?
Help me
be a secret agent.
I'm sorry about this.
Why is he laughing like that?
Activate physical manual control.
ARE YOU SURE?
Of course.
Damn it!
We'll try something different today.
-Jeez.
-Did you just let me hit you?
-Not at all.
-You can't fool me.
I saw you grin before taking the hit.
I can see your every move now.
My eyes are functioning
at a much better rate.
The more I learn about them,
the more I'm satisfied.
-Why didn't you dodge though?
-You called this a training.
Talk about a shitty feeling.
Mi-na, all you have to do
is take my side in any case.
And why is that?
Because I'll always be
on the winning side.
I won't lose again. Never.
In any fight.
So all you have to do is stay by my side.
This is some next-level bragging.
Stop fooling around
and come at me seriously.
You took the words right out of my mouth.
Seriously?
Shit.
Recognize this?
It's not my style.
How about now?
What is this?
-Why were you at Bong Man-cheol's turf?
-I wonder who told you that.
I hear
your men caused a commotion.
It's nothing to get
your panties in a twist with.
Who was the punk dressed in black?
Whoever it was,
it's none of your business.
You rather choose not to talk?
Do you really think I won't find out?
For someone who suggested a partnership,
you're being exceptionally rude.
A partnership
is built on trust and transparency.
Well, I also am curious
as to what you're thinking.
Until when will you keep coming by
as if this is your house though?
I'll come when I want
and leave when I want.
I hate you.
That I know,
but suck it up.
Remember
that our fates have been linked
by Ko Yong-deok.
Hwang Deuk-gu came by
with nerdy-looking thugs?
Really?
Who knows what he's thinking?
Ko Yong-deok was definitely easier.
Hwang Deuk-gu
is a hard man to read.
Why must I understand him though
when I can just use him to my advantage?
Watch your back.
You already know this,
but don't trust anyone.
Sure, come by whenever you want.
This is your real home after all.
-You're here.
-Hi.
BEAUTY PRODUCTION
Hwang Deuk-gu
and Choi Ye-won's partnership.
Does it make sense to you?
No.
How can we get rid of him?
It's what Ye-won wanted.
She'll signal us
when it's time to make a move
like always.
There are many suspicions
regarding Park No-sik's death.
-Who would kill a well-off assemblyman?
-I got it.
Why would they kill him?
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Why are they dropping that?
Honey, there a truck!
I think we found them.
Can you verify?
Yes, it's them.
An incredible piece of technology that is.
Can't they make a few more of those?
Even if they do,
not everyone could have them.
Gi-beom, brief us on the victims.
Name, Kwon Gi-tae. Age, 44.
Occupation, lawyer.
He recently opened an online channel
called Justice Served
and got on Argos' bad side
by digging into them.
-His wife--
-Okay, we get it. You're Superman.
Isn't that right?
Right.
I'm sure I can also
do something cool with this.
Don't be arrogant.
Someone's life is on stake.
-Dad!
-No!
-Dad...
-No...
No...
Mom...
What?
What was that?
Gi-joon...
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Gi-joon...
My gosh.
Goodness me.
Let's go.
No one goes that far just to retaliate.
Could there really be
another reason for this?
Tae-woong, do you remember anything
from your past that could help...
What I mean is...
Does anything come to mind?
I don't know.
Not really.
I don't care what the reason is
since it won't make a difference.
There will be no mercy.
None.
Shit.
I won't kill you
since there's no replacement.
It's not like we didn't try.
This is just impossible.
That's the excuse you give me
after killing countless people?
Kim Dae-sik, who was barely activated,
was also a failure.
He was only useful
as a self-detonating bomb.
That was before I came.
However, the results
came out after you came.
No human
can withstand this much reconstruction.
And I'm a man who never gives up.
If you don't want me
to stick these in you instead,
you'll make this work.
Just keep in mind that this is something
I seriously want.
I truly mean that.
Anyway, I don't want you skipping meals.
Carry on then.
The police station
and the hospital?
Are you proud of yourselves?
Are you, you fools?
Find out who did this, right now!
Clear the body
and enjoy your meal.
After obtaining what they were after,
they erased traces of any evidence.
They are imitating me.
Hurry on in.
Gwang-cheol.
Tae-woong!
You said you had other errands to run
when I asked you to join me.
Was that a lie?
Before we joined Rugal,
we weren't in a state to maintain
any personal relationships.
So, of course, we have nowhere to go
and no one to see.
It's obvious.
There's no need to explain yourself.
Right.
How did you leave the organization though?
It probably wasn't easy.
Those in the organization
killed my sister.
My freedom was at the expense of her life.
It's why
I must be live well.
Like the police.
At least
somewhere near their level.
Why the police
of all people though?
Because being like those
who are my polar opposite
is the only way to protect myself.
What about you?
Me?
A successful businessman
who was fucked over
by a blindly righteous tattletale.
That's odd since Mi-na told me
a completely different story.
Mi-na, you...
You see, I'm a big collector.
I begged Chief Choi to give it to me.
Ta-da.
I got it.
Can you activate it?
You want me to take it out?
What is it? You can't?
It might corrode when exposed to oxygen.
You're a quack, aren't you?
Bring it on. This way.
All right, you quack.
My gosh.
-We should inform Chief Choi.
-No.
-What?
-Don't you know anything about covert ops?
But still,
this is nothing trivial.
That can't be.
Kang Gi-beom.
I can't believe he's the one
who did this to me.
I don't need to hear your opinion.
You should start going outside.
Why is that?
It's his dream to kill you.
What's wrong?
-Do you not want to?
-I'm not fully recovered just yet.
What if I run into him?
If you don't want to,
then there's nothing I can do.
-Just die now.
-I'll do it!
I'll do anything you ask me to do!
I guess
you'll stay alive for a while.
Send me this signal
and keep tracking it, got it?
What?
Wait. Where are you...
Where...
Hey, Kim Dae-sik's mastermind.
-Min Dal-ho?
-Hey, Gi-beom.
Why are you here?
Weren't you looking for me?
We have a lot of things to chat about.
We just can't die, can we?
What do you think would happen
if I were to twist your neck?
Spare me.
No.
I'll kill you one day.
How frightening.
Where is he?
Why the hell do you ask?
Damn it!
What's going on? This scared me.
What is that?
Damn it.
He never told me that would happen.
Fuck.
Was the voltage too high?
Hello.
What's wrong?
It looks like you were caught
fooling around.
Me? Don't be ridiculous.
Wait.
Hold on a minute.
Wait!
I see. You weren't fooling around.
You were doing something dangerous.
What is it?
Tell him yourself.
Well...
So...
I resuscitated Kim Dae-sik's equipment.
And then,
it suddenly made this noise--
Cut to the chase.
Yes, sir. He has it.
Chief.
I can't find Gi-beom.
Turn on the streaming device.
Yes, sir.
-Goodness!
-Gosh!
Hwang Deuk-gu!
You've risen from the dead,
Kang Gi-beom.
Is there no audio?
No. We can only see what he's seeing.
He's probably wearing an earpiece.
-Turn it on.
-Yes, sir.
You're him, aren't you?
How are you alive again?
Why did you send Kim Dae-sik?
Why did you kill him?
How did you get your new eyes?
-Did you kill Assemblyman Park?
-Whom are you working with?
-Is Director Gu still alive?
-Answer me.
Who are you?
Rats like Officer Kim here?
He sure does love his kids.
But he doesn't seem to care about
other people's kids.
Gi-beom, it's him.
Sergeant Mun, Officer Kim,
and all the witnesses we were protecting
were killed in his hands.
I remember that evil voice.
It's him.
Was it you, Deuk-gu?
Did you really want to meet me?
Yes, because you're the reason
that everything happened.
You don't have to flatter me like that.
Gi-beom, we want him alive!
Gi-beom.
Gi-beom!
Chief, please send us in.
I'll catch him myself.
Rugal. All of you will go.
-Yes, sir.
Find Gi-beom first and stop him.
Sir.
Hwang Deuk-gu is our target, not Gi-beom.
Stop Gi-beom and capture Deuk-gu alive.
We need to hand him over to the police.
Why, sir?
How can we spare a scumbag
who took so many innocent lives?
I won't let your recklessness
ruin everything we've worked up toward.
Do as I command.
Yes, sir.
Capture Deuk-gu
and bring Gi-beom back.
Yes, sir.
You've become quite fast.
I wonder why.
Artificial eyes?
Or is it another body part?
That's none of your business.
First, I'll beat you to a pulp.
After that, you'll rot behind bars.
Before doing that,
have you thought about how
you'd persuade your superiors?
Everyone wants something
bigger and greater than them.
Isn't that why
you were brought back to life?
It's the same for me.
I always have a reason
for killing someone.
Thanks for your last words.
I'll kill you now.
What happened?
The screen suddenly turned off.
This is impossible.
Shut him down.
He's currently in combat.
We don't know what kind of side effects
he'll have if he gets shut down.
If he doesn't shut down right now,
he'll suffer even greater damages.
Proceed.
Hurry!
You're running out of time.
What did you say you were going to do?
Are you a defect as well?
No.
Hwang Deuk-gu.
Hwang Deuk-gu!
It'll be my turn next time.
You can look forward to it.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
Are you a defect as well?
You should have killed him back then.
I'm coming for you in my own way.
The prototype is almost ready.
Argos got attacked. They were strange.
-Gwang-cheol.
-We lost connections with Gwang-cheol.
How long can he last
without the batteries?
Find everything about Hwang Deuk-gu.
I'm not trying to catch you.
It's someone who's crazy about blood.