RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Where is she?
Tell me the truth. Where is Yeo-jin?
You can't, right?
Because you faked it all.
Is that what you wish to believe?
Then tell me that I'm wrong, you bastard!
Where's Yeo-jin?
All that you have believed in
will start to crumble.
Even you
can turn into someone like me now.
Tell me where she is,
or I'll rip you apart.
This isn't the best place to talk, is it?
Why don't we go find an open space
that is nice and sunny?
You psycho...
I will tell you where Kim Yeo-jin is.
But you'll have to get me out
if you want to know where she is.
You have until tomorrow morning.
Do not get help from anybody.
You'll do it, right?
Then how can I know that she will be okay
until then?
I told you,
I checked with my own two eyes.
On my way here, I felt so bad
leaving your wife all alone there.
You're a valuable asset to us.
We should've treated you with respect.
Hey.
-Take good care of her.
-Yes, sir.
Can we talk?
Specifically
about Kang Gi-beom.
It'll be fun.
Even all the backstories you didn't know.
You'll hear it all.
I told you that you'll go insane.
I wanted to be the one telling you
that Kim Yeo-jin is alive.
That's why I ran to this police station.
Do you know how excited I was
while waiting for you?
Tell me everything.
Where are you hiding Yeo-jin?
Do you still think we are different?
Just answer my question, you bastard!
Harder! Punch me harder!
Kill me
and save the world.
Except for your woman.
What? You can't do that?
Then give up on the world, Kang Gi-beom!
Get me out of here and go save your woman.
Is it that difficult?
What has the world even done for you?
Have you already forgotten everything
it put you through?
Open your eyes, Kang Gi-beom.
Face the truth!
It does seem suspicious,
but I found no evidence
to prove that she's alive.
I tried my best as well,
but found nothing at all.
Whether we find evidence or not,
the problem is that Hwang Deuk-gu
is destroying Gi-beom.
Continuing to chase the traps
that bastard set up
will only lead to more confusion.
Tae-woong,
is there anything else we can do?
How about we do some digging
on the dark web?
I heard those IP addresses
aren't traceable.
This is Bradley's idea.
Even on the dark web, money is exchanged
when people sell and buy stuff.
Tracing bank accounts?
Yes, I heard they use cryptocurrency.
What about it?
It means the cryptocurrency accounts
are 100 percent real,
because they need to receive money.
Analyzing and tracing
cryptocurrency exchange details
may lead us to some clues.
If we can raid them
and catch them red-handed...
Then we'll be able to find out
whether Yeo-jin is alive or not.
IF YOU NEED TO REPORT A CRIME, DIAL 112
Please don't hurt Gi-beom.
I'm begging you. Please don't hurt him.
FAIR, FRIENDLY POLICE SERVICE
Find that place.
Please don't hurt Gi-beom.
I'm begging you.
Please don't hurt him.
Please. I'm begging you.
Please, I beg you.
Are you all right?
Hwang Deuk-gu was right.
Yeo-jin is alive.
-Hey.
-Sir.
Song Mi-na came by this morning.
She couldn't even take one day off?
-What about Hwang Deuk-gu?
-Everything's okay,
but Mi-na asked me about Gi-beom's wife.
-She did?
-She said she read the case file again
and asked who the real culprit is.
Anything else?
No, that's all she said.
You already know the rest.
But I keep getting a weird feeling,
so I thought I should tell you about it.
Okay, keep me updated.
YUYEON POLICE STATION
Why did you want to see me?
What's up?
I clearly warned you
that you should just get lost
unless you're going to work for me.
As you can see, I'm still here.
Does that answer your question?
That bastard was nowhere to be seen,
but he's in a holding cell now.
You heard, right?
Yes.
Hwang Deuk-gu, that asshole...
He won't be able to make it
through the night.
-Seriously?
-You should do something too.
What do you want?
Clean up the mess you made.
What do you mean?
Choi Ye-won.
All right.
She's been getting on my nerves anyway
because she's trying to boss me around.
All right, then. Let me pour you one.
Cheers.
Shall I go out?
Or do you guys want to come in here?
Fine, I'll go.
-Let's get this over with.
-Son of a bitch!
Why do you think I'm sparing you?
Clean up the mess.
WOMEN'S CHANGING ROOM
Gosh, you scared me.
That's what Hwang Deuk-gu said?
Yes. Frankly, even I can't tell
what's real and what's fake.
That sly bastard.
Is Gi-beom okay? I'm worried about
how this is going to affect him mentally.
Can we proceed with the idea
that Bradley came up with?
Yes, give it a shot.
You'll have to protect Gi-beom though.
Yes, sir.
Please send Mi-na and Gwang-cheol.
Okay.
Even if they started out on the dark web,
they end up using regular networks
later on as the frequency
and file sizes increase
because of the speed.
Koreans can put up with everything
but slow Internet speeds.
So you're saying the regulars eventually
migrate to messengers or e-mail, right?
Yes. We just need to trace
the information from both sides.
Then catching these perverts
will be a piece of cake.
The blacklist is done.
Now, I'll send it off to our hunters.
One more. Send!
-Who is it?
-I'm here to pick up the empty plates.
Gosh, I put them outside.
Who are you?
Do you have some time now?
What is this about?
This way, please.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
-Go bring him, please.
-Please wait inside.
I heard you turned yourself in.
Is it true?
I won't ask you to get me out,
so just leave.
Do you think I came here to hear that?
Are you afraid Choi Yong might kill you
while I'm locked up?
Why are you doing this?
You won't understand even if I tell you.
Are you running away from Choi Yong?
Or, from me?
The holding cell next to mine is empty.
Stick around if you're curious.
This is about Argos' fate.
I don't have time for jokes.
I understand that's everything to you,
but my situation is different.
What is it that you want?
I'm waiting
for the clueless fool
to finally open his eyes
and come back to my arms.
Whatever the reason is, it looks like
you'll be locked up here for a while.
You think so?
But you see,
life is an unpredictable beast.
I haven't heard from Mi-na
and Gwang-cheol.
-Tae-woong, can I--
-Gi-beom.
What? This is awkward.
You may go do your own thing now.
This is the last time
I'm letting you do this.
Okay.
Get going.
There's nothing.
I thought we'd find
some evidence at least.
Let's hand them over to the police
and get moving.
-Where's Gi-beom?
-He left.
Are we doing the right thing?
If my sister were alive,
I'd have gone to save her at all costs.
I'm not sure if this is the right thing,
but I know that this is the only way
we can help Gi-beom.
Shouldn't we also go
and talk to Hwang Deuk-gu?
No, absolutely not. Especially you two.
I will take sole responsibility
for all misconduct.
-Tae-woong.
-This is an order.
Then what do we do now?
I'll follow Gi-beom.
You two can prepare for the next move.
Let's go.
I'm sorry, guys.
This is the only solution
I can think of now.
Who's the one
going in the other direction?
It's Gi-beom.
Sir, what time are they transferring
Hwang Deuk-gu?
Get the vehicle's location.
-Put Gi-beom on.
-Yes, sir.
I can't connect to him now.
-Kang Gi-beom is on his way there now.
Pardon?
I bet he's after Hwang Deuk-gu.
No way.
Make sure he doesn't get into a scuffle
with the police.
Yes, sir.
Hit the gas.
Bravo!
I'll fix everything.
Everything that is about to happen
from this moment on.
Pull over.
Stop!
You piece of...
Hey, what's your problem?
Shut off all the cameras.
We must pull out now.
Then we won't be able to monitor
what's going on.
This cannot get leaked.
Never.
But what about the cops
who are already at the scene?
I'll take care of that.
Just leave.
This is considered obstruction of justice.
I'll pay for it.
~Later, not now.
Where is Yeo-jin?
I turned myself in, expecting
to rot in jail for about 20 years.
Shall I go to jail or not?
You should have done things my way
if you wanted to get what you want.
Good job, Kang Gi-beom.
I did what you asked,
so tell me where she is.
Tell me, you bastard.
The smell of freedom!
Kang Gi-beom,
you're no longer the man you were now.
We'll take our time
now that we're in the same boat.
The van was nauseating.
Hwang Deuk-gu.
Hwang Deuk-gu!
Would I leave you behind
when I'm just getting started?
Tail us.
58B5986
I have no choice
but to only move forward with this.
They never appreciate
what easily falls in their laps.
Anyway, you'll be thanking me soon.
You'll risk your lives to hold me off
for just a few minutes?
Let's get this over with.
You have no right
blocking the roads like this.
You're done going rogue.
Starting now, you'll follow my orders.
Get him.
Got it.
Hello.
The boys found this
at the scene.
All right.
Now, how about that reunion?
58B5986
BUILDING 3
Yeo-jin!
Gi-beom?
Gi-beom...
Are you hurt or injured in any way?
No.
You've lost so much weight.
I look nothing like myself, do I?
No, you're the same.
You haven't changed at all.
Let's take this off though.
Gi-beom, I--
You don't need to say anything.
I know I took too long.
It'll be all right now.
RESTRICTED NUMBER
Sorry to kill the mood,
but you should back up a little.
Our deal is over.
Oh, dear.
Says who?
What the hell do you want?
Back off if you want to save her.
I'm up against a man
who can dodge bullets,
so of course I came prepared.
I wonder if that can be said
for your wife as well.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
Nothing I do is random or unplanned.
From the moment
I turned myself in to the cops,
I have been waiting for this moment.
-You son of a--
-That's enough.
Stop right there.
Step any closer
and bullets will fly into
her pretty little face.
Get out here.
Talk to me face to face.
You won't get your way here.
There's nowhere to run
and no one's here to help you.
Mi-na, there's another one
in the adjacent building.
Why don't we start
with Kang Gi-beom's right leg?
How about I tell your husband
how you've been living your life?
-What's wrong?
-No.
What?
You knew everything.
When Kang Gi-beom
was being accused of murder,
you kept quiet and said nothing.
No...
What's wrong?
I wonder how he'll react
when he finds out.
Never.
I can't let you lose everything
all over again.
What are you talking about?
To prevent all of that,
there's only one thing you can do.
I'm sorry, Gi-beom.
Yeo-jin, please calm down.
If only we hadn't met again.
If only...
I had not survived the attack.
How could you even say that?
Do you have any idea
how glad I am that you're alive?
I don't need anything anymore,
so just come with me.
I'm sorry, Gi-beom.
I love you.
Yeo-jin.
Yeo-jin...
Hold on.
Were you waiting for me?
How are you here?
I opened my eyes to find myself uncuffed.
It seemed like I got lucky,
so I came home.
Who got you out of jail?
Someone must have helped you.
The one who came back into my arms
opened the door of the police van
and uncuffed me.
Well, get back in there.
It can be a holding cell
or actual prison for all I care.
That's kind of mean of you.
Escaping police custody in broad daylight?
Because of you, Argos and I...
Don't you realize how bad this is for us?
The Choi Ye-won I know
is a skilled negotiator. Are you not?
Then at least give me the name
of your accomplice.
Wait a second. What was his name?
Kang...
Kang?
Kang Gi-beom...
Kang Gi-beom?
Anyway, don't wake me up for anything.
I want to have a good sleep tonight.
How dare you drag us into this
when all you care about is your pride?
What do you think you're doing,
Ye-won?
I'm done letting you
do whatever you please.
Isn't she...
She's Kim Yeo-jin.
She's dead.
Please take care of her
so that Gi-beom won't be shocked
when he sees her.
Okay.
Bradley, something's seriously wrong
with Gi-beom's eyes as well.
The oil in his eyes burst.
It's nothing serious, right?
Stress usually increases pressure
in the eyes.
But for the oil to seep out like this...
I truly hope
it didn't flow into his brain.
Fix him at all costs.
I will.
What were you guys doing
when Gi-beom was chasing the vehicle?
We were focused on our task,
so we weren't aware of it.
What?
So what about Kim Yeo-jin?
Did you find her or not?
Sir.
Shouldn't you be asking whether
she was alive to begin with?
Sir.
I allowed him
to go, sir.
-Why?
-I believed he could control himself.
And he did.
How could you say that
when he's lying over there?
Sir, is there something we don't know
regarding Kim Yeo-jin?
Sir, we're perplexed here.
Please tell us everything, sir.
I'm certain Argos will target
Gi-beom next.
Then we should protect him.
It'll only be a matter of time
until they get to him.
We should still buy some time--
His colleagues died.
He searched far and near.
In addition, he assaulted Ko Yong-deok.
Argos will never give up.
They will kill him, his family,
and his friends.
Are you going to just sit and watch?
Do you want to save him?
Yes.
Ms. Kim.
Detective Yang, what brings you here
at this hour?
Is Gi-beom home?
He's on his way.
This is great. I bought extra.
Come inside. Let's have dinner together.
Okay.
We need to kill them first.
Sorry?
Argos will be baffled to see them dead.
We'll attack them and leave no one alive.
We can't spare anyone.
Does that mean
we can save
both Gi-beom and his wife?
This is the only way to save them.
This will place her
in suspended animation.
If you take too long,
she will die.
You need to be thorough and quick.
If you so much as hesitate,
this plan will fall through.
Yes, sir.
What are you planning to do afterward?
I trust you,
but what if they suspect me
as the criminal?
-Perhaps, it's best to tell Gi-beom--
-No.
NAME: LEE EUN-JEONG
AGE: 32
What happened?
What happened to me?
What about my husband?
It's a long story.
But this was the only way
to save both of you.
What does he mean?
INCUMBENT POLICE OFFICER KANG GI-BEOM
MURDERER WHO KILLED HIS WIFE
Gi-beom is a murderer?
He didn't stab me--
I know.
You must be baffled.
But you must accept things
as they are for now.
I need to see him.
Please bring him here.
Not right now.
It'll only exacerbate the situation.
He won't have me by his side!
That's even worse!
Let me go! Let go!
Let go! I said, let go!
I will save him!
I give you my word.
After some time,
you will understand everything.
Gi-beom...
I heard Kang Gi-beom died while trying
to break out of prison.
If he was in his right mind,
he wouldn't have killed his wife
or gouged out his eyes.
I'm glad he died.
He probably wouldn't have made it.
It gives me chills
that he was a police officer.
I know.
They need to take strict measures
when hiring police officers.
The mentally ill should be exempted.
Choi Geun-cheol.
"Choi Geun-cheol"?
It's about time you stepped down
from the stage he fabricated.
Cut the nonsense.
Do you still think
I'm the one who killed your wife?
Who else could it be?
I told you. It was all fabricated.
He fabricated her death,
acted like he cared for you,
and pretended to be a victim.
Don't you get it? He did it.
I'm Chief Choi Geun-cheol
from the National Police Agency.
I was the one who decided
not to prove your innocence.
Argos will continue to track you down
until the end.
Here's a gift.
You're free now.
Why did you ruin my life
without my consent?
I wanted to give you a new pair of eyes
in exchange for working for me.
Simply put, you'll become a human weapon.
I have full control over you.
That includes all the information you have
as well as your thoughts.
This imbalance is the root
of all that's unjust.
If it reaps fruit,
a balance is soon to follow.
Let's put this high-tech individual
to good use.
Trust the information provided
by your eyes and your own judgment.
Sir, you were the one
who was concerned about the dangers
Gi-beom's eyes could pose.
Let's find out
how dangerous they are.
This is your opportunity
to bring me good results.
Argos. Is there another reason
other than that?
You've been listening to me well
up until now.
So why are you suddenly doubting me?
You're a crazy bastard.
I shouldn't have told you that information
so easily.
I'll give you back what's yours.
Take your time and give it some thought.
Gi-beom, what did he say about Chief Choi?
It's nothing. Let's go.
No.
Never.
I can't let you lose everything
all over again.
I'm sorry, Gi-beom.
If only we hadn't met again.
If only...
I had not survived the attack.
I love you.
You still need to rest.
Where's Yeo-jin?
Where is she?
Gi-beom, you should rest a bit more.
Gi-beom.
Gi-beom, you can see her later.
That's how
she vanished.
I had concealed her identity,
and it backfired on me.
I wasn't able to track her.
You killed her to save her.
But she ran away from you?
There was nothing you could do?
That means Gi-beom knew nothing
when he was falsely charged
and went to prison.
Are you sure
that you did all of that for me?
Of course. When I had helped you
escape from prison,
she had been under my protection.
Then why did you never tell me
that she was alive?
If everything went as planned,
we wouldn't be having this conversation.
I had no idea
whether she was alive or dead
or what she had to go through.
And yet, I was calling myself a hero
and obeying your orders.
Why didn't you tell me?
Despite having
my own family member to save,
I was fighting for Rugal
and saving people.
The past doesn't matter.
You're a part of Rugal now.
Don't forget your duties.
Don't tell me
that you were the one
who gouged out my eyes.
What are you blabbering about?
Did you stab her and gouge out my eyes
so that I'd join your team?
Answer me!
Put your gun down.
Put it down. This isn't right.
What kind of human does that?
Why did you do this to me?
This is an order. Put it down!
Why did you do that to her?
That's enough.
-Move aside.
-You can blame him for his mistakes.
But you can't blame him
for not being perfect.
He did the best he could.
Do not look down on his sincerity.
I don't understand
that "sincerity" either.
White lies
can't be considered a sincerity.
The one I need to take my revenge on
is you,
Choi Geun-cheol.
Subtitle translation by Soo-ji Kim
I'm done caring for anything anymore
and that includes Rugal.
Let's go back together.
Nothing you say now
will change our situation.
Is he really going to kill them all?
Kang Gi-beom is obedient to me these days.
Do you know why?
It's because he's discovered the truth.
Find Choi Geun-cheol.
We'll also end up used and abandoned too.
But I cannot allow insubordination.
Come back to us.
I won't let you have your way.