- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
- Is it just you and I? - Just you?
Yes. I guess you and I are doing something.
You two are a team today.
- Are we a team? - Yes.
I'll tell you once the guests are ready.
I was surprised to see today's guests on my way up here.
I'm sure he was our guest, but I didn't see his face.
- We wore the same clothes. - Really?
I was embarrassed to see that.
You might look better than him.
You'll see.
You might look better.
It was so shocking. His style...
- Gosh. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Gosh, you're here. - My goodness.
(Glancing)
Don't do that. Stop it.
(Check jackets and blue shirts)
(They are wearing the same clothes, but look totally different.)
- Please have a seat. - Please sit.
(He's a great actor and entertainer.)
(Ong Seong Wu with magnetic charm is back with his song, "Gravity.")
- Hello. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - Look who's here.
(He's a rising star of 2020, Lee Do Hyun with refreshing charm.)
(He starred in "Prison Playbook" and "Hotel del Luna.")
(He looks like a cool cartoon character.)
(Seo Ji Hun with outstanding appearance)
Hey, ZICO.
- Hello. - ZICO.
(ZICO who sang "Any Song," the biggest hit of 2020)
I have a good feeling
(He's trying to imitate ZICO.)
- ZICO, have a seat. - Please sit.
- Nice to meet you. - Hang on.
Have a seat.
- ZICO, you should sit here. - What?
- Where? - Why?
No.
- Don't do that. - What?
Kwang Soo, please.
It's worth a try.
Let me give it a try. Have a seat, ZICO.
- What are we doing today? - It's nothing.
This is crazy.
Are we a team?
You're a team with Kwang Soo as the center.
You are Team Lee Kwang Soo with outstanding appearances.
(Team Lee Kwang Soo with outstanding appearances)
This is crazy. Don't we look nice?
You will have a race with Team Jee Seok Jin of entertainers today.
You should come up with a great pose that will give you a head start...
on Team Jee Seok Jin on the special stage.
(A great pose?)
- This is crazy. - Whatever we do,
- you'll have to cover your face. - Why?
- It's supposed to be cool. - That's not the pose.
- I can do this. - Or you could turn around.
- You should look cool. - Should I cover my whole face?
- Hey. - Kwang Soo.
I'll just stand at the back.
Don't ruin it and just cover your face.
You stay out of this, baby octopus.
- I'm in trouble. - What kind of pose shall we try?
Let's just see how we look together.
You know what? This is so...
This is killing me.
Can I go to another team?
I don't think this is right.
We're wearing the same shirts.
Really? I want to go.
Get me other clothes. I'm going crazy here.
This is so embarrassing.
Do you think I should... I mean...
Is it better that I sit on one side? Gosh.
Don't we look like caregivers standing here?
We look like caregivers.
- I'm sorry. - What should I do?
You should sit somewhere else. We look like your caregivers.
Each of you should strike a pose you want at the same time.
- A pose I want? - Yes.
- Is this it? - No.
- This is good. - It looks cool.
You look cool doing this.
You look like you're about to poke someone's buttocks.
He's not like ZICO.
(Same pose, different vibes)
I look different.
- What about this one? - Good.
We all turn right.
And we stand like steps. It's like a gradation.
- We go like this. - It's a good idea.
- That's good. - And our looks get better going up.
- Okay. - It means you're the ugliest one.
- No. - Stay seated.
- Our looks get better upward. - It's not like that.
Come here. We can make it look like human evolution.
Exactly. It's something like that.
So the ameba should be here.
Ameba? Did you call me an ameba?
You should do this here.
Stay seated. You're number one.
Me...
ZICO, do you want to stand out?
(A special stage under the spring sun for Team Kwang Soo)
We have something for today. Hello.
- Hello. - What is this?
I'm sure something's going on here.
- Hello. Are we performing today? - There's something.
- Is it a puppet show? - Gosh.
- Hang on. - There are crutches in the back.
I just saw crutches.
- Did you see crutches? I did too. - Where is Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo, come on out. - Kwang Soo's in the back.
- Why is he backstage? - I see crutches here.
- Why are crutches here? - Kwang Soo is like our guest.
Kwang Soo, why are you backstage?
What's going on?
We should talk.
- I guess he's performing. - Can Kwang Soo...
walk out in a cool way?
(The black curtains open.)
- My gosh. - What's that?
What? It's ZICO and Kwang Soo.
- What's going on? - What is he doing?
(Surprised)
(What is going on?)
What?
- We have male guests. - What is going on?
- Today's guests are... - Seong Wu.
- so handsome. - Why are you...
There's Lee Do Hyun too.
- My gosh. - She's so excited.
Hey.
Why is he...
- What is he doing? - Why are you there?
- ZICO. - What is Se Chan doing here?
Se Chan and Kwang Soo, you shouldn't be there.
- What is going on? - What is Se Chan doing?
(Excited)
- We have male guests. - Seong Wu.
- Seong Wu has a really small face. - Male guests.
His face is so small.
- You guys look like... - You're loving this.
They're not even looking at us.
- Will you take a look at us? - Aren't you talking to me?
- Will you look at us? - You're not talking to us at all.
Why are you standing there?
- What are you doing there? - What are you doing, Se Chan?
(They're not convinced.)
- Come out of there! - Come out.
- You can't be there! - We're a team.
- Come here. - Let's go forward.
We're a team.
- Kwang Soo is walking. - Right.
- Really? - He's walking.
- He's wearing socks. - Hey.
- Kwang Soo. - My gosh.
(Serious)
You're not supposed to wear slippers on a TV show.
It's not a slipper. It has a heel.
- It's more like a sandal. - All right then.
I was very surprised to see today's guests.
We have good-looking guests.
I can't believe we have male guests.
What are the two servants doing there?
- Servants? - What are squids doing...
in this group?
- I'm not a squid. - He's a baby octopus.
Se Chan, take off your jacket.
- No. - You're compared to him.
Without the jacket, he looks more like him.
I came here dressed like this and found out he came looking like this.
You two are dressed alike.
- This is driving me crazy. - How did it happen?
Seong Wu looks fashionable, but your outfit looks like...
- the uniform of "Happy Together." - Come on.
What are you talking about?
- It's the same color. - That's not true.
- It's not a good color. - Right.
It's the color you wear at bathhouses.
I'll introduce them to you then.
- This is funny. - Why do you...
- keep smiling? - I'm so happy.
Today, So Min said...
she's wearing light makeup. She got ready for this.
- I look natural. - So Min.
Please introduce yourself one by one.
Hello. I'm Actor Lee Do Hyun.
He's handsome.
- He has a great voice. - I know.
It turns out you're the one who presented an award to Yu San Seul.
Right. When I presented the award, you were there as Yu San Seul.
- Really? - You did?
(The presenter is Do Hyun.)
Yu San Seul of "How Do You Play?"
(He presented the Rookie of the Year award to Yu San Seul.)
After 27 years...
- You were there as Yu San Seul. - Really?
- I was out of my mind that day. - What a coincidence.
On Running Man, the winner always gets a prize.
- That's right. - I've always wanted to win it...
and give it to my parents as I watched the show.
- What kind of prize? - Like Korean beef...
- or gold. - I see.
- That's right. - The prizes have gotten better.
We have a massage chair too.
- Do you have a massage chair? - We have a massage chair,
a tablet PC, and everything.
- I'll try my best. - We have great guests today.
ZICO is here too.
It's like ZICO's Korea.
He swept the whole country.
(Dancing around)
(What's going on?)
Gosh, this is so...
- Just play any song - He's preparing for his concert.
I should go forward like this.
- What? It looks more like this. - What's that?
It's like a comedy show.
- This is what comedians do. - It looks like a comedy show.
That's not what I did.
This is what ZICO does.
We did the "Any Song" Challenge. Did you watch it?
- I did. - Did you?
- Yes. - Cavewoman Ji Hyo did it.
That's right. I watched it.
We have the original artist here.
- Ji Hyo, you should show him. - To "Any Song,"
- Hi. - you should dance with him.
It's just a random dance to any song.
- Ji Hyo. - Don't worry about him...
and dance as you like.
- ZICO, please stand next to her. - ZICO.
- Don't panic. - Okay.
The original artist is finally here.
I get to see him dance. There he goes.
(What would the original artist's "Any Song"...)
(and Cavewoman Ji Hyo's random dance look like?)
Don't worry about her, ZICO. Just do your dance.
- Just mind your dance. - Look at Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, just focus on your dance.
What?
- Ji Hyo knows how to dance. - She watched it.
(What? Does she know the dance?)
- She knows it. - Hey.
Don't practice it.
- What is going on? - What is she doing?
- She practiced the moves. - What?
- What's wrong with Ji Hyo. - She knows the moves.
What's up with Ji Hyo?
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo's shocking transformation)
She knows the moves.
(She got out of the cave and communicated with the world.)
She knows how to dance.
I'm very disappointed in Cavewoman Ji Hyo.
- What a bummer. - She's too good.
Ji Hyo, why are you so good?
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo finally got out of her cave.)
I practiced the moves.
- The cave collapsed. - ZICO.
- The cave gave way. - I'm so disappointed.
- I know. - Ji Hyo.
We will have this part cut for you.
It's not funny.
- How could you... - We should change her nickname.
You can't communicate with the world...
- Okay. - like that.
Now that I finished ZICO's dance, I'll go back to the cave.
Okay. You should do that.
Please give ZICO a big hand.
- ZICO. - What?
ZICO.
Shut your mouth.
I can't help but look at him.
Don't say things like that.
If you have time for that, go change your clothes.
- I can't stand this. - He's cute.
Why would you do that with your mouth?
Next up after...
- Do Hyun and ZICO, - I'm curious.
we have Seo Ji Hun here.
Hello. I'm Actor Seo Ji Hun.
- I like his voice. - Jae Seok, Ji Hun is...
younger than you think.
- How old are you, Ji Hun? - I'm 24.
Really? Only 24?
I was really surprised.
Ji Hun, what is your number-one concern these days?
- I really like YUN DDan DDan. - YUN DDan DDan?
- You're like So Min. - We have a fan of YUN DDan DDan.
- I like YUN DDan DDan too. - She's a fan of YUN DDan DDan.
(Silent)
It's over.
(He gives no reply.)
- Hey, you should say something. - End of conversation.
It makes me look bad.
- Say something to her. - The end.
"Is that so?" You could've said that.
You can say, "I like him too."
- "We have something in common." - Just say anything.
I don't know why everyone tries to keep me at a distance.
All right. The end.
(So Min makes everyone keep her at a distance.)
Seong Wu is back after a long time. It's been a long time, right?
Yes. I haven't been on a TV show for a long time.
I know. You haven't been on TV shows for a while.
Is there a member you've wanted to meet here?
I...
We're here.
Just make yourself comfortable and talk.
- I wanted to meet Kwang Soo. - Why?
- Why? - Could you tell us why?
(He forces Seong Wu to say why.)
He's very funny.
- I met him at an award ceremony. - That's right.
When I met him there,
I thought he was very humorous.
Do you remember anything he said that day?
Just make something up.
(He said Kwang Soo was funny, but he doesn't remember anything.)
- He didn't listen carefully. - He just sighed.
- He just doesn't remember anything. - Why would he sigh?
The end.
Today, we have Team Lee Kwang Soo with good-looking members...
and Team Jee Seok Jin with entertainers.
- Is he the center? - What?
Is Kwang Soo the center?
All members get 50 R coins as base money at the beginning.
50 R coins? Today's race is about R coins.
The team who wins in each mission...
will hand in 15 R coins.
And the losing team will hand in 20 R coins.
And the team with more R coins of the center...
- will win the race. - So it means...
I should have more coins in order to make our team win.
- The coins of the center? - I should have more coins.
You should hand in your coins.
The center of the winning team...
and the top two members with most coins will win the prize.
- Two members? - The center of the losing team...
and the two members with the least coins will get a penalty.
I will show you that Seok Jin will be torn...
into pieces in our team.
I'll show you how he'll be torn.
I should trust my team members.
(What's the first mission for R coins?)
The first mission is...
Return of Unlucky Center.
We have 30 eggs here. 20 of them are boiled, and 10 are raw.
10 raw eggs?
Gosh, that's a lot.
Each team will break 15 eggs.
The team with less raw eggs wins the game.
This is Kwang Soo's trademark.
- This is not good. - Look at that.
- You go first. - You should go first.
All right then.
- Se Chan, you go first. - Me?
- I'll try one first. - Okay.
Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - It's good. I have a good feeling.
- 1, 2, and... - I think it's raw.
1, 2, and 3.
- Okay. - Nice.
He did it.
You just succeeded, so you can try one more time.
I think it will break.
- There are 10 raw eggs. - Can I change it?
- No, you can't. - He says I can.
- You can't switch. - You can't.
- No. It's over once you touch it. - Once you grab it,
you can feel it.
Can you feel it? Go ahead and try.
- Why? - You said you can feel it.
Why are you twisting my arm?
(You can talk to me. Why are you twist my arm?)
When did I twist your arm?
At a slight tickle, I feel pain here.
- I didn't twist your arm. - It must've hurt a lot.
You should sound strong.
- "Why are you twisting my arm?" - Right.
- Why did you sound so gentle? - He sounded like a little kid.
- Did I do that? - I'm innocent.
You should yell at him.
(ZICO, Do Hyun, Ji Hun, and Seong Wu has broken 12 eggs.)
Good. You did a good job.
- Now it's Kwang Soo's turn. - Watch carefully, guys.
(Kwang Soo needs to break 3 eggs.)
You'll see why he's Lee Kwang Soo.
(Watch carefully. You'll see why he's Lee Kwang Soo.)
- Good. - This is a good chance.
That's dangerous.
- Yes! - Gosh.
- What's with him? - Kwang Soo.
This is amazing.
Kwang Soo, that doesn't seem like you.
- Did you just drool? - I did.
- Are you that happy? - I'm so thrilled.
Is this what you're doing today?
I'm sorry. I was carried away. Just hurry.
- He's drooling. - No.
- This is... - That's dangerous.
(Did he pick a boiled egg again?)
- I have a bad feeling. - This is...
(Stepping back)
(Breaking)
(It's not surprising that he broke a raw egg.)
I knew it.
(He tries one more time.)
- That's right. - It's okay.
- The probability isn't so bad. - It's okay.
- The odds are good. - You have one left.
- You're doing a good job. - Is your forehead okay?
- Kwang Soo likes this game. - How many eggs?
They broke eight raw eggs.
- You broke a lot of raw eggs. - We did a good job.
- It's 8 out of 10. - 8 out of 10?
We broke 8 out of 10, right?
- Are there 10 raw eggs? - Right.
Shall we begin?
I'll break two eggs without a break.
- What's that hat? - One...
- "What's that hat?" - It's funny, isn't it?
Is it Leon's hat?
It's 1 and 1.
It hurts.
Didn't it hurt?
I love this moment even though it hurts.
- Enjoy it. - I'm having a lot of fun.
So Min looks like she's on a spring picnic.
So Min looks pretty today.
It looks like a spring day.
She looks like a freshman in college.
Look at her smile.
Seriously, no one's looking at her as you say that.
They all are staring into empty space.
They only care about eggs.
They are looking at the apartments.
- Why are they so distracted? - It's unbelievable.
I know I'm quite old.
I admit it.
So Min, just break an egg.
(So Min is back to her job.)
She's good. This is what you should do.
(She broke 2 raw eggs in a row.)
(The good-looking members respond to the raw eggs.)
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, and Jae Seok broke eggs in turn.)
It broke.
- We don't know it yet. - It's a tie.
- How many eggs are left? 2? - Seok Jin, there are 2.
- There are only two. - I should do this right.
- Seok Jin, please. - It has to be raw.
(Raw)
(What's Team Jee Seok Jin's fate?)
(A raw egg)
(We win!)
- Well done. - It's raw.
So what's good for them?
- Why are you moving on so fast? - What's the rush?
I don't know what else to do.
Since Team Lee Kwang Soo won, they should hand in 15 coins.
Team Jee Seok Jin lost, so they should hand in 20 coins.
It's just five more coins.
Now each member will go into the Cashier's office...
and hand in R coins in the order that the center determines.
As I informed you earlier, the center goes in there last...
and return the R coins to make up the shortage.
And the center...
can check the remaining R coins of the members.
And he can point out the member who returned least R coins.
If the center points out the member who handed in the fewest coins,
the member will make up the difference instead of the center.
I didn't know about that.
If he fails to single out the betrayer,
the center will hand in another five coins for not believing his member.
- If I get it wrong... - Yes.
When you go into the Cashier's office,
you'll be told the cumulative number of coins.
- The winning team goes first. - Okay.
Let's make this look beautiful.
We should do this equally.
Three coins per person.
Then you won't have to return your coins.
We should protect Kwang Soo.
- We should. - Right.
- So we will hand in our coins. - Okay.
- Let's do this right. - Do we need to give 20 coins?
- We should hand in 20 coins. - How many coins per person?
- Let's be conscientious... - Hand in three coins.
Three coins per person.
- And I'll hand in five coins. - That would look great.
- Let's do that. - All right.
- I'll hand in 3 coins. - 3 coins.
This is just the beginning.
- Seok Jin. - This is the first game.
This is the first game.
I can tell that you're thinking of petty tricks.
- Me? That's not true. - He should single out a member.
Even if I don't hand in my coins, I'll be safe if he guesses wrong.
That's why I have to hand in three coins.
- You go first then. - Kwang Soo, determine the order.
I'll call the most reliable one first.
Do Hyun goes first.
- Me? - Okay.
- Do Hyun goes first. - Yes. I'll be right back.
- Just three coins. - Remember what we said.
- I don't want anything else. - I think they are naive and nice.
They seem very nice.
Can I give you my coins here?
(Do Hyun seems quite reliable. How many coins is he handing in?)
(He promised to give 3 coins.)
(Do Hyun handed in 3 coins as he promised.)
He handed some to them.
- Next up is Ji Hun. - Okay.
You shouldn't give them any.
How many did the person in front of me give?
(Do Hyun gave 3 coins.)
(Will he keep his end of the bargain as well?)
(He gives 3 as well.)
Kwang Soo will probably suspect me, right?
- Here. - Take them.
- ZICO, why are looking at me? - Gosh.
I can't believe you. Isn't it a bit too early?
- Why are you looking at me? - Isn't it a bit early?
Kwang Soo, go.
Can I pick Se Chan before paying up?
- Don't do that. - No?
- Just go first. - Do I need to go first?
You've already betrayed us.
(He's going to check how many coins there are.)
(Did any of them betray the team?)
Hello.
(There should be a total of 15 coins.)
(There are 12 coins in total. 3 are missing.)
"12"?
Do I pick the suspect here?
Or do I do it over there?
(He can either pay for everything or catch the traitor.)
- Can I pick without paying up? - Yes.
I'll do that.
Okay.
(He's going to pick the traitor.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
How many did you give them?
Look at his face.
You look worked up.
- I'm fine. - He must've paid a lot.
You look upset.
There's a filthy loach among us.
(They burst into laughter.)
- There's one. - I bet there are more.
I'm going to catch him.
- One? - Really?
There is one loach...
- Is there a loach among you? - that is ruining our team.
I can see my future in him.
- Please pick. - I trust you guys.
I pick...
(Which one of them does he think paid the least amount?)
Se Chan.
(He picks Se Chan.)
I think Se Chan paid up.
- Goodness. - He did.
There's no one else to pick.
Seong Wu looks brazen.
- Guys like him betray easily. - You paid?
- Let's see the result. - I'll tell you.
Kwang Soo, you have...
- failed. - Hey.
- See? - Please pay five more coins.
You'll become broke if you trust the wrong people.
What?
The total is...
(Se Chan checked the total amount.)
(I should pay 3 coins.)
(He'll pick me, then.)
(He wanted Kwang Soo to suspect him and paid 3 coins.)
The loach is among them!
- It's 1 of these 3. - I saw all of them paying.
ZICO seemed as if he was wrongfully accused.
(Which one of them is the loach?)
Kwang Soo, please pay five more coins.
I should've just paid three back then.
(He pays 5 more for wrongfully suspecting Se Chan.)
We'll start with our loach.
- I'm speechless and upset. - She'll go first.
- She won't be able to betray us. - I'm a scapegoat.
The loach will go first.
(Lady Loach goes first.)
(Amidst everyone's suspicion, what will she do?)
You're already back?
- Yes, because I paid. - Did you not pay?
- Really? Let me check. - I think this is...
- a good deal. - I bet she paid up this time.
- You're right. - Because...
- She got caught in the first round. - Of course, I paid up.
There's no way I wouldn't have.
Seok Jin, you need to watch Jae Seok.
I bet Jae Seok will accuse me no matter what.
See? He's acting.
(Exclaiming)
Look at how awkward he looks.
Already?
Then...
Here.
(Next up is Haha.)
(There's a total of 3 coins.)
(There are only 3 coins.)
Someone didn't pay, right?
- Then... - I'll...
(Haha, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo have paid.)
I trust you guys.
I hope I'll be able to smile when I get there.
I had no idea So Min would do that from the get-go.
- Goodness. - He's driving me crazy.
Gosh.
My goodness.
They've all gone insane.
How could they do this?
Is it that hard to pay three coins?
I did expect some of them to betray the team but...
(He needs to pay all 14 coins or pick out the traitor.)
Gosh.
You guys are something.
- Seok Jin, trust me. - Did you see?
There is a loach among us.
- Seok Jin. - Catch the loach.
- Seok Jin. - Yes.
Jae Seok looks thirsty.
Will you pay up or pick the suspect?
The latter, of course. I'd be a fool not to.
If you pick me,
- that would be your mistake. - Pick one.
You need to trust me.
- Jae Seok looks anxious. - Your mouth's full.
Look at me.
- How many did you pay? - I didn't know she'd betray us.
I'll be honest. I paid two coins.
That little...
(I know the truth.)
- I'm serious. - I ought to just...
- You paid two coins? - Yes.
I paid two coins.
If the people who went first paid the correct amount,
- I'd be relieved. - Hey.
Will you only believe me once I crack one of these open?
- What are you doing? - I'm innocent!
- Goodness. - You picked the right ones.
- You did. - You picked well.
He's extremely unlucky.
- That's strange. - Why were all of them...
- boiled eggs? - None of them were raw.
- One of them should've burst. - I bet you paid one.
- One? - Jae Seok too.
I paid two!
- I paid two! - You're good.
- You're good. - You are.
There aren't even that many eggs left.
Goodness.
Why are all of them boiled?
You should've been this lucky during the previous game.
I can't express my innocence!
- Goodness. - Please pick the suspect.
Okay.
I think he'll get it right.
(Will he be able to pick out the traitor?)
- Jae Seok! - Goodness.
Jae Seok.
- I think So Min... - You're probably right.
- paid 1 coin. - I paid 2 coins.
I bet she paid one.
- You paid two? - I'm sure she paid.
- You caught him. - I did.
- Seok Jin, - I got it right.
you have...
- failed. - What?
I told you.
- You paid? - She...
Why didn't you believe me?
(Is the traitor someone else?)
(Jae Seok paid 2 coins.)
I should do this.
You know, right?
- She's the real culprit. - My gosh.
- Who didn't pay up? - It's So Min.
I know it looks like I'll pay three, but I won't.
(Ji Hyo didn't pay anything.)
Okay.
The first mission is over.
Change into your uniforms and move to the next location.
(Both centers failed to catch the traitors and paid more.)
(There's a mysterious ranking list.)
What are these photos?
You guys look so unctuous.
That's the face Kwang Soo makes when taking photos.
- He raises his head. - It's my favorite photo.
He loves that angle.
He poses like that at airports abroad.
- He likes that angle. - It's that.
Excuse me, but are Se Chan and Kwang Soo in disguises?
(They look too ugly.)
Not at all.
Our team is known for being good-looking.
This mission is called Get into Any Rankings.
(Get into Any Rankings)
Get into any rankings
What's the problem?
A professional company...
has surveyed 112 individuals in their 20s and 60s.
I'll give you a different genre for each round.
Predict your rankings after discussing among yourselves.
Place your pieces among the 12 rankings.
You'll get points if you're right.
- I need to rank myself? - Correct.
More than one piece...
- can be on each ranking. - Really?
The team that gets the most correct rankings wins.
You'll need to get 2 out of the 3 rounds correct.
This is tricky.
We don't know how others think of us.
- Here's the first question. - Okay.
We asked 112 people in their 20s to 60s.
"Who do you think was the most popular..."
"to the opposite gender when they were young?"
(Who do you think was the most popular...)
(to the opposite gender when they were young?)
- This is... - This is easy.
This is...
- definitely me. - Popular to the opposite gender?
The most likely ones are over there.
- Right. - There's ZICO,
Seong Wu, and more.
The four lowest rankings are neck and neck.
We're definitely neck and neck.
- That's heartbreaking. - Four?
Yes, four. We'll be neck and neck.
You're right.
When we were young?
The age range is...
- Too broad? - Yes.
- I think you and Se Chan... - I agree.
- will be placed higher. - But...
Seong Wu said something very kind.
He said the age range was too broad,
so the others had good chances as well.
- Not at all. - He's so kindhearted.
- That's not what I meant. - He said it so nicely.
- Thanks. - That's not what I meant.
Since the elderly know them two better...
That wasn't the nuance he gave off earlier.
It sounded like he was saying, "Cheer up."
(He was pitying them.)
- "You can do it." - "You can do it."
- That's what I felt. - Not at all.
I wasn't going to say this.
(He suddenly interrupts them.)
Then don't say it.
Cut.
It's best not to say anything if you're hesitant.
Let me brag about my bachelor days.
I hope this will help.
Someone asked for my number on the streets.
Did you give them your pager number or what?
- What? - What did you give them back then?
We didn't even have pagers.
Did you give them your homing pigeon's name?
(Did they exchange letters through homing pigeons?)
- 9999-9999? - "9999"?
They asked me...
- for my number. - Cut.
What about you, Do Hyun? Were you popular?
- I bet he was. - Do tell us.
We need to rank ourselves.
Back then, you had to be humble...
- and not brag about such things. - Right.
- But times have changed. - Right.
- To be honest, - Yes, be honest.
it was Valentine's Day in elementary school.
There were chocolates on my desk.
- How much did you have? - On your desk?
- Can I brag? - Of course.
- You can. - He's almost 60, and he bragged.
My mom came to school...
- and helped me carry them home. - My goodness.
This was in second grade.
Did you participate in relay races during field day?
- Every time. - Goodness.
Then there's nothing more to say.
- I was the last runner. - The fourth runner!
- He was the fourth runner. - The fourth runner?
The fourth runner is always the popular one.
- Seok Jin... - I was quite athletic.
- Didn't you play basketball? - In school.
Yes, I played basketball in high school.
- Then girls would've liked him. - He had to be popular.
- Sports drinks... - Beverages?
Girls gave him sports drinks.
- Yes, sports drinks. - He reminds me...
- of the protagonists in TV dramas. - Right?
We see people like him in TV commercials too.
Yes, by the fountain.
Ji Hun, what about you?
Me?
In middle school, after classes began,
for about three days...
(For 3 days after starting middle school...)
- Yes? - What happened?
Girls were lined up.
- And... - Just to see you?
To get a glimpse of you?
So that they could cleanse their eyes!
Girls come by to look at handsome boys.
I can't believe things like that happens.
- Exactly. - Girls line up?
We only thought that happened in movies or TV dramas.
Many went by to get a glimpse of Se Chan too,
but for a different reason.
- Like coming to the zoo? - To get a good laugh.
- Right. - Because they were fascinated.
Now let's hear from ZICO.
I wasn't a popular kid because of my looks,
- but retreats or... - Exactly.
- at school picnics. - Because you could sing.
After performing in front of the other kids,
I'd rise in fame.
Which song did you perform to?
"Rising Sun" by TVXQ.
"Rising Sun"?
Could you show us how you performed to it?
I don't remember anymore,
but it was something like this.
Well, he's such a good dancer.
He looks cool even dancing those small moves.
Se Chan, how about you?
In my case...
How have you been lately?
- How have I been lately? - Are you good?
Yes, I've been studying to learn new things.
I'm not kidding when I say that in high school,
a group of girls actually...
fought over me.
- What? - Why?
They liked me so much and they all wanted me.
- What? - They fought over me.
It's not a joke.
This is the most hilarious thing you said today.
Really? So what happened?
Well, the choice was mine. I had to make a choice.
After fighting over him,
they came to the conclusion that it was a draw.
Just like we predicted,
a lot of the members on that team will probably be...
- high up in the rankings. - That's right.
Let me tell you one hard fact though.
I went on my first group blind date in high school.
Was it in Hanyang?
Yes, we traveled on horses to get there.
Where did you tie up your horse then?
- Your horse... - My horse?
- Next to Namdaemun... - He's taking it for now.
There were trees alongside it.
- Trees? - What did you do on dates?
Shoot arrows?
Or a game of tuho?
Don't be ridiculous.
We just wrote down names...
- on a paper. - Really?
But you would've had to write it in Chinese characters.
We still wrote in ancient Korean, so don't worry.
Ancient Korean?
We wrote in Korean, all right?
The Korean published in Hunminjeongeum.
That's what we wrote in.
So three girls wrote your name down?
Ji Hyo, I bet you were popular in school.
Of course, right?
- Me? - She probably was.
I bet she was popular.
I never went on group blind dates...
and no one set me up on blind dates either.
Popular kids don't know that they're popular.
- They don't. - Later on in life,
you realize you were popular.
She was a cavewoman back then too, so of course, she didn't know.
I never caught on to those things.
You probably all know Ji Hyo's photo from high school.
The one with the slick bangs.
It looks like she had a temper back then.
- Tell us how it was. - That was me in high school.
The middle school I attended had some strict rules.
Our hair had to be a short bob.
You definitely are older than how you look.
- Now I'm curious. - Is this you in middle school?
- Yes, that. - In middle school?
- No wonder... - I had just been crying.
- So there you are. - I don't mind your hair though.
You were pretty.
So Min, what about you?
Many think that I was popular in school,
but my mom never helped me carry the chocolates I received.
In fact, she helped me make...
the chocolates I wanted to give to the boy I like.
I feel bad for your mom.
- Goodness. - She helped me make them.
- When it comes to love... - That's right.
She makes sure she gets it.
The boys that I liked...
would like my best friends though.
I have some sad memories.
So that's what it was like for So Min.
The boys she liked had feelings for someone else.
- Jae Seok too. - It was like that for me too.
- He'd bring up the mood. - Things would heat up,
but the ladies would choose my friends instead.
Jong Kook, weren't you popular too?
- Most definitely. - Well,
I...
- Of course, he was famous. - Older girls were more fond of me.
That suits you though.
Nothing can be better than that.
There was a salon I'd go to when I was in high school.
- He's on a different level. - The hairstylists?
- The older girls there... - The hairstylists?
- Yes, in their early 20s. - They were adults then.
Yes, older girls liked me when I was in high school.
It's probably because you managed the store.
(That's why.)
I bet you were cool back then.
You managed salons too?
- You managed stores? - Really?
- No, hold on. - I had no idea.
You managed the salon for them?
- Is that what you did? - Anyway,
older girls were more fond of me.
It's so believable though.
So now...
Yes, go ahead and predict where you would be on the ranking.
- Our own? - Yes, guess your own ranking.
Just know that we need to win this round.
We have to guess our own ranking correctly.
Most of us are probably high up.
We're high up in the ranking.
- But... - Kwang Soo and I...
- Exactly. - We'll be low on the ranking.
Jae Seok could be high up in the ranking though...
since he's funny.
- Right? - The funny ones...
were popular in school.
- I bet he's in the top three. - Let's start with Seok Jin.
I...
- It's all about guessing correctly. - But Seok Jin's well-known,
- so... - In my case...
Our team needs to win, so I'll put myself in ninth place.
You think three are beneath you in the ranking?
- Eighth place? - To be honest,
I think you're probably in 10th place.
Shut it.
(Mr. Popular explodes.)
- The choice is yours. - I was quite popular, you know.
Go with your gut then.
- I was popular with the ladies. - Go with your gut.
- Follow your gut. - Okay.
(He trusts his gut...)
(and puts himself in 7th place.)
No, don't be like that!
- His gut? - You told me to follow my gut!
- I know I said that, but... - If I'm being honest,
- this is where I should be. - Stop it.
- But your gut feeling is wrong! - This is what my gut is telling me.
Add a splash of conscience too.
- Exactly. - I'll add a lot of it.
- Exactly. - Add some conscience.
- Okay! - Nice.
- Happy now? - Yes, we're good.
- Okay, fine. - It's so that the team can win.
Ji Hyo, don't be too modest.
- Ji Hyo... - Don't be modest.
It only makes sense that you're high up in the ranking.
What is your take on this?
- Me? - Yes.
Just be honest with us.
First place?
(1st place?)
Nice one!
- Do it then. - Put yourself in first place.
- Go ahead. - You should.
- Go for first place. - Look how brazen you are.
I truly believe...
- I'm in first place. - I love that about you.
You should do whatever you want regardless of what others think.
- No matter what others say... - Regardless?
- Be yourself. - Go for it.
- First place. - Prettier kids...
- were most popular in school. - Right.
So Min is probably high up on the ranking too.
So Min, just follow your gut.
I think I could be in third place.
(Laughing hysterically)
- Unbelievable. - Why are you laughing?
- I'm pretty, you know. - Yes, I know that.
(You're the only one who doesn't know.)
Can't I even laugh now?
- "I'm pretty, you know." - You never know though.
So Min was adorable as a kid, so she was probably popular.
- I agree. - Third place.
- I bet you were popular. - Wouldn't second place be better?
I think I could be higher in the ranking,
but I'll settle for this.
Team Kwang Soo, you're up.
- This is a team game, guys. - We know.
Let us be objective, okay?
Personally, I believe in you.
I bet you're in seconds place.
I was quite popular in school, you know.
- I bet you were. - You're tall so...
- They're trying to fool you. - I liked to joke around too.
This is a trap.
Why would you think that way?
Because they think I should be high up?
Anyway, keep in mind that this is a team game.
- You're in 2nd place. - 2nd place sounds good.
- Second place sounds good. - Where's your confidence?
Of course, you're in second place.
- Right? - Go for it.
I'm not sure but...
You're in second place. Gosh.
So what?
I'm putting myself in second place.
He's being ridiculous.
The team leader has no consideration for his team.
There's no one in the lower rankings.
- First place. - Seong Wu.
- First place! - Don't be modest.
This isn't me being modest.
I just think that the members of Running Man...
have a better chance to be higher up in the ranking.
- What? - No way!
If that's the case, you'll be in ninth place.
- We're a group of eight. - Not all of them.
- Is that so? - Seok Jin.
Not you.
- Not you. - Quietly but firmly...
I still think I'm better looking than some of you.
So not me, then.
- I'm loving your style. - Nice one.
That's him being modest too.
You could be right though.
Don't forget that you played basketball.
- He was actually popular in school. - Right.
Do Hyun, just think about how you really were.
People don't approach me easily though...
because they find me to be quite cold at first.
- So I wasn't... - What's your estimate ranking?
Well, about 4th or 5th place?
That high up when you think you weren't popular?
- Unbelievable. - Are you kidding me?
It's right for popular kids to say that.
- He's not like us. - "About 4th or 5th?"
Unbelievable.
If we started off by saying that,
we would've said "below ninth."
I'll go for fourth place.
Sure, fourth place.
All right.
- Good one. - How modest.
ZICO, you're next.
I think you'll be in first place.
ZICO's song has been trending these days.
I'm sure everyone has heard "Any Song" by now.
- Then... - It's third place for me.
- Third place? - Yes.
People will criticize Kwang Soo now.
You said you expected to be high up.
I can't believe you threw me under the bus like this.
- But you're our team leader. - What?
- You're our team leader. - You're the worst, you know.
- Se Chan's up. - He doesn't have much of a choice.
I'm definitely higher up than Seok Jin.
- So eighth place. - He should be beneath me.
His estimate isn't modest at all.
- Go for 8th place. - Yes, 8th place.
- Right. - It's not so bad.
- All right. - Okay.
(Who Was Most Popular in School?)
So we now have the result.
If we put ourselves too high up in the ranking...
- Tell me about it. - I don't know...
who's in 12th place, but that person should just leave.
- Here we go then. - Sure.
Let me reveal the result.
One...
(Which team guessed the most answers correctly?)
Two...
Three.
(A blast of air)
(Jong Kook's eyes open wide.)
Okay!
- We win again! - Again?
- Gosh. - Let me show you the result.
- What's that? - Here it comes.
- What? - Seok Jin...
I got it right!
- I'm in 11th place. Gosh. - I'm in 7th place.
- I'm in 5th place. My gosh. - Gosh.
Ji Hyo, you got it right.
- Do Hyun is in 10th place. - I'm in 2nd place.
That was close. ZICO is in 3rd place.
- ZICO got it right. - He got it right.
(From Team Lee Kwang Soo, ZICO and Ji Hun got their places right.)
(From Team Jee Seok Jin, Ji Hyo is the only one who got it right.)
(ZICO, Ji Hun, Ji Hyo)
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, look at that.
- Kwang Soo. - Gosh.
The survey wasn't done very well.
This is serious.
- Do Hyun is in 10th place. - All right.
Do Hyun is hilarious.
He guessed he'd be in 4th or 5th place.
After bragging about receiving sports drinks and everything...
You should never be arrogant.
- Do Hyun is so funny. - You should be humble.
Let me explain.
People in their 20s cast the most votes for ZICO.
- I knew it. - But all the other age groups...
cast the most votes for Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, you're incredible. - Ji Hyo is strong.
Also, all the age groups cast the fewest votes for Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin got the fewest votes from all the age groups.)
You're below me.
I understand that.
- They don't know what I was like. - He's angry.
That's understandable.
Okay, I get it now. So this is how it works.
I get it now.
Here's the second question.
"Who would be the most boring at clubs?"
(Who would be the most boring at clubs?)
(I'm super fun!)
- Wait. - This question...
For this question,
- I'll definitely be near the top. - I will be in the lower ranks.
So fun people are supposed to be at the bottom, right?
What are you guys like? Kwang Soo.
What do you do at clubs?
I'm kind of tall,
so I attract a lot of attention.
So what exactly do you do?
Around me...
Are you pretentious or frivolous? What are you like?
I'm pretentious and frivolous.
I'm both.
You're pretentious and frivolous?
- You're P and F. - I'm P and F.
You're P and F?
- Yes. - You're P and F.
First of all, I put on...
all the designer clothes I have at home and head out.
I want to stand out.
First of all...
"That guy is wearing such strong perfume."
He wears a lot of designer clothes.
That's so old-fashioned.
It's just to send a signal to the girls.
- "Here I am." - "I'm cool."
- You're a show-off. - Also,
if I just dance to the rhythm,
people don't really notice me.
As soon as I enter, I shout even louder than the music.
(Shouting)
(He attracts attention by shouting and wearing designer clothes.)
"Here I am!"
People look at me.
Hey, come on!
Here we go!
Let's go!
(He is pretentious and old-fashioned.)
He shouts that at a club?
In the end, I'm surrounded by about 200 people,
- all shouting. - Excuse me.
- Excuse me. Do you work at a club? - No.
- I go there to have fun. - Do you carry things there?
- No, I just have fun. - Then why do you shout...
It's just to get in the mood.
I think I've seen someone like him in front of a club.
You're like me.
- I shout a lot too. - You should.
- Here we go. - Here we go.
Here we go!
(They look like middle-aged men after a team dinner.)
- That's right. - But you two...
Both of you would be near the bottom.
- Se Chan too. - Then...
give us some music, and we'll talk about what we do.
(Running Man Club is open.)
- It's club music. - Kwang Soo.
- 1 by 1... - I just...
(This is what P and F does at a club.)
(He pretends to be attractive.)
He hasn't done this a lot.
- Gosh. - I can't stand it.
(Do you want to dance with me?)
(He hits on someone with his eyes out of focus.)
I've been to a club with him, and he actually does that.
(Input error: You like me?)
(He moves his body in a weird way while looking into space.)
What is this?
- He doesn't know how to have fun. - Hold on.
- What is he doing? - Wait.
- Just a second. - What is that?
Excuse me. Please stop the music.
Who were you talking to?
If a girl over there notices me...
- Do you see ghosts? - Why would I see ghosts?
- I don't see ghosts. - Do you see ghosts?
I just make eye contact.
- Eye contact? - Yes.
Do Hyun.
Imagine you're at a club.
(He enters a club.)
You put your hands in your pockets?
He's hilarious.
(He warms up in such a cool way.)
Do you really do that?
(His dance spirit is heating up.)
It's going up.
He's describing the build-up.
(His spirit is nearing its peak.)
(Here's the hammer dance.)
(What kind of dance is that?)
(No one has ever seen this kind of dance.)
(He's in the zone.)
- This is how I break a sweat. - Good job.
- Is that what you do? - Do Hyun, good job.
- ZICO. - Let's say...
I like the music.
(Here we go.)
(Cute)
What is that?
What is he doing?
(Relaxed)
(Oh, that's what you're supposed to do.)
What is that?
(Amazed)
(The drunken fist?)
(Se Chan stands up.)
What is he doing?
(Shouting)
(The shouting middle-aged man is back in the club.)
(It's that man again.)
(Shouting and bumping)
Let's go! Here we go!
(He continues dancing even after bumping into the table.)
Stop it!
Come on!
- This is what I do. - Good.
I like to keep the mood up.
What I do...
They all have their own styles.
Let's show them what we do.
- Seok Jin is going to be hilarious. - Seok Jin.
- His dance looks funny. - Give me some music.
The music suits him. It's like at a roller-skating rink.
Why are you suddenly playing this kind of music? Why?
You're making fun of him!
- What is this? - It's okay. I like this song.
Isn't it "Cheri Cheri Lady"?
I do this for a while...
to get in the mood.
And then we do the train.
- What? - We do the train.
- What do you mean? - We do the train.
What year is this?
You do the train?
(The train never stops.)
We did this all the time back in the day.
Everyone did.
(Welcome to the 80s.)
(We can't relate.)
I love this.
(Techno is for me.)
This is it.
(Jae Seok moves his hips to the beat in an embarrassing way.)
Come on, let's go!
- I love this! - Jae Seok!
(Shouting)
(Dancing)
They have similar styles.
(They start dancing as a duo.)
(Dancing together)
(ZICO can't stand it.)
(They're out of control.)
(The middle-aged men are having the time of their lives.)
Jong Kook, come here. Let's sit down.
(The dance turbo is on.)
Let's go!
(He minimizes movement to prevent muscle loss.)
Way to go! I love it!
Someone take over.
(Here comes So Min.)
(She turns into a female techno warrior.)
Okay!
(Poking)
Nice.
(Their dance reaches the boiling point.)
- I love it! - Very nice!
- That's what we used to do. - That was fun.
- We always circle around. - This is it.
- We always do the train. - We were amazing.
- This is what we used to do. - I'm dizzy.
That was fun.
- That was so fun. - I loved it.
I had a blast.
Now, please guess your places.
I'm sure about Jae Seok.
He's definitely in 11th or 12th place.
- I don't think you're at the top. - You're in 11th place.
- Is 3rd place okay? Okay. - 3rd place.
I think you'd be in 3rd or 4th place.
- I bet Ji Hyo is in first place. - Ji Hyo?
- I'd be in 1st place. - Ji Hyo would be in 1st place.
- She's at the top every time. - Ji Hyo would be in first place.
- Her image... - So Min.
So Min would be near the top.
- So Min would be near the bottom. - So Min...
- I'd say 10th place. - Either 10th or 11th place.
Is that the image I have?
Do I have an image like that?
- We should both go here. - Right. Both of you.
That might be a good strategy.
- Let's both go here. - I like it.
(Team Jee Seok Jin is done making their guesses.)
- He'd be near the bottom. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, you know you're near the bottom, right?
- He'd be in 7th place. - What about 8th, 9th, or 10th?
- I'll go for ninth place. - Good.
Ninth place.
That's not bad.
I'll go for seventh place.
All right.
- That's not bad. - That's not bad.
- Do Hyun... - Do Hyun...
- is really boring in real life. - He is.
- I'm very fun. - You're an amazing dancer.
I should go here.
(I'm at the bottom.)
You're super boring.
Do Hyun, do whatever you want.
- Do you admit it? - Of course.
- That I'm fun? - Yes, of course.
That's where boring people go.
It's okay.
I want a prize.
He's so cool about it.
(He swallows his pride to win a prize.)
You're in 12th place.
- You're in 12th place. - I don't go to clubs a lot.
- We know that. - We know that.
It's just about having a fun image.
- I have no choice. - With "Any Song"...
- That's a good choice. - Well done.
"Any Song" is so popular.
(Who would be the most boring at clubs?)
- We have a good chance of winning. - Will this hurt?
Let's win this. Let's do this.
Let me reveal the result.
1, 2, 3.
(What's the result?)
We win again!
(Team Lee Kwang Soo is the final winner.)
- Let's see the result. - You got it right.
We lose again? Why?
- Why did we lose? - Why?
Let's see the result.
- What is that? - I got it right.
- I got it right too. - I got it right.
(The correct ranking)
(3 members of Team Lee Kwang Soo got their places right...)
(while no member of Team Jee Seok Jin got it right.)
- Do Hyun really is in 2nd place. - I got it right.
He's in 2nd place?
Hey, you're in 2nd place.
(Do I look so boring?)
Is that my image?
Haha placed 11th.
Haha, only a few people think you are like Sean.
Only your close friends think that.
(Only his close friends think he is a loving husband.)
What do you mean Haha is like Sean?
He said his image is like that of Sean.
What kind of nonsense is that?
- Seriously. - That's ridiculous.
- Only my close friends think that. - That's right.
- The public doesn't know that. - No, it doesn't.
Thus, Team Lee Kwang Soo won.
(Team Lee Kwang Soo won the 2nd round.)
Yes!
Team Lee Kwang Soo will submit 15 R coins...
and Team Jee Seok Jin will submit 20 R coins.
- Se Chan, go first. - Shall I go first?
- Okay. - Shall we go in this order?
I know Se Chan will make the right choice.
Gosh, I didn't want to go first.
(The first person's choice will affect everyone who follows.)
(What will be Se Chan's choice?)
- You are done, right? - I am done.
- ZICO, go right ahead. - Okay.
ZICO, I don't doubt you.
(Will ZICO remain loyal?)
Look at Ji Hun. He is taking out R coins as he goes.
People who pay up are different.
(Seong Wu submits R coins last.)
(My goodness.)
- How many were there? - How many did you submit?
How many did you submit?
What is it, Seong Wu?
- Go, Kwang Soo. - I don't doubt you guys.
(Is Seong Wu shocked due to the number of R coins?)
If you didn't pay up...
I... Kwang Soo.
I had no choice.
- I had no choice either. - I...
(It's time to check the number of submitted R coins.)
(The current number of R coins)
(Only 1)
You jerks!
(He gives an angry shout.)
That startled me. What is it?
Let's break off the team.
- Why? What is it like? - What is it like?
You know,
this number is ridiculous.
(We aren't a team.)
Failing to catch the traitor would be harder.
- I will catch the traitor. - How many R coins are there?
- Four? - Shut it!
We aren't a team.
(He is seething due to the shocking result.)
- I can't believe them. - Well done.
- What a twist! - Catch the traitor.
Will you pay for everything or catch the member who paid less?
I will catch the traitor.
- I will catch the traitor. - Please pick one.
(4 out of 5 members submitted 0 R coins.)
There are so many suspects.
I guess someone submitted zero R coins.
I think the lowest number is either 1 or 0.
I will let you defend yourself one last time.
I know how many coins Se Chan submitted.
- ZICO could be lying. - So...
I submitted as much as Se Chan did.
(You little...)
Don't curse!
(A sense of betrayal makes him curse.)
There are two loaches!
I am sorry. I am sorry.
- That's not true. - Hey!
- My goodness. - Don't let him fool you.
Listen, Kwang Soo. Earlier...
- Do Hyun. - We started off on the wrong foot.
- You know what I mean, right? - For goodness' sake.
What did you do?
I had no choice but to follow.
(Kwang Soo is speechless.)
- And... - How many coins are there in total?
And I saw the need to get back on the right track.
- So you... - You have an idea now, right?
- Are you saying you paid up? - Yes.
- How many coins did you pay up? - I can't tell you that.
How many coins did you pay up? Tell me honestly.
No.
Tell me!
- Tell me! How many coins? - I can't tell you.
I see why your mom grabbed you by your hair.
- I see why your mom did it. - I can't tell you.
Seong Wu can't even laugh comfortably.
- I am... - I know. He is nervous.
the first person...
who didn't follow the wrong trend.
- You are saying you paid up. - Yes.
- He is trying his best to survive. - Seong Wu submitted two coins.
Really?
My guess is 0, 0, 1, 1, and 2 coins. Did I get it right?
- The wrong trend... - You are close.
- Did I get it right? - Kwang Soo looks upset.
No, no. That can't be right.
I wouldn't be so angry if that's the case.
- Is it worse? - Is it worse?
- My goodness. - Is it worse?
Then you should pick anyone.
He should just pick one of them.
(Failing to catch the traitor would be harder.)
This isn't a team. For goodness' sake.
I will pick 1 of these 3.
- Okay. - One of us?
I told you that we started off on the wrong foot.
- Don't be ridiculous. - You started off on the wrong foot?
Tell me how many coins you submitted and I won't pick you.
- How many coins? - I will whisper it in your ear.
I don't want the others to know.
He can lie, so it doesn't matter.
I pick Do Hyun.
(My goodness.)
- It's you. - Why do you think that?
What he whispered in my ear makes no sense.
It's you.
- It's you. I pick Do Hyun. - But...
- we started off on the wrong foot. - Do Hyun.
Kwang Soo,
(Will Kwang Soo succeed to apprehend the traitor?)
you have...
- successfully picked your traitor. - Okay!
(Sighing)
- You... - Se Chan!
- Seriously. - You shouldn't be that way!
- What are you talking about? - You shouldn't be that way!
Do Hyun,
go to the Cashier's office and pay up the rest of the R coins.
It annoyed me that he lied.
Everyone submitted zero coins.
- For goodness' sake. - Go.
(Since Do Hyun has been apprehended as the traitor,)
(he submits 14 R coins.)
(Seong Wu was the person who submitted 1 R coin.)
- Let's go. - All right.
Ji Hyo should go first.
We need to start off on the right foot.
- Ji Hyo, can you pay two R coins? - I will...
- I will do that. - Let's do this right.
(They submit R coins in turn.)
- Our total was 1 R coin. - 1 R coin.
(There are 8 R coins in total.)
Is this a family?
Okay.
Go ahead.
I pick Haha.
(Seok Jin picks Haha.)
Seo Jin, you have...
- succeeded. - All right.
Haha, pay up the rest of the R coins.
(Haha had submitted 0 R coins. He pays up 12 R coins.)
(The current number of R coins)
(Team Lee Kwang Soo and Team Jee Seok Jin)
The last mission which gives you a chance to win more R coins is...
Trust the Piggy Banks.
(Trust the Piggy Banks)
You will play Name Tag Elimination for a limited amount of time.
(They will play Name Tag Elimination for 30 minutes.)
A team member can win R coins...
by removing the other team's name tags...
or finding and submitting the other team's name tags...
to the center.
To the center.
All coins will be submitted to the center,
but the center can't put them in the piggy banks.
The 12 members' piggy banks will be in the centers' room.
The centers must distribute coins to the members.
Then those members will enter the room...
and put the coins in the piggy banks of their choice.
- I need to trust the team members. - Seriously.
Are you out if your name tag gets ripped off?
- You keep playing. - I see.
The center can also win coins...
in the centers' room through a separate mission.
Okay. I got it.
- Let's start the race. - Let's go.
We need to win as a team.
(Team Jee Seok Jin has 30 coins, Team Lee Kwang Soo has 43 coins.)
I need to beat Kwang Soo.
I think I am losing.
- That's right. I am winning. - But I have Jae Seok and Jong Kook.
They are good at...
- Name Tag Elimination. - That's right.
Once they bring me name tags...
Should I put my interest first?
Should I put the team's interest first?
That's the question.
(You can avoid the penalty if you have a lot of R coins.)
Okay. In this round, I plan to put the team's interest first.
I should focus on...
finding the hidden name tags.
Everyone on that team must be stronger than me.
I will yank off the name tag of anyone I meet.
So Min, Ji Hyo...
I could find my teammates' name tags...
and sell them for two coins each...
- to the other team. - You could do that.
(Betrayal is engraved on his DNA.)
The race will start.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
The race starts.
Shall I go?
(The race starts!)
The race starts.
- Did it start already? - It started.
The two of you will have a quiz.
A quiz?
- Listen to the question. - I think I have an advantage.
You never know if I do this seriously.
The center who answers the question correctly first...
- will get 1 coin from the other. - 1 coin.
The coins you get from the members as well as the quiz...
need to go into the piggy banks.
So I need to give them to my team members.
I should save up the coins...
and give them at once.
Who do you trust the most?
I trust Jong Kook the most.
He doesn't lie to your face.
I don't trust anyone but Seong Wu.
Your team is the absolute worst.
Here comes the first question.
- Jae Seok has a son, right? - Yes.
When is Yu Ji Ho's birthday?
(When is Yu Ji Ho's birthday?)
(What kind of a question is this?)
(Flustered)
Do you think we are Jae Seok's slaves?
(The ridiculous question disheartens them.)
This is driving me crazy.
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok is looking for name tags.)
(ZICO spots Jae Seok...)
I spotted him.
(and begins to chase after him.)
(Jae Seok is unsuspecting.)
- We need to find name tags. - I know.
- Where can they hide... - ZICO is behind you.
(He stops abruptly.)
(He sees Jong Kook too late.)
ZICO is behind you.
(He's shocked.)
- Wait for me. - Goodness.
(The tables are turned.)
- This is so scary. - Come here.
- I'm so scared. - Come.
What do I do?
I'm sorry, ZICO.
No.
- Rip it off. - Don't.
We started less than five minutes ago.
You can't do this. You can't.
He's so funny.
- Don't. - Turn around.
- Sorry. - No.
He's so funny.
He ran up from behind to rip off my name tag,
and then he was petrified when he saw you.
(He didn't see Jong Kook.)
You had no idea ZICO was there.
- I had no idea. - He came up so fast.
(So Min takes the name tag and runs away.)
It's my lucky day!
I got lucky. Thanks, Jong Kook.
I have to answer this before Jae Seok gets here.
Let's go for it. Let me answer.
- August 2... - I'm here.
- You're here? - You're here already?
(So Min arrives at the centers' room.)
Hey.
(Nice, So Min.)
Good job.
- Did you rip ZICO's name tag? - No, I was there at the right time.
Anyhow,
this is the first one.
So Min, I'll give you coins for the name tag.
- Thank you. How many are there? - Is it three?
That's it? Only three?
If we get Ji Ho's birthday right, we get one.
If he doesn't get the question right, do we lose this?
- No. - It's not like that.
- We keep this. Wait. - Okay.
Get back out there for now.
- Do I leave? - Good job.
No, I should put them away.
No, we'll collect them first.
- No. - No.
10 seconds ago, he said he'll never give them to you.
That's not true. Our team has to win.
He doesn't trust you or Haha.
- That's not true. - No.
- Leave. Our team has to win. - I have to check.
- It's for the team. - Keep playing.
Let me answer. August 22.
(August 22 is incorrect.)
- How am I supposed to know? - What's the question?
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo.
(When is Jae Seok's son's birthday?)
October 28.
(October 28 is incorrect.)
(Striking)
You didn't hit me earlier.
(My answer was incorrect.)
(Ji Ho's birthday is the question?)
You lost your chance.
I'll help.
It's May 1.
I'm right. It was the password.
- Let me answer. - Seok Jin.
- May... - May?
(May 1)
- 1. - 1?
(May 1 is...)
(correct.)
You're correct.
(He picked up Haha's answer.)
- Did he get it right? - He got this right?
He did.
Seok Jin, get a coin from Kwang Soo.
- So I give it to you? - Yes.
- I'm going to collect them... - We have to win.
- and go at once. - You have to get first place.
Continue your activities. Why are you being lazy?
Get the name tags.
So I work like a dog and give him the coins?
That's up to the centers.
I'll keep you in mind.
This isn't good. It's not worth working hard.
This isn't looking good.
What's my team doing?
(ZICO is looking for another chance.)
That scared me. She's pink.
That scared me.
- Can I pass by? - Yes.
- Come here. - Why?
Come here. Hurry up, punk.
- I can do one-on-one. - I don't think so.
(He checks that she's by herself.)
(He starts attacking.)
(Why is he running away?)
(It's Jong Kook again!)
Get him.
(Jong Kook was waiting for him to get close.)
(He strikes when ZICO is in range.)
Please, Jong Kook. Please.
Please.
(Ripping)
Come on. What was that for?
- Gosh, Jong Kook. - Do I take this?
Okay. Sorry, ZICO.
Hey.
Serves you right, ZICO.
(Jae Seok enters the centers' room.)
Hey. Okay.
- No way. - Jae Seok.
- Do you... - You have another one?
How many times did ZICO get his name tag ripped?
ZICO and Ji Hun.
What's he doing?
(What on earth are these two doing?)
Why does ZICO keep getting eliminated?
Give me some, and you can take this.
- Sure, I'll do it. - Okay.
- Alright. Okay. - Do it.
Let's see.
(2 for the captain and 1 for each of them)
- Did you hear that? - I did.
We almost caught up.
What's my team doing?
Jong Kook!
- Let's work together. - Okay.
Over there!
(Jong Kook is bullying them.)
(He falls like autumn leaves.)
He's strong.
- Don't come. - Get him.
- Rip his name tag off. - Go.
- Get his name tag. - Don't do it.
- Sorry. - Rip off Seong Wu's name tag.
- Get his name tag. - Please.
We're sorry.
- Sorry. - Wait.
(He gets betrayed by his team and is eaten alive.)
Sorry.
What?
- Come on. - Sorry.
(ZICO is back!)
(This is his third time trying.)
(He grabbed the name tag first,)
(but can he avoid Jong Kook?)
Hey.
Goodness.
(Isn't this the same face as before?)
(He tried to help.)
(Ripping)
(Who are you trying to help?)
(He has to worry about himself.)
- I got another one. - Okay.
- ZICO! - What's this?
He didn't even get one.
Just hide!
Why is my team not coming?
- Hey. - Thank you, Seong Wu.
- What's my team doing? - I know.
(He's going around looking for name tags.)
I'm first place.
- Se Chan. - Jae Seok.
Where are you going?
I'm running away.
Do you think you can get my name tag?
- Sorry? - If we wanted to.
Why are you two going around together?
(He's outnumbered and retreats.)
You scared me, ZICO.
(ZICO appears.)
- Let's get to work. - Who are they? It's 2-on-2.
It's 2-on-2.
Let's see.
- I can't do it. - Who is that?
- Let's run away. - Let's go!
- Help me, Jae Seok. - Hurry up.
They'll get me for sure.
ZICO, get So Min!
So Min, hurry up.
- They're after me! - ZICO!
- I can't do this. - Hurry.
- Go. - Hurry.
- ZICO. - Go, Jae Seok.
Go, Jae Seok.
Hey.
ZICO.
- Why is it in the front? - ZICO.
Rip it, ZICO.
- Get her name tag. - Hold on.
Get So Min's name tag, ZICO.
(Ji Hun joins them.)
Come here.
(Ripping)
(He got Jae Seok's name tag!)
- Good job! - Get it.
- Rip it off. - So Min.
Okay.
(They also got So Min's name tag.)
There were three of you.
Are you all right?
- Yes. - ZICO.
Let me answer.
Hey, what were you doing?
- What were you doing? - He's disheveled.
I lost three times.
Today's name tags were all yours.
Pardon?
It was all you. You need to rip off name tags.
- I got two. - Okay!
Good job!
He has two of So Min.
This is going to be between ZICO and So Min.
Okay, good job.
- How many? - Six coins.
You never know.
Do I have to answer the questions right?
No, I give you whatever I want.
Do you want to go first?
- Where? - Get one more. Hold on.
I lost three times. It's not good to send me out there.
How many coins did you give up in the first game? Be honest.
- Pardon? - How many coins did you give?
In the first game?
(At the first Cashier's office,)
(he hesitated...)
(and didn't submit any coins.)
If I tell the truth...
If you tell me the truth, I'll give some to you.
One.
Get lost.
(That didn't work.)
There's more.
Okay. Good job, Do Hyun.
- Three. - Are you collecting them...
- or will you give me some? - I'm collecting them.
- You are? - Yes.
- Come back. Get more. - How many are you collecting?
I'll have to see.
Wait.
- Don't lose hope. - Promise me.
Don't lose hope. I'll remember who got the most.
- Let me vote. - Okay. Come back.
Jong Kook is bringing a lot.
It's mine.
- More? - Five is for me.
Our team has to win.
- Who? So Min's? Okay. - Keep coming.
Two. Great!
When can we submit the coins?
Right now,
I'm collecting them.
Se Chan, tell him you want some.
I want some.
- I want some. - I'm collecting them.
I'll be honest and give you two.
- I'll take three. Just a few. - Wait for it.
Put them down.
If not, I'll let them take my name tag.
I'll let them take it every 20 seconds.
I'm leaving. I'll show my back every 20 seconds.
Hey, take my name tag.
- Hey, I wasn't finished talking. - Hurry.
Before I let them take my name tag every 20 seconds.
Give me five for now. Are you in or not?
I'll keep showing my back. Give me five.
I'll be honest and give you 2. I'll take 3.
Three for now. This is for the team.
Give me 3 and take 2.
Fine.
- 3 and 2. - Fine.
I don't remember seeing Se Chan's name tag.
(He's finally in the piggy bank room.)
- Ji Hyo is gone too. - Hey, Ji Hyo.
(He doesn't do...)
(as promised.)
- Where is he? - What was that?
- I'm done. - That didn't sound right.
- Why? - Why was there a pause?
No, it went...
(He's making excuses.)
then thud.
(I don't trust him.)
I'll get back.
I need to see you, Seong Wu!
Let's take each other's name tags.
- Each other's? - Yes.
(Haha tries to bargain.)
Sure. Okay.
(I like this guy.)
Or should we rip our own and trade?
- You love peace. - Right.
Rip them off at the same time.
- What? - At the same time.
1, 2, 3.
Rip it.
(Glancing)
(Ripping)
(Haha puts his name tag back on.)
I didn't rip it off.
What is this?
- What? - You ripped off your name tag.
Give it to me.
Rip off your name tag.
I didn't know you would do it so fast.
Give it to me.
I am a busy man, Seong Wu.
I am sorry, okay?
- I will get going now. - Can't I rip off his name tag now?
You can't do that when your name tag is ripped off.
You are the man. Seriously.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook is looking for name tags.)
Where could they be?
(Trailing behind him...)
(is Do Hyun.)
(He holds his breath...)
(and chases after Jong Kook!)
(Waiting for his chance)
They used to hide name tags in here.
(Jong Kook was looking for name tags...)
My goodness.
(when he spots Do Hyun.)
I didn't expect you to look back.
You should have walked over faster.
You grew up watching Running Man, right?
Of course.
- You are the tiger. - Let me help you feel...
what it's like.
(Please spare me.)
(It's a touch-and-go situation.)
Jong Kook, please.
(Despite his effort,)
(the kid who grew up watching Running Man is outmatched.)
You are too strong!
(Jong Kook is relaxed.)
(Ripping)
(I didn't think Name Tag Elimination would end so quickly.)
I wasn't going to rip off anyone's name tag.
I was looking for the hidden ones. Why did you follow me?
(After the storm,)
Look at this.
It broke.
(only the traces of a ruthless fight remain.)
Do Hyun, you got your name tag ripped off.
You always participate in a race with someone like him.
- Yes. - How do you do it?
- They could be at the cafeteria. - There must be many here.
Shall we go inside?
- They could be here. - You are looking in there.
(They flaunt their skills as the fruitless search continues.)
Of course.
You are incredible.
I didn't think to look in there.
They could be here.
You didn't see this, did you?
(There is an envelope containing a name tag.)
This is a new pattern, right?
- Whose... - Whose name tag is inside?
Gosh, it's So Min's.
It's So Min's.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
- Give me So Min's name tag. - Why?
- Why? - I want to sell it.
(I want to sell it to the other team.)
Come on.
I am dying here.
- You can't do that. - Why not?
You can't sell your fellow team member's name tag!
- Seriously. - Give it to me.
I want to sell it for two coins.
I don't have any coins.
Give it to me.
What are you doing? What is it?
(So Min appears.)
(Both of them are flustered.)
- What is it? - It's nothing.
- What were you doing? - What?
What were you doing? What is that?
- What is that? - Whose name tag is it?
- Whose is it? - Whose is it?
- I can't tell you. - Why not? We are on the same team.
- It's yours, right? - No.
- Whose is it? - Actually,
it doesn't matter whether it belongs to someone on my team or me.
- I used to think the same. - Hurry up and spill.
But even a team member's name tag does matter.
(I figured it out.)
(Haha gave a new meaning to a fellow team member's name tag.)
I used to think the same until a moment ago.
- But... - What do you mean?
even a fellow team member's name tag has its use.
- Please explain. - It didn't occur to me at first.
What do you mean? What use does it have?
Whose is it? Give it to me.
- I have everyone's. - Whose is it?
(Whose name tag does she have?)
- Tell us. - In that case,
- give me mine. - Why?
I will give you yours.
- Is it Jae Seok's? - Yes. I have his.
Give it to me.
- Come on. Give it to me. - Give it to me.
- I can't trust you. - You are holding it too tightly.
Come here.
I will pay a coin for it.
(He wants to buy Jae Seok's name tag.)
I will sell it to you for two coins.
You are a swindler.
- Hey! - Let me see it.
(Jae Seok forces the trade.)
(He opens So Min's envelope.)
There is nothing inside!
(Annoyed)
(So Min is the queen of investment.)
She is the absolute worst.
I hate her.
What is wrong with her?
(Jae Seok, thank you for the trade.)
She keeps getting worse.
(After the trade...)
Se Chan.
I will sell 2 of my team's name tags for 3 coins.
- My coins? Can we do that? - Yes.
I don't need these name tags.
- Hold on. Stay right there. - Come here.
- Stay there. - I have four name tags in total.
- Hold on. How... - I found them.
- Did you find them? - How did you find so many?
I can't do anything with them since they belong to my team,
so I want to sell them.
I need coins because Seok Jin probably won't give me any.
Thus, I want some coins for myself.
- So this is a private business. - I am running a private business.
3 coins for 2 name tags.
Five coins for these.
- I have seven name tags. - In that case...
I will pay three coins.
I will sell these for five coins.
- How many do you want to sell? - Three name tags.
You said earlier that you would sell four name tags.
There are some I can't sell.
Listen.
We can't buy from a private seller who changes her words.
- Let's go. - I have three name tags to sell.
- Let's go. - Buy two name tags.
ZICO, buy two name tags.
- Buy two name tags. - ZICO.
This is how you do business.
(This is how you do business.)
They are so cheap.
(She is tired from meeting annoying customers.)
I would buy all of these name tags.
I don't even know. I will get going.
(It's another peace race on Running Man.)
I should have gotten more coins.
- I will give you the next question. - Okay.
This one is about So Min.
I don't know anything about So Min.
On Running Man, So Min once said,
"In high school, 'Blank' went into my clothes by accident."
- Blank? - What goes in the blank?
- It went into her clothes? - Yes.
Let me answer! A flower.
Is it incorrect?
(Kwang Soo hits his head with the stick part.)
Gosh, I am sorry.
- It was an accident. - What did you use to hit me?
It was an accident.
Are you okay?
- You were closer than I thought. - All right.
I shouldn't have stretched my arm.
- I shouldn't have stretched my arm. - All right.
Let me answer. A petal.
(Seok Jin's answer is incorrect.)
(Aim well.)
It's here.
(What? Kwang Soo hits his head with the side this time.)
(Seok Jin explodes.)
What are you doing?
I hit you properly this time.
- It felt different, you jerk. - Why?
(It's a strange toy hammer that hits with a thud.)
What?
I hit you properly this time.
(While the two centers argue)
Hold on.
Did you put coins in the piggy banks?
- No, I didn't. - You didn't?
(This is strange.)
ZICO, did you put coins in the piggy banks?
Seong Wu, did you put coins in the piggy banks?
I never went into that room.
(No one has received coins from the center.)
- I... - Everyone, gather around.
Do Hyun.
Do Hyun, did you put coins in the piggy banks?
- He never gave me the coins. - No?
- I never got any coins. - Listen, everyone.
You have the right to go in there.
(You have the right to go into the piggy bank room.)
- What would we do in there? - We don't have coins.
Kwang Soo has the coins.
(The coins the naive members collected...)
(are in the greedy center's hands.)
Hold on. We need to make a complaint.
Come here. Gather around.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Why didn't you give a single coin to the members?
- What? - Everyone is dissatisfied.
- Go! Go and work! - Come here.
- Go and wok! - Come here.
- You did nothing. - Why didn't you give a single coin?
- What are you doing? - I am...
You instigated them.
I am their representative.
Why didn't you give a single coin to the members?
Hard work pays off, okay?
It's not like I will take all the coins.
Shouldn't we get the coins...
- once we give you the name tags? - That's right.
- Listen. - Hey, don't be like that.
- Give us two coins each. - I will give them to whom I trust.
- That's the captain's duty. - That's right.
- Give us two coins each. - Let me ask you this.
Who is your captain?
Then why are you listening to him?
We will put some coins in your piggy bank too.
Be fair. We will put some coins in your piggy bank too.
Stand up straight.
- Guys, this is... - You jerks!
(How dare you talk back to the center?)
Go and work!
Do you think I am lazing around? Go and work!
- Don't let him sway you. - Use this time to get...
as many name tags as possible.
If I were you, I would give away my name tag to sabotage him.
- Hey. - I didn't think about this.
Why are you ganging up on me?
(The group action makes Kwang Soo anxious.)
- I will distribute them as I want. - Okay.
I will distribute them as I want.
Close your eyes.
- Close your eyes. - We worked hard!
I will distribute the coins.
(They close their eyes willingly because they are nice.)
I see someone who didn't close his eyes.
Do Hyun didn't close his eyes. Oh, I am wrong.
Close your eyes.
(He gives 3 coins to Seong Wu.)
(Is he taking them back?)
Hold on.
Let go. Let go if you want your fingers intact.
(Flustered)
- Did you pass by me already? - I will give you some.
Hide your coins.
Hide your coins. Don't show each other.
I distributed all the coins.
- We only got a few. - I distributed all the coins.
I worked so hard.
I distributed all the coins. I don't have any coins left.
- You don't have any coins left? - No.
- Are you certain? - Yes. I distributed all the coins.
Okay. Kwang Soo,
can I check your back pockets?
You jerk.
What?
- This is unfair. - The only thing I have is a phone.
(When he takes out his phone, they hear the sound of coins.)
(Hold on.)
- Hold on. - What was that sound?
Okay. You guys passed the test.
(Everyone passed the observation test.)
- Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- That's a lot! - I will give them to you.
I will give them to you.
There is no one I can trust, okay?
- This is too much. - Listen.
The member who paid one coin earlier,
Seong Wu, will get five coins.
- What? - You will get five coins.
This is nothing to be happy about.
Put one coin in your piggy bank.
- Okay. - Put one coin in your piggy bank.
- The rest... - I paid one coin earlier too.
- Did you pay one coin, ZICO? - This is too much.
ZICO, leave the room.
Go. Go and work!
(ZICO goes back to work.)
- I will give you one. - Thank you.
- Put them in my piggy bank. - I will do that.
If our team loses,
- we will get the penalty. - Okay.
Look at the forest, not the trees.
It's the team that matters.
(The center's favorite member, Seong Wu enters.)
(He puts one coin in his piggy bank.)
(Then he adds another one.)
(He has a conscience, so he gives one to Kwang Soo.)
(Seong Wu deviates a little,)
(and Ji Hun is next.)
(He embezzles without hesitating.)
(Like center, like teammate.)
(Do Hyun and Se Chan were discontent. They deposit the coins.)
Five minutes left.
You have to hurry!
Rip off name tags like crazy. We're losing right now.
- Hurry. Anybody! - Hurry up.
Should I go now?
(ZICO was abandoned by Kwang Soo,)
(but he shows his loyalty near the end.)
- They're not my team. - Okay!
- Four dollars. - Hurry!
(He flung ZICO earlier, but he loves him now.)
We're behind by 12 to 13.
- Your team has enough. Take it. - Wait.
Your team has enough. Give it to yourself.
Race is over.
This is the last chance.
(Race is over, and this is the last chance to deposit coins.)
(Did Kwang Soo and the team see the forest or the trees?)
- I think we won. - You guys already won.
Race is over.
We're counting the coins right now.
As I said before, we'll compare which captain has more coins,
and the team with that captain wins.
1st and 2nd place on the winning team will win prizes,
and the last two on the losing team will face the penalty.
I heard something shocking from that team,
but I hope it's not true.
Somebody sold their name tag.
- No way. - Somebody gave 2 to 3 coins...
per name tag.
- I hope it's not true. - This is the funny part.
They sold other people's name tags for cheap...
and sold their own at a higher price.
Other people for cheap, and theirs at a higher price.
I heard my name tag got sold for a coin.
My team fell apart.
There was no other way. I didn't want to lose.
- Seok Jin, look at yours first. - Okay, I will.
This.
It looks heavy.
- You probably have a lot. - I know, I gave him a lot.
I gave him everything.
- Stop lying. - I gave him a lot.
That's a lot.
Haha is lying 100 percent.
Seok Jin got...
43 coins.
(Seok Jin's piggy bank had 43 coins.)
43 in this?
That's a lot.
- I gave you all of them. - I gave you them all.
Really? You gave me a lot.
(Kwang Soo opens his piggy bank.)
We should have more.
His...
I don't hear anything.
Maybe we won.
- We won. - I think we won.
Wait.
This can't be. My gosh.
- Was that it? - Wait.
- See? - We won.
- We're family. - Wait.
That was everything.
- Goodness. - This is unbelievable.
These people.
(Team Kwang Soo acted collectively.)
- Let me tell you. - These people.
Kwang Soo's piggy bank...
- had 16 coins. - What?
(Only 16?)
- What? - Overall,
Seok Jin had 70,
(Kwang Soo was ahead by 13.)
and Kwang Soo had 56.
(With only 56, Team Kwang Soo loses.)
(Team Seok Jin wins.)
- This is family. - This is unbelievable.
- This is family. - Team Seok Jin wins.
This is amazing.
You guys! I told you.
Really?
No, look.
I got seven, and I gave you everything.
I didn't get too many.
They took the coins for themselves.
This is so unfair.
1st and 2nd place are as follows.
So Min came in first place.
(So Min places first.)
I came in first?
- What did you do? - I came in first?
Yes. I'm in first place?
The individual businesswoman won.
She got a couple from us.
(She collected small sums and created a miracle.)
She got none in here, and she won?
Jae Seok and Jong Kook come in second.
(Are we 2nd place?)
Jong Kook!
(Seok Jin, So Min, Jong Kook, and Jae Seok win prizes.)
Kwang Soo, open each one.
I don't know anymore.
I won't let this go.
I'm looking forward to this.
Ji Hun first.
I'm not really suspicious.
Like this? Okay.
- Is there a lot? - Is there a good amount?
It looks kind of heavy.
(Spilling)
(He's shocked.)
- How many? - Ji Hun deposited 14 coins.
He took all for himself.
Did you not give me any?
I gave you one.
- You gave me one? - Yes.
Kwang Soo.
(Do Hyun's piggy bank is next.)
Do Hyun is convincing.
(There's also a lot.)
Do Hyun took 10.
- 10? - This is funny.
This team is so funny.
They're all like Kwang Soo.
- Se Chan. - I don't have too many.
(As expected)
12 for Se Chan.
- 12? That was less than I thought. - Yes, 12.
(He accidentally spoke what was on his mind.)
Really?
That was less than I thought.
He even caused a revolt.
How many?
- He has a lot. - Seong Wu...
- had seven. - That's less than I thought.
- Really? - Seven? Wait.
- What happens then? - That wasn't what he expected.
ZICO doesn't have much.
(ZICO seemed the most sneaky on Team Kwang Soo,)
ZICO had two.
(but he was the only loyal subject.)
- ZICO. - I gave you everything.
Kwang Soo,
you found teammates who were similar to you.
What's wrong with them?
Kwang Soo, you will be getting the penalty.
Last place is Do Hyun,
and fifth place is ZICO.
(Do Hyun and ZICO will get the penalty.)
My bad. Was that too loud?
- ZICO. - Yes!
(He cheered.)
My bad. I was too loud.
ZICO lost because he didn't cheat.
That's true.
- Sit down. - Sit.
Hold him so that he doesn't fall backward.
- How intense is it? - It's good.
No, it's not too bad.
It's just the forehead.
Wait.
(That was full of captain's love.)
- You'll walk home like this. - ZICO.
- You can hit Kwang Soo. - This is so unfair.
(Running Man kid Do Hyun...)
(also gets a taste of the show.)
(Slapping)
(Kwang Soo also gets a taste of master forehead slapper's skill.)
He absorbed the force.
You know the lucky draw, right?
Please go in whatever order you decide.
- Go ahead, Jae Seok. - Should I go first?
I like...
I hope he gets Yu San Seul's CD.
Me too.
- Please. - Everybody,
there's a pattern.
This is not random.
- Is there a pattern? - Yes, Jong Kook's massage...
goes to the end.
Kwang Soo's life-sized figure belongs at the other end.
- Five. - Yes.
Let's go!
(What did he get?)
Say it out loud. What number is it?
Five.
Kwang Soo!
(He wins a life-sized figure of Kwang Soo.)
(He clenches his teeth.)
- At the end. - Genius.
Genius.
- A life-sized figure of Kwang Soo. - Genius.
I moved this.
I know. You moved it.
- Why was this here? - He added it at the end.
- This. - My gosh.
(Please take good care of it.)
You must take it.
So Min.
What number is it?
Eight.
(She wins autographed name tags of the members.)
- Autographed name tags. - Oh, dear.
I don't want it.
So Min, sell them.
I'll buy.
Sell them.
- It's on her back. - Let's see.
She'll fly away.
She's rich.
I don't think...
It's nothing again.
47. It's a dud.
That's better than mine.
Why? We should congratulate you.
Why would you congratulate me? Where am I supposed to put this?
I want the set.
(Center Seok Jin picks last.)
He picked.
(What is it?)
1, 2, 3.
2... 21.
(21!)
Air fryer.
(He wins an air fryer.)
That's awesome.
This is the most economical.
You have an air fryer at home.
I do, but I had it for over 10 years.
- Air fryers came out 10 years ago? - Of course.
- Really? - Be quiet.
I don't think they've been around for 10 years.
- Maybe 7 or 8 years. - Okay.
Air fryer!
(Seok Jin takes the air fryer!)
Good work.
(We would like to thank ZICO, Seong Wu,)
(Do Hyun, and Ji Hun for a great time.)
(With familiar faces Hong Hyun Hee and Kim Ji Min)
(It's a lively atmosphere like a team dinner.)
(But something's strange.)
(There are way too many cameras,)
(and people start disappearing one at a time.)
(Will they go through the door...)
(or will there be resistance?)
(Nobody knows what the consequences are.)
(Will they take the R coins or leave it alone?)
(They have many options.)
(Will they win or lose?)
(You have to act when nobody's looking.)
(The mystery stimulates their curiosity.)
(This intense race has no answer. How will it end?)
(Race Nobody Can Tell: Hey, You Can Find Out Too!)