(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
Was it just...
a familiar habit?
Or was it an act of reconciliation...
that was aroused by pity?
Was it an apology for condemning and hurting each other?
Was it an act of regret for past decisions?
Or...
was it a submission to impulsive desire...
due to loneliness?
(Episode 13)
You should go.
Don't rush...
leaving this place.
I mean,
look carefully before you decide.
Find a place that will treat you appropriately for what you offer.
Don't rush and accept less than you deserve.
What's wrong? Are you still up?
Jenny suddenly got a fever.
Jenny.
How bad is it?
I gave her medicine, but it won't go down.
Why weren't you picking up?
Where did you go?
I had a drink with Je Hyuk.
Sorry. I didn't hear it.
Let's go to the hospital first thing in the morning.
I'm going to get a cold towel.
Sorry, Jenny.
Daddy's sorry.
Let's forget this ever happened.
Wipe it from your memory.
I'll do the same.
It was a mistake for both of us.
It can never happen again.
I know.
I feel the same way.
I'm sorry for asking for a favor out of the blue like this.
Don't be sorry.
It is sudden though.
May I ask why?
Is something wrong?
No. I've gotten sick of Gosan, that's all.
So? Do you think there will be a position for me?
I'm sure plenty of places will want you.
Give me a little time. I'll make some calls.
Is there any place you're thinking of?
Anywhere is fine, as long as it isn't Gosan.
Okay. I'll be waiting for your call.
Joon Young.
You can't let in a minor at night.
I'm sorry, sir.
Are you trying to get us shut down?
What will you do if something goes wrong?
I'm sorry. I'll tell him to leave.
What? Hey.
Aren't you going to work?
What?
Jenny has to go to the hospital, and Joon Young has to go to school.
Yes, that's right.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
What about Joon Young?
Joon Young, are you ready to go?
Let's take my car today.
Have you seen Joon Young?
- Isn't he in there? - No.
Where were you?
I stepped out.
You'll be late.
Hurry up and get ready. Let's take my car today.
Joon Young.
Do you smoke?
No.
Okay. I'm glad you don't.
I trust you.
Why did you ask him that all of a sudden?
I could smell it. Didn't you?
You're not even sure. Did you have to ask when he has school?
I'm his guardian.
He didn't even tell us where he went...
so early in the morning either.
Of course, I should ask when I can smell it.
Let's take a look at your ear.
Good job.
Gosh, great job.
When did she take the fever reducer?
Two hours ago.
She went over 38°C last night.
My goodness.
Open wide. Good girl.
You're such a good girl.
That's it.
Make sure it doesn't develop into pneumonia.
- Keep your place humid. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Bye.
Joon Young, there's a flu going around.
Be careful not to catch it.
Your break is soon, right?
Won't you come visit me?
- Here you go. - Thank you.
(Keep Quiet)
Hey.
- What are you doing? - Hey.
- Nothing. - Let's go to the convenience store.
(Family Medicine Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
(Lee Tae Oh)
What is it?
Did you get to work okay?
Did you call to ask me that?
No.
I'm asking just out of curiosity.
Joon Young...
doesn't smoke, does he?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Don't you know how old he is?
I'd know if he did.
Right.
I didn't think he would either.
I only called...
for verification, so don't mind it.
Okay, you should go back to work.
This needs your approval today.
All of your appointments are finished for today.
Good work, Nurse An.
There's an opening in Busan.
What do you think?
I'm attaching the conditions in a separate file.
Take a look and let me know.
(Job opening for medical professor)
"Busan"?
No, I just think...
it's a bit too far.
The conditions aren't bad.
While we're on that, let me meet with Joon Young.
His break starts tomorrow, so I assume it'd be okay to meet.
He won't pick up my calls nor return them.
Okay. I'll speak to him.
Let's schedule it for tomorrow.
Okay. I'm hanging up.
By the way...
If Joon Young's not happy with it,
would you reconsider?
I'm talking about you leaving for Busan.
Of course.
His opinion is the most important to me.
It's been a while...
since you bought me flowers.
Whenever Jenny gets sick, it's always tough on you.
I feel sorry and thankful.
No matter the reason, it makes me happy.
She's playing well.
I'm glad it's not too serious.
She still needs to take her medication for a week.
You must be hungry. Let me make dinner.
Did Joon Young not come home yet?
He called to say he'd eat dinner with his friends.
Right.
About what you said this morning...
Joon Young doesn't smoke.
I think you made a mistake.
He can be grumpy,
but he wouldn't do anything bad.
I trust he doesn't do it if he says so.
Even if he does, we can just reason with him.
He's going through puberty.
Thank you.
You should pay more attention to him too.
Let's make dinner now.
Okay.
Jenny.
Did it hurt a lot?
In front of you.
- This makes me mad. - Hurry up and shoot.
Get up. Get up.
Watch it.
What are you doing?
Stop doing that.
Hey, kill that one.
- He's the ace. - I don't think so.
In the back. Back up.
In the middle, pick up the gun.
- Sorry. - Shoot again.
- Okay, okay. - What are you doing?
Hurry up. Come on.
Just go in.
- Just listen to me and throw it. - Me first.
How?
You're late.
I was hanging out with my friends.
I heard you're on a break starting tomorrow.
Let's go see your mom in the evening.
I think she has something to say to you.
About what?
I think she's planning to leave town,
but she wants to discuss it with you.
I'll bring Joon Young to your place tomorrow evening.
What's wrong? Does it taste bad?
I only followed the recipe.
No, it's not that bad.
Are those new clothes?
It's pretty. It suits you.
You always looked good in those colors.
It's too late.
I mean, it's too late for us.
I bought this three years ago.
And you want me to do what with you?
I don't want to make a fool of myself.
Let's stop, okay?
I know it's too late.
I missed so many opportunities to work things out.
But...
I don't want to end it like this.
We got married and got a divorce.
But we never dated each other.
We got married because our parents thought we'd be a good match.
So we just skipped everything...
and didn't get to know each other.
That's where it all went wrong.
I know this isn't the right order,
but I want to do everything I never got to do with you.
We can always end it after we try everything.
Okay?
I didn't know you could be so clingy.
- Is it annoying? - I'm not interested in this game.
I always thought...
my job was to earn you money.
I never once cleaned or cooked for you.
I didn't know this before, but I finally realized something.
All the stuff you did...
to quietly take care of me...
was what kept our marriage going.
I swear I don't think of this as a game.
I didn't know because I was indifferent and stupid.
And now, I want to do stuff...
that I never got to do for you.
You just need to take what I give.
Just think of it...
as a return on overdue mileage.
What's the worry?
You have nothing to lose.
You're all done.
Why? Are you not interested?
I'm not sure.
He's suddenly so different, so it's kind of scary.
And I'm worried I might be wasting my time.
- That's how I feel. - I think you still like him.
It's obvious how it'll end.
You should try everything you want before you die.
That way, you won't have any regrets.
Why don't you trust him this time?
I think he has finally learned his lesson.
How's my condition?
Last year, I was fine.
You said it felt like a period cramp, right?
It looks like a fibroid.
I don't think you need a biopsy.
It's nothing serious.
It's common at our age.
I thought it was due to stress, but I guess I'm not that healthy.
I'm starting to get depressed. I feel like I'm really getting old.
No one can beat time.
Let's see how it develops after you take your medicine.
If it doesn't get any bigger, you can just leave it.
It's almost time for lunch, isn't it?
- Okay, you can go now. - Thank you.
- Sun Woo. - What brings you here?
She's here to see you.
You're done with your morning consultations, right?
Let's eat lunch together.
I need to talk to you about something.
Judging from the look on your face, it sounds like it's good news.
I'm glad you're here. I also have something to tell you guys.
Have you made a decision?
Kind of.
Why don't I know what this is about?
Are you also seeing someone?
Did you get yourself a boyfriend?
Gosh, you're so lame.
Let's go. I'll tell you once we're there.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(Joon Young's homeroom teacher)
Hello?
Hello. How have you been?
Joon Young?
Okay, ma'am.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry. Let's talk next time.
Don't worry about it. You should go.
Oh, right. The director isn't here, so I didn't get to tell him.
- Can you talk to him for me? - I'll explain to him.
Don't worry. Take good care of Joon Young.
We're no longer married.
But when it comes to our child, we're always asked to come together.
Why is that?
How long...
does a married couple's connection last?
(A World of Married Couple)
I heard you guys got a divorce.
May I ask whom Joon Young is living with?
I'm sorry if I made you feel uncomfortable.
But I want to have an objective view of Joon Young's situation.
Right now, he's living with me.
I heard he fought with Hae Kang.
Did he get severely injured?
Joon Young only got a few scratches.
But Hae Kang's condition was a lot worse.
So his parents took him home.
Judging from how it looks, we think Joon Young might've...
beat him up unilaterally.
What are you talking about?
- Are you sure about that? - We'd like to talk to Joon Young.
According to the kids, Joon Young hit him first.
It happened at the basketball court after school ended.
So a lot of kids witnessed what happened.
Some kids even took videos.
Can we please meet Joon Young?
It's true. I hit him first.
Why did you hit him?
I'm sure you had a reason.
Aren't you going to tell us?
You need to tell us what happened, Joon Young.
Did Hae Kang talk badly about your mom again?
Is that why you hit him?
Tell me. What did he say?
I stole a bag of chips...
at the internet cafe.
And Hae Kang saw that.
He told me he'll tell everyone.
So I told him to go ahead.
What are you? A piece of trash?
- Live a decent life. - What did you say, you punk?
- What's going on? - Hey, stop.
- Hey, stop it. - Joon Young.
- Who do you think you are? - Hey, stop it.
That punk tried to lecture me, and it was annoying.
I think I just misheard something.
You stole what?
Okay, let's say you hit Hae Kang...
because you were angry.
But why did you steal?
Why would you do something like that?
It was a mistake.
You guys make mistakes, too.
Right?
Whatever the case, what you did was wrong.
You know you need to fix it until it's too late, right?
How do you fix a wrong that has already been done?
Isn't it too late?
You should apologize sincerely and ask for forgiveness...
from both Hae Kang and the Internet cafe owner.
Let's...
be calm and do one at a time.
The principal says...
they want to call a school violence hearing.
Shouldn't we meet with Hae Kang's parents first?
Why is everything so easy for you two?
Does apologizing make it forgivable?
Is that how it works for adults?
Joon Young. How could you say that?
We need to prevent the school violence hearing.
Let them do it.
- It doesn't matter. - Lee Joon Young.
I won't go to this school.
I'll drop out! Problem solved!
What's with that attitude?
How could you say you'll drop out?
We're not telling you to apologize no matter what.
Let's talk first...
about why you did it,
and what you want to do going forward.
Let's go to Mom's house and talk.
Why should I go there?
You can go if you want to.
Don't you want to go to my house?
No, I don't.
I have nothing more to say to you.
What was that about him smoking?
I just brushed it off that time,
but did something happen?
Actually, Da Kyung said...
she smelled cigarette smoke on him.
It was probably the internet cafe.
The smell gets on you if you're there for a while.
Maybe he doesn't feel at home in your house.
He didn't do this when he lived with me.
The most he did...
was skipping his academy.
He seems like a completely different kid.
Are you saying he developed problems after he came to me?
I'm asking if something happened that I don't know about.
How would I know when he won't talk?
What is it?
It's Do Chul.
Hae Kang is in the hospital.
They're going to get his medical record...
and request a school violence hearing.
What should we do?
Of course, I should know.
How's Hae Kang doing?
You must have been scared.
Anyway, thank you for calling me, madam.
Yes.
Okay, bye.
(Councilman Cha's Wife)
You're home late.
I scolded him for fighting with a friend, that's why.
I heard he hit Hae Kang.
I need to meet with his parents and talk to them.
Don't worry. I'll handle it.
Your stepping in and reconciling with them...
won't solve the problem.
Avoiding the school violence hearing isn't enough.
What about his stealing?
Does he even repent and admit what he did was wrong?
So? What do you want to do?
Do you want to punish him?
I'm sure it'll hurt right now,
but it may be better for Joon Young to receive proper punishment.
- Don't you agree? - He's going through puberty.
Everyone makes a mistake like that at his age.
It's not like he committed a serious crime.
I'm trying to talk some sense into him.
He's repenting plenty.
Do you really think this is just a teenage rebellion?
As long as things like this don't happen again, right?
How's Hae Kang?
May I see him and see how bad the injury is?
What good will it do if you see him?
I want to apologize to him first.
And to you too.
I'm very sorry.
You must think it was just a scuffle among kids...
that can be swept under the rug by the adults.
I'll bring Joon Young soon to apologize.
I thought it was only right that I apologize first.
I'm very sorry.
You.
Do you think I'm using the situation with the kids...
for personal reasons?
What do you take me for?
That is not what I mean.
My child did something heinously wrong,
and Hae Kang was hurt.
I know nothing can compensate you,
but I'll pay the medical bills...
and as much compensation as you want.
That's only proper.
Do you think I'm a beggar? I'm so annoyed.
They were close since childhood. I don't know how this happened.
It breaks my heart.
Madam.
Please find it in your heart to forgive Joon Young.
This will never happen again.
You know...
he's not like that.
"He's not like that"?
Sure.
There are parents who mistakenly think they know their kids.
Did he tell you why he hit him?
My son was worried about your son and gave him some advice.
That was why he hit him.
Yes,
I heard.
It's my fault. I taught him wrong.
Like teaching him would have any effect.
You don't think this was the first time he stole, do you?
I heard things kept going missing from inside the classroom.
Did you know that?
You're a doctor, so you should know.
Kleptomania requires treatment.
Shouldn't you take him to the hospital?
Do you have proof?
All the kids in the class suspect Joon Young.
Actually, from what I can tell, I think they're convinced it's him.
How do you know so little about your son, Dr. Ji?
I officially apologize for him hitting Hae Kang,
but don't accuse him of things he did not do.
We won't condone that either.
And if you don't?
What will you do?
What are you going to do about it?
You're here to apologize, and you're threatening me?
Don't even dream about settling.
We'll follow the directions of the School Violence Committee,
so you and your son...
better be ready for it.
You don't think this was the first time he stole, do you?
How do you know so little about your son, Dr. Ji?
Are you feeling sick?
I'll register you for just English and math, okay?
Good night, son.
What about me?
Why do I have to live like this?
It's not like I did anything wrong.
I'm sorry?
What did you just say?
It doesn't cost that much for a bag of chips.
You don't have to worry about compensating me.
But you should guide him well so he doesn't sleep out.
I understand earning money is important,
but I'm a parent too.
I kick out all underaged kids when it turns 10pm.
I think my employee forgot about it that day.
Your son rushed out in the morning.
Hey kid.
Your father came here with you to apologize,
so you should live well.
Also, don't forget I have security cameras here.
Gosh.
I'm really sorry.
Was it that day when we saw you come in the morning?
You didn't step out for a moment.
Were you there all night?
I fell asleep.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Why did you go out so late without saying a thing?
I heard you...
talking about sending me abroad to study.
I left because I didn't want to hear it.
I didn't want to be home.
I won't send you abroad if you don't want to go.
I don't want to send you far away either.
Da Kyung didn't mean anything by it.
She only said that for your benefit, so don't be offended.
Let's not...
tell Mom about this. It'll make her worry.
Are you worried Mom would worry?
Why did you hit Mom back then?
It's over already.
You two saw each other's bitter ends.
Why are you seeing her again now?
Why are you living such a complicated life?
Aren't you two strangers since you got a divorce?
Although we got divorced,
you're still our son.
A couple can part ways, but not a parent and a child.
It must be the toughest on you,
but it's your mom and dad who love you the most.
Are you making me an excuse again?
Don't you think it's cowardice?
What I initially saw in Joon Young was hatred.
He was scratching Chairman Yeo's car.
This whole thing started...
because of the divorce, right?
It won't be helpful to try and find an answer from the past.
If you want to fix it, it's best to look at the present.
The date for the school violence hearing has been set.
It'd be best if you could settle before then.
Have you met with Hae Kang's family?
Don't be late tomorrow to see Hae Kang at the hospital.
Hello, madam. It's me, Yeo Da Kyung.
How's Hae Kang doing?
I'm glad to hear that.
Yes.
I called because of that.
Maybe you should stay outside.
You don't have a great relationship with Hae Kang's mother.
That's why I should be the one to solve this.
Don't worry, Joon Young.
I'll take care of this, okay?
We're here.
Thanks for making time for us.
Sorry, Do Chul.
I should've taught him better.
It's normal for boys to fight sometimes.
Honey.
The doctor told us he could've fractured his facial bone.
How could you take it so lightly?
I'm sorry.
I'll teach Joon Young well and make sure...
he doesn't do this again.
I hope so.
I'm very worried about him as a fellow parent.
If people could turn better after a few scoldings,
judges and police officers...
wouldn't need to exist in this world.
I'm sorry, madam.
Joon Young.
We'd like to hear what you think.
I'm sorry.
I won't hit you again.
Whatever.
I want you to apologize for treating me like a psycho.
You were always a jerk,
but you weren't a loose cannon.
You never used to sleep outside...
or steal stuff.
I told you to stop living that way and to live a proper life...
because I was worried.
But you told me you never did any of that...
and that I'm lying.
You treated me like an idiot.
Tell him you're sorry.
I guess he's not ready to sincerely apologize.
You guys can go home.
I'm sorry, Hae Kang.
Will you please forgive him...
for my sake?
I'd also like to apologize...
to both you and your husband.
What are you doing? You're making us feel uncomfortable.
Please get up.
We'll make sure...
Joon Young doesn't do this again.
I apologize to you from the bottom of my heart.
Hello, madam.
Councilman Cha, you're here too.
My goodness, Da Kyung.
Hae Kang seemed to like this.
You didn't have to come all the way here.
You're too kind.
It's nothing compared to how upset you must've felt.
Hae Kang.
Did you talk with Joon Young?
I'm really sorry.
Ms. Ji.
Will you please leave?
What are you doing? You're making things awkward for all of us.
People might think we made you kneel on the floor or something.
Will you please leave already?
When people are really sorry,
they have trouble finding words to express themselves.
Joon Young is very sorry about what he did to you.
Right, Joon Young?
I'm at fault for what happened.
I suggested that Joon Young should study abroad.
But that must've upset him a lot.
Joon Young got upset because of what I said.
But if you even call a school violence hearing,
I'd feel way too guilty about what I did to Joon Young.
It'll upset Tae Oh as well.
Please forgive Joon Young for my sake.
Tae Oh and I will talk to him so that he doesn't do this again.
Gosh, we never expected you to apologize like this.
My parents are also very worried about Joon Young.
And they're very concerned that you and your husband...
have to go through this.
It was just a fight between kids.
You don't need to be so worried. We're friends.
Thanks. We were able to sort things out thanks to you.
Joon Young.
I'm not that hard to talk to.
So if anything bothers you, feel free to talk to me about it...
like a friend.
We'll only feel comfortable if you feel comfortable.
The test results will be out in about 2 to 3 days.
Okay.
Go home safely.
- Okay, thank you. - No problem.
How many more patients are there?
Two more, sir.
It must be tiring to treat patients since it's been quite a while.
It's not that I'm tired.
I had important plans that I had to suddenly cancel.
That's why.
- Golf? - A hospital directors' gathering.
That's golf.
When will Dr. Ji be back?
She's only out today.
Her son's future is at stake. Be patient.
Did I say anything?
- Send in the next patient. - Yes, doctor.
You took the afternoon off.
Why did you come in?
I'm sorry for causing you concern.
I'll see the afternoon patients.
Okay. You do that.
Don't worry. I explained everything to Dr. Kong.
- Thanks. - I heard Da Kyung fixed it.
You know Councilman Cha's wife is a big mouth.
Everyone knows already.
Dr. Ji.
Can you see a patient right away?
Sure. Okay.
Let's talk later.
What do you think?
When did the stomachache start?
It started a while ago,
but it has been getting worse recently.
You said it feels like gas at times, right?
Yes.
Actually, I was diagnosed with irritable bowel syndrome before.
Do you think that's it?
You get constipated and have diarrhea often.
It does look like irritable bowel syndrome.
I'll prescribe some medicine for now.
Come back if it doesn't improve.
- Any chance you're pregnant? - No.
Although I am pretty irregular.
We're done. Pick up your prescription.
Thank you.
Don't just accept that your periods are irregular.
You should see a gynecologist.
Okay, I will. Thank you.
Doctor. We have several patients backed up.
Can you see patients after hours today?
We'll tell some to come tomorrow if you're too tired.
Sure. I'll make up for what I missed.
- But give me 10 minutes. - Yes, doctor.
Are you sure?
Maybe you're mistaken.
I'm sure.
I'm sure Sun Woo knows too.
That's why she got on her knees in front of Councilman Cha's wife.
I made sure Hae Kang's family won't say anything about it, but...
I think we should keep a close eye on Joon Young.
I'm too ashamed...
to face you.
I'll feel terrible if Joon Young goes down the wrong path.
I feel responsible too.
He needs to grow up well so I can stand tall too.
Don't you agree?
Thanks. But Da Kyung,
let me be the one feeling guilty.
Don't you feel guilty too.
I'll feel too bad...
if you do.
I was prepared for that much when we brought him here.
So trust me and let me handle everything regarding Joon Young.
Okay.
Thanks.
- Here you go. - I'll take that, thank you.
I can't stand having my life so complicated and annoying.
Everything will be simpler if you're gone.
That would be the best for Dad too.
You should leave.
Go where you want.
I'm fine.
(CEO Lee Tae Oh)
(Sun Woo)
Aren't you leaving?
I should.
It looks like Ye Rim and Je Hyuk are getting back together.
He's being sincere.
He turned over a new leaf.
I thought they would.
That's good.
- It's a good thing, right? - What about you?
What about me?
You said you had something to tell us.
Ye Rim seemed to know generally what it's about.
What is it?
I...
may leave Gosan.
What?
I'll tell Dr. Kong when the time is right.
I'll train my successor...
so the hospital isn't harmed, so don't worry.
I'm not worried about that.
What about you?
Can you be apart from Joon Young?
That's what he wants.
Why?
I don't know why he's pushing me away.
How did you feel when your parents got divorced?
I don't know.
I was angry at both of them.
I wondered why the adults were acting that way.
I was confused.
The funny thing is,
if they didn't keep in touch, I got mad at that.
But if they did once in a while, I'd get mad that they were in touch.
You were angry at them both.
Things were complicated and you were confused.
Okay.
If that's what it is,
it's probably best if I leave the picture.
Sorry. I'm going to leave first.
(Tae Oh)
(CEO Lee Tae Oh)
(Sun Woo)
Hey, what's up?
Let's meet right now.
I need to talk to you.
I need...
to tell you something before I leave.
I know...
it wasn't the first time Joon Young stole something.
You do?
How did you know?
Da Kyung told me.
She spoke to Councilman Cha's wife.
Don't worry.
- We'll take care of it well. - How will you take care of it?
We'll reason with him.
We hurt him a lot,
so we should trust him and wait for him.
Kleptomania...
isn't something that simple.
I know what you're nervous about,
but just leave it to us now.
I'll raise...
Joon Young properly...
to become someone right and strong.
I'll raise him to become...
someone happy.
Are you confident you can raise him well without me?
Yes.
What is that about Joon Young not going home for a night?
Is it true what Hae Kang said?
It was the day...
I was with you.
Why is it so easy for you and Mom?
Does apologizing make it forgivable?
Is that how it works for adults?
It's over already.
You two saw each other's bitter ends.
Why are you seeing her again now?
Why are you living such a complicated life?
Aren't you two strangers since you got a divorce?
Are you making me an excuse again?
Don't you think it's cowardice?
No way...
Could he have...
No, that's impossible.
Where's Joon Young right now?
Go ahead. Didn't you say you have something to talk about?
About...
when you slept over at the internet cafe...
What about it?
Did you...
come to me that day?
Did you?
Yes.
(A World of Married Couple)
Dr. Ji disappeared?
You were hurt because of what the adults did.
I'm responsible for half of it.
Can't you give him some time?
He needs some time to breathe.
Let's trust him and wait.
Aren't you tired yet?
No, I'm happy.
We're really a family now.
You know what I mean, don't you?
What's making you so anxious?
What I can't stand...
is that my child hates me.
Whether it's hatred or resentment,
you should respect Joon Young's feelings.
Did something happen to Sun Woo?
I said, where's Sun Woo right now?