(A World of Married Couple)
(All characters, organizations,
places, and events are fictional.)
I love you.
You know that, don't you?
Yes.
I know.
My son, my house,
and my life.
I'm not going to lose anything that's mine.
I'll just carve Lee Tae
Oh out from my life.
Your house is set as collateral,
and it's even registered under
your husband's enterprise.
I have to say, you have quite a big dream.
I'll do whatever it takes...
to return it back to normal.
If he already registered it
under someone else's name,
you might not be able
to save a single penny.
Okay then.
What comes next is very important.
The best strategy for a divorce
is to keep this confidential.
You can't let your husband find
out, so control your emotions.
You need to fool him properly.
If you can't even do that,
you'll just have to live with it.
Do you think Joon Young's sad as well?
He really liked his grandmother.
And it's his first time witnessing
the death of someone close.
I'll take care of Joon
Young, so don't worry.
You should just focus on yourself.
Don't overwork yourself either.
I'm worried you might lose your health.
I'm sorry...
for doubting you and pressuring you...
thinking that you were cheating on me.
I think it's because I love you too much.
You know how married couples
can be after a while.
I guess I wanted to check
how much you love me.
Just a second.
I'm sorry. It's my patient.
I'm becoming friends with her so
that she doesn't get suspicious.
We both frequently visit
each other's houses.
(A World of Married Couple)
I heard you were very
close to Chairman Yeo,
so I trusted his recommendation.
(Episode 4)
The STD test came back positive.
Take the antibiotics
diligently, and it'll be fine.
At this age?
I'm mortified.
There's no need.
It's a common illness among adults.
It is, right?
So... You...
don't get it only through that, right?
Do you mean sex?
Well, you can get it because
your immune system is weakened...
from fatigue or stress.
And you can catch it from
others in a sauna or at a spa,
right, doctor?
You're sure I can trust that doctor, right?
You saw her ask me to
take care of her husband.
She's very quick,
so she'll know not to make problems.
Don't worry.
What?
It is very unlikely it was caught
through something other than sex.
It's almost a 99 percent probability...
that it was through sex.
It'll be fine. Calm down.
She's done.
(Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
Did the doctor explain everything...
Honey.
Thank you for explaining everything.
I'm a doctor.
I have a clear duty to tell a patient...
about the cause and
treatment of an illness.
I don't know why you thought I'd lie
to cover up your friend's cheating.
If you're done with business
here, have a nice day.
Sure. I...
misread you, Dr. Ji.
What?
Chairman Yeo. Da Kyung's dad.
He's with Sun Woo right now.
They're talking very seriously.
I don't know what about.
Your conviction as a doctor. Sure.
I apologize if I hurt your pride,
but you're a married woman
before you're a doctor.
Depending on the situation,
it could've been much
better to keep it a secret.
I don't know.
I can't condone secrets
between a husband and wife.
Are you saying you know
everything about your husband?
That's right.
I know everything about my husband.
He doesn't know how to keep secrets.
I never knew he was so whipped.
That's right. Your daughter...
is seeing someone.
Oh dear. I didn't mean to
expose your daughter's secret.
They seemed very serious,
so I assumed the family knew.
She would've told us if that were the case.
Da Kyung is naive because she
always had a sheltered life,
but she's a smart girl.
Not as smart as you, of course.
- Have a nice day.
- You too.
- Mr. Chairman.
- Hi.
Hello.
- How was the burial?
- It was nice, thank you.
- Chin up.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Have a nice day.
What are you doing here?
Well... I was in the area.
What did you and the chairman talk about?
Why won't you answer us?
Who is he?
Bring him home.
Let us meet him.
Don't bother.
We're only dating.
Someone saw you.
- They said it looked serious.
- Who saw us?
Okay, then.
If it isn't serious, end it.
I'll find you a nice guy,
so behave and wait for us to set you up.
No.
What's wrong with you?
You insisted on moving out,
so I persuaded Dad for you.
But you let yourself be the subject
of gossip that you're dating.
You're making me look bad.
You know how scary Dad is when he gets mad.
I'm an adult.
Please respect my personal life.
Dad.
If you won't be set up, move back home.
Nothing good comes of a
girl living alone, kid.
But... You look like you gained weight.
Go on a diet.
Hi, Mom.
- You must be tired.
- I'm fine.
Dad.
Hey!
- Dad!
No Eul!
Do you want a ride home?
Thank you.
Isn't it hard raising a child
alone after getting a divorce?
What choice do I have?
Everyone struggles and does
what they can to survive.
Isn't she anxious about living apart...
from her dad?
I think she got used to it now.
She doesn't really ask for him.
Thank you for the ride.
Mi Yun.
Yes?
You know why I went to
the office that night,
don't you?
I'm sorry,
but I'm not sure what you're talking about.
I see.
I'm sorry for wasting your time.
I better get going.
That's not what I meant.
I said, let's break up. Just leave!
Get out!
I saw your husband leave.
I think they had a fight.
I'll look into the details.
Are you upset about something?
Not really. I just want a drink.
What on earth were you thinking?
You know,
I'm not saying this because
the donation was pulled out.
You should've sugarcoated it
to avoid shocking your patient.
The patient wanted to know.
His wife was my patient.
Exactly.
Didn't you know she's the wife of
our hospital's biggest sponsor?
I think...
making your doctor's conscience
the reason is overdoing it.
To be honest, I know you relate to her.
She was cheated on by her husband.
As an onlooker,
I think you're taking big risks.
The one who's taking risks is you.
What?
I know you're a double spy.
How much longer will you keep it up?
(Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
I doubt I have to worry about you,
but a hospital is a place
where many people frequent.
I came here out of concern.
You know Gosan is a small place, don't you?
Please make sure...
no one hears about our family's issue.
I wouldn't leak personal details.
Please don't worry about that.
Do you...
resent me?
Would it have been better...
if you didn't know?
I'm not getting a divorce.
People who don't know anything...
will assume I'm living with
it for my husband's money,
but we spend so many years together.
Money can't be the only thing between us.
Will you be able to forgive him...
for the rest of your life relying
on the time you've spent with him?
He just...
fooled around with a woman once.
There's nothing to forgive.
For men,
sex is like excretion.
I'm the person who turned
him into the man he is today.
His background, wealth,
and even his personality.
I can't let a divorce...
waste all the time and effort...
I've spent on him.
Please pick up your phone.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. Something came up at work.
My staff can't handle it themselves.
- At this hour?
- I'm sorry.
Don't wait up for me and go to bed.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
He just left. Can you check for me?
I'm sorry, but I think I have to go home.
- Okay, take care.
- I'm sorry.
(Recording)
Hyun Seo.
You have a car...
and a place.
Good for you.
Did you get yourself a rich old man?
What are you doing?
It's over between us.
Is that what you thought?
That's too bad because I'm not done.
Get lost.
Hyun Seo.
That crazy woman turned out to be
a hospital's associate director.
It's her, isn't it?
What's going on between you two?
Are you two dating?
She's just a doctor who treated me.
My life has nothing to do with
her, so mind your own business.
Just get out of my life.
Are you crazy?
The receiver cannot be reached.
Did something go wrong?
Why won't you pick up?
(Lee Tae Oh)
Hello?
Hey, why are you still up?
You left in a hurry, so I got worried.
How did it go?
We took care of what was urgent,
but it's going to take
us some time to wrap up.
Do you need to work all night?
I think so.
You're working so hard.
Get some rest when you can.
Okay, thanks.
I love you.
Me too.
(Did something go wrong?
Why won't you pick up?)
Sun Woo!
Sun Woo.
What are you thinking about?
You didn't even hear me call you.
Just some miscellaneous stuff.
Are you coming home from work?
- Is something bothering you?
- No.
I just came out for a run.
I saw you seeing what you saw.
At the parking lot.
You caught me.
Tae Oh got caught...
at the worst place and time.
What am I supposed to do now?
How can I help you?
Is getting a divorce the right thing to do?
I'm not sure.
I feel like our family will be fine
if I just turn a blind eye to it.
But I don't know if I can live
like that for the rest of my life.
I'm starting to question my entire life.
And I wonder...
if I'm no longer attractive as a woman.
That's nonsense.
This is absurd.
I can't believe I'm telling you this.
You can talk to me anytime.
If you want, we can get
some drinks at a nearby bar.
Maybe next time.
Thanks, Je Hyuk.
You're late.
Yes, I'm tired.
Did you eat dinner?
Yes, of course. It's way past dinner time.
- You did great.
- Thank you.
Come back in two weeks.
Make sure you keep a
controlled diet until then.
- Okay, thank you.
- No problem.
- Go home safely.
- Bye.
I'm here to meet Dr. Ji Sun Woo.
I heard she's an associate...
There she is.
Should we go inside?
Or do you want to talk here?
Let's go inside.
I heard you're looking for this.
Where is Min Hyun Seo?
Why do you want to know?
You just worry about this.
This has your husband
going into that house.
I want a deal.
Got that?
This is a hospital.
- What are you doing?
- Exactly.
Who'd be hurt more if
I start screaming here?
What do you want?
20,000 dollars?
No?
Then 30,000 dollars.
I have no money to give a dirtbag like you.
Have it ready next week...
unless you want everyone to
know you hired someone...
to tail your husband.
Is Hyun Seo...
safe?
Why? Do you think I
locked her up somewhere?
Hyun Seo says...
she hates you.
She says she wants to take
that money and end it.
One week.
You said you could
definitely get the evidence.
What happened?
You don't seem capable of
leading the fight in this war.
At this rate,
you'll be worse off if you get divorced.
Doctor.
What is it?
Your husband must have sent these.
(You are an amazing woman)
Do you like the gift?
Why did you send me this?
Let's just say a friend is
sending you some comfort.
Don't read too much into it.
It's client management too.
Regardless, Tae Oh is my client after all.
Thanks anyway.
You know, I don't think too much
when things are complicated.
I don't decide with my brain.
Things don't go as planned anyway.
There's no answer in life.
It's not bad to follow your
heart and go with the flow.
Have you ever been...
betrayed by someone close to you?
Do you trust your husband?
(Family Medicine Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
The ECG and endocrine
function were all normal.
The allergy test...
didn't show anything unusual.
Even you can't find the cause.
I think it's more psychological,
rather than physical.
I'd recommend seeing a psychiatrist...
I know my illness.
I don't need that.
Just give me my usual meds.
Most people mistakenly think
they know their own problems.
Don't do that.
Why don't you get help from a professional?
What about you, doctor?
You have the same symptoms I do.
- Mr. Ha Dong Shik.
- Don't try to handle it alone.
Get help from a professional.
Raise your feet and look at the ceiling.
Lift your spine.
Straight up.
Keep your core engaged.
Back to the resting position.
Look straight ahead.
Lift your knee slightly...
and push your leg back.
Push it back slowly.
Look straight ahead.
Pull your shoulders back
and make your hip straight.
Hold that position and push back.
Not too quickly. Push back slowly.
Relax your shoulders.
Keep your hips straight.
Back up.
One more time.
I have three older sisters,
so...
I can tell by looking from
behind when someone's pregnant.
- So?
- I wondered if that was it...
when I heard this would be your last week.
I'm a bit dumbfounded.
I don't know what you mean,
but if you have a problem with my
quitting, get a refund.
I let things be with you...
only because you were Director Lee's toy.
But this changes things.
I can't keep quiet anymore.
Tell her. As much as you want.
That's what I want too.
But you won't be able to.
You were an accomplice, but now,
you act like you're a loyal friend?
It's laughable.
Do you think she'd back off
that easily even if she knew?
She'd probably let you have a baby alone...
and ruin your life.
Haven't you ever thought that
Sun Woo may know everything...
and is playing dumb?
And Director Lee is dragging his heels.
There's no cure for stupidity.
Should we go out for dinner?
Why don't we go somewhere
nice to cheer ourselves up?
I'll text you the address. See you later.
Okay.
What is it?
I guess you're going somewhere nice.
Have we not heard from the investor yet?
Why do you have so many questions today?
Sorry, sir.
You know...
why I went to the office that night,
don't you?
(Lee Tae Oh: Pairing restaurant address...)
Da Kyung, get in.
What brought you here?
You didn't tell me you were coming.
What do you mean?
I came because I missed you.
You saw me now, so you should go.
- I'm busy.
- Hey.
How can I leave after seeing you so gloomy?
Get in. Let's go shopping.
I have to buy clothes too. Hurry.
Come on, honey.
Come on.
Hey, what do you think?
Did it look good on me?
Are you sure you don't want
that clothing from earlier?
I'll buy it for you.
Forget it. I don't need it.
I think it'd look perfect on
you if you lose a little weight.
Stop saying that.
Gosh. That's so cute.
How adorable. Gosh.
Hello.
- Hello, Mrs. Yeo.
- Hello.
Hello.
How pretty.
Hey, come here. Help me pick out something.
Why are you buying this?
Is someone pregnant?
My friend's son who is in
college knocked up a girl.
My friend's becoming a grandma next month.
How immature, right?
Those 20-year-old kids were so fearless.
Not only is she becoming a grandma,
but she has to raise the kid too.
I feel sorry for her.
Just choose one so we can go.
Hey. I don't want to
become a grandma too soon.
Make sure you remember it, okay?
Excuse me, could you wrap this up?
Sure.
This looks nice.
Why didn't you wait inside?
Well?
Isn't it nice to come out after so long?
Joon Young, you must be excited.
I'm happy to skip cooking.
Are you excited to eat good food?
I'm not a kid.
I don't get excited by such a thing.
Then why are you excited?
It's been so long since the three
of us came to a place like this.
Anyway,
it looks nice.
You have a high standard.
Of course, I booked the
hottest restaurant for us.
Let's go in.
Gosh.
Dr. Ji.
Fancy running into you.
Did you have a meal here?
We came without a reservation,
and they didn't have any tables.
We were just leaving.
I see. Take care.
Why don't you join us, then?
We have a reservation.
Gosh. I don't want to be a nuisance.
I wasn't sure how I could thank you...
for your condolences.
If you're okay with it, please join us.
Shall we?
My husband is about to arrive,
so we were worried too.
Would that be okay, honey?
Sure.
Yes.
Honey, over here.
How's your dating life?
Are you okay?
Da Kyung is very social.
She has many friends.
That's why many people mistake her,
but she says she doesn't have a boyfriend.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Perhaps I heard wrong.
I have to do my homework. I'll leave first.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
We'll leave first.
His dad loves him so much.
No matter where they go,
they always stick side by side.
A son is special to a dad.
Since Director Lee is so handsome,
I bet many actresses made moves on him.
Of course. There were many of them.
But Tae Oh is really
faithful to his family.
Should anything ever happen,
I believe...
it's nothing more than
an excretion for men.
You're right. All men make mistakes.
Chairman Choi's wife decided
to look over his mistake too.
He promised to give her a building.
Hello?
If you're a doctor,
you should watch what you say.
Don't you know you have to
protect a patient's privacy?
You told me he'd get a
divorce in two months...
and have the baby with you.
I thought you introduced
him to your parents.
I'm sorry if I put you in
an uncomfortable situation.
(Min Hyun Seo)
Who is it?
It's me.
Hyun Seo.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
But can I stay at your place for a while?
I made up my mind.
I decided to have an abortion.
I'm not financially stable.
And I don't have any
parents who can help me out.
All I do is get beaten
up by the baby's father.
I don't deserve to have a baby.
My baby will only end up
with a miserable life.
Don't look at me that way.
I feel a lot better now
that I've made up my mind.
My life is just as important to me.
I don't want this baby to hold me back.
I envy you.
You don't need to worry
about this kind of stuff.
You have parents whom you can lean on.
And you're going to get married soon.
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
To be honest,
my boyfriend is actually married.
What am I going to do?
This is driving me crazy.
But you said he told you that
he's going to get divorced soon.
He told me that he wants to get
divorced as soon as possible.
He told me he can't stand her.
But the problem is his wife.
She's brazen enough to stay
married even if she finds out...
about her husband's affair.
What kind of woman is she?
She looks down on people
and belittles them.
She's extremely arrogant.
He must hate living with a woman like her.
Well, he told me he doesn't
feel sexually attracted to her.
He only sleeps with her
every once in a while...
because he feels like he needs to.
But I'm not even surprised.
She's too old now.
It's late. You've done enough.
Aren't you tired?
I'm almost done.
I'm going to go upstairs.
(Min Hyun Seo)
(Son Je Hyuk)
Did you find an answer to your question?
No, not yet.
Are you free tomorrow?
Why don't we get a drink?
Where's your mom?
Eat fruit. Stop eating chips.
Don't you think your
lips are a bit too red?
Does it look weird?
No, I'm just saying.
What do you think, honey?
Aren't you going to a workshop?
I think it's a bit too much.
I haven't gone out in a while,
so I dolled myself up a little.
But neither of you seem impressed.
It is a bit too much,
but that doesn't mean you look bad.
I cooked dinner for you guys.
You just need to heat it up.
Okay.
Hey, I heard he's
transferring to another team.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Gosh, that's a pity.
- He was pretty good.
My gosh.
- I can't believe he's leaving.
- It's all about the money.
You came here early.
You look nice today.
But then again, you always look nice.
Can I also have some wine?
I never even imagined...
What?
Being at a place like this alone with you.
But?
It's not so bad.
It's just "not so bad"?
I'll have to step it up.
Why do people cheat?
There are two types of men in this world.
The ones who cheat and
the ones who get caught.
We can't overcome our instincts.
Men aren't...
the only ones with instincts.
My new place is still being renovated,
so I'm staying at a
hotel for the time being.
Yes.
I'll see you at the hospital soon.
Okay.
- Thank you.
That's absurd.
Why don't you believe me?
That was totally because I was jealous.
Men are all about establishing
a line of command.
No one makes it obvious,
but I know what Tae Oh's position is...
among his friends.
What made you lose it that day...
was the anxiety stemming from
the long-established line...
being threatened.
Saying it was because
of me is just an excuse.
Don't you agree?
You're too good...
for a jerk like Tae Oh.
You knew, didn't you?
That I like you.
I had an inkling.
And yet, you came today.
This isn't such a bad way
to get revenge on Tae Oh.
You can refuse.
It's your choice.
(Bird's Hill Hotel Parkade)
That's hilarious.
Why are you here?
Why didn't you just call me?
Let's break up.
What happened yesterday
was out of my control.
- Just calm down.
- I got rid of the baby.
What?
Are you happy?
We don't have to see each
other anymore, right?
Are you leaving already?
I was hoping to do it one more time.
I should get ready for work.
It's 4am.
I have a family, you know.
Gosh. You really ruined the mood.
Do you...
want to tell Ye Rim or should I?
Tell her what?
Should I tell Tae Oh then?
If you want, go ahead.
But...
you don't have any intention
of breaking up with Ye Rim.
If you want revenge, get it from Tae Oh.
Women are faithful not because
they don't know how to cheat.
They just refrain from doing
so because they believe...
having trust in each other
as a couple is important.
That's why it would be best for
you to stop living like this.
Bring me T.O. Entertainment's
corporate account statement,
as well as Tae Oh's personal account.
Research all of them and
pass them over to me.
Are you...
threatening me right now?
Yes.
You shouldn't try to do
everything on your own.
You should get a professional's help.
I found this at the restaurant
on your husband's birthday.
It'll be helpful to you.
(Family Medicine Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
Use your own fork.
- Fine.
- Hey, it's my dad.
Wait. I have to shoot him.
If you don't believe me,
I'll tell your father about us right now.
Are you crazy?
My son, my house,
and my life.
I'm not going to lose anything that's mine.
I'll just carve Lee Tae
Oh out from my life.
(A World of Married Couple)
He's our newest psychiatrist.
I'm Kim Yoon Ki.
Don't you feel like Sun Woo changed?
She's acting strange.
Didn't things get resolved...
after you sent her the
flower basket last time?
Tae Oh doesn't know yet, does it?
Don't worry. I haven't said anything yet.
You should sort things out with that man.
Don't let him drag you around.
I guess your parents don't
know you're pregnant, Da Kyung.
That's why you should never
try to take what's not yours.
Were you always so vulgar?
If you decided to have
fun with another woman,
you should've been sure enough
to never see your son again.
I couldn't help it.
It's not a crime to fall in love!