All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.
We had to be perfect.
“I will not get swayed no matter how hard it gets.”
I told myself that over and over again.
The joys of life.
The sorrows and the pain.
Happiness.
Because we should share them all...
since we're married.
Because he's my counterpart with whom I share my fate.
Because I shouldn't waver no matter what happens.
But now...
What is this woman saying?
Tae Oh...
slept with me.
I told you, didn't I?
That nothing precluded you from becoming like me.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you think I believe you?
You're trying to ruin our family before you leave.
Should I tell you what color underwear he was wearing that day?
I don't lie.
It's up to you...
whether or not you believe me.
You're so cheap.
You're a dirty harlot.
Aren't you ashamed to face Joon Young?
It was the night Joon Young left home and slept...
at the internet cafe.
What happened?
What about Joon Young?
I saw him off.
That's fine.
I'm sorry...
for causing a scene.
You and Dad should go.
We'll go after Tae Oh comes home.
Yes. We can't leave you alone.
I'm fine.
It's late. You should go.
You look terrible right now.
Did that woman say something strange?
This isn't the first time she acted strangely.
It doesn't bother me.
I'll just ignore her.
What did she say?
I said, nothing.
I want to rest.
Please go home. Okay?
(Episode 15)
I'm hungry.
Should we eat something?
Snap out of it, idiot.
So many people are hurting because of you.
How much more must they suffer?
You piece of trash.
Sorry.
Where's Joon Young?
Where's...
What happened?
Did you sleep with her?
With Sun Woo.
Answer wisely...
if you don't want to repeat the same mistake twice.
Everything...
depends on your answer.
Will you tell the truth or lie to me?
If you tell the truth, I will resent you for the rest of my life,
but if you lie,
I'll never forgive you.
But, I can't forgive lies.
Lying would be truly betraying me.
So be honest with me.
Are you seeing another woman?
You choose which would be worse.
I heard it was the night Joon Young left home.
The night I was up all night because Jenny had a fever.
The night you lied to me, saying you were with Je Hyuk!
I called countless times because our baby was sick,
but you were doing that with that woman?
- Did Sun Woo say that?
Did you sleep with her?
Did you?
Yes.
What's the deal with you two?
It was...
a mistake.
It meant nothing to me. It was just a mistake.
That's all. Nothing more.
It was a mistake I never want to make again.
She won't be here anymore.
She's leaving.
She handed in her resignation already.
Stop letting her bother you, Da Kyung.
Who cares where she is...
when it's you I can't trust!
I trusted you...
when she said you were stalking her.
Even when I saw your phone full of her pictures,
I still trusted you.
When she became your alibi at the police station,
I thought...
she did it because you're her son's dad.
I thought she did it for Joon Young.
But I get it now.
You two are still attached to each other.
You, and that woman too.
All that woman cares about is ruining me.
Why would she share such an embarrassing thing with you?
She's trying to break us apart!
Don't let her words mislead you.
You're the only one I want to protect.
I tried to make her leave because I want to be happy with you.
And finally, it's happening!
Is that why you slept with her?
To make her leave town?
Do you expect me to believe that?
We loved, married,
and raised you together.
The person I spent the most of my life with...
is your dad.
We fought terribly...
and parted ways because we couldn't live together anymore,
but it wasn't just hatred we had for each other.
Just like how you missed him,
I missed my husband too,
although it was only for a short moment.
It's normal to feel confused and betrayed.
I'm so sorry.
I'm okay with it even if you continue to hate me.
I'll still remain by your side to support and protect you.
What I want...
is for you to cherish yourself. That's all.
You're different from your parents.
You can live differently.
Just remember that,
okay?
I'm sure the whole school knows...
that I'm a thief.
It'll be tough,
but you can fight through it. You have me.
I'll protect you by your side.
Let's get through this together, okay?
Can't we just leave?
Let's go somewhere no one knows us.
Are you okay with never seeing your dad again?
Yes.
I don't want to see him ever again.
Okay.
Let's go, wherever it is.
Give me just a few days to get things organized.
Okay?
(A World of Married Couple)
Thank you for telling me the truth.
I bet it wasn't easy.
Does Joon Young know what happened...
between the two of you?
I feel sorry for him.
I won't let...
Jenny become like Joon Young.
I'm not like that woman.
I don't want to act crazy and hit rock bottom.
I know I can overcome this.
I'll make sure to overcome it even if just for Jenny.
I'll get through it...
with you.
Da Kyung.
But give me some time.
- I need time.
Take as much as you need.
Take your time.
I'll wait.
Also, I'll try my best too.
Eat your breakfast.
Thank you.
The soup is delicious.
Good.
Enjoy it.
I'm going to check up on Jenny.
Okay.
Come here.
Jenny.
I'll see you after work.
I'll see you.
Okay.
I don't want to meet him.
Stay in your room.
Where's Joon Young?
Tell me what you need to say. I'll make sure to let him know.
I'm here to apologize. I want to do it face to face.
He doesn't want to see you.
Joon Young.
Joon Young!
What are you doing? I said he doesn't want to see you.
Just leave!
He doesn't want to meet you. He doesn't even want to talk to you.
He's scared of you right now.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I hit you.
I apologize.
Can we please talk?
I didn't hit you out of hatred.
- I was just really angry...
Let's at least clear the air between us.
Don't you want to do that?
If you don't leave, I'm going to call the cops.
You should go now. Stop bothering him.
It's over now! Just go!
- Was everything part of your plan?
- What are you talking about?
You said we should keep it a secret! You said that yourself!
Do you still have feelings for me?
I did what you asked.
I gave up everything and backed down.
All I asked of you was to make sure Joon Young didn't get hurt.
You promised to raise him well.
You said you'll make him happy.
But how dare you hit my son in front of her and her family?
So what?
Did you tell her to get back at me?
Do you really want to take this even further?
Are you scared she might leave you?
Da Kyung is nothing like you.
She's willing to forgive me for the mistake I made.
Too bad, right? You must be disappointed.
Do you really think...
she'll be able to forgive you?
she'll be any different?
Don't even think for a second that Joon Young likes you.
He's just being like that because he's angry at me.
I'm never going to give him up.
This is your last warning.
Give up on Joon Young and end the fight here and now.
Otherwise, I won't stay still.
I swear I will put an end to you.
I will completely destroy your life.
No, you just destroyed your own life.
You tried to get back at me with that one-night mistake,
but you only got humiliated.
Do you still not know your place?
What can you do to me?
What are you going to do?
I will never let an insane woman like you raise Joon Young.
I'm going to take him back as soon as possible.
So keep that in mind.
What if Dad comes back?
What if he tries to take me away?
Don't worry. Your dad will never be able to bother you again.
I told you I'll protect you.
Can I help you?
Tell Chairman Yeo...
that I'd like to meet him.
How long are you going to keep a tail on me?
Or did you put a tail Tae Oh?
I'm sure I made myself clear that I'll do anything...
to make sure my daughter is happy.
I guess that means you finally admit that your daughter is unhappy.
What did you say to my daughter last night?
You mean you want to know what happened...
between me and Tae Oh.
I knew a long time ago that you didn't trust Tae Oh.
So I'm sure you can already guess what happened.
What was...
Da Kyung's dream?
My daughter...
liked to travel ever since she was young.
So I took her to many different places.
She especially enjoyed going to art galleries.
Come to think of it, it was nice then.
She had said she wanted to gain more experience and develop...
a better eye for art,
and then operate an art gallery.
You are...
more than capable of making that come true if she wanted.
Naturally.
She could've lived up to her potential and lived freely.
She was held back unexpectedly by Tae Oh.
Your precious daughter is wasting her youth...
because of a man.
Isn't that tragic?
Seeing her struggling with her second-wife complex...
makes me pity her...
as a fellow woman.
That's why I came here today, knowing I'm not welcome.
Since you'd do anything...
for your daughter.
Da Kyung, it's Mom.
- Are you okay?
Of course, I'm okay. Everything's fine.
Why did you call?
I think Ji Sun Woo really did leave.
The real estate agent said her house is up for sale.
She packed up her things and left with her kid,
so you don't have to worry anymore.
Are we doing the right thing?
Where are you moving to?
Return them to the kids.
Tell them I'm sorry...
for me.
I'm sorry to you too.
Sorry for asking you to do this.
Joon Young.
It was because I liked you.
Because I was worried.
It was because I wished you'd stop.
I wasn't being holier-than-thou.
So...
I'm sorry if I offended you.
I'm sorry too.
Thanks.
Shall we go?
Okay.
It's empty.
- Hello.
Many of Dr. Ji's patients left,
so it's a bit empty.
Did Dr. Ji say when she's coming back?
No.
Dr. Sul says she thinks she left.
She left? Completely?
(Tae Oh)
What happened between you guys?
Sun Woo said she and Joon Young left.
Is that true?
(Sun Woo said she and Joon Young left. Is that true?)
I'm sure you thought hard about it before making your decision.
I just...
want you to be happy.
I wanted to tell you that.
Your message has been saved.
It's strong and sturdy.
It was maintained nicely too. Come in.
The owner left very suddenly,
so the furniture is still here.
Take a slow look around.
Okay.
Are you with the real estate agency?
Is someone looking at the house?
Yes. She's looking upstairs.
When do you think our house will sell?
I can't say. The market has been slow lately.
It's not like we can drop the price that much. I'm worried.
I'm sure there will be a buyer soon.
Every house has an owner meant for it.
Da Kyung?
What brings you here?
Do you know each other?
Do you mind if we chat? You can go ahead.
Sure.
Think it over and give me a call.
Sun Woo gave me a key and asked me to pack up her things.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I just wanted to confirm that she really did leave.
That isn't all...
that you want to confirm.
Aren't you anxious because you're not sure if it's really over...
between them?
I understand. I'd be the same way.
I'll let you get to work.
Tae Oh won't...
get over Sun Woo so easily.
Sun Woo ran away like she did because she knows this.
On what grounds are you making such claims?
Did Sun Woo tell you to say this to me?
I guess she did.
I thought so.
Je Hyuk said this to me.
Even when a man has a woman beside him,
he won't be able to get over his previous love.
He thinks Tae Oh is like that.
You know Sun Woo went into hiding once, right?
Tae Oh came to see me then.
He asked me if I could check on her well-being for him.
His eyes looked so desperate.
Why do you think Tae Oh acted that way?
I know very well how torturous it is to live...
while doubting your husband.
That's why I wanted to tell you as another woman...
and as someone with experience.
If you don't believe me, you can come to my house.
I'll show you some security footage.
She forwarded me her login for the security company.
You'll be able to see how often Tae Oh came...
and how many times he wandered around the empty house.
- Thank you.
Let's consider this a trip.
Let's not think about anything for a while and just relax.
I feel strange.
It's because the place is unfamiliar.
You'll get used to it soon.
Don't worry about anything and just have positive thoughts.
Just choose where you want to go and what you want to do.
I'll do everything for you.
We can even go back if you want to.
I wrapped up all the urgent projects at work.
Should we go on a trip?
Where to?
You shouldn't overwork yourself,
so how about somewhere warm to recuperate?
Maybe Bali or Hawaii?
How's Hawaii?
Okay.
I can go anytime, so you should pick the dates that work for you.
Great.
I'm sorry.
Can I...
sleepover tonight?
Another time.
I'm sorry. I went too far.
I'm so bad at reading the mood.
Gosh.
I didn't upset you, did I?
- I'm home.
Where's Jenny?
She's asleep.
Nothing happened, right?
No.
I'm going to make some ramyeon. Do you want to eat with me?
I'm okay.
Okay, then.
Thank you.
Do you really not care where we go?
Every school is the same.
Your hospital is more important.
Should we look for a place in Seoul while we're at it?
We should think about your university too.
You should meet someone else too.
You should date someone nice.
I'm okay with it.
Why did you dislike Dr. Kim Yoon Ki?
Because you were too good for him.
- What?
He's not good enough for you.
How's Joon Young doing?
(How's Joon Young doing?)
Are you doing well?
(Ji Sun Woo)
Hello?
I'm sorry.
I left without saying goodbye.
I know I shouldn't feel this way.
But I can't stop worrying about you.
Is everything okay?
Joon Young and I are planning the future.
He's a lot calmer.
We even laughed together.
The kids told me they understand and that you don't need to be sorry.
Can't you just stay?
Enough about Joon Young. What about you?
Are you doing okay?
The air is nice here.
The stars are so vivid.
And thanks to that,
things have become a lot clearer now.
Thank you, Dr. Kim.
I won't forget how much you helped.
Dr. Ji.
Can you tell me once you decide...
where you're going to go?
(Yeo Da Kyung)
What do you want?
I'll convince Tae Oh...
and make him give up his parental rights for Joon Young.
So don't expect to get any child-rearing expenses.
When did I ever ask for that?
It's because you might use that as an excuse to show up before him.
Make sure you guys won't ever have to meet again...
because of Joon Young.
You know very well that Joon Young was just an excuse.
That's why you came all the way here.
It was just a one-night mistake.
And I'm going to believe that.
If you don't want to get humiliated, just promise me...
that you'll never show up before us again.
If you don't,
I'll just sue you for having committed adultery.
I have nothing more to fear. You think I won't be able to do it?
What is it that you want to protect?
Tae Oh?
Your family? Or your pride?
Will your anxiety subside...
if I promise not to show up?
That's none of your business.
You're right. It's your right to choose.
And that's none of my business.
But before you choose, there's something you need to know.
What are you doing?
I'm going to show you...
Tae Oh's true nature.
This used to be my favorite song.
And because of that, Tae Oh liked it, too.
This isn't just our favorite song. There's a special meaning to it.
He proposed to me...
with this song playing in the background.
"Let's get married, Sun Woo."
"I promise I'll make you and our baby happy."
"I'm not doing this because you're pregnant."
"It's because I love you, Sun Woo."
"I want to share my life with you."
"Let's live together."
Did he say something similar to you?
Did he tell you you're his one and only love?
Did he whisper words of love?
Don't lie to me.
You have no proof.
Follow me. I'll prove to you that I'm not lying.
Where are you taking me?
To my house.
What about that?
I was shocked when I first saw the resemblance.
Don't you get it?
Look carefully.
I saw everything in your bedroom when I went to your place.
We had the same perfume.
The same kind of underwear.
And even wore the same type of wedding dress.
They were all the same, and it completely creeped me out.
Did Tae Oh pick them out for you?
Or...
did you pick them yourself?
You went through my stuff and bought the same things.
How much worse can you get?
Don't you think you're being immature?
I don't have irrefutable evidence that you want.
However,
I don't lie.
I don't know whether or not Tae Oh is conscious of it,
but you...
are a lot like me.
What do you think?
Many people dress like that.
Don't try to force it.
He's meticulous and detail-oriented, right?
Everything must go according to plan.
You probably thought...
he was free-spirited, and that drew you to him.
He probably fell for you,
who looked up to him and provided for him.
You and I are the type that he's instinctively drawn to.
Are you trying to insist that he's still into you?
Why am I listening to your delusions?
What if a woman like that appears again?
You're right. It's a common look.
There are plenty of women like us.
Sadly, Tae Oh is a free spirit.
He is drawn to the woman who takes good care of him,
but once he feels like he is being stifled,
he'll look for a place to breathe.
Just as he fell for you...
while he was with me.
I'm sure by the time...
Jenny is Joon Young's age.
Can you guarantee that won't happen?
That's how useless it is.
That's all that supposedly great love amounts to.
What is marriage?
You're blinded briefly...
by the misconception that it's fate and get married.
Is it worth giving your all as collateral...
just because you lived together for a few years?
Knowing you'll be miserable.
I still don't get it.
One thing is for sure.
You can't raise a child with a man you know will hurt you.
Think it over.
It may be your last chance...
to escape.
(Movie Production Investment Proposal)
Did you sleep well?
The investor I'm meeting with today really liked the manuscript.
I have a good feeling about this.
That's great.
I'll call you once the investment is confirmed.
Let's celebrate.
See you later.
(Movie Production Investment Proposal)
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll call you once we cast the other roles.
Sure.
Let's have dinner soon with the director.
Sounds good.
Give me a call.
Thank you.
(Card declined. Please try again.)
Is there a problem?
It keeps getting declined.
Do you have another card?
Thank you.
Funny seeing you here.
Hey, there.
Sorry about last time.
What brings you here?
I was meeting an investor.
Are sponsorship talks going well with the chairman?
Chairman Yeo flaked on that promise ages ago.
Didn't you know?
Why? Did something happen?
You should know better than I do.
- Sir? Sir.
This card won't work either.
Okay, then.
Mr. Lee!
Where's Mr. Lee?
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
Why were the corporate cards canceled?
I was told by the chairman...
to close everything and kick you out.
What?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I finally found an investor and we're about to sign!
If I leave, who's going to take over?
I told you, it's over for you.
Are you crazy?
Who are you to tell me that?
If you want to see your daughter for the last time,
you should come to your senses and go home.
(Wife)
The person you have reached is not available.
Honey. Da Kyung.
Why won't you pick up your phone?
Did something happen?
I think your father's really angry at me.
No.
Let's talk in person at home.
Call me back when you get this.
What are you doing?
I said, what are you doing?
We settled all the documents.
Take this and get lost.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
Bring this car to the location.
Yes, sir.
Why the car...
"Documents"? What documents?
Divorce documents!
Giving up your rights to Jenny's custody.
Also, the title I gave you at the company.
It's over. Don't you get it?
Father, why are you suddenly acting like this?
There must be a misunderstanding.
I'm not your father!
- Father.
The only thing I wanted from you...
was to make...
my daughter happy.
Had you done your job properly,
I would have cherished you...
like a real son and as a friend.
When a father raises their daughter preciously,
that's what they dream of.
But unfortunately,
this is as far as it'll go. It's just as I had predicted.
Let's end things here.
Don't you ever...
show up in front of us again.
I'll speak to Da Kyung.
Where is she right now? Where's Da Kyung?
Jenny.
Honey.
Da Kyung.
Don't bother with him and get in the car.
I'll take care of it.
You should wait in the car.
I thought you said you'd forgive me.
We decided to work on it together.
Why would you suddenly do this?
That's when you made just one mistake.
But that wasn't the case.
I won't be fooled again. It's over.
There's no need to listen to everything your father says.
Let's take care of our problem on our own.
Dad knew everything!
He was preparing for everything because he was worried about me.
I feel sorry for Jenny who has you as her dad,
but it's a hundred times better not to have you around.
Don't you ever think about seeing her again.
You're all I have.
I love you, Da Kyung. Please.
The song you used to propose to me...
was used on that woman too.
The perfume you bought for me was the one she used too,
as well as my underwear, wedding dress, and everything else.
Who am I to you?
What was I to you?
What are you talking about?
The delusional one wasn't that woman.
It was me.
I found out everything.
To you,
I was just a substitute for Ji Sun Woo.
Go to that woman.
Da Kyung. Wait.
Jenny! Jenny, wait!
Da Kyung, let me talk to Jenny for a minute.
Da Kyung! Let me talk to Jenny!
Get out!
I said, get out!
It's all your fault.
I lost everything because of you!
Did you plan everything to ruin me?
What did you say to Da Kyung?
The house, money,
and my family too...
I'm left with nothing.
(Son)
Hey, Mom.
I took care of everything.
I'll be right there. Wait there until I arrive.
What about Dad?
Did you settle everything with him?
Use this money to get yourself a motel room or something.
And think about what you're going to do now.
Let me know once you come up with a plan.
I'll help you rent a studio.
You're a monster.
I never should've met you.
You ruined my life.
You should've just killed me.
That would've been better for both of us.
Will you please get to your senses?
Think of all the things you've done...
before trying to blame others.
You're the one who ruined your life, not me.
Do you still not get it?
Joon Young knows everything.
Knows what?
He knows why I hit you.
Joon Young knows everything.
Joon Young hates you. No, he loathes you.
He knows how monstrous you are.
He can never be happy with you.
You might be able to abandon me, but not Joon Young!
I'm going to meet him...
and tell him exactly what you did to me today.
I'll tell him how you completely destroyed my life.
He deserves to know that, doesn't he?
My goodness, did you receive a private lesson?
- What are you talking about?
My goodness.
It's nice to be outside.
I heard the land where the film set was going to be built...
is going to be sold at a very low price.
I guess Chairman Yeo and his family aren't planning to come back.
My husband also thinks the same way.
But it looks like Dr. Ji is back.
Mr. Lee was forced to get a divorce and got kicked out.
Chairman Yeo and his family left Gosan.
And now, Ji Sun Woo comes back like she had it all planned.
Doesn't it seem like...
something happened between them?
There are rumors saying Dr. Ji was the one who got them divorced.
Every married couple has a story we don't know about.
Don't get yourselves in trouble...
for talking about other people's families. Be careful.
By the way, what's the director's plan?
The chairperson seems pretty stern about it.
And my husband also thinks it's hard to find someone like her.
So he's going to do his best to bring her back.
That's good.
(Employees only, Visitors must park somewhere else.)
Hello.
Dr. Ji.
- Dr. Ji.
- Have you been well?
- How are you?
Yes, I know.
- Have you been well?
Bye.
Dr. Ji.
(Associate Director Sul Myung Sook)
How nice. Congratulations on becoming the associate director.
When are you going to start working here again?
I asked you to come because the director asked me to.
I'm supposed to convince you.
He knows you've been back for quite a while...
and thinks you should hurry up and come back to work.
He's very nervous that you might end up...
working at another hospital.
Do you think it's a good idea?
I feel too ashamed to come back here.
Don't worry and start working here again.
We left your office empty all along.
Stop making the director feel so anxious.
Thank you.
By the way, about Tae Oh...
I don't think he left for good.
Remember Woo Ho Sang?
My high school friend you met last time.
He told me he saw Tae Oh pretty recently.
- Where?
He looked all haggard...
and was fighting a street bar owner for not having paid properly.
My friend felt bad for him, so he offered to pay instead.
But once he looked back, he was already gone.
When was that?
About a week ago.
Why don't you look for him?
I'm worried he might get himself in trouble.
Why should I?
He's probably thinking clearer now.
When are you coming home?
Okay.
Joon Young. I'm home.
Joon Young?
Joon Young.
(Son)
I'm taking Joon Young.
(A World of Married Couple)
I'm glad Joon Young hung in there so well.
I think it's really over now.
Let's do it before it's too late.
It's so easy. Why did we push it off?
Are you still mad...
because I said no once?
You don't have to say anything.
Let's just stay like this for a little while.
Have you heard from Tae Oh?
I'm sure he won't show up again.
You were always the only one for me.
Let's start over.
What use is that now?
You ruined everything, Dad.
The truth is,
Je Hyuk said he thought he saw Tae Oh recently.
Sun Woo.
Will you come see me?