(All characters, organizations, places, cases, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Episode 19)
Well, you are not my family.
But you can pretend to be my family and come see me.
I cannot do that to you...
no matter how awful I am.
First place of military service exam.
Yeon Soo.
Congratulations.
Do you think you will not pay...
for what you have done to me?
Will you not accept the certificate?
This is all because of you.
This is all because...
you are the son...
of His Majesty.
Will you accept this certificate from me?
Are you all right?
I heard that you almost got hurt from the gambling house.
I am sorry. I feel like I am responsible for it.
No, you are not. I went there on my own will.
How about looking for a way to become a court lady?
You are pretty.
Pardon? Court lady?
Well, why not?
When His Majesty comes out in disguise, approach him...
and win him over.
That way, you will be able to enter the palace right away.
He comes out in disguise?
Yes. He says he comes out in disguise,
but everyone at the palace knows that.
He often goes out at night.
Please go in. He is waiting for you.
Are you not curious...
what I told...
His Majesty in there?
Yeon Soo.
Did you come here with the vice-curator?
With the girl and the drunkard too?
- You... - Take...
as much time as you want.
Were you that surprised?
Pardon?
I ask because you have been only staring at me...
since you came in and did not say a word to me.
I am sorry.
I mean,
my apologies for not knowing the rules of the palace.
I am not used to the rules here.
I get to laugh thanks to you.
There is no need for that.
Rules are not necessary between you and me.
Right.
Is that so?
Of course.
Under one condition.
You must pretend not to know about my night outing.
Please keep it a secret to your lady as well.
What do you say?
I will comply.
I will assign you to Chief Administrative Officer Baek...
whom you have met the other day.
You will help him with his tasks.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Open it.
Here.
My gosh. This is no way to treat your guest.
Guest?
I did not know guests brought swords.
You know?
I am a guest...
as long as you do not cause trouble.
What?
You are the one who barged into our house, making a fuss.
Have you already forgotten?
Why are you fighting when I am having a meal here?
You will chase away my appetite.
Goodness.
She is right. Stop it.
You will spoil our happy reunion.
You little brat.
Come over here. You brat.
I do not want to harm you.
- Not yet, at least. - "Not yet"?
You are unbelievable.
It is because of me.
He found me when I went to the palace gate to wait for you.
No, it is all right. He would have probably tailed me anyway.
Come with me.
So you are still alive, which is unfortunate.
Thanks to you.
By the way, why did you suddenly get a job at the palace?
To be successful.
I need to make a living,
and as you know, I am very talented in martial arts.
What about you? What are you getting at?
I have never been stabbed by a sword before.
I thought I would die when I passed out.
When I gave it some thought after waking up,
I thought it would be a shame...
if I kill you with that simple method.
This is between you and me.
Do not get others involved in this. If you do...
Why not?
Will you tell His Majesty that I am planning treason?
Do you think I cannot?
I will bring you and your great family down.
I doubt you can.
Your brother is planning the treason with me.
What?
Do not look at me that way.
He came back to me willingly.
Unlike you,
he is greedy and ambitious...
just like me.
You scumbag.
What are you doing?
Be careful. You will get hurt.
Are you okay? Are you injured?
If you do not want him to die, follow me.
What is this lunatic saying?
Is that a threat?
Think however you like,
but I will not allow you to stay here.
Go.
Go inside your room.
I will bring my belongings,
so wait.
Are you...
very upset with her?
No.
I have given up on her.
Sorry?
I had been letting her do whatever she wanted...
because I realized...
that she was hanging on with the strength that she had.
But then, a guy appeared,
and she is swayed by him.
I cannot take it anymore and have decided to give up...
winning her heart.
Then why did you tell her to come?
I will have her.
Even if she does not like me,
I will keep her beside me forever.
I will fulfill a wish of hers,
so I believe I have the right.
Then why have you spared him?
- He is dangerous. - You are correct.
But seeing how he and the King...
could not recognize each other...
made it quite fascinating.
The King who kills his son twice.
That will be enough to justify our revolt.
He will die...
in his father's hands.
There is no other way.
Are you going to kill him?
If you do, you will have to flee for killing a royal family member.
Will you abandon Aeng Du and her father?
Or will you bring them along?
But why are you leaving?
Because that will keep everyone else safe.
And...
I do not care about him.
So do not fight him.
I do not want to see you get hurt.
I am just temporarily moving out.
Goodbye. Do not see me out.
That is enough!
You want him to take his father's place?
I have no desire to make Nok Du do such a heinous deed.
And you have no right to dethrone the King.
(Royal Command)
My lord.
Everyone is siding with him.
He will make his move soon.
What will you do?
I will become...
a king who will exercise his absolute authority.
He wiped out a village full of women...
as he pleased.
Lady Chun was on his side, but he killed her with no regrets.
Grand Prince Neungyang...
should never take the throne.
The guards will stop you. Let me accompany you.
Stay.
If anything happens to me,
please do what I have said to you.
Yes, my lord.
Please be safe.
You may not leave.
This is a royal command.
Move aside.
I must speak with His Majesty.
Please stop.
I will relay your message.
Move aside!
I have served the King twice as long as you did.
I am doing this to protect him.
So move aside.
Please wait while I bring out the palanquin.
Eat.
On that day when the village for widows was attacked,
did you rescue me, right?
I did although you returned.
How did you get through...
all those thugs?
I have enough power to do that.
Or perhaps, you had enough power to scheme such a thing.
I had no choice.
Is this who you truly are?
Are you someone who threatens people by taking hostages...
and kills innocent women?
So?
Were you disappointed?
You were never curious...
about who I was or what I did.
That is not important.
It was for me.
It was the most important.
Then why are you treating me this way?
Because money could not win you over.
No matter how much I tried, you never accepted my feelings.
I resorted to another way, so just stay put and...
I have told you clearly.
I left that house,
but I have no plans to stay obedient under this roof.
So if that is what you want,
you may as well kill me.
That is the quickest solution.
I must meet with the Queen.
I heard you were locked up.
What is going on?
And what do you need to tell me so urgently?
You have kept that with you all along.
(20 years ago)
Please bury this alongside my son.
Yes.
I asked you for that favor...
because I was going to keep this with me at all times.
I lost him before I could even feed him.
This gives me comfort.
Come to think of it,
I never got to ask you this.
Did he safely get buried?
Your Majesty.
I have something to tell...
What are you doing here, Chancellor?
He says he comes out in disguise,
but everyone at the palace knows that.
He often goes out at night.
He comes out in disguise?
I might be able to kill him without even entering the palace.
Or I might die instead.
Boss, are you okay?
Do I look okay to you?
I am going to catch those jerks...
and teach them a lesson.
- Darn it! - Gosh, walk slowly.
Be gentle.
Those darn jerks.
Hey, walk slowly.
Be gentle.
Those darn punks.
Are you here to see me?
No.
I dropped by while I was passing by.
I wish you good luck with your new job.
What about you?
- Are you okay? - Of course, I am okay.
I get to live in a huge house.
And as you can see, I am allowed to go wherever I want.
So do not worry and just focus on doing well.
What is it?
Do you also think I look very handsome?
I already know.
You really have no sense of shame.
You do not look handsome,
but you do look like a rookie who has just became an officer.
Go on inside.
I ordered you not to leave your house.
I apologize, Your Majesty.
But there is something I need to tell you.
I heard you told the guard...
that you are trying to protect me.
Yes, that is correct.
Tell me.
What are you trying to protect me from?
And how are you going to do that?
I am aware of a man who is getting ready to betray you.
Who is that?
It is Grand Prince Neungyang.
He is doing so many evil things...
to steal the throne from you.
What did you say?
Grand Prince Neungyang?
You must arrest him and punish him right now.
And as soon as you are done punishing him,
I also ask you to kill me...
for being disloyal.
You sounded so sincere...
that I almost believed you.
Repeat what you just said.
What did you just say to me?
Your son who was born...
20 years ago...
is still alive, Your Majesty.
What? He is alive?
How did you find out?
I met that man by coincidence...
and ended up hearing about some things...
I should not have found out.
He is...
the eldest son of Jung Yun Jeo...
and a living witness.
My so-called brother...
is your son, Your Majesty.
My father...
raised him as his son.
How do you expect me to believe that?
Please forgive us!
What?
There is another man who is aware of this.
Who is that?
It is Heo Yun,
the chancellor.
He has been blackmailing me.
He told me that he will frame me as a traitor...
if I did not keep my mouth shut.
However, I could not do that.
I could not dare to deceive you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
You must not get fooled by him.
Then...
who am I supposed to trust?
You?
You were my closest friend and most loyal servant.
But how can I trust you when you have been lying to me?
Do you know how much I wished that I would be wrong?
As I was constantly suspicious of you,
I still hoped that I would be wrong!
Do you have any idea how much I hoped that I was mistaken?
Please kill me, Your Majesty.
But Your Majesty, you still cannot...
trust the words of Grand Prince Neungyang.
That is enough!
I want you...
to quietly take him to the dungeon.
Your Majesty, you can punish me all you want!
But you must not trust Grand Prince Neungyang!
Your Majesty!
You must not trust him!
Do not let him fool you!
Your Majesty!
I am Yeon Soo, the newly appointed chief administrative officer.
I heard you came to the palace,
- so I thought... - I already heard about you.
His Majesty has given orders to urgently arrest someone.
Follow me.
Okay.
The evidence is loud and clear.
What is the point of meeting him at this point?
The guards will be outside,
and it will be hard for you to even meet him.
But I should still give it a try.
I need to hear two sides of the story.
Then let us go together.
- Okay. - I prefer to go alone.
I will not be late.
That brat.
No one can find out about the man we are about to arrest.
So we need to make sure not to cause a scene.
- You must escape. - What is the matter?
Arrest him right now!
This is the royal command!
Run toward the backdoor.
I will be right behind you.
You should go.
Where is my father?
Lord Heo asked me to give this to you.
He said that you would need this to prove who you are.
That way!
Go!
Are you all right?
The person who saved Jung Yun Jeo was definitely a woman.
I said I can go by myself. Goodness.
You are injured. How could I let you?
Wait here.
It will not take long.
Yes, I will wait.
See you soon.
You missed him?
How could you fail to catch him?
Please forgive me. I will find him at all costs.
Did you find anything else?
I found this from Lord Heo's room.
This document explains it.
Make sure you find Jung Yun Jeo.
I give you permission to kill him if necessary.
You just need to bring his corpse to me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Open the gate.
(Episode 20 will air shortly.)
(Episode 20)
How long have you been plotting treason?
Your Majesty.
Was it 20 years ago...
when you lied to me that you had killed Yun Jeo and that boy?
Or...
was it when you hid the document from the former king?
I told you...
to bring the document if you found it.
However, you told me right away...
that the document was burnt.
Was this your agenda?
Were you trying to dethrone me...
and give the throne to someone who is more legitimate than me?
Your Majesty.
You must have thought...
that I did not have the right to the throne...
just like everyone else.
That is why you decided to abandon me...
to serve under a new king.
I deserve death, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
You can punish me all you want,
but you cannot trust Grand Prince Neungyang...
no matter what.
He is...
Grand Prince Neungyang?
Are you still talking about him?
Fine. Go ahead!
Tell me how he is trying to plot treason.
I managed to escort your family as I was worried...
the royal guards might take them away.
As long as you stay silent,
I promise I will spare them.
If you end this mess by taking full responsibility,
your family might have a chance...
to live their lives comfortably.
This is all Grand Prince Neungyang's doing?
Yes.
He was framed for treason when he entered the palace...
because of a long story between him and His Majesty.
Then, is Grand Prince Neungyang...
behind Lady Min's death?
Grand Prince Neungyang told me the same thing.
He told me that Lord Heo was behind all of this.
Whose story must we believe?
Please think long and hard how Grand Prince Neungyang...
inserted himself into this mess.
He is cruel and meticulous.
There is only one place for him to spend his night in secret...
during his outing in disguise.
It is the best gisaeng house in Hanyang.
The gisaeng house is at the foot of Mount Okmyuk.
- Pour me a drink. - Thank you.
- I would like a drink too. - Sure.
Yes. I ought to pour you a drink.
Your Majesty, could you take me to the palace...
and make me your queen?
Be quiet.
Lower your voice.
All right. Chief State Councillor. Have a drink.
You too. You ought to have a drink as well.
You told me you do not like me.
Okay, I get that. But you see,
I am going to make you like me.
Goodness!
- Your Majesty. - My queen!
If you will not listen to me,
I will go to that king.
Okay, then.
I am a better king than he is.
What are you talking about? You are drunk.
Nok Du.
Nok Du!
Make sure you find Jung Yun Jeo.
I give you permission...
to kill him if necessary.
You just need to bring his corpse to me.
Are you looking for this?
She is the Queen. Do show your respect.
I apologize, Your Highness.
I am...
a chief administrative officer at the police bureau.
I had visited the palace and lost it.
But you seem...
to be lost.
Sorry?
I am...
not familiar with the palace yet.
Take this.
I know my way around this place.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Lord Heo asked me to give this to you.
He said that you would need this to prove who you are.
What are you doing here looking all dazed?
I was waiting for you.
And you came.
Why do you look so sullen?
Is someone tormenting you at the police bureau?
I am.
What?
I think I am tormenting everyone else.
I should have lived a quiet life.
That was the right thing to do.
I made the wrong decision.
- Hey... - I am lost.
I wish someone could explain it to me.
But I do not know...
what to ask to whom in order for no one to get hurt.
I have no idea.
I am lost.
I was blabbering too much.
Forget it.
Forget everything I just said.
I had no idea what you were saying anyway.
Enough with the pitying. Go home and get some rest.
Go.
Let me walk you home first.
No one will welcome you there.
- So leave. - No.
You go wherever you please.
Let me do the same.
What? Hey.
Go now.
No.
Do you still like me?
I am always so coldhearted towards you.
You look beautiful in my eyes.
Why are you so complicated?
What are you so afraid of?
Why are you so fearless?
You do not know what tomorrow will bring.
That is exactly why...
I say whatever I want.
And I am walking you home because I want to.
We should...
hold hands as well.
I will let go once we get to the end of this road.
Then I should walk slowly.
I was not aware of what happened at the chancellor's place.
I am certain Jung Yun Jeo was there.
We must catch him ourselves.
I will head to Aseowon.
Tail Nok Du for me.
He will try to find his father.
This is a drawing of Jung Yun Jeo.
Move secretively.
You...
Do you still dress like a woman?
I have my reasons.
By the way, did you go to the chancellor's house, did you not?
How do you know that?
What happened to the man whom you rescued?
How are his injuries?
- He left that day... - Where to?
He left because he could not trust me. He did not tell where.
Who is he?
He is my father.
I see.
He was slightly injured, but he left in good condition.
He left with the chancellor's right hand,
so do not worry.
I see.
By the way, why are you here?
Will you take revenge on Grand Prince Neungyang?
"Revenge"?
He is not home yet.
Then could you give this to him?
This is the only thing I know that he likes.
You should wait and give it yourself.
I need to go somewhere.
Is that so? Then you can come back and give it to him.
Please give this to him.
Well, okay.
Goodbye, then.
Bye.
Chief Administrative Officer?
We came here because of you.
Why do you look so frail...
as if you have not eaten for days?
Did you fail to catch a thief or something?
I always fail to catch them.
But...
were you on your way to the gisaeng house?
Yes.
I had something to do there.
I am sure you do not want to become a gisaeng.
You are right. That is not why.
I am trying hard to find a job as a servant in the palace.
Your goal...
is also to enter the palace?
I heard you get to earn...
a stable income if you get a job in the palace.
I see.
I guess you are still having trouble falling asleep.
Have you not tried what I told you to do?
No, I could not do it.
It has been a long time...
since I left my wife to be lonely all by herself.
I could not dare to bother her and ask her to soothe me...
after all those years.
That is okay.
You may have left her to be lonely for a long time.
But who knows? She might also be waiting for you.
She might be waiting for you to reach out to her.
(Inn)
Boss.
I will find those jerks tomorrow no matter what.
You should stand guard and wait.
Okay.
Hey, you are...
Look who is here.
The foot of the lamp is always dark.
I searched all over for you, but I could not find you.
But we ended up meeting so nearby.
I am so glad to see you.
I think you have the wrong person.
Oh, is that so?
Let me see.
- Boss! My goodness! - It hurts.
Hurry up and run after her!
- Let us go! - That little brat!
(A plague has spread...)
That little brat.
Why do you keep running?
My bottom hurts so much because of all the beating I got.
Let me see. You stole my money,
and you made me get a flogging.
No, it is okay. Come here.
Come here.
It is dangerous. Get over here.
My goodness.
What...
(A plague has spread...)
Boss! Boss!
My goodness, Boss!
What are you doing here?
Everyone in this village died because of a plague.
- A plague? - Yes.
- She is dead. She has to be dead. - Yes.
I bet she is dead.
Move.
- Master. - Hey, you are here.
By the way,
is there anything wrong with Dong Joo?
- Why? - She dropped by earlier...
and asked me to give you this.
But she looked very desperate and sad.
Where am I?
Is anyone there?
Hello?
Help!
Help! Someone is down here!
Hello?
Hello? Is anyone up there?
Help!
Hello?
Is anyone there?
My goodness, it is pouring.
Hey.
Are you sure that guy is not hiding her?
He is also looking for her.
Then maybe she just ran away...
just like last time.
No.
There is no way.
Then where could she be?
You searched all over the city.
I will be back.
Hey, take this with you.
Take this.
Go on.
My goodness.
Help.
Someone is down here!
Help...
Nice one.
I need to go home now.
- Let us try one more time. - My gosh.
Hey, come on.
That is not fair.
- Let us try again. - No way.
- My gosh, come on. - Stop it.
I said I need to go home now.
There is not much left.
Boss!
I finally found you, you darn jerk.
- Get out of my way. - No.
I am going to kill you today.
I will let you meet...
your girlfriend in paradise. You can look forward to it.
What?
Oh, I guess you did not know.
She is dead.
I killed her.
We should...
hold hands as well.
I will let go once we get to the end of this road.
Then I should walk slowly.
Dong Joo!
No, Dong Joo.
Dong Joo, wake up. No!
Dong Joo.
Dong Joo, wake up. Dong Joo!
I am ashamed to say this,
but I cannot seem to fall asleep.
Please forgive my bad manners.
Pardon?
It is not your fault.
Everything is...
Everything is my fault.
Your Majesty.
If it pleases you,
could you...
stay with me...
tonight?
Just like old times.
Are you all right? Are you awake?
What are you doing? You should not move around yet.
Go away. Go.
Hey.
How could you say that...
to me?
Do you know how worried I was?
Did I ask you to worry about me?
Why did you look for me?
Why did you jump into the well?
What is going on with you?
Dong Joo.
I had a task to fulfill.
I have been living my whole life trying to complete my task.
Once I was done with it...
When I join my mother after completing my task,
I thought I could be really happy.
That was the reason I lived for.
But...
I was about to die even before completing my task.
Why...
Why did it have to be you?
Why did I think of you?
Why did I only think of you at that moment?
You keep making me want to live.
You keep...
I do not know...
what you are trying to fulfill at the expense...
of distancing yourself from me.
I do not know what you are afraid of.
But whatever that may be...
or whatever happens to us,
we are alive and together now.
So...
can you not follow your heart and just like me?
I just...
like...
I really...
like you.
I like you.
Fine. I like you.
I like you so much that I am about to lose my mind.