(Yongsang Moving Service)
My dad...
decided to move south.
As for me...
Here's the key to my place.
I'm sorry for troubling you.
I'm the one who's sorry.
I'm practically asking you to take care of the house.
Like I told you before, it's because of my son.
He's rarely home because his dream is to become a travel writer.
But still, he sometimes visits every once in a while.
So I can't put my place up for rent.
But I can't leave it empty either.
Would it be okay for your son and I to live in the same house?
I really don't think this is right.
I told you that he only visits every once in a while.
His room is on the 2nd floor, so you can stay on the 1st floor.
Feel free to make yourself at home.
I'm sure your dad will want that.
I'll pay you rent even if it's not that much.
Whatever makes you feel at ease.
But don't pay me too much.
Mr. Kim, I'll go bring my car.
Once you arrive,
find the nearest hospital.
You want me to get ready to die?
That's not what I meant.
Don't worry.
Do you have anything to say to me before you go?
I guess you're too excited to even care about me.
Gosh, you never moved your entire life.
Even your heart beats slowly.
But you're suddenly leaving so quickly.
I don't want to be a burden, so I should hurry up and leave.
Don't say that.
You should draw.
Draw what you want to draw.
That's a grand coming from a poet who never writes any poets.
You're the one who should start writing poems again.
Speak for yourself.
Right back at you.
("If cats could talk, they wouldn't.")
(Quote by Nan Porter)
I'm on my way there.
I've never been there before.
But I have to say, the neighborhood feels familiar.
(Sonamu)
You have arrived near your destination.
I don't think this is it. I think we searched the wrong address.
We're at the right place. That's the house.
But this is...
I can't believe this. How in the world...
I bet he'll get the wrong idea.
I can't believe I'm moving in next door.
Who would think it's a coincidence?
Should I bring him some rice cakes?
No way.
I'd seem like a nasty stalker. Anyone would think that way.
I'm not going to look. Let's not look.
(Cheongbongsan-ro 70)
Hey, Jae Seon.
Sol Ah?
What's wrong with your voice?
What?
It's because the cat is sleeping.
I heard you moved. Where's the new place?
Why do you ask?
Because I'm worried you might be out of cat food.
Send me your address.
I'll go pick it up myself.
I have to go to your neighborhood anyway.
Okay, come over. I'll give it to you.
Okay.
How's Sergei?
I'm worried he might be stressed because of the new environment.
You only care about the cat, don't you?
Then why did you take him and make things uneasy for both of us?
You think I made things uneasy?
I was trying to be nice.
You must be mistaken.
Do you think I'm expecting something in return for caring for the cat?
Is that why you think I made things uneasy?
No, not really.
No?
Is that why you took the cat?
Gosh, no.
I just felt bad for you, and I'm the only one you have...
No, not that you have feelings for me or anything.
But you don't have any other friends.
And as your old friend...
My gosh.
It's already ridiculous that I'm taking care of your ex's cat.
I don't get why I also need to explain everything.
- Forget it. - I'm sorry.
I didn't know...
your dad collapsed that day.
I hope he's healthy.
And I hope you're okay too.
I'll carry this for you. Where's your new place?
What? No, it's okay.
Where do you think you're going?
I can go on my own.
- It's heavy. - No, it's not.
Hey.
(Sonamu)
I'll carry it for you.
No, it's okay. I'll just take a cab.
- You're dressed so lightly. - I'll take a cab.
- Give it to me. - Gosh, it's okay.
Will you stop offering to help?
I didn't know,
but you're quite clingy.
(Sonamu)
- Go back inside. - Okay.
- Go on. - After I watch you leave.
No, you should go inside first.
See you. Bye.
(Sonamu)
Where is she going?
Why isn't he going inside?
She's going through so much.
Here. It's from Jae Seon. Eat up.
Aren't you going to eat?
Hey, do you know how hard it was for me to bring this here?
My gosh.
I guess I should just unpack.
You should draw.
Draw what you want to draw.
Draw what I want to draw?
I'll see you later.
Hey, cat.
Pussycat?
Kitty.
Sergei?
Sergei Rachmaninoff.
Gosh, he won't even answer me.
Hey, aren't you going to see me out?
Hey, hey.
My gosh, I even let him use my pillow.
Gosh, he's so ungrateful.
Forget it.
You know what? You're not even my cat anyway.
I'm only taking care of you until...
Let's not get too attached.
Go ahead and have fun all by yourself.
She forgot to take that.
Water. Water.
Here it is.
There you go.
Don't drink too much.
This isn't even my house, so don't pee all over the place.
The lights. The lights.
The lights.
I might work overtime today, so be a good boy, okay?
The laptop. The laptop.
If you're bored, you can watch this.
I'm going to leave now.
I'm really leaving this time.
Why am I human...
when she's not even around?
Sol Ah, you must be so tired.
You took the day off yesterday...
and probably had lots of fun.
But you have to do that again because tomorrow is a holiday.
No, it's not that. It's because I moved yesterday.
Ji Eun, I heard you're moving today. You should go home.
I'll go after I'm done with this.
Sol Ah, you should help.
Help a colleague.
Organize the references for the new children's wear project.
And these are the materials for the organic grain powder.
Find adequate images for the concept.
Get rid of the background image.
Make sure you do a delicate job.
No, I can do it myself.
You're still here? You should go.
You need to move today. Go on.
Yes, you should go. I'll do it instead.
She has it easy thanks to her connections.
On the other hand, you're doomed.
These birds stay on the trees...
and mate when the seasons...
Sol Ah, take a nap if you're tired.
Okay, thanks.
Bye, Sol Ah.
Bye. Take care.
- See you. - Bye.
When will she come back?
I'm done.
The unexpected downpour...
is causing havoc for people who didn't bring umbrellas.
It's raining way too hard.
Why won't I change?
Am I okay up to the garden?
I still haven't changed?
I left the house...
and I'm still human?
I'm human again?
How is this possible?
Her belongings.
Her smell.
You moved to a house in this area?
Well... It's not this way.
It's that way. Over there.
I can manage from here.
Which direction is it?
What?
So... It's...
It's way...over there.
I'll take a detour.
Don't do that. It's quite far away.
The terrain's rough, there's a steep incline,
- and the road's crooked... - You acted weird last time.
Where exactly do you live?
Well...
(Sonamu)
Don't get me wrong.
The house happens to belong to the woman my dad married,
and I happened to have no idea.
I'd never have moved in if I'd known.
I'd have done anything I could to find another place.
I really didn't know.
I really didn't.
You're acting weird.
I knew it.
See? You got the wrong idea.
I thought you would, so I couldn't tell you.
That's why I hid and sneaked glances.
It's not like that at all.
That's not what I meant.
See? You're boiling.
You have a fever.
I didn't expect that from you.
You're blushing.
Hey, kitty. How are you?
Oh? Kitty.
Kitty.
Meow.
Did I leave it open?
Let's see.
Here.
Stay still, will you?
Keep still.
He didn't eat at all.
Shall I give him some milk?
How about a new name?
What kind of a cat's name is Sergei?
You don't come when I call that name anyway.
What should I call you?
Hong Jo.
You can be Hong Jo.
You're Hong Jo while you're with me, okay?
Hong Jo.
Answer me.
Hong Jo. Hong Jo.
How about... Darn it.
Hey.
My gosh, are you serious?
I didn't know this was here.
You're drawing Beodul Love again?
You have such elegant taste.
What's wrong with that?
Beodul Love is my ideal type.
Hello?
Yes, Dad. Yes.
Okay, I'll see you at home.
Okay, bye.
He's even awkward with his parents.
Hey, did you recently meet your parents or something?
Yes, I was adopted only three years ago.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I was joking earlier, but it must've offended you.
No, not really.
You see...
I don't have a mom either.
She recently passed away.
After my mom died, my dad fell into depression.
He doesn't eat, smile, or talk.
It's as if his time just stopped.
Why are you telling me that?
What?
That way, it'll be fair.
It's okay. Please just be quiet.
Hey, come on.
I feel like I made a mistake because I didn't know you that well.
So we should get to know each other.
We might have some similarities.
And when you open up your secrets,
- you naturally become friends. - You're so loud.
Sorry.
I tend to talk a lot.
I'm always like that with my dad...
I did it again.
I don't know why I tend to talk so much...
Are you leaving?
You're not leaving?
- Then can I keep... - Keep your mouth shut.
Okay.
Hey, the thing is, I kind of tend to...
I found him.
My Beodul Love.
They're not facing each other,
so they don't need to force themselves to talk.
He just stayed by her side.
(My Helpless Beodul Love)
He didn't want her to try too hard.
She didn't need to do anything.
He wanted her to rest.
They weren't awkward in the silence.
It actually consoled them.
Hong Jo.
Do you know what I mean?
What would you know? You're just a cat.
Who says you can come up here?
Move. I can't see.
Hong Jo, stop.
(My Helpless Beodul Love)
Hey, are you mocking my drawing?
Where did I put the fever reducer?
Hong Jo.
Hong Jo. Hong Jo.
My cat threw up. I think he's sick.
How long has it been since he threw up?
About an hour.
I think he got a stomachache because he drank milk.
Cats should only drink lactose-free milk.
No, not you.
Because you don't like...
- cats. - You're right.
I don't like them.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Please don't be sick.
I thought she didn't like cats.
Why is she doing this?
And why...
do I become human only around her?
Why is it her?
(Episode 4)
Hong Jo.
Hong Jo. You don't feel sick anymore?
You must feel better. I'm glad.
Hong Jo, come here.
Meow.
It's good food, so eat a lot.
You eat so well.
(New messages)
Are you all right? Look outside your door.
(Medicine)
Nice!
This house has a great view.
Your fever. Has it gone down?
Yes. Thanks to you.
Only you
Did something good happen?
Kind of. A lot happened yesterday.
You think I'll be curious if you say that?
What happened?
- Shall I tell just one thing? - Yes.
- I'm... - Yes?
back to drawing cartoons online.
That's great. What will you draw?
That's a secret.
Hang on.
If that becomes successful, will you quit your job?
I came here for you.
I feel lonely already.
I want to escape from this sticky note nightmare too.
Hey.
Go on and stick it. You're welcome to.
You asked me to talk to you.
So this time I'll say it.
Insong Industries' banner.
(Our executives' safety is our competitive edge!)
This?
They want to change a word.
From "executives'" to "staff'".
(Our executives' safety is our competitive edge!)
Okay. I'll do that right away.
I sent it.
Oh. Okay.
(Incoming file)
(From executives to staff!)
Oh, no, this is...
Excuse me.
This isn't what I meant.
From "executives'" to "staff'".
Yes. "From executives to staff".
No. So, I meant...
It's not "from executives to staff".
Change "executives'" to...
(From executives to staff!)
Darn you.
Look at this!
She asked him to change "executives'" to "staff'",
and he changed the whole thing.
"From executives to staff"!
Doo Sik, you really are amazing.
- Well done. - My gosh.
How did you land this job?
Are you protesting?
Stick to using sticky notes.
Talking just made things more confusing.
My goodness.
You idiot.
- Don't hit me. - Neener, neener.
What's the noise about?
Ms. Kim, let's keep work and private life separate.
You were besties in high school, but this isn't high school.
I apologize.
You were way too happy.
What is it? What happened last night?
The truth is,
the place I moved to.
(Sonamu)
My previous caregiver...
would also laugh and cry because of him.
What is he like?
What do you want?
(Sonamu)
What are you doing?
Oh.
Are you and Sol Ah completely okay now?
I felt so suffocated, caught in-between.
I tiptoed around you both for the past year.
No. For the past 10 months.
Sol Ah even counted the number of days...
you dated someone else.
That's not all, is it?
Tell me. What happened between you two?
What on earth...
is Sol Ah to you?
Sol Ah is...
- Kim Sol Ah. - I see.
- What about me then? - You're Ko Doo Sik.
What is that? That's totally meaningless.
When you said Kim Sol Ah's name,
I thought you were going to use a poetic expression or something.
I'm Ko Doo Sik, she's Kim Sol Ah. Are you reading a roll book or what?
Hey.
Sol Ah even moved to the house across the street.
What are you going to do now?
Things will get noisy.
You never listen to me.
(Sonamu)
Hong Jo? How did you...
It's dangerous up there!
Hong Jo. What are you doing up there...
Did you just look at me?
When I called out, "Hong Jo", did you just look at me?
Hong Jo.
You did it again. You're really looking at me.
Gosh, you're acting all cute when you're in danger.
All right, fine. I'll save you. Come here.
No! Don't come down.
Wait right there. I'll save you.
Do not move an inch.
You know, Sol Ah is quite feminine.
We're just not aware since we've known her for so long.
She was in the art club in high school.
She's so delicate, a real woman.
Hong Jo, wait right there.
I'm on my way. I'm here.
Don't you worry.
I'm here. I'm here for you.
Hong Jo. Hong Jo?
Did I put the ladder here?
She gets scared so easily too.
Hong Jo. Where are you?
Hong Jo.
Hey! Come on, it was so hard coming up here.
Darn. Wait right there.
I can't believe it.
Wait for me.
I'm sorry.
Hong Jo.
Hong Jo. Hong Jo?
Where did he go?
Hong Jo.
By any chance, did you see a cat...
Wait, where did that guy suddenly pop out from?
He had some odd-looking eyes.
Oh, right.
Hong Jo, he had your eyes.
Does he live nearby?
I didn't even get to thank him.
If it weren't for him, I would've been hurt badly.
He saved me.
(Devoted Mr. Gogalbi)
There she goes, staring at the ground again.
I've never seen her.
She moved in to the second floor flat lately.
She's always like that, every time I see her.
Shoulders hunched like some shriveled up bracken.
How about some bracken for tomorrow's side dish?
Sounds good.
- Good job today. - I'll go boil them.
(High School Genius artist, Ko Doo Sik)
Why can't you talk to him?
It's a nightmare...
Some male ghost was pressing down on me.
Hong Jo, I'm off to work.
This is hers.
Can I have two dollars' worth of fish-shaped buns?
Okay.
Thank you.
Hi.
I was waving to that guy.
"That guy?"
Oh, my goodness.
I saved you.
Right, it's you. On the rooftop yesterday...
You suddenly disappeared, so I didn't get to thank you.
Thank you so much.
So... No!
That was on the ground.
I saved you.
I'll give you this. Here.
Do you live near here?
I moved here recently.
I'll see you next time then.
- Goodbye, ma'am. - Bye.
Hello.
We've met again.
What a strange coincidence.
Hey, you! You didn't pay your fare.
I saved you.
You must've left your bus card.
One more person, please.
I saved you.
(1 dollar, 90 cents)
He had to pick the one that costs 10 more cents.
- I saved you. - You saved me.
Yes, sure.
Are you all right?
I saved you.
I know you did, but how far will you follow me?
This is where I work. It's my workplace.
Only people who work here can enter.
If you're just here to play, go on your way, okay?
He looks just fine, but he's the village idiot.
I may look human,
but I can't even ride a bus without her.
Being a human has a time limit.
When I get tired and fall asleep,
I become a cat.
Cats sleep for an exceptionally long time.
Hong Jo, I'm home.
Hong Jo.
Hong Jo?
You tipped something over again.
My goodness.
Again?
It was open last time as well.
It was you.
Yes, well,
it is a very old house.
Where's my toothbrush?
Why do I keep...
Yes.
I'm just on edge because it's my first time living alone.
This won't work. I should go to bed early.
If I sleep...
Why is this...
Jae Seon!
Jae Seon! Lee Jae Seon!
What's wrong?
There's someone in my place!
Who's here?
There was definitely someone here.
It's not Sergei?
The balcony window's always open.
Can a cat open it with its paw?
You must've forgotten to close it.
You can't remember if you're wearing clothes or not.
It might be a pervert with a fetish for smelling breath.
My toothbrush disappeared.
It's under the bed?
Sergei.
Sergei's that pervert.
What about this then?
I gave it to the village idiot earlier today.
So what is it doing back here?
I don't know who the village idiot is,
but there's no one in this house.
It's just you and me.
You won't go and get...
the wrong idea again, will you?
Just because I called you over at night with barely anything on.
Hey! Don't give me that look.
It's not like that. Don't you ever get ideas.
I didn't say anything.
Anyway, thanks for coming over.
Oh. Do you want something to eat?
I have some jajang ramyeon.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'll be very clear. It's not ramyeon.
It's jajang ramyeon.
Okay then.
Okay.
I have something for you as well.
What's that?
I made something.
You made it yourself?
It's not much. I made it with leather scraps.
I wonder if it will fit.
Right. You're allergic to cats.
I'm fine.
Hey, will you...
Go away.
It's okay. Leave him alone.
No. Just a moment.
Come here.
Stay here for a while.
Will you cooperate? This is an important event.
It's beautiful. Thank you.
Here.
My gosh. It's just the right size.
It's not for your wrist.
What?
Oh, no wonder it was a bit big.
It's an anklet.
It's a collar for the cat.
- What? - It's for Sergei.
Oh.
You didn't carve its name on it, did you?
He has a new name. It's not Sergei.
Why?
You'll send him away soon anyway. Why confuse him?
- What did you name him? - I won't tell you.
Since I'll send him away, I'll keep his new name to myself.
He won't respond to it anyway.
He was Sergei since he was a kitten.
No. He looks at me when I call him.
What did you call him?
If I say "Hong Jo", he looks...
I said it.
"Hong Jo"?
I didn't expect that from you.
- What? - You're blushing.
The pot.
Ouch.
Hey, did you...
Will you...
Don't worry. I won't get the wrong idea.
What if it's...
the right idea?
(GFRIEND's Umji's OST "Welcome" has been released.)
(Meow, the Secret Boy)
I think that guy is a cat.
He could really be a weirdo.
He's like a kid. He needs looking after.
I told you to be careful. It's dangerous.
That man?
I don't know what he's thinking.
What more is there to say? It's just you.
That guy who came over. He's the Beodul Love, right?