(Episode 7)
Hey, kitty! I'm going to eat you up!
Oh, right.
I'm no longer a dog.
(This webtoon series will stop being published.)
It's a little embarrassing to upload a notice.
No one's even waiting to read the next one.
I'm craving tteokbokki.
One that's made with really thick rice cakes.
Do you want to go and eat tteokbokki together?
One that's made with rice cakes.
Hey, you're amazing.
Do you even know how to read minds?
But I guess you don't know how to tell time.
I need to go to work.
Thanks...
for last night.
(Sonamu)
Hey.
The weather is great today.
The breeze is very nice.
I'll see you then.
("We're not the ones who decide to raise cats.")
("Cats are the ones who decide to live with us.")
(Quote by Paul Leyhausen)
Are you interested?
(We're hiring.)
I don't want your money.
(Sonamu)
Hey, why are you going to stop publishing your webtoon?
I'm done publishing "Beodul Love".
Why? It means so much to you.
I'm also done with Jae Seon.
What?
Can you set me up on a blind date?
Will you stop being so lame?
What? This is what people always do.
Seeing a different guy is the best way to get over a guy.
No, not that.
You told me so many times that you were done with Jae Seon.
I made it clear with him too.
I told him that I'm going to stop following him around like a puppy.
I'm sick of liking a guy who's like a cat.
You're right. You should start seeing someone.
A blind date? Okay. What kind of guy do you want?
Someone who's like a dog.
Is that supposed to be a good thing?
Someone who likes no one else but me like a loyal dog.
Someone who only cares about me,
follows me around, and always waits for me.
From now on, I'm only going to date guys who are like dogs.
Hey, you're that kind young man.
You're here again.
Welcome.
Have a seat.
Hey, you're the guy who came here with Dae Sung last time.
Today, you came alone. Come here and take a seat.
You don't have any money?
Call your family or something.
My goodness.
My gosh, I thought you were a decent young man.
You look completely normal, but this is very impolite.
I guess he really wanted to eat here.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Stop.
Don't touch anything. Leave everything as it is.
I'll teach him a lesson and turn him into a decent human being.
She's going to make me human?
(Devoted Mr. Gogalbi)
My gosh, he's so handsome.
My goodness.
Hey, guys. I'm back.
Hey, you're...
Sorry.
Were you also in my high school art club?
You seem oddly familiar.
- You're here. - Did you hire a part-timer?
Well, I'd love to hire him.
But your mom's keeping him here.
I'm keeping an eye on him so he doesn't do anything funny.
Mom, you really know nothing about marketing.
Look at this place. It's completely packed.
He's handsome enough to be your lucky charm.
Well, it's nice to see that we have a lot of customers today.
Gosh, but I never got to take a break today.
Let me sit down for a minute. My goodness.
Gosh, I want to get a massage.
My gosh, it's okay. We have customers here.
Okay, fine. That feels very nice.
You're doing great. Yes, that's it.
- Sorry to keep you waiting. - Oh, gosh.
My goodness, I'm sorry. Let me...
- It's okay. - No, I'll get you a new one.
I'm sorry. Gosh, I should throw this away.
He's a dog.
- I guess he really likes it. - He's a dog.
- Our fish is really delicious. - He's definitely a dog.
- Enjoy. - Jae Seon.
Be honest with me. Do you like Sol Ah or not?
Are you going to ask her out or not?
- What? - Are you going to date her or not?
What are you doing?
Stop being so vague.
I respected your way of doing things,
and Sol Ah told me to stay quiet, so I did.
But this is where it ends.
It's time to draw a clear line this time.
Stop giving Sol Ah hope.
I don't intend on giving her hope.
Good for you, you punk.
I'm going to set her up on a blind date.
What?
Should I not?
- Do whatever you want. - You'd better not regret it.
Who's the guy?
Hey, Doo Sik.
I'm waiting on top of the stairs.
How long do I need to wait for that guy who's like a dog?
I sent him on a cab, so he'll be right there.
Guk Bong.
What are you doing here?
I'm here on a blind date.
You too?
Look at you all dressed up.
Well, I wish you good luck.
Is this where you're meeting your blind date?
No way.
Did Ko Doo Sik send you here?
Then are you the dog...
I mean, the part-timer?
You work at Devoted Mr. Gogalbi?
I haven't been on a blind date in ages.
What do you think about me...
as your blind date?
Blind date, my foot.
Forget it. Let's just go get some food.
Come on.
Stop following me from behind.
Where are you going?
You told me not to walk behind you.
No, I meant let's walk together.
My gosh, let's go.
Look.
Hello, we opened a kimchi stew restaurant.
Participate in the event, and win a free gift.
- It's being held over there. - To celebrate our opening,
- Let's try that. - we're holding an event.
- Hello. - Hello.
If you guess the correct cup, you get to win a prize.
- Would you like to play the game? - Yes.
Okay then.
This one.
- You're wrong. - Let me try one more time.
- One more time? Okay. - Yes.
This one.
- You're wrong. - Let me try one last time.
- One last time? Okay. - Yes, it'll be the last time.
Okay.
- It's my last time. - It's in here.
- Okay. - Watch carefully.
(Play a game with the swindler, and win a free gift.)
This one?
Goodness, I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
Would you like to give it a try?
- Yes, he wants to play. - Okay then.
Gosh, you got it right! Nice!
Try it again. Try it one more time.
(Free gift)
One more time.
Gosh, I was really impressed.
- What do you want to eat? - Tteokbokki made with rice cakes.
"Tteokbokki"? There's a place I frequently go to.
Should we eat a spicy one or...
No, let's eat the sweet one today.
Hey.
Hey, I thought you wanted tteokbokki.
Yes, tteokbokki.
Let's go eat that.
There's a tteokbokki restaurant right around the corner.
They use freshly made rice cakes, so it's very chewy...
Tteokbokki...
It's okay. Eat up.
Hey, you can't just...
You need to put it in front of you first.
We can't call this a blind date, but I had a lot of fun.
Thank you.
I always used to envy my friends who had older siblings.
I wonder if I could think of you as my older brother.
Did you get touched by what I said?
You're so not my older brother.
Are you going to stop drawing "Beodul Love"?
I want to keep seeing your drawings.
I don't know what to draw next.
Draw whatever you want.
I found out that people don't always like what I like.
And more importantly, I don't know what I want to draw next.
I guess other people have it all figured out.
I guess they quickly get new ideas.
But not me.
I guess I'm just not good enough.
Try looking for it again. I'm sure you'll be able to find it.
I'm not sure.
But when are you leaving?
I'm leaving?
You're not?
Oh, I see. Are you going to leave after you save up some money?
Why would I leave?
I thought your dream is to become a travel writer.
No, it's not.
Then what's your dream?
(Jae Seon)
The person you have reached is unavailable.
(Sonamu)
(Call logs, Kim Sol Ah)
I'm going to put this in my room.
And I'm going to put this one on my desk.
Where should I put this?
Where were you?
On a blind date.
Yes. A date. I had a blind date.
I called you.
Oh, did you?
I didn't know.
It's been a while since I had fun that I couldn't check my phone.
We ate sushi and I got this as a present.
Your present is a cat doll?
You don't like cats.
Well, anyway,
Bang Guk Bong used his amazing dynamic visual acuity to win...
Wait.
Your blind date was with Mr. Bang?
Yes.
The point is that...
I'm eating and living just fine.
As if nothing's wrong. Everything's fine.
I'm going now. Hey, let's go.
I have something to say.
I don't.
I found someone who'll take the cat.
Hong Jo?
Who?
Someone who likes cats.
I shouldn't have left him with you from the start.
Thanks so far.
And sorry.
They'll come for him tomorrow evening.
Tomorrow?
Will you really send him away?
Yes.
I should.
I was just fostering.
I knew I had to send him away.
I thought you two got close.
Do you know how Hong Jo came to me?
There's a complicated history involved with Jae Seon.
It's for the best.
It's all for the better.
I should get some cat snacks.
Since he's leaving tomorrow.
A person who abandon cats.
A person who won't keep them close.
(Devoted Mr. Gogalbi)
A person who took a cat in...
only to send it away.
Will you really send him away?
Yes.
I should.
I'm not a person.
I'm a cat.
Don't you think this cat is beautiful?
Did it lose its owner?
Cats don't have owners.
What do you mean?
Dogs have owners but cats don't.
Cats just choose who they want to live with.
And this cat chose you.
Really?
Then can I take it home?
It's used to living outdoors.
It will come to see you.
I want to give it a snack.
Grandma!
What a lie.
Humans make the choice.
Not the cat.
Grandma, you were abandoned too.
Like me.
I'll be abandoned once more.
As always, the choice...
was the human's.
There's only one option.
To become...
a real human.
Kitty, have some anchovies.
How do you become a human?
A human?
My grandma once told me a fairy tale.
Where can I find mugwort?
To become human,
do I have to wait until spring?
Hong Jo, I brought you a snack.
Hong Jo!
What do you think he ate this time?
Well, I think...
I think he ate garlic.
Last time it was milk. This time it's garlic.
You keep feeding your cat weird stuff.
Is it so you can see me once more?
What?
I was just kidding. You looked so serious.
His symptoms aren't too bad. I'll give him some medicine.
If he still seems unwell, bring him right back.
Play with him when you have the time.
He could be causing trouble just to get your attention.
(Vitamin drink)
I'm sorry.
Oh? Ji Eun?
Do you live nearby?
Yes. Do you live in this neighborhood?
Yes.
Take one first.
No. You go first.
Okay then.
(Buy 1 get 1 free)
Oh, it's... It's okay.
Thank you.
Bye.
See you at work.
I go this way too.
You don't have to walk me.
I'll go on my own.
Okay. Take care.
Why do you keep following me?
I'm just going home.
Just because you realized we went to the same high school,
doesn't mean...
you have to suddenly act so nice.
Was that too much?
But I really do go this way.
This won't work. I should overtake her.
Why... You needn't...
What...
Will you not follow me?
Darn it.
What does she think I'll do?
(Devoted Mr. Gogalbi)
I feel like something just passed by.
- Hey, Dad. I'm back. - Hey, you're back.
Why do you look so down?
I think someone at work hates me.
My gosh, this is crazy.
Stay still.
See? I can't even brush him properly.
I don't deserve him.
I keep you alone all day because I'm busy with work.
And in the evenings, I'm busy drawing my webtoon.
Plus, I always make you get sick.
You should meet someone who truly cares for you.
I'm too careless with you.
Good boy.
You should look nice and pretty and make a good impression.
I didn't ask for this hairstyle.
I'll be fine as long as I don't fall asleep.
Then I'll stay human.
Hong Jo.
Hey, have you seen Hong Jo?
Did you open the window?
I hope he didn't go outside.
I won't leave.
No, not you. I was talking about Hong Jo.
I'm not going to leave.
I'm going to stay.
Here.
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
What about your dream to become a travel writer?
My dream is to become human.
A real human.
I guess you also have trouble falling asleep.
You keep thinking weird things.
Milk is the best cure for insomnia.
- What are you doing? - I'm making a shadow.
Oh, a dog?
That's not how you do it.
This is how you do it. Stick your fingers together.
Then you do this.
- What about a cat? - "A cat"?
I don't know.
Should I adopt a dog after I send away the cat?
I'm not going to fall asleep.
(Episode 8)
Bang Guk Bong.
Bang Guk Bong. Are you up?
I'm coming in.
Excuse me.
Oh.
Gosh.
What?
Where is he hiding?
I prepared this for his last day.
Did you get his things?
The cat's things? Not yet.
I need something of yours. To come back.
What?
I mean...
He must be used to you. Let's give him something of yours.
Oh. Shall we then?
Oh.
Why would you put this in there?
What are you playing at?
My gosh.
Hey! Not this! Are you crazy?
My goodness. Darn you.
Must you send him away?
What if he comes back?
Cats don't come back.
Only dogs do that.
What if he does?
I'll send him back.
I'll be late.
Feed Hong Jo the snacks if you see him. And lock up.
Roads are dangerous,
and lots of people don't like cats. See you.
You don't like them too.
- Cats. - A leading food company...
is releasing a pet food brand.
The client's a large company. Who wants the project?
Whoever pulls this off will be seen in a whole new light.
- Ji Eun? - What?
Why would someone else answer?
I mean...
Ji Eun does work hard,
but she lacks the experience,
and projects like these...
I'd like a fresh approach.
- A fresh approach? - Ji Eun...
seems a bit overwhelmed.
Someone can accompany her.
Let's see...
Ko Doo Sik, Kim Sol Ah.
Yes?
What?
Oh, yes?
Sol Ah, are you working on "Beodul Love"?
I'm envious.
You have time for yourself when at work.
When does the next episode come up?
I quit that webtoon.
My ego was so transparent that I found it right away.
Too bad.
Don't be too disappointed. You have great techniques.
Not everyone has to be creative.
Some have to take a supporting role.
Quietly and staunchly, behind the scenes.
Yes, I guess.
The three of you can come up with a proposal.
- Okay, will do. - Okay.
This is good.
Sorry for not recognizing you after drawing together for three years.
Now that I recognize you, it feels like we're great friends.
Yes.
Hey. Anyone can tell that she's uncomfortable.
When we're alone, how about we speak freely?
Eun Ji.
It's Ji Eun. Ji Eun.
I know. It's Eun Ji Eun.
I was confused...
Sorry, Eun Ji Eun.
Ms. Eun?
You're really having trouble eating. Do you need some help?
(Indirect kiss!)
I'll take some more.
- Some soup too. - Hey, that spoon is dirty.
Is that better?
Just have mine.
(You don't have to stop him.)
- Really? - Yes.
- Have mine. - Wait.
I need to use the bathroom.
We should've left her to eat her lunchbox.
Why did we bring her here to make things awkward?
- Hey. - What?
Of course it's awkward.
She's the one who tattled it to Ms. Park.
Imagine how she would feel.
No way. Don't jump to conclusions.
You're the one who should stop overreacting.
It's not easy getting over Jae Seon, is it?
You look so haggard.
It's not what you think.
I'm sending the cat away too today.
I feel much better now.
Get over that cat with a dog.
How did the blind date go?
Didn't I tell you?
Those darn cats ate all the food waste...
What's with that face, young man? Why do you look so depressed?
Are you worried about something?
I'm the man you should come to when you're worried.
Back in the days, my middle name was "worry".
So, tell me what's up.
It seems to me like it's not about some childish dating problem.
She's getting rid of me.
It is a dating problem.
Yes, I knew it. Every time, dating is the problem.
Of course she'll get rid of me.
If I think about it, I haven't done anything for her.
All I did was receive things.
Well, it's natural for people to rely on others.
I'm not even a person.
What are you then? Are you a cat?
Yes.
I see.
How can I become a real person?
Even I'm not a proper person either.
Gosh, you.
You should've told me from the beginning.
I heard he's Sol Ah's stepbrother.
- What? Is that true? - Yes.
If he's family with Sol Ah, he's like family to us too.
I know. We can't even order him around from now on.
- I guess so. - What do we do?
The restaurant is a mess right now.
We need all the help we can get.
It's not like money makes a person,
but it is necessary for people to live more properly.
Consider it an advance from your paycheck.
- It's made with rice cakes, right? - Yes, it is.
Do you want some fried snacks too?
She didn't say anything like that.
Hong Jo, I'm home.
Hong Jo.
Hong Jo, where are you?
Where did he go?
What do I do?
Hong Jo.
Should I go ask Jae Seon?
I should keep looking for him.
Hong Jo.
What do I do?
(Cat Shelter)
Shall I rest in here?
Hong Jo.
- Did you see the dead cat? - Yes.
I feel so sorry for it.
Where is that cat?
I lost my cat.
The security guard buried it in that empty lot over there.
Hong Jo.
Please...
Miss, what are you doing here?
I'm looking for a cat.
I heard a dead cat was buried here.
Oh, that cat?
It got hit by a car, so I buried it here.
Was it yours?
I don't think it is.
- Thank you. - I thought...
you were going to hurt the cat.
Why would someone do that?
Because they're noisy,
dirty, or believed to bring bad luck.
Because they're weaker than humans.
People even abandon their pets.
I saw an expensive breed nearby.
It had hurt its leg.
I was waiting to catch it and look after it.
Abandoned pets?
An abandoned pet cat is as good as dead.
It'll get much colder soon.
Is Sol Ah in?
Why won't she answer her phone?
I came for the cat. Can I come in?
The new owner's waiting for it.
The agreed time's already passed.
I'll just take the cat.
You can't take it.
I talked about it with Sol Ah.
The cat's not here...
anymore.
What does that mean?
Cats are like that.
When it's time to leave,
they leave on their own.
Hey.
Wait.
I'll turn into a cat if I sleep.
And I'll be abandoned.
(Sonamu)
Kim Sol Ah.
What happened?
The new owner waited for a long time.
Sorry.
Did something happen?
I lost it.
Hong Jo.
What?
When?
I don't know.
You don't even know when he disappeared?
I didn't see him this morning...
And you didn't care?
He always comes back after...
So what?
So you always left the window open?
I told you to be careful.
Yes.
I'm sorry for being careless.
But all this while...
Neglecting it is abandonment too.
What?
You abandoned him.
Again.
"Again"?
What are you saying? Why would I abandon Hong Jo?
Do you think...
I still have feelings for you,
so I got rid of the cat your ex-girlfriend had?
Do you think that little of me?
It's not that. You...
I didn't abandon Hong Jo.
The one I abandoned...
is you, Jae Seon, not Hong Jo.
I shouldn't have taken in his cat at all.
A cat is a cat.
I just can't like...
Hong Jo.
You darn cat.
I can't help it. I am a dog.
A dog that...
fell for a cat.
Tteokbokki and fish-shaped buns?
Thanks anyway.
Let's eat.
If I hadn't gone out to look for Hong Jo,
it wouldn't have gotten so soggy.
You were...
looking for the cat all this time?
Yes. I thought I'd lost him, but he was sleeping in the closet.
That shameless jerk.
Why did you look for it?
It's not your cat.
There's a saying.
Cats don't have owners.
It's the cat that chooses which human it wants to be with.
I bet humans came up with that.
To avoid the responsibility.
I guess that's possible.
What would you choose?
I don't know.
(Missing cat)
(It's called Hong Jo.)
Hello?
I'm the person who said I'd take the cat.
I'm sorry about earlier.
The cat...
Oh, no. I think it worked out, actually.
Pardon?
I just found out that I'm pregnant.
I'd resorted to having a pet instead of a child.
We've been trying so hard, you see.
I'm sorry.
The doctors had said we were infertile,
but we got pregnant.
I'm sorry.
Don't go. Mom.
Mom, don't go.
- This will be... - Mom.
- his second time being abandoned. - Mom, don't go.
- We're really sorry. - Don't go. Don't go!
Don't go. Don't go.
I'm sorry.
Jae Seon.
(I'm sorry.)
I found him in the closet.
He was fast asleep.
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
Hand him over.
I'll take him.
Sorry, but you can't have him.
I won't let you.
You can't have him.
Why not?
You don't like cats.
I like...
Hong Jo.
(I'm alone again today.)
I think I found something I want to draw.
Who lost their passport?
Mr. Bang Guk Bong?
Are you Mr. Bang Guk Bong?
(Meow, the Secret Boy)
Hong Jo likes you too.
Did you just come out of that house?
She liked him for 10 years?
It has been a long time.
There's no room for me to get in between.
Who are you?
I might not be able to show up in front of you.
You really won't talk about yourself.
I want to be with you.
What can't you say?
You put the scarf around a boy's neck?
Hong Jo was wrapped in this scarf?