(Episode 5)
Look. There he is. The village idiot.
It's him. He followed me around all day.
I can't believe he even followed me home.
Who are you?
Get out.
What? That's what I should be saying.
My gosh, you're acting like you live here or something.
Hello? I'm a little busy right now.
Actually, there's some guy...
Did my son come home by any chance?
What?
He sent me an email.
He sent me a photo of the Uyuni Salt Flat in Bolivia...
and wrote "Going home" right beneath it.
Isn't that so poetic?
He comes and goes whenever he wants without really saying anything.
And he comes in through the balcony instead of the front door.
So don't get too startled.
And unlike me, he has milky-white skin.
He's really dashing.
You might get shocked by how good-looking he is.
Anyway, he doesn't have a cell phone,
so let me know if he arrives.
I think he's here already.
Here. It's your mother.
You made her worry. Don't try to avoid her.
Hello?
- Guk Bong, is that you? - Well...
It's so hard to see you, my son.
Are you healthy?
Send me some photos you took during your trip.
- Well... - Oh, right.
I sent you dried filefish fillet. Share them with Sol Ah.
Will you answer me? Why aren't you saying anything?
You love dried filefish fillet. It's dried fish.
Well, yes.
Let me introduce him to you.
Did you introduce yourself to Sol Ah?
What am I supposed to call him?
Like I told you before,
you guys may be the same age, but you were born earlier.
You're older?
("Comets are like cats.")
("They have tails, and they do precisely what they want.")
(Quote by David Levy)
Your name is Guk Bong, right?
I heard you use your mother's last name,
so that means your name is...
Bang Guk Bong.
No.
Don't you like your name? Bang Guk Bong?
Don't call me that.
Why are you talking to me like I'm your friend?
Can you keep your manners?
Things are already pretty awkward between us.
You secretly watched me...
without even telling me who you are.
That's not even funny.
I didn't move in here because I wanted to.
And I pay rent even though it might not be that much.
So you can't just show up and kick my friend out like that.
- "Friend"? - Yes.
- He's my friend. - You guys...
aren't friends.
Do you think you're my older brother or something?
You keep talking to me without honorifics.
Okay, fine. Let's talk comfortably if that's what you want.
Bang Guk Bong.
Hong Jo.
I left him outside the balcony.
Did you see him on your way in?
Did you leave the folding door open?
My gosh.
What's going on?
Hong Jo.
Where were you?
Come here.
What?
Did he go upstairs?
I have a bad feeling about the new house.
I think that guy...
is a cat.
"A cat"?
For some reason, so many people around me are like cats.
What did you spill on your jacket?
You kind of smell funny.
This?
If you're hungry, let's have breakfast.
Can you make some toast?
What an interesting guy.
He's like a kid. I feel like I should take care of him.
Forget about that.
You've always been taking care of your dad.
And now, you're even going to take care...
of your dad's girlfriend's son?
That's why you always get involved with people need care...
and don't have anyone who takes care of you.
Take this.
What?
Your so-called brother left it here.
He did? This is my umbrella.
Why would he use my stuff?
See? Guk Bong does whatever he wants.
I wonder if I should move out and get a new place.
Why would you move out?
Don't even think about it. Let me see that guy in person.
Jae Seon, do you have time this evening?
This guy might really be a freak.
I guess I could close early today.
Okay.
We'll go there and intimidate that guy.
You're going to come to my place?
I'm not Bang Guk Bong.
Hey, Guk Bong.
My friends are coming over tonight. Is that okay with you?
"Friends"?
You mean that guy?
That's actually why I'm cleaning. Can you help me take out the trash?
I also need to go grocery shopping.
What was that?
You need to step on plastic bottles and cans...
so that they don't take up too much space.
Then you just put them in the box.
There.
And as for the boxes...
What are you doing?
I'm going to go to the supermarket.
What? Do you also need something?
Would you like to come with me?
(Fresh Fish)
Goodness! Hey!
What?
What are you doing?
Hurry up and take it out!
Hong Jo likes fish.
Are you serious? What is the matter with you?
My gosh.
I'm sorry about that.
Are you insane? Those are the ones we can take.
(Fresh fish for memorial services)
Hey!
Why are you buying so many?
Hong Jo likes salmon.
How do you know what he likes already?
These are mine.
Let's pay separately. You have money, right?
You don't have any money?
What should I do?
- I'll pay for that as well. - Okay.
I'll just have to bear with him.
I'll just have to bear with everything.
- Hey, you're here. - Hey.
Where is he?
I think he left without saying anything.
Is it okay living here?
Does he...
I brought you a gift.
- You're allergic. - I took some medicine.
This is what you call true love.
I guess we both struggle...
with love.
- What? - What?
That must be Doo Sik.
Hey. Where is he?
Where is he?
Why do you look like that?
To intimidate him.
Mr. Bang Guk Bong.
I came to say hello. Why don't you come down here?
- He's not home right now. - What?
He got scared, didn't he?
Gosh, it's hot.
Remember when you fainted after the pirate ship ride?
You fainted right next to me.
I told you what you need to do to not get scared.
I know, but I was still scared.
Jae Seon, you still wear that ring?
Well, yes.
This is the art club ring.
I still have it.
I bet you do.
You cherished it more than your own life.
Do you remember?
- The ski resort? - Yes.
She fell while snowboarding and broke her finger.
Her finger turned purple because it was so swollen.
But when we tried to cut the ring, she threw a fit and told us...
- to cut her finger instead. - Hey, hey.
It wasn't even a promise ring. It was just a friendship ring.
- That's enough. - Fine.
Do whatever you want.
- Where are you going? - Where are you going? You're drunk.
Let me take a tour around the house.
Is this the bathroom?
Sorry.
Wait a minute. Was that him?
Hey, you're here. Why didn't you...
What's wrong with this house?
I need to pee.
I haven't seen you laugh like this in a long time.
Really?
No one else other than us can make you laugh like this.
You're right.
Things are finally back to normal.
I agree.
Why did you run away...
if you were going to come back like this?
You really know how to put on an innocent face.
I'm sure you remember what happened between us.
You have to go to work.
Yes.
I think something just happened.
Did something happen?
Something definitely happened.
Go to work.
See you this evening.
I'll pick you up from home.
What?
Is this getting out of hand?
Maybe. And it looks bad.
Let's go.
Okay.
(Jae Seon)
Where are you?
Is something wrong?
(Where are you? Is something wrong?)
It was a legendarily cold night.
The cold showed up instead of the guy I was waiting for.
Sorry.
You apologize so indifferently.
Do you want to feel so indifferent?
So you keep running away?
So nothing will happen to your life?
You ran off to another woman...
and ran away from her too.
I'm right.
You ran away from her.
I knew it.
You also...
ran away from home.
But still, thanks.
For coming back.
To my side.
Will something happen again?
Between you and me?
I told you.
To me, you are...
Kim Sol Ah.
You're saying that again.
That's good enough for me.
What is Sol Ah to you?
Sol Ah is...
Kim Sol Ah.
What is that?
That's totally meaningless.
Need I say anything else?
Friends,
lovers, terms like that...
can work for others too.
Only you can be Kim Sol Ah.
There's just one of you.
- Hey. - Gosh.
- I'm fine. - You're not.
The human language helps them understand each other.
Get home safely!
But it also brings upon misunderstandings.
So basically...
it's just me.
No one else works for him...
but me.
He means that you can't be anything more to him.
Yes. Kim Sol Ah is a proper noun.
There's only one of me. I'm irreplaceable.
I'm a proper noun.
My goodness.
Since when were you there?
For a while.
I wish you'd say something when you come and go.
Okay. Sleep well yourself.
(Will you upload "Helpless Beodul Love" Episode 1?)
Shall I click yes?
Or not?
Look.
This is my lucky ring.
I won a drawing contest when I wore this ring.
Will Jae Seon see it too?
("Helpless Beodul Love" Episode 1 upload complete.)
Don't you read this, Lee Jae Seon.
No, no, no. I want everyone I know to not read it.
I read it.
- What? - "Helpless Beodul Love".
Was that yours?
- How did you know? - How could I not?
It's titled "Helpless Beodul Love". As if that nickname's forgettable.
- Why did you read it? - I had to read it.
My parents, my three sisters, and their husbands read it too.
- To up your views. - Hey!
You're welcome.
- Hello. - Good morning.
Sol Ah. I read "Helpless Beodul Love".
I'm reading it right now.
Hello, Ms. Kim the cartoonist.
Do you think you could give me an autograph?
Excuse us.
(Beodul Love, open the door.)
(Can't I come with you?)
Are you out of your mind? You told them?
It was to help you.
What if Ms. Park hears and thinks I want to quit my job?
No, she wouldn't.
You're so stupid.
Good morning.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Good morning. - Ji Eun.
How about a coffee before we get to work?
Sure.
What now?
Wait.
Does she know?
I can't hear from here.
Do you think she's telling right now?
Yes.
Turn around.
Excuse me.
What did you tell Ms. Park?
I mean, it's just in case you got the wrong idea.
It's about my webtoon.
I work on that at night after work or on the weekends.
So it won't get in the way, I always put my job first.
Did you... tell Ms. Park about it?
Why would I...
tell her?
What? Because...
Because I was given a job?
Is that what you think?
She's really hard to read.
I know, right?
Anyway, that means she got in using her connections, right?
No, it means the opposite.
She was upset that we thought of her that way...
because it's not true.
No, it means she did get the job using her connections...
but isn't a tattletale.
Cat language is so difficult.
This is all because you told everyone about...
Hey, wait.
Did you show Jae Seon as well?
- I wonder if he saw it. - Hey.
- Or maybe he hasn't seen it yet. - Answer my question.
I sent the link, but he didn't reply.
Maybe he's busy. That's probably why he didn't reply.
Thank you.
Here are your drinks.
- Hey. - Do you need anything else?
- It's okay. - Okay.
Hey...
You seem busy.
Yes, but I can talk. What's up?
- If you're busy, I'll just... - No, I can talk.
By any chance,
did you read my webtoon?
Did you leave the window open?
What?
Hong Jo?
Do you think he came to greet me?
I told you to be careful. It's dangerous.
Gosh, okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Just a second.
- Yes? - We'd like one cheesecake...
and one whipped cream cake.
Okay. Anything else?
Why did he suddenly shut his heart?
Hong Jo, why don't you tell me?
Why do you think Beodul Love suddenly shut the door?
Hey, come on.
You're my first reader.
You saw everything up close for the very first time.
My gosh.
Maybe I shouldn't have uploaded this.
(Why won't he open up?)
(I wonder if he isn't cold.)
What does this mean?
(Why won't he open up?)
Giyeok. Nieun. Digeut.
Do you get it?
What is this?
"Haemong Flower Landscaping".
"Jungdon Real Estate Agency".
"Devoted Mr. Gogalbi".
You won't repeat?
Here comes your fish.
Fish...
Do you have money?
No.
Be a bear.
What?
You don't have any money?
I'll pay for that as well.
Yes.
I'll just have to bear with him.
No way. You mean...
you want me to bear your costs too?
You should learn manners before the alphabet.
It's a nuisance to ask just anyone for money.
And it's rude to ask them to bear things for you.
That's how the public sentiment is like these days.
Hey. Aren't you Dae Sung?
How are you?
You said it's a nuisance.
This is called looking out for neighbors.
Here's your fish. I hope you enjoy it.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- Sir? - Yes?
- Can we have more kimchi? - Of course.
Dae Sung.
Who is this cute-looking guy?
My friend.
Your friend? What were you two doing?
We study the alphabet as well as basic manners.
Enjoy your meal. Dae Sung, eat all you want.
Isn't he sweet?
Yes. Young men these days wouldn't do that much.
How many people read it?
1,000 people? 10,000 people?
(17 views)
Isn't this a bit too few?
Me, Ko Doo Sik, Ko Doo Sik's family,
our coworkers...
Just three other people read it?
Was Jae Seon 1 of those 3?
Will you stop shaking your leg?
What?
I'm not shaking my leg.
She caught you slacking off.
This won't do. I'll use her weakness.
Ji Eun?
Yes?
Could I buy you a coffee?
A good friend opened a cafe and workshop.
Here.
(Sonamu, 1 free americano)
The darn light bulb.
I need to put in a new one.
What?
I wish someone would look at it for me.
Hong Jo.
Are you showing concern for...
As if you would.
Cats are like that.
No cat would hug someone for being in pain.
(Sonamu, 1 free americano)
Can I get you anything else?
Oh, no thanks.
You again.
Why do you keep creeping up on me like that?
Are you a cat or what?
I want to look.
- At what? - Your drawing.
I'm sorry, but I need to focus.
Can you not stand behind me?
Who told you to stand in front of me?
Can you please leave?
Your room is upstairs,
isn't it?
What was that?
- Doo Sik? - Come out for a second.
Hye Yeon and Da Som said they wanted to see Jae Seon's cafe.
We're almost there.
Hey, but...
Come on, I know you live right across the street.
I'll order you a coffee.
- Get over here. - But...
He's so stubborn.
Hong Jo, I'm going out.
You're here.
Yes. Doo Sik said he's bringing some of our colleagues.
- They're here. - Jae Seon, I brought guests.
They work with me at Nalsaem Design.
He's my friend. He owns the place.
You're so handsome.
This cafe is so beautiful.
Are those leather items handmade?
Oh, yes.
- Do you guys want some coffee? - Sure.
- What will you have? - An Americano?
- Me too. - Coming right up.
Please have some.
Then are you three friends from the high school art club?
Yes. Our art club was famous.
We won all the medals at the national art competition.
Sol Ah won bronze, Jae Seon won silver...
Wait. Who won the gold medal?
I don't know. Was it someone from our school?
Why don't you know? You don't remember?
You know, that person. It was that...
Oh, it seems like my memory is coming back. It was a guy, right?
Yes, right. A guy.
Right. Wasn't he a year older than us?
- Right? - Yes, yes!
- I remember now. - You're right.
He was older. He was a big guy too.
- Right. Man, you're really smart. - I know.
Hold on. But what was his name?
Name? His name was...
She's right there.
What?
- Ji Eun. - How long was she sitting there?
I just got goosebumps.
How do you know Ji Eun?
She was in our art club too.
I didn't know she worked with you.
She was in our art club?
The one who won the gold medal?
Oh, that...
I... No, I mean...
See? She said no. You don't even know.
No, that's not what I meant...
She means she didn't win the gold medal.
If she didn't win the gold medal...
The Grand Prize.
What...
You're drawing Beodul Love again?
- You have such elegant taste. - What's wrong with that?
Beodul Love is my ideal type.
You knew, right?
What?
That we were in the same art club at high school.
Why didn't you tell us?
- I did. - What?
I know what Beodul Love is too.
It's about my webtoon.
I know what that ring is too.
I was in the same art club as you guys in high school.
Do you see this ring?
We were in the same art club.
It's true! The ring.
Eun Ji Eun. You're that Eun Ji Eun.
Now I remember. You wore glasses, right?
I have perfect eyesight.
Right, not glasses, but you had braces.
You wore braces, right?
I have healthy teeth.
She transferred to another school,
so we didn't have time to become friends.
Or did you transfer to our school?
- You don't remember, do you? - No.
Well, I can't remember all of my friends from high school either.
- Right. - Anyhow, what a coincidence.
But Jae Seon, how did you know?
This is the Lee Jae Seon that I like.
He seems cold and indifferent,
but actually, he's watching everything.
Even things other people overlook, so meticulously.
Like a cat.
I'm sure he saw my webtoon too.
Sol Ah, why aren't you uploading...
the next episode of "Helpless Beodul Love"?
What?
I'm curious why Beodul Love suddenly closed the door.
That's...
It's obvious. Since he doesn't like her.
There could be another reason. They even kissed.
The reason isn't important.
He said no,
but continuing to ask him why is so annoying. Isn't it?
That's true. Not accepting the fact she was rejected...
and continuing to knock on the door is a bit inappropriate.
She will become more mature in the next episode, right?
Instead of waiting in front of that door pathetically?
I'm not sure.
Why? I like a woman who looks after me.
Jae Seon, did you see Sol Ah's webtoon?
(Why won't he open up?)
(I wonder if he isn't cold.)
I'm hoping it's a different story.
It seems like you're too obsessed with the story about Beodul Love.
I'm sure the Kim Sol Ah I know can tell a different story.
I'm just hoping.
That's what I was thinking. It's too cliche.
An obvious fantasy where a girl gets saved by a guy?
That's not the story.
Hey.
I just opened it up now,
and her views increased, and there are even comments.
(Look at the number of views. The writer is crying right now.)
(That girl is such an annoying character.)
(My 9-year-old daughter loves this story.)
(Please keep your childish diary to yourself.)
Something came up at home, so I have to get going.
Sol Ah...
Hey, you.
Stop looking at it.
It's just an obvious fantasy.
A man saving a woman.
It's actually Beodul Love who was saved.
To save him from being locked in the cave,
the girl visits every day in the cold winter...
to knock on the door.
Do you want a drink?
It's lactose-free milk because of the cat. Do you mind?
So,
where did you get that idea?
You're just like Hong Jo.
Where did you usually stay?
By the window.
No, I mean, where was the favorite place you visited?
The roof.
You know more than you show.
I thought you were an idiot.
It's the guy who was here, right?
Beodul Love.
You know things you don't need to.
(Why won't he open up?)
Go to work. See you this evening.
I'll pick you up from home.
(Sol Ah)
The person you have reached is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Where are you?
Is something wrong?
(Where are you? Is something wrong?)
(Unread)
You promised to meet and he disappeared?
Just like Beodul Love?
How much do you want to know?
Without an explanation or greeting?
He had met someone else.
That was the explanation and greeting.
Why do you like someone like him?
It wasn't one-sided from my part.
Jae Seon does disappear when he wants to sometimes,
but he always comes back.
Did he come back?
What?
Isn't it you...
that came back?
No.
We're a bit like that.
Like planets that can't stay away from each other.
But you can't get closer either.
Did you always come back...
to orbit around him?
Yes.
You're right.
I'm a puppy.
He took me far away and left me there,
and I came back, wagging my tail.
Waiting by the door, asking to be let in.
I'm a little dog.
He'll keep you waiting by the door.
He won't let you in.
You came back to him,
and he isn't thankful at all.
What's the matter?
Why are you...
leaving me by the door?
Come in whenever you want.
Let me in or send me away. Do just one thing.
If you're a friend, stay a friend.
Don't check my temperature and get me medicine like a boyfriend.
If you're sick of being Beodul Love,
don't act like Beodul Love.
Let's talk inside. I felt bothered about...
what I'd said about your webtoon.
Exactly.
You should've been more clear.
"The kiss was a mistake. I take it back."
I'd have gotten the hint if you'd made it simple.
"Only you can be Kim Sol Ah. There's just one of you."
Why did you confuse me?
It's true that you're special.
Let's go back to...
where we were.
Where we were?
I can't do that.
Something hit me.
I'm always in the same place, looking at you.
That's it.
That must be why you think it's okay to run away.
Because you can always come back to me.
I knew you for a long time.
Or rather...
I thought I knew you.
I thought it was right for me at least...
to protect you.
I think I made you run away.
- It's not like that. - Then...
what's your reason?
Why is it not me?
The scarf.
What?
The scarf you always wore.
Where is it?
What about it?
Did you throw it away?
What are you talking about?
Are you changing the subject?
Forget it.
Why won't you continue? Talk to me.
Quit running away and tell the truth.
Why can't it be me?
Why can't I mean anything to you?
Tell me.
Please, tell me so I can understand.
Let's stop.
I'm trying to stop.
Your silence.
It used to comfort me, but not anymore.
I won't be a puppy anymore.
I'm no longer a dog.
She abandoned you.
(Sol Ah)
(Take him if you want.)
Hong Jo.
No cat would hug someone for being in pain.
A human...
can hug.
(Juniel's "Fall in Love" has been released.)
(Meow, the Secret Boy)
How can I become a real human?
I'll set Sol Ah up with a guy.
What's he like?
Like a dog, he likes only me.
He looks at, follows, and waits only for me.
I found someone who'll take the cat.
- What if he comes back? - I'll send him back.
There's only one way.
What does that mean?
Cats are like that. When it's time to leave, they leave voluntarily.
What do you choose?