(All characters, places, companies,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
Jin Ho.
Mom, don't go.
Wait.
Mom...
Don't leave.
Mom.
Eun Seop!
Lim Eun Seop!
My gosh. It looks like you have such a happy life, Eun Seop.
Your dad, mom, and sister...
all have big smiles on their faces.
I think you have a very happy family.
Gosh, Eun Seop. What's wrong?
Eun Seop.
Eun Seop, stop. Look at me.
What's wrong? Eun Seop.
What's the matter, Eun Seop?
Lim Eun Seop!
Eun Seop.
Where have you been? How's your cold?
Hey, you're still not well. You need to bundle up...
I'm not cold.
What's wrong? You seem upset. Did something happen?
(Episode 8: Where Suspicions Become Reality)
You can sit here.
The lights were on, so I thought you were here.
I always leave the lights on.
So that anyone who gets lost at night can come here.
Are you hurt?
I rolled down the hill.
What happened? You're a pro hiker.
You're okay, right?
Why did you come here?
Because you were taking forever.
Everyone's worried about you.
But it's late.
I brought a flashlight today.
They said I'd have to walk for just half an hour,
and I actually got here in exactly half an hour.
And I didn't trip or fall, even once.
I told you not to come.
The walk here wasn't too bad.
And these shoes you got me are so awesome...
I didn't give them to you so that you could come here.
Never come up here again.
Even if...
I am sick...
or...
never come back.
You can't come up here.
Drink it and come out.
"A long, long time ago, a brother and sister set out on a journey..."
"to become happy."
"They had heard..."
"there is a bluebird somewhere that gives you happiness."
"After climbing many mountains and crossing many rivers,"
"they arrived in the village where the bluebird was supposed to be."
"But the bluebird that gives you happiness..."
"was nowhere to be found."
You should go in.
"In the end,"
"the brother and sister came back home without finding the bluebird."
- You... - No.
What?
Hey, have some breakfast before you go.
I don't have much of an appetite. I'll eat later.
(Good Night Bookstore)
What are you doing here?
You're here.
- When the courier comes later... - I know.
(Hyecheon West Market)
We're here, Mother.
You're here to shop?
Hey, it's been a while.
Is your skating rink doing well?
Not really.
Oh, right. I dried some sweet potatoes.
Come pick them up.
I've been meaning to stop by for weeks.
See you later then.
All right. See you.
Are you here?
Oh, it's you.
(Health Food)
What do you need? Is your son still sick?
What's going on? He looks fine.
I want some of that brain tonic.
Why do you need it?
It's for Hwi.
You said she didn't need it.
You said that, didn't you?
You said she's been a bad student all her life...
and a brain tonic couldn't suddenly turn her into a good student.
I said you could take it...
for practically no money,
but you insisted on only getting tonics for your son...
Come on! Just give it to me.
Gosh, that stupid woman...
Mom.
You only call me Mom when you need something.
Are you very angry?
I told you not to go there.
I don't like you going there even when you feel fine.
And you were sick.
Why would you go up there in that condition?
You're shopping with your son?
Yes. See you.
How many times have I told you?
Last time, someone was missing,
so I understand that.
It still bugged me,
but what could I do?
But this time, you weren't feeling well.
You were sick.
You should have stayed home.
Why do you keep going up there?
What is up there anyway?
In that condition...
Mother, that mountain is nothing.
What do you mean it's nothing?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Whatever, forget it.
I saw that woman.
What?
This morning when I was sitting on the floor,
I saw an illusion of her.
So I followed her...
and ended up in the mountains.
I told you...
it's dangerous, didn't I?
I'll never...
go up that mountain without your permission again.
The cottage... No.
I'll never go anywhere...
without your permission.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Okay.
Never come up here again.
("Bluebird")
Hi, Hae Won.
I came for some sawdust porridge.
When you said sawdust porridge,
I really thought it was porridge made from sawdust.
It's actually oatmeal porridge,
but I made that name up since it looks like ground-up sawdust.
Does it taste like sawdust too then?
No, not at all.
It's really delicious and savory.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
Hey, I have to go somewhere today.
Where are you going?
I have something to do in Seoul.
You're going now?
Yes, I'll be back tomorrow.
I'm going to leave Gunbam with Su Jeong.
Okay.
Make sure you check the boiler. We can't have another accident.
Sweep the backyard too.
And don't skip your meals.
Come on, seriously.
Seung Ho, go on and eat.
Where are you going?
Hello.
- How cute. Hello. - Hello.
Come here.
- Seoul. - What for?
Well, I barely receive any royalties now.
In order to continue to make a living,
I think I'll have to write another novel.
Really?
At least that's what the publishing company said.
It's meaningless then.
But this time, I'm thinking of hearing them out.
I spent five years worth of living expenses on the repair work.
Nice.
I guess it's true your craving for writing comes from hardships.
Don't jump to conclusions.
I don't know how it's going to go.
I can live somehow even without money.
See you.
All right, I won't jump to conclusions, Ms. Shim.
Have a safe trip, ma'am.
Don't you worry about Gunbam!
Eun Seop.
Hey, Hae Won.
- Where's Eun Seop? - He's not here.
What is that?
It's the stuff Eun Seop asked me to bring.
And let me see...
This is for you.
(Oh Yeong Woo)
What is this?
Oh Yeong Woo asked me to give that to you.
Oh Yeong Woo?
Yes, he owns a cafe in Seoul.
He asked you to drop by in spring when you're in Seoul.
Why do you look so pale? Did you catch a cold?
I don't know, I feel kind of cold.
Catching a cold lately is no joke. You should go to a hospital.
You should at least take some medicine.
I'll get better soon.
You won't get better.
You need to go to a hospital for colds lately...
- Let's go. - Are you finished?
I have to go. Go to the hospital. I'll see you later.
- I never knew about this place. - Take some medicine.
You're already finished? Let's go.
"What did they say when they broke up?"
Hey. Get lost.
"Did he carry her bag for her when they left?"
I told you to get lost.
Who told you to follow me when I'm going home? Goodness.
Myeong Yeo.
Don't say my name, Cha Yun Taek.
"Why did that..."
"have to happen in the evening?"
Just get off at the next station.
I can't stand the sight of you.
"Were they both used to..."
"seeing each other crying?"
Don't cry and get off.
- What's going on? - Are they fighting?
I...
I like you so much.
I love you so much.
"We run at full speed seeking love..."
"somewhere at the end of this world."
Love, my foot.
I can't live without you.
Cut the nonsense.
"But after giving up on that love,"
"we return to where we were in the first place..."
"with all our energy drained from our bodies."
"Although we call that..."
"a breakup,"
"when we use up all our energy for that one person,"
"we can call that..."
("I ate the carrot you had picked")
"love as well."
("The Wind Blows, I Like You" A travel essay by Lee Byung Ryul)
(Good Night Bookstore)
Hae Won, you can go home now.
- What? - Do we have cold medicine at home?
Yes, we do.
Bring that to the bookstore.
- What? - Bring that to the bookstore now.
Eun Seop, the book club gathering will start in an hour anyway.
Can't I just bring this thing with me then?
Oh, right.
- What? - Don't forget to bring it later.
What... What did you...
Hey!
My daughter, I'm home.
Dad, do you know what Eun Seop said to me...
on the phone just now?
What did he say?
He asked me to run an errand.
Eun Seop asked me to run an errand for him.
Oh, I see.
In a very mean and oppressive tone.
"You brat. Bring the cold medicine to the bookstore now, you brat!"
This is how he sounded.
He asked me to run an errand for him and bring him medicine!
Dad, are you listening to me?
Of course, I am.
No.
Turn it off.
("Bluebird")
Hello!
- Gosh, it's so cold. - Hi, Hae Won. How have you been?
Hi! I'm back.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hae Won, did you see a doctor yet? When you have a cold...
- You have a cold? - Where's Eun Seop?
- My gosh. - Where is my crazy brother?
Hey, Lim Eun Seop.
You'd better not make me run an errand for you again.
- Hi. - We'll have red bean buns today.
Red bean buns? It'll be tasty with milk.
- Go sit down. Don't do anything. - Yes.
This is cool.
Seung Ho, I'm going to move this.
- 1, 2, 3. - Su Jeong.
- Gosh, Seung Ho... - Oh, no!
What? Gosh, Seung Ho is such a troublemaker.
Gosh, seriously.
Goodness.
My gosh, thank you.
- Here, Hae Won. - Oh, thank you.
My, it smells delicious.
- Eat as much as you want. - Thank you.
Gosh, it looks too nice to be eaten.
- Just dig in. - Grandpa is roasting up some buns.
- Really? Let's eat them together. - You made this yourself, right?
- Yes, of course. - Thanks.
Oh, right.
(Donghan Daily)
(Elderly British Man's Special Journey)
I recently read an article about a beautiful story.
An 80-year-old man who lives in the UK...
decided to travel according to a travel guide,
which he'd had all his life.
So he flew to Germany...
to go to a place in Bavaria.
He was told that it's a bustling city,
where a music festival takes place every year.
But something seemed off.
He followed the route mapped out in the travel guide,
but the city was nowhere to be found,
and he got lost in a dense forest.
After wandering the forest for two days,
he finally managed to find his way out.
Then he returned home...
and showed the map to people, saying something's wrong with it.
But someone, who saw the travel guide, said this.
"Look."
"This travel guide was published right after the First World War."
"A century has passed since the First World War ended."
He did go to the place...
where he had wanted to go all his life,
but it looked completely different from what he had seen...
on the map he had studied countless times.
(Elderly British Man's Special Journey)
You call this beautiful?
Not sad?
Right?
Really?
I think it's beautiful.
His plan failed,
but he went through the difficult journey...
for his happiness and to do what he had wanted to do for years.
I think that alone deserves applause.
As you all know, my dream...
is to travel to a faraway land like that.
Challenging yourself like that is brave and beautiful,
- but this article... - Hold on.
Doesn't this story remind you of "Bluebird"?
- Oh, right. - In that book,
two siblings begin a journey to find the bluebird of happiness,
but they return without finding it.
I feel bad for them, Hwi.
No, don't.
They returned...
and found the bluebird of happiness at home.
The story has a happy ending.
To be honest, I don't really like that story.
What? Why don't you like it?
It just doesn't make sense.
Happiness was always there,
but you just didn't know?
It's so futile.
Well, what's wrong with that?
Maybe you just weren't aware of it.
Right, I'm a gem,
but Kim Young Soo doesn't see that. It's just like that.
- To him, you're not a gem... - Whatever! Quiet.
You're wrong.
Anyway, I'm personally not a fan of that story.
Really?
- But... - You're right.
I agree with you.
We go to a faraway land to find the bluebird of happiness,
but the bluebird was at home the whole time?
Maybe...
it's just an excuse we came up with...
to console ourselves because it is hard to attain happiness.
I personally think that happiness is out of reach.
Hae Won, still...
Right, it's just...
- my personal opinion. - No, it's not about that.
I am a gem.
- I really am. - This isn't about that.
I'm a gem, everyone.
But I saw him with Song Jae In...
Song Jae In? Who's that?
So...
what's your plan for the signing event?
Well... It's up to you, isn't it?
We could do something like, "Meet the Author".
What do you think?
That sounds good.
I'm fine with anything you suggest, Sweetie.
By the way, can we go for another drink?
Sure, something simple.
- Come on. - No.
- Bye! - I am a gem!
- Bye, Hae Won. - I am a gem!
- Gosh, let's go. - No, I really am.
- Seriously... - Bye, guys.
Can you please agree with me just once?
All right, let's go.
I'll get going too.
Just a moment.
Take this.
What is it?
Medicine.
Take it before sleep, and you'll feel better.
No, it's all right.
(Medicine)
Hae Won.
Mok Hae Won.
Take this.
I said it's fine.
Still...
No, thanks. I won't take the medicine anyway.
Bye.
- Hae Won. - I said I won't take it.
Just it with you.
You got better without taking any medicine.
I won't take medicine either.
I'll feel better...
after a good night's sleep.
Just take it, please.
Please?
Then what will you do in return?
If I take this medicine,
what will you do for me in return?
I...
have to do something in return?
Yes.
I'd like you to.
Like what?
For example,
you could give me an answer to my confession.
I want your answer.
Can you do that for me?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I like you, Eun Seop.
A million roses
For you
Mom!
Where's my book?
Which book are you talking about?
The one I have to read this week.
I have to bring it to school, but I can't find it.
Didn't you give it to Eun Seop?
You asked him to read it and tell you what it's about.
That's right. What do I do?
What do I do now?
What else? I'll call Eun Seop.
Okay. I'll go pack my bag.
Hello.
Yes, Father.
It's about the book Hwi gave you the other day.
Oh, you mean the novel?
What was the title?
Hey, what's the title?
The Rye something...
She says, "The Rye something".
"The Catcher in the Rye"?
Yes.
Oh, okay.
I can run up there quickly.
All right.
What did he say? Where's the book?
Is he bringing it here? What did he say? I'm in a hurry.
Well, the thing is...
Yes? What is it?
Dad, I really don't want any more penalty points.
My life will end.
So what's the matter?
It's in the mountains.
No way.
It's in his backpack he left in the mountains.
He didn't bring it back the last time...
Whatever. Tell him to go get it right now.
Tell him to crawl up that mountain like a squirrel right now.
I should ask him to, right?
No!
Never! He can't go up that mountain.
He can't.
Never. No way.
- Mother. - No, you can't.
Do you understand?
I'll take responsibility for whatever happens to Hwi.
You can't go up there, okay?
- I'll just... - You...
promised me, remember?
You promised never to go up there again, didn't you?
I did, but...
How about I go? What do you think?
Or should we go together...
You can't go there.
Then let's not go there at all.
I'll just...
Hi, Hae Won.
Do you have some time right now?
Are you busy?
Mother.
Please don't. Talk to me.
Get off me.
The situation is not right.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Talk to me instead.
(Good Night Bookstore)
Never mind what my mother said.
She's been worried since I suddenly disappeared the other day.
That's why she asked you.
I can go there alone.
I'll tell my mother that you went with me.
Eun Seop.
We could do that,
but I've never told such a lie before.
I'll come with you. It's no big deal.
Did you know this was here?
Yes.
It looks like a grave.
This is where suspicions become reality.
Suspicions?
If you suspect something will happen while standing here,
it often comes true.
Wait for me!
I think it was back in high school.
I'd been worried about my father using a cultivator.
Hey, you're here.
What's the matter, Mother?
- Your father's cultivator... - In the end, he injured himself.
That's scary.
It means misfortunes will happen for real.
No.
Sometimes, good suspicions come true too.
Hae Won, where's your seat?
Where?
- I'm over there. - Where is your seat?
C-3.
You're next to me!
Come here.
Yes!
I'm glad you're behind me.
I've never seen a wooden headstone.
The dates of this person's...
birth and death are unknown.
Don't suspect anything.
It may come true.
You can go back first.
The summit is just up that way.
Since I'm here and all, I want to see it.
Bye.
It's slippery.
Hold my hand.
I didn't know it only took an hour-long hike to see this view.
It's beautiful.
To be honest,
I can't seem to look you straight in the eyes.
All I have to do is accept the fact...
that you don't like me.
But it's so hard for me.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
You were such a warm person.
You were so warm to me.
I guess that's why I suspected about your feelings for me.
But I won't do that anymore.
Since you told me not to, I won't suspect anything.
I really won't.
But Eun Seop...
Never mind. Let's go.
A bluebird really exists, Hae Won.
Don't lie.
It's not a lie. You can believe me.
You've never seen it though.
That's because you usually can't see it.
It appears sometimes.
How does it appear?
Like a miracle.
A miracle?
What is that?
Oh, gosh.
My suspicions really became a reality.
When something you believed would never come true...
becomes reality.
Who makes that happen?
The bluebird does.
It's always the bluebird by your side who does it.
It makes miracles happen.
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(There are things you can see more clearly when you're alone.)
(And it's not so bad to learn from loneliness.)
(The less you expect, the calmer your days are.)
(It's painful to genuinely want something.)
(But I'm not without desires.)
(I kissed Irene in the mountains. I almost fainted.)
(I can't joke about it anymore, which means it's serious.)
(She now lives behind my eyes.)
(When the Weather is Fine)
I thought you hated me.
No way.
What's going on between you two?
What I saw earlier was real, wasn't it?
Myeong Yeo. How about you write a novel based on your life...
since college?
Your book.
Are you not interested in publishing it at all?
- What? - Nothing.
I'm just afraid you'll suddenly disappear.
I was anxious about everything.
I was worried my insecure moments of happiness...
would disappear all of a sudden.