(All characters, places, companies, )
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
- Hae Won. - Yes?
I have to bend over and pick that up.
- Go ahead. - Like this?
Yes, bend over.
Okay.
You're teasing me, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I just want to be close to you.
I'm not that slow-witted.
Yes, you are.
- I am? - Yes.
Jang Woo is the quick-witted one.
You're right.
Eun Seop!
- Hi, Hwi. - Hi.
What was that?
- What's going on here? - What are you talking about?
Hyun Ji, I think I just saw something weird.
What did you see?
Eun Seop and Hae Won...
No. What are you talking about?
I think they ate something.
I smell something.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Eun Seop, Hwi got kicked out of the bike shop today.
Hey, don't tell him.
You have no idea how stupid she is.
She thought a 300-dollar saddle cost only 30 dollars.
Please.
What are we doing here anyway?
I wanted to steal Eun Seop's wallet,
but since he's here, I can't anymore.
I see. Then let's go.
All right. We should get something to eat too. I'm hungry.
Let's pick up where we left off.
What?
(Episode 10: Let's Hold an Event)
(Hyecheon Bus Terminal)
Gosh.
- Hey! - Hi.
- You just got here? - Yes.
- It's been slow lately. - I know.
Excuse me.
Do you know where Mr. Lim Jong Pil lives, by any chance?
Lim Jong Pil?
Lim Jong Pil...
Is he talking about Jong Pil?
I guess.
Why do you need to see him?
What's the matter?
Well...
We have all kinds of screws, sir.
We sure do.
Hello... Darn it.
- Hello. - Someone is looking for Jong Pil.
Jong Pil? Isn't that...
Eun Seop's dad's name?
Who's looking for him?
You have to do it right this time.
I get it. Be quiet.
I'm not going easy on you.
Cosmos... It's 17 dollars.
Please sign here.
Hey, take your delivery case off the pool table.
- I get it, I get it. - You brat.
Hurry up and hit it.
Give me a second. I need to calculate the angle.
What's there to calculate? Just hit it.
Take this and leave.
Isn't that Jong Pil over there?
Someone was looking for him.
- Come on, hit it. - I'm leaving.
Just hit it like this.
My goodness.
Hey!
Jong Pil!
What?
Come here.
Someone was looking for me?
Yes.
At the bus terminal.
Who?
Well, they did mention...
he looked like that man. You know, Eun Seop's...
Hey, don't think you can run away.
We're going to Jin Ju's for another drink.
Let's go.
Jong Pil, come on.
- Are you guys done? - Yes.
All right, thanks.
Lim Hwi!
Hey, Hwi!
What's taking her so long?
Lim Hwi!
Lim as in "limbo".
Hwi as in "whistle"!
Lim Hwi!
Hey, Kwon Hyun Ji! Hyun Ji!
Gosh, it's freezing.
Who's that man?
My gosh, do you have a crush on me or something?
- Gosh, that's no good. - Shut it.
- What? - Let's go.
Isn't this the first time we're locking arms like this?
Gosh, be quiet.
Goodness.
Lim Eun Seop.
Eun Seop.
Wake up. Wake up and play with me.
I'm bored. Please?
Eun Seop.
Lim Eun Seop?
Here.
Hae Won.
- Was it good? - What did you do?
How does it taste?
It tastes weird.
Get up already.
You're so mean.
What?
You're glowing.
Never mind.
- Eun Seop. - Yes.
Shall I cook something for you?
What? You?
What's with that reaction?
I'm a good cook. Well, I'm at least better than my auntie.
I'm serious.
I don't put ham in soybean paste stew.
It's too fishy.
Oh, dear.
What exactly went wrong?
Hey.
Well, it was practically impossible to obtain your cell phone number.
You're obviously very serious about protecting your private life.
Just cut to the chase, Crybaby.
I'm calling about the contract. What will you do?
I can't wait forever, you know.
Oh, that.
So what's your decision?
Will you do it or not?
I'll do it.
What? You'll do it?
I won't if you have a problem with it.
No, no. It's not that.
I don't have any problem with it.
Then send the contract via registered mail, Crybaby.
Within a week.
Hey, hold on. Wait.
You see, we normally...
don't send contracts via registered mail.
Then what do you use? Pigeon post?
Well, our company culture is...
Everyone here loves meeting people.
That's why I always have in-person meetings back-to-back.
Why don't you...
Come by my office whenever you have some time.
I'm very busy,
but I'll make some time just for you.
It's on Hoedong-gil in Paju...
6:18am.
9:18am, 12:18pm, 3:18pm, 6:18pm,
and 9:18pm.
Those are the train times to my town.
Hey, are you saying...
I should come to where you are?
I guess you don't get it.
The one who's asking for a favor should travel.
Hey, Myeong Yeo...
Hello?
Are you signing a contract for a book?
When did you get in?
Just now. Are you signing a contract for a book?
Yes, I am.
But you made a big deal about not wanting to write anymore.
You said you couldn't think of anything to write about.
You went on about how your creative well has dried up.
What's gotten into you?
When you've hit rock bottom,
the only way to go is up.
I've been hit by poverty.
Speaking of which, why are you taking those?
I see you holding my carrots,
my potatoes, and my tomatoes. It's bothering me a lot.
Oh, these? I bought these.
- You bought them? - Yes.
I bought them while staying at Eun Seop's place, so they're mine.
I see. You bought them.
I have to say, I'm really curious about your new book.
I don't know about other things, but I'm a fan of your novels.
- When the book comes out, let's... - Hey.
Winter will be over soon.
Shouldn't you wake up from your hibernation?
Didn't you initially say you'd go back in spring?
What? Who?
Oh, Eun Seop's biological father.
Mom, where's my gym shirt?
Oh, it's in the bottom drawer.
But he's dead.
Then who else would it be?
The uncle?
Well, I think so.
But everyone in the village...
is gossiping about Eun Seop's biological father being back.
What? They're gossiping about it?
My gosh.
Goodness, this darned place.
I never liked this place.
This tiny town.
When anything happens,
people gather and gossip.
They gossip about the vagrant that lives in the mountains.
When he comes into town to do some work,
they gossip about that too.
Whether that man had a little boy or not...
was also a topic of their gossip.
The same goes for whether we took that boy in or not.
They gossip about everything!
I mean, that man died years ago.
I can't believe these people still remember that man's face.
Goodness, I'm so sick and tired of this.
Gosh.
By the way,
why is that man looking for you?
Well, I suppose he wants to ask where Eun Seop is.
Something like that, I assume.
But he hasn't shown up yet,
so maybe he already went to the bookstore.
Why would he go there? Why?
What would he do there? What now?
To extort money from Eun Seop again?
Even last time, he took a lot of money from Eun Seop,
saying that he wants to buy a boat.
When he hurt his leg, he said he needed money to pay hospital bills.
What kind of excuse will he give this time?
Gosh, Eun Seop doesn't even have much money.
Why does he keep showing up?
Gosh, no way.
I'm sure he won't do that again.
Okay, fine. Money isn't important.
What worries me is how he keeps...
He keeps asking Eun Seop to go out to the sea with him...
Mom, Dad. I'm going to school.
All right, Hwi.
- Okay, have a good day! - I will.
What are you talking about?
But he's dead.
Then who else would it be?
The uncle?
Hey!
(Good Night Bookstore)
Has it been five years?
It was before you went to do your military service.
That's the last time we met, right?
Yes.
- Did you buy the boat? - No.
I didn't.
But...
I did find this.
Do you have this too?
It was taken on the same day.
I took this picture.
I need you to come with me right now.
- Where? - It's a bit far from here.
- If we have to sail there, I... - Well...
I guess...
it's something like that.
Get yourself together, son.
I'm the only family you have.
Can't you see?
The blood flowing in your veins...
and the blood flowing in mine are the same.
That's why we have a connection.
You came back for your mom.
You stayed by her side nursing her for three years, right?
You know what that means?
In the end, it's all about family.
Do you understand?
You still act politely...
and courteously to those parents of yours, right?
You do that because they are not your real family.
Because they are not your real family.
What?
What? "Real"? Real what?
Goodness, that dog...
Darn it.
(Good Night Bookstore)
- What is he saying? - Hwi, you're here.
Oh my goodness.
What are you doing outside?
No, no.
Are you done talking?
Hae Won.
Yes?
I...
Tell me.
I have to go somewhere.
Where?
Just someplace...
I might not come back today.
- Is that okay? - No.
But go ahead.
We have to prepare for the flea market too.
Oh, I'll try preparing it by myself.
Eun Seop! Don't go, you can't go!
You stay right there! You're dead meat if you leave!
What's wrong with her?
She seemed pretty upset.
Mom!
- Mom! - Why you...
Why did you come back from school?
- Are you skipping school again? - No...
- Wait. - I told you.
At least be diligent in school if you can't get good grades.
What are you thinking?
- Wait, Mom! - What?
Eun Seop is running away.
What do you mean?
That uncle or whatever came over...
and told him to follow him.
He didn't ask for money?
Money, my foot.
That would've been better.
He took Eun Seop somewhere.
Talking about family and blood.
Did Eun Seop...
really follow him?
He followed him without hesitation.
It would've been better if he took money from us.
I'm so mad!
(Hyecheon, Seoul)
(Hyecheon, Gangneung)
(Bukhyeon-ri, Downtown Hyecheon, Seohyeon Village)
Hey, I'm here.
- Hi. Let's go. - A flea market?
Yes. It sounds like fun.
(A few days ago)
Everyone. Let's host an event.
What kind of event, Su Jeong?
A flea market.
"A flea market"?
Are you giving us an idea for a city hall event?
I was thinking on a much smaller scale.
What's a "flea market"?
I know what it is. I totally do.
It's like sharing, exchanging, and reusing things.
No, that's not it Hwi.
Su Jeong, a flea market is...
selling things you don't use.
Right. Oh, that's right.
That's not good.
I use everything I have.
You can also sell things that you're good at making too.
Right, Eun Seop?
Right.
(Until spring comes after the cold winter)
(Good Night Bookstore's Flea Market)
- Did you sell a lot? - Yes.
- Look over here. - Goodness.
- Come here and get yours. - Over here.
We have more for everyone.
Why are you so mad, Hyun Ji? Brighten up a bit, okay?
- Only for today. - That looks good.
How about selling your pies or quilts, Auntie Su Jeong?
Five dollars for you, Miss.
I think a lot of people will buy it.
What about me?
Hyun Ji, just go with calligraphy. You're good at that.
Goodness.
What would you like for me to write?
Well... Can you write this for my son?
"Jun Yeong, mommy loves you."
His daddy doesn't love him?
Pardon?
(Calligraphy)
(Jun Yeong, Mommy loves you.)
(Daddy doesn't.)
Hae Won, what about me?
Try it.
It looks tasty.
Try it. We have red bean porridge too.
Try these green onions.
They're delicious.
Oh, I could sell the lamps that are sitting in storage...
at cheap prices.
Attention, everyone!
This is a rare opportunity!
Full-color signs...
of all sizes!
Take a look!
Yes!
Come on!
Everyone, sing!
- How much is this? - Thank you.
All right.
What's with her? Why isn't she saying anything?
Hwi, how many have you sold?
Jang Woo, take over.
- Take over? - I'm going to the bookstore.
You're going to the bookstore, and I have to take over? Hwi!
(Good Night Bookstore Flea Market Bestsellers)
How much is this?
- This book? - Yes.
Well... I wonder how much that is.
It's okay.
I've never planned an event this perfect in my whole life.
That makes me wonder...
Come take a look!
Hi, Jang Woo.
You did a great job.
- Thank you. - Let's go in.
Okay.
What if the mayor is so impressed...
and promotes me to deputy mayor?
Hello, sir.
Even if all 50 million people in this country attend the event,
I don't think that's going to happen.
Hyun Ji, you hate me, don't you? We need to talk.
We seriously need to talk.
- No? - Is everything decided?
No, we haven't decided what Hae Won is going to sell.
Well...
I'm going to sell books. I work at the bookstore.
With who?
Who else?
This one looks interesting.
(Books for modern people who are depressed)
(Books to read in the bathroom)
(Books to recommend to your ex)
Really?
(Books to read while drinking hot coffee on a winter day)
How much is this one?
This one...
Excuse me.
Is there anything I can read when I need a break from my studies?
- Well... - It's 4 dollars and 20 cents.
Thank you.
You're good at this.
- Hae Won. - Yes?
Do you think...
Eun Seop will come back?
I don't.
Hae Won.
Eun Seop is going to leave.
With that man.
To somewhere very far away.
No. He said he'd be back by tonight.
He said he called your mom to let her know.
- So you don't have to worry... - Hae Won.
Eun Seop...
is a little different this time.
I don't think he's coming back this time.
I'm sure of it.
I'm going to live with you from now on.
I want to quit working on fishing boats.
It's about time, don't you think?
You're a grown-up now.
They raised you,
and you've stayed with them all these years.
I believe you've done enough.
I...
Do you see that small building over there?
You were such a bookworm as a kid.
Whenever I visited you,
I'd bring books, and you would...
"Once upon a time, there lived on a huge mountain..."
"a little boy..." There, there.
"And his mom."
Oh, they're just like us.
You'd be over the moon.
That's why I bought that.
(Good Night Bookstore)
With the money you've sent me over the years,
and the money I've earned working on the boats.
You bought it?
That building?
Some people...
are meant to be alone...
from birth to death.
Your father was one of them.
So am I.
And so are you.
Where did it go?
The thing about us is that...
we can't live with anyone.
It's here.
In the end, your mom...
gave up and left too.
This goes here.
It's in our blood.
In our blood.
What's this?
We're meant to be alone...
all our lives.
We're meant to be that way.
That's why I want to live with you now.
You and I are both going to leave eventually.
Shouldn't we stick together until then?
That way, we wouldn't have to get hurt.
What?
Do you think...
you're any different?
(Good Night Bookstore Flea Market)
Hey, aren't they amazing?
The City of Hyecheon...
educates those incredibly talented kids.
Those extraordinarily talented kids...
Hear me out.
They learned how to play those instruments at school.
- Jang Woo. - Yes?
I'm trying to focus here.
Sure, I'm trying to focus too.
- Please be quiet. - All right.
Aren't they fantastic? Fine, I get it.
Did you enjoy that?
- Yes. - Yes.
For 30 years...
Can you play for us?
- What? - You're a cellist too, aren't you?
Play for us.
I am, but...
Please, Hae Won. I'd love to hear it.
- Please don't do this. - Please.
- I can't. - Ji Yeon.
Excuse me. Ji Yeon!
- Ji Yeon! - Hey.
- Hae Won wants to play too. - Be quiet.
- Please. She plays the cello. - Ji Yeon, ignore him.
- She wants to play for us. - Ignore him.
You know how Jang Woo is.
- Hae Won is an amazing cellist. - Don't listen to him. Never mind.
- She wants to play the cello. - No.
- Ji Yeon, Hae Won wants to play. - Ji Yeon, no.
(Flea Market)
Eun Seop.
What's wrong? You seem upset. Did something happen?
Some people...
are meant to be alone...
from birth to death.
So am I.
It's in our blood.
In our blood.
We're meant to be alone...
all our lives.
We're meant to be that way.
Just because.
What do you mean?
I was just thinking... What if you vanish all of a sudden?
What?
Do you think...
you're any different?
(Hyecheon, Gangneung)
That train ride sent me...
on a trip down memory lane.
We used to ride the train very often.
We did. And you cried every single time.
"I love you, Myeong Yeo. I'm sorry, Myeong Yeo."
Sniff, sniff. Sobbing and crying.
I meant every word I said to you.
Oh, is that so?
This clause here.
Take this out, and I'll sign the contract.
(This book must be based on personal experience)
I can't take that out. It'll be the most interesting aspect.
No. To me, it won't be interesting at all.
Who are you to decide that?
I make the call because I'm the chief editor.
Look. When someone's house in on fire,
the spectators may get a kick out of it,
but it's a nightmare to those locked inside the house.
Why don't you know that?
I cannot write about such a horrible nightmare.
Then...
- why don't you mix it up? - What?
Mix fiction with nonfiction.
Who cares? I wouldn't know...
which part is fiction and which part isn't.
If that's the case...
I will never ask you which parts are based on facts...
and which parts are fictitious.
We're good now, right?
Here.
I need your signature here.
What is this?
I knew you'd pull this on me, so I brought an alternative version.
This contract entails what we just discussed.
This is what a competent chief editor does, you know?
That's the one you just took out.
What?
What? Hold on.
You believe that?
- I fooled you again. - Gosh, seriously.
Goodness.
Wasn't it so much fun?
Yes, it was really fun.
Well, I did sell them cheap.
But I got rid of a lot of the old inventory.
So all in all, it was great.
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to open a pie shop.
I'll call it Crystal Pie.
But I have to say,
I was so impressed by Hae Won's cello performance.
Me too!
I've never seen that before.
Same here. I've seen my classmates fiddle with the cello,
but Hae Won is obviously on another level.
Agreed.
I want to learn something like that too, Hae Won.
Really?
By the way, Uncle Eun Seop isn't here yet.
Gosh, I know.
I wish he was there with us.
Right? Totally.
Gosh, I told you he isn't coming.
Hwi, you'll burn your clothes.
It's getting late. We should all get going.
- All right. - It feels empty here without him.
- I know. - Where are you all going?
We're not done yet.
Doesn't the composition look weird?
- Yes, a little. - I think it moved.
- Are we doing it now? - Hey, Hae Won. Yes, we are.
- Hold on. - Can I stand here?
Yes, that's perfect. It looks perfect now.
All right, let's do this.
Wait! Don't forget about me!
- Gosh, seriously. - I'm coming.
- Here? - A little more to the left.
Okay, that's it. Stop right there.
Okay.
Hae Won, why are you holding a rag?
Seung Ho, you should look at the camera.
Was that it? I think I closed my eyes.
I think I'll look good in this one.
Jang Woo, you should get going. I can organize the rest alone.
It's okay. I'll just finish this.
Eun Seop talked my ear off,
so I can't just leave.
- Hey, Hae Won. - Yes?
How are you doing these days?
You seemed to have a lot on your mind.
Oh, right.
I had been feeling a little frustrated,
but I'm okay now.
Living in Seoul is exhausting, isn't it?
I used to feel frustrated from time to time as well.
I felt like I couldn't digest anything when I had to eat alone.
And hanging out with friends didn't make my loneliness go away.
But you see,
I remember them as fond memories now that time has passed.
"Memories"?
Yes, just like you're...
building memories here.
I remember my experience in Seoul...
very fondly.
Where should I put this?
- Hae Won. - Yes?
Oh, can you take it to the storage room?
The storage room? I came from there.
I wish you had told me sooner.
As for the light bulbs, can you leave them in the front yard?
- Leave them outside? - Yes.
Then I have to separate them. I wish you had told me sooner.
Oh, and bring those books back.
All right.
Thanks.
Even if that's the case,
I can't let him go, honey.
I don't want to.
I will stop him.
I'll tell him not to leave.
I'll beg him.
We should let him go if he wants to leave.
How could you say that so easily?
Eun Seop is not our...
He's not our son, you know.
You see,
I still remember the day you brought him home...
and told me not to get too attached to him...
because he's not our child,
but I just couldn't do that.
I mean, how is that possible?
He ate with us and slept by our side.
That little boy always fell asleep...
in my arms,
so how... How can I treat him like a stranger?
He is my son.
Don't you agree?
Apparently, we should treat him like a stranger.
Everyone in this town is saying that.
You see,
even when he left us for three years to look after his mother...
and be there for her in her final moments,
I trusted him.
I really did.
That he would come back one day.
Even when...
Eun Seop never gave us...
one phone call during those three years.
You told me numerous times that Eun Seop...
would not return.
Not me.
I had complete trust in him.
And he came back to us.
Back to us.
He is with us now.
But still, family...
Blood is thicker than water.
"Blood"?
Is that the same for you as well?
Is that how you define family?
Is having a blood-related family that important to you?
So did you only adore and love Hwi as your child?
No!
That's not true.
Just once.
Could you tell me...
just once?
Please?
I wanted to tell you...
that I love you.
Hey.
You're hungry, right?
That I really love you.
What's this?
Oh, my goodness. This is...
Oh, goodness.
This is my favorite.
It's a rhino beetle, right?
Did you bring this to show it to me?
Goodness, it's such a rare kind.
I haven't seen one in ages.
Hold on to it for a moment.
You must be hungry. I'll set the table for you soon.
Wait a minute. You must be hungry.
Hwi, look. Your brother brought...
such a rare beetle to show it to mommy.
Hwi.
Your name is Hwi.
Hwi as in "whistle".
Goodness, Eun Seop.
You've been here for two hours already.
Do you like her that much?
Mommy...
Honey.
Are you okay?
I'm watching a drama.
I wanted to tell you that I missed you.
That I'm sorry.
But I couldn't tell you any of that.
Come here, Hwi.
You're going to leave anyway.
Forget about it. Whatever, just go.
Don't touch my bicycle.
If you're going to leave anyway, don't dare leave a thumbprint on it.
Go on that boat and sail across all the way to the Pacific, okay?
Who cares if I sail on a boat...
or disappear?
You never liked me.
Since I was born!
I liked you since I was born.
When I was a crying baby.
When I saw the world for the first time.
I've liked you ever since then, you idiot!
"Don't cry."
"I won't leave."
Why?
Why is it so hard to utter these sentences?
Because you're my brother.
Because you're my brother!
Because you were already my brother when I was born.
So I liked you since the beginning. What do you want me to do?
I hate you, Eun Seop.
I hate you so much, Eun Seop.
Get lost, get on that boat!
Whatever. I don't even know.
I'm going to tell Mom and Dad everything.
Mom, Dad! Eun Seop is...
- This one's expensive. - being mean.
How expensive?
- Was it very expensive? - Yes.
I wanted to treat you big time and bought it downtown.
It's been a while...
since you spent money on me.
This was what I wanted.
Yes, this was it.
I thought it was 30 dollars,
but it was 300 dollars.
I guess you're rich, Eun Seop.
Next time, just give it to me in cash.
A student doesn't need such an expensive saddle.
There's so much you can do with 300 dollars.
Excuse me?
Don't laugh, you lunatic!
You're ridiculing me if you laugh when I'm crying.
Get out!
Oh, this is good.
Oh, nice. This is really great, Eun Seop.
It's so nice! Okay!
Out of the way!
(To Jecheon, Cheongnyangni)
What an honor it is...
for you to come all the way to see me off.
Hey.
Why don't you tell me now?
- About what? - That day.
Why did you break up with me?
I broke up with you so many times.
About 1,000 times, maybe?
The last one.
September 5, 2010, at 9:23am.
You texted me, "Let's break up."
Explain that to me, Myeong Yeo.
I didn't memorize everything...
because I still have feelings for you. Don't get me wrong.
I just have it memorized because I was so dumbfounded.
No matter how many times I think about it,
I can't grasp the reason why we had to break up that day.
I didn't do anything wrong.
What was the reason?
Not sure.
I can't remember a thing.
You don't remember anything?
Come on. Do you think I would remember that?
It has been more than 10 years. How am I supposed to know?
The train is approaching the station.
Please step back and remain in the safety zone.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Contact me when the first draft comes out.
Get lost, Crybaby.
Why don't you tell me now?
That day. Why did you break up with me?
September 5, 2010, at 9:23am.
You texted me, "Let's break up."
Explain that to me, Myeong Yeo.
(Where are you?)
What I'm asking is,
was he put in jail or not?
The arrest warrant has been rejected.
How could I possibly put him in jail?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
I'm going to put that jerk in jail by all means.
- Is there any evidence? - There's a ton.
Gosh, are you sure?
Hello.
Let's break up.
(Let's break up.)
Not sure. I can't remember a thing.
It has been more than 10 years. How am I supposed to know?
Gosh.
How dare you?
How dare you look down on me?
Who do you think you are?
Answer me! Who do you think you are?
Hey! You little...
(Good Night Bookstore)
The man who was here yesterday...
Yes?
Is he your uncle?
Yes.
Hwi said...
you're going to...
leave here soon.
That's not true, is it?
You're leaving too when spring comes, aren't you?
When the weather becomes nice...
and this place becomes warm,
you're going back, aren't you?
Eun Seop.
I don't know what's going to happen to us in the future.
But...
for the very first time,
I'm curious what happens next.
I'm really curious...
what comes next.
Eun Seop.
What about you?
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(Good Night Bookstore held its very first public event.)
(Irene was more or less our leader.)
(I'm grateful to the book club members for all their hard work.)
(In the pictures that captured their memories, )
(they all look so happy that I almost feel jealous.)
(Irene has become a lot more cheerful...)
(since she came here at the end of last year.)
(Maybe it's just me, but she seems to laugh more often, )
(and her darkness has faded.)
(Every time she smiles, it's a dazzling sight)
(When the Weather is Fine)
It's the landlord's daughter.
She says if I don't pay the rent immediately,
I'll be kicked out.
I hear you went on a blind date during the lunch break.
What type of girl do you like, Jang Woo?
You signed a contract with Myeong Yeo?
Cancel it.
I have to publish her novel.
There's something I need to find out.
Tell me not to leave.
Tell me to stay with you.
Tell me, Eun Seop.
Are we...
in love?