(All characters, places, companies, )
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
What an honor it is...
for you to come all the way to see me off.
Hey.
Why don't you tell me now?
About what?
That day.
Why did you break up with me?
I broke up with you so many times.
About 1,000 times, maybe?
The last one.
September 5, 2010, at 9:23am.
You texted me, "Let's break up."
Explain that to me, Myeong Yeo.
What was the reason?
Let's break up.
I said let's break up.
Myeong Yeo.
Class is over. We need to go.
Everyone else left.
How could you wear a sweater with a dog on it?
Higher.
Let's break up.
You should still keep pushing.
- Come on! - Oh, okay.
Harder, higher!
Aren't you going to push?
I will.
- Stop crying. - I wasn't crying.
- Hey. - What?
Don't you think you walk too straight?
Oh... I'll... walk like this then.
I have a headache.
(Let's break up.)
Let's break up.
(Why?)
Why?
Answer me.
No reason.
(Episode 11: Two Different Stories)
(Come to Hyecheon University Hospital Room 803.)
(Cancer Ward)
Cancer ward?
Why do you bring tangerines all the time?
You brought them for yourself, didn't you?
We can eat them together.
I said, no! You always eat all of them.
Why don't you have some? They're in season.
I asked you to bring peaches.
I should raise a peach tree for you. You and your peaches.
I want to eat peaches that look like your face.
Where can I find peaches in this season?
Hey, Myeong Yeo.
- Wait. - Peaches.
What is it?
You're finally letting me see you now that I'm dying?
I asked you to come to the reunion,
and you never showed up.
I'm here now.
That's what's important, isn't it?
- Ms. Choi Sun Yeong? - Yes?
You asked to be moved to a room of six?
- Yes. - You'll have to wait.
Okay.
Are you really going to die?
Yes. That's what they say.
Hey. You two better watch out for breast cancer too.
Don't forget to get tested regularly.
Come on.
What's with her?
You tell me.
By the way, you really are old fashioned.
I can't believe you brought canned peaches.
Who buys canned peaches these days?
- Gosh. - Goodness.
Hey.
What happened to your eye?
What do you say?
Does this make you feel better?
What?
Sadness can be lessened by someone else's sadness.
What are you talking about?
Do you like this?
Myeong Yeo!
Hey, tell me what's going on.
Shim Myeong Yeo, explain what's going on.
You saw it. What's there to explain?
Right, but what did I see?
I have glaucoma.
- Have you seen a doctor? - I told you. It's such a hassle.
Are you out of your mind?
Quiet down. Why are you yelling? We're at the hospital now.
I'm okay.
It doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt at all. That's all that matters, right?
Let's go. Go get some tests done at least.
- Hurry. - Gosh, look. It's already too late.
Why are you saying it's too late? Just go get some tests done!
I've lost vision in that eye.
Su Jeong.
I've already lost vision in one eye.
Myeong Yeo.
Gosh, losing vision in one eye is no big deal.
The rest is totally fine.
You don't need to see me off. Just look after her.
Wait, hey!
Hey, just listen to me and get some tests done!
Hello?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
Just a moment, please.
Hello?
Right.
The landlord said that?
Yes, okay.
What was that?
Oh, it was the landlord's daughter.
They want me to vacate the property immediately...
if I'm not going to pay rent.
What?
So you'll go there now?
Yes, the landlord lives in Suncheon.
I should visit them and talk to them in person.
So they let you...
use this property for free until now?
Yes.
It was a derelict house.
I'll see you later.
I'll come with you.
- What? - The store can be closed for a day.
We got rid of a ton of old books at the flea market.
What? Are you uncomfortable that I'm tagging along?
No, not at all.
Let's go together.
Okay.
- You're cold, right? - Yes.
Raise the temperature to 28°C.
(Raise the temperature to 28°C.)
The temperature setting has been changed.
It'll get warm soon.
Hi, Mother. I'm walking up to the second floor now. Yes.
Gosh, Mother.
You've gotten so young. Didn't I see you this morning?
You should've given me a heads-up about this...
Hello. You're Lee Jang Woo, right?
- Yes. - I'm Jo Young Mi.
Hello.
Gosh.
By the way, why were you on the train that day?
Remember that day? I was standing under the maple tree.
I thought about it and realized that you were on the train too.
Yes.
As for me, I was running away from home.
What about you?
It was a weekday.
Why did you skip school and get on the train?
The train is approaching...
Hello?
Are you...
Jin Ho?
I'm...
your mother.
Kim Jin Ho.
Kim Jin Ho...
is your name.
I gave you that name.
I guess your dad never told you.
My name is Eun Seop.
Lim Eun Seop.
Jin Ho, the thing is...
I'm very ill.
So...
I'd like you to visit me.
You see,
I...
miss you very much.
I'm in Andong.
Can you visit me?
So? Did you meet her?
No.
That day, I didn't go.
Why not?
(Train Ticket, Hyecheon, Andong)
I felt like...
I'd be betraying my parents if I went there to see her.
Also,
I saw you on the platform that day.
What?
Nothing.
Enjoy.
Shouldn't servers wear masks these days?
Drinking in broad daylight?
Yes, I have a reason to drink.
I heard you signed a contract with Shim Myeong Yeo.
Yes.
What about it?
Annul it.
I don't like it.
No, I'm good.
Why don't you like it?
You two were in a relationship.
For 20 years.
Everyone in the industry knows that.
So, annul the contract immediately, Mr. Cha.
If you want to publish my next book, that is.
I have to publish her novel.
There's something I need to find out.
"Mr. Hamil, can people live without love?"
I guess we're done.
Is there anything you want?
Is there anything I want?
I really need you as a writer.
Tell me.
What can I do to publish your next book?
"Instead of answering my question,"
"he took a sip of mint tea, which is good for one's health."
We're here.
I know you're not sleeping.
"He looked at me without saying a word."
Get out.
I don't want to.
"He probably thinks I'm still too young..."
"and there are many things in the world I'd better not know."
Hurry up and do it.
What?
Okay.
- I'm leaving. - No, wait.
I'll do it.
"Mr. Hamil, why aren't you answering me?"
"Mr. Hamil, can people live without love?"
Is this...
what you wanted?
Yes.
This means everything to me.
"'Yes, ' he said."
("All My Firsts", A Novel by Cha Yun Taek)
(To my love)
"He lowered his head, looking embarrassed."
"I burst into tears."
Welcome.
Come on in.
Thanks for coming all the way here.
We could have talked on the phone.
I thought it'd be better to talk in person.
Well...
Apparently, my daughter happened to pass by your bookstore recently.
She says your bookstore is doing very well...
and we shouldn't have given away that house to you.
We recently held a public event,
and it attracted quite a few people.
That must have given her the wrong idea.
If you're unhappy with the situation,
I'll start paying rent this month.
Forget it.
Come with me to my study.
Pardon?
If you're unhappy with the situation,
I'll start paying rent this month.
Forget it.
Come with me to my study.
- Pardon? - Come on.
I knew he'd do that.
He wants to show off.
Show off what?
His books.
Since he heard that the young man from the bookstore was coming over,
he has been organizing his antique books all day.
I see.
Does someone play the piano?
Yes.
I do.
Really?
I recently started.
It's quite fun.
I see.
Are you familiar with "Deer", a collection of poems by Baek Seok?
Yes.
Only 100 copies were ever printed,
so they were very rare.
("Deer", Baek Seok)
Is this...
Even the poet Yun Dong Ju failed to get his hands on it...
and had to transcribe it by hand.
How did you...
I have my ways.
It might just be an unofficial copy.
Still, it made me so happy. I couldn't put it down for a while.
(A Pitch-dark Night)
"The lights in the room are out."
"The white clothes hanging from the rack..."
"look distant and cold."
"I hear the sound of horse bells from the northwest."
"I open the door. The night sky is pitch-dark."
"There is a scent of pine mushrooms in the air."
Don't worry about...
what my daughter said.
Still...
I'm glad you turned the house I abandoned...
into a bookstore.
Yes, but...
I raised her with love.
But that doesn't mean a thing once money is involved.
Everything in the world changes.
Everything changes and leaves.
Your children are no exception.
But books are different.
While containing so much,
they rarely change.
Keep your bookstore going.
I told you from the start you could do whatever with the house...
as long as you use it as a bookstore.
Yes.
That's right.
- I had a great time today. - Oh, me too.
Where are you headed too?
I have to get back to work.
- I see. - Don't forget to have lunch.
- We can see each other again. - Okay, I'll see you later.
Okay.
- Have a good day. - Goodbye.
Well, well. Hello there, my friend.
My friend who is older than me.
- What? - What were you doing just now?
What do you mean? Why?
I knew you'd deny it.
What? Deny what?
Will you still deny it after seeing this?
Say something, my friend.
My friend who is much older than me.
Well, Hwi...
I was just briefly saying hi.
- Is that so? - Yes.
I bumped into an old friend of mine.
Oh, so if you bump into an old friend on the street,
you smile warmly with a bashful look...
and shake their hand?
Jang Woo, I didn't know that about you.
Just give me that.
How...
How could you be so mean?
You're not like your brother at all.
You're quick to catch on.
Unlike Eun Seop, you know.
Come on, my friend.
I even pay 10 dollars for information...
Kwon Hyun Ji brings me.
Goodness, seriously.
Gosh, Jang Woo. I was just asking for 10 bucks.
Thank you!
Thank you, and I'll treat you like my brother for the next few days.
That's gross, so just call me Jang Woo.
Really? Send!
No, don't send it...
I'll be really grateful if you delete that.
Shall I delete it then?
How could you...
Why aren't you at school?
It's lunchtime, so I'm taking a stroll.
You should be in the cafeteria eating lunch then.
Come on, you weren't eating at work either...
and wearing that goofy smile over here.
That's because I came here briefly for lunch...
So you know it's the same thing, my friend.
My friend who is much older than me.
Well, I should get going since I'm busy.
Take care, my friend. Bye.
Hurry up and go. Get going.
Didn't you...
just tell me to go?
Oh, I was telling you to drop me off at school and go.
Jang Woo, I'm in a hurry, so let's go.
My lunchtime is almost over. Or maybe it's already over.
Do you want to see me receive penalty points?
Do you know how many penalty points I received lately...
because of Eun Seop's "The Catcher in the Rye"?
Let's go then.
I don't have much time either.
Let's go, my friend.
Hwi, why are you so heavy?
Just keep pedaling, my friend.
Why do you have such weak legs for a man?
You know that day...
The day...
when I got on the Mugunghwa train.
I really wanted to die that day.
That's how I felt back then.
(A murderer's daughter sits here.)
Waking up in the morning and going to school...
felt so miserable back then.
- Hey. - Come on.
I was pondering how I should die...
And then...
I decided to go to a station near a river.
I was going to go there and die.
But...
it felt like I wouldn't die if I just walked in.
I was thinking if I should put some rocks...
inside my pockets.
But I suddenly felt so hungry.
Fine. Then shall I eat one last meal before dying?
But after I finished eating,
I felt sleepy.
Then shall I take a quick nap?
The whole day went by like that...
and something came to mind.
Right, I'll never die at this rate.
No.
I must die.
I must die. I'll die...
and make everyone who bullied me regret it.
Hey, Mok Hae Won!
Mok Hae Won!
Come back!
Ouch, that hurts.
Hey, Mok Hae Won!
You brat! Hey, Mok Hae Won!
How did...
Mok Hae Won.
It still puzzles me.
How did my aunt know I was there?
Is that why you decided not to die?
Yes.
If you want to die,
I will die with you.
What are you saying?
Let's die together. My mom is dead too anyway.
Come on, seriously.
Why? Are you scared?
The thought of wanting to die suddenly vanished.
It felt like...
my aunt would keep nagging me even when I was dying.
I'm glad you lived.
Thank you for not dying, Hae Won.
Tell me.
Tell me, Eun Seop.
Tell you what?
About us.
Is this love?
I want to hear your answer.
Yes.
It is love.
I feel the same way.
(Hodu House)
Gosh, you scared me.
What's up?
Hey, how much of the novel have you written so far?
What is this about?
How much have you written so far?
Look, mister.
It hasn't even been three days yet.
Hey, what kind of crazy chief editor...
shows up at an author's place and harasses her...
just a couple of days after signing a contract with her?
Are you losing your mind?
You must have the opening sentence figured out.
Oh, the opening sentence?
You have it, right?
The opening sentence... I did write something.
Don't tell me you came all the way here to talk to me about that.
I sure did. I came all the way here to talk to you about it.
You must have a lot of time on your hands, Crybaby.
My editors do all the work. All I do is sign things off,
so I don't have much to do. You know?
Really? That's great.
What do you mean?
You know Sun Yeong, right?
Yes, Choi Sun Yeong?
Right, she's dying.
What?
She has metastatic breast cancer.
It has spread all over, so she can't even get chemotherapy.
She has less than a month left to live.
Hey, you're talking as if she's a complete stranger to you.
I'm not the one going through it.
She was living in Seoul, but she wanted to die here,
so she's at the university hospital now.
I have to go see her.
Give me a ride to the hospital.
Come on. Unlock the door.
Hey.
I'm tired because I drove all the way here.
Can't you drive?
No, I can't. I don't drive.
Why not? You used to be a good driver.
Nonsense. Anyway, let's go.
My gosh, this is what happens when I'm not around?
- It's huge. - Oh, my.
Look.
Hey.
Look at this one going bald.
I almost didn't recognize him.
- What? - My gosh!
- Look who's here! - Cha Yun Taek!
Hi, Sun Yeong.
Hey, she likes peaches.
Really?
- What? - Well, you know.
You two look quite lovely together.
- What are you saying? - Oh, that's expensive.
- Hey. - What?
What's up?
I heard your family has a bookstore.
Yes. By the way, I got a new saddle for my bike.
I'm so fast now.
If you see me riding my bike, you'll be very surprised.
Hey, hold on.
I want to go there.
- Gosh, this is... - I actually know where it is,
- It's awesome. - but I don't want to go alone.
And more importantly...
Did you hear what I said?
What?
I want to check out your family's bookstore.
I actually...
So? What is it? What have you got for me?
Young Soo likes books.
What?
I heard there's a book club.
What's with you?
No, you can't come.
Don't come. If you come, you're dead.
Actually, you can come.
- What? - As long as you keep...
your end of the bargain.
You must be tired.
A little.
Go upstairs and get some rest.
I'll stay here.
No, it's okay.
Go on. You must be exhausted from all the driving.
Get some sleep.
All right.
- Go on. - Okay.
What?
I have to do something. There are so many books here.
I need to organize these.
Let's see.
What?
Nothing.
Hey, Eun Seop.
Yes.
I want to sleep with you.
What did you say?
I said I want to sleep with you.
Well...
Then I'll...
Is this what I'm supposed to do?
Yes.
If this is love,
I wish you could tell me.
Tell me not to leave.
Ask me to stay by your side forever...
like the perpetual snow that never melts.
- Hey, Yun Taek. - Yes?
You're so good-looking now.
Gosh.
Did I look that lame back in the old days?
Yes.
Why ask? You know the answer, Crybaby.
- "Crybaby". - "Crybaby".
Okay, fine.
Bye, guys.
We won't walk you out.
I'll see you again soon, Sun Yeong.
It was nice seeing you.
- By the way... - Yes?
It's been bothering me.
What are those bruises on your face?
What?
Do you get shots on your face too?
Why is your face bruised?
Oh, these?
I bumped into a wall.
Right, Su Jeong?
Yes, that's right.
I was pushing her wheelchair the other day, and... Right?
It was an accident.
I bumped only slightly, but I ended up with all these bruises.
It's true.
Choi Sun Yeong.
Does her husband still hit her?
She's dying.
Why doesn't she divorce that jerk? What's holding her back?
I really don't understand.
Could this be...
what she thinks?
Since her husband doesn't hit her all the time,
- she just puts up with him. - What?
Honey, look at this.
What do you think?
When he's not hitting her...
It's pretty.
Right?
- Where's Hae Won? - She'll be here soon.
I prepared bulgogi for Hae Won...
and rice balls for you.
I hope this is enough.
Maybe I should have prepared more.
It'll be fine.
Okay.
He might be the sweetest and warmest person there is.
What?
Why would you get so upset?
You don't remember what you said earlier?
It wasn't meant for you!
You little...
"Yes."
"It's just that he lost his temper for a moment."
Honey, I'm really sorry.
I must have been out of my mind. Gosh.
Honey, forgive me this once.
It'll never happen again.
I'm so sorry, Myeong Ju.
"Look how desperately he begs for forgiveness."
She must tell herself that and keep forgiving him.
She holds on to false hope.
In the end, he breaks his promise.
He goes back on his word and hits her again.
He lost his temper for a moment?
Anyone can get angry, but they hold back.
If he can't hold back his anger, why should she put up with him?
You're right.
Even if he only hits her occasionally, he still hits her.
He's a warm person?
Does that make sense?
No, it doesn't.
How could she...
What does she see in him?
I feel sorry for him.
You married him because you felt sorry for him?
No.
I married him because he was nice to me.
Nicer than anyone else.
But he hits you.
Yes.
But I feel sorry for him now.
Come to your senses.
Hae Won will soon realize what's going on.
Before that, you should...
I feel sorry for him.
Auntie, hurry up!
Honey, hurry up!
Idiot.
Pull over.
- Here? - Yes.
Thanks.
I really feel sorry for him.
I couldn't leave him.
It's just that he hits me when he gets angry.
I could never leave him.
If I did,
who would want to be with him?
See you tomorrow.
See you.
- Bye. - Bye.
(Strategies to Increase Resident Satisfaction)
- Excuse me, Jang Woo. - Yes?
I hear you went on a blind date during the lunch break.
How did you know that?
Goodness, don't you know how people here are?
I'm pretty sure...
our manager knows what I had for lunch today by now.
So? How did it go?
Well, I'm not sure...
Did you like her?
How did it go? Did it go well?
Well, she did seem like a nice person.
You must be surprised if you didn't know about this.
Well, to tell you the truth, this isn't the first time.
- Have some cake. - No, thanks.
I'm on a diet these days.
- You're on a diet? - Yes.
If you're a civil servant, what are your hobbies?
- Pardon? - All the civil servants I know...
seem to have a hobby or two.
It must be a real drag...
sitting in the office all day.
How do you like your job?
Don't you think it's boring?
It must be pretty tedious.
No?
I don't know how to explain,
but I don't really seem to be attracted...
to women I meet on blind dates.
I get what you mean.
Still, that's a shame. I hear she's pretty.
How do you know that? Did someone take pictures or something?
We have our ways.
So what type of girl do you like, Jang Woo?
- Me? - Yes.
Are you interested in anyone?
This looks delicious.
- That's beef tenderloin. - Beef tenderloin?
Well...
I guess I like girls who have pretty smiles...
and love to eat.
Girls who love to eat and have pretty smiles?
That's too hard.
Is it?
- Go back to work. - Okay.
Go back to work.
That's too bad.
Goodness.
You know,
what are the sparkles of light called...
when the sunlight reflects off the surface of lakes?
"Sun glitter".
Poor thing.
I should have died instead.
I want to shine like that too.
I should've died instead.
Pull yourself together. You're the chief mourner.
I deserve to die instead.
Even after death.
I should've died instead...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
How dare you?
Let go of me.
Let go. How dare you?
How dare you do that to me?
Let go.
Let go!
Let go, you wench.
Hey. How dare you do that to me?
Tell me. How could you?
Come here.
Let go of me!
How dare you? Let go.
How dare you? Say something.
Let go. Let go!
How dare you!
Hey! How dare you?
Who are you to hit my sister?
- Move! - How dare you? Hey!
Get out of my way!
- No. No! - Come here!
- Let go! - No! Myeong Yeo.
- Stop it. - How dare you?
- Please, don't. - Let go of me.
You wench!
Darn it! You little...
Darn!
Hey!
My sister was beaten from time to time.
By her husband, who was so friendly and warmhearted.
Get a divorce.
Get a divorce!
You don't deserve to live with a scumbag like that!
Myeong Ju, get a divorce. You don't deserve...
No, no!
Come here.
- What did you just say? - No!
I'll teach you a lesson...
No!
Myeong Yeo.
Let's go. Let's get out of here.
Hey!
Stop! Get over here!
Hey! Get over here.
You can't go anywhere! Come out!
My story starts from here.
This is the first sentence of my novel.
You know, Eun Seop...
Never mind.
What were you about to say?
It's nothing. Next time.
(Good Night Bookstore)
(Chief Editor Cha Yun Taek)
("The Fog and The Forest")
(Bestselling author Shim Myeong Yeo's "An Empty Field")
(Sign contract with Shim Myeong Yeo, Meeting with Shim Myeong Yeo)
Hey.
Who do you think is the one...
who killed my brother-in-law?
(Hey. Who do you think is the one who killed my brother-in-law?)
(Thanks to Seo Tae Hwa and Lee Seo An...)
(for their special appearance.)
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(I was the son of a vagrant who lived in a mountain...)
(and one day, I was abandoned.)
(And I was raised by my adoptive parents.)
(Although I don't think of that as a weakness, )
(some people expect me to be hurt by it.)
(Why aren't you miserable?)
(Weren't you the boy who lived in a cottage in the mountains?)
(Wasn't your father a vagrant?)
(Do I have to live a miserable and sad life as they want me to?)
(I thought about it long and hard, and the answer was no.)
(I realized there's no reason to be miserable...)
(when I feel grateful to so many people.)
(Anyhow, it's all in the past now.)
(When the Weather is Fine)
I'm sleepy. I want to keep looking at you.
- Ji Eun Sil? - I want to ask you something.
Can I?
He's a new member of our book club.
Let's give him a big hand!
What is this? Explain.
I mean the fax you sent me last night!
Did you come to return that?
It's just an excuse. To be honest, I liked you.
I liked you first.
For a very long time.
I'm in trouble now.
I don't think I'll forget this for the rest of my life.