(All characters, places, companies,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
I didn't know it only took an hour-long hike to see this view.
It's beautiful.
To be honest,
I can't seem to look you straight in the eyes.
All I have to do is accept the fact...
that you don't like me.
But it's so hard for me.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
You were such a warm person.
You were so warm to me.
I guess that's why I suspected about your feelings for me.
But I won't do that anymore.
Since you told me not to, I won't suspect anything.
I really won't.
But Eun Seop...
Never mind. Let's go.
Who... are you?
If I told you...
that I have always loved you...
from that moment until now,
what kind of expression would you wear?
(Episode 9: The Secret of the Boy Who Hated Dung Beetles)
Hold my hand.
I like you.
Then...
I'll call you when I arrive in Seoul.
Okay.
You should get back.
Bye.
- Auntie, you're back. - Where have you been?
Gunbam!
Gunbam.
Where are you going?
Gunbam, you're so adorable.
Come here.
You bit me? That's okay. You can bite me again.
Gunbam, you're so handsome.
Who said you look shabby when you're this handsome?
I'll teach that person a serious lesson.
But...
But the thing is, Hae Won...
All warm, sweet things...
made me anxious.
I was worried that the precarious moment of happiness...
might vanish in a flash.
About yesterday...
Drive safe.
- Hello. - Hi.
I'm so busy today.
Let's go.
Hey there!
Hey.
- Be safe. - Thank you.
The road is covered with ice.
I brought you coffee. Here, have some coffee.
It's very cold today, isn't it?
Here I come!
Oh, no.
Gosh, that hurts.
Gosh, my dear saddle. Be better, please.
What's wrong with you these days?
Snap out of it, okay?
Gosh.
Hae Won.
You seem to be in a good mood.
Yes. Why wouldn't I be?
By the way,
why did you suddenly start cooking?
What?
You've been cooking these days.
Just eat. I'm doing it for an important reason.
Hello?
Oh, I see.
The electrical repair technician.
Then could you come next week?
Yes, someone will be here.
Thank you.
Eun Seop, you haven't been here for a while, right?
Yes, it's been about a year.
There are many new releases as the new year has just begun.
As you know, it's when books are the most popular.
Right.
Oh, the editor-in-chief asked me.
About what?
Your book.
Do you really have no interest in publishing it?
Not yet.
Why not? Is the manuscript not ready yet?
I heard it's ready to be submitted.
I don't feel the need to publish it...
because there are already so many great books in the world.
Come on. Don't think like that.
Your book, among all other great books,
will play its own role.
Maybe later on.
Come on. Just let us publish it.
I heard you've always dreamed of becoming a novelist.
Just hand over the manuscript, and your dream will come true.
Why hesitate?
Hold on.
The book you're looking for must be in another warehouse.
- I'll go find out. - Okay.
Every day, the sun rises and sets.
The same goes for life. There are bright days and dark days.
Some people...
have the sun shining on them all the time.
However, there are some who live in darkness all their lives.
Do you know what people are afraid of?
Losing the sun, that's been shining on me all along.
Having the light fade away...
and not being able to see the dazzling sun ever again.
It would've been better if I had never seen it.
I know the warmth,
and I've made the scrunched-up frown because of the dazzling sun.
That's why I'm afraid.
Still, Hae Won,
I like you.
Eun Seop!
Then...
I'll call you when I arrive in Seoul.
Out of the way!
Coming through!
Out of the way.
Hey! Young Soo!
Gosh, this is annoying.
That darn saddle.
It's killing me!
A heavy snow warning has been issued for Gangwon Province tomorrow.
Some areas are expected to receive more than 30cm of snow.
Be sure to prepare your facility for strong winds.
- Auntie, turn down the TV! - A drought warning has been...
(Good Night Bookstore)
When did you get here?
Just now.
I thought you took a train.
I did. I drove to the station...
and left my car in the parking lot there.
Oh, I see.
I'll be going now.
I have to head out soon.
- Where are you going? - Jang Woo is hosting an event,
and he insisted that I come.
I see.
Have fun.
Am I not allowed at the event?
What?
I mean, you're not asking me to come with you.
You can come too.
Go get ready. Let's go together.
No, I'm not coming.
Why not?
I don't want to.
- Hae Won. - Yes?
Come here.
I don't want to.
Come on.
What?
- Why are you picking a fight? - I'm not.
- You are. - Yes. I mean, no.
Come with me.
I don't want to.
Why not?
It's just that...
you seem to feel uncomfortable around me.
I do?
Yes.
It seems like you're regretting it.
I'm regretting what?
What happened in the mountains.
If you think it was a mistake,
that's fine with me. I don't want things to be awkward.
Don't worry about me.
It wasn't a mistake.
How can I believe that?
Let's do it again so you know it wasn't a mistake.
I thought you hated me.
No way.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
(A Meeting With Writer Shin Yeong Chun)
Hyecheon's afternoon culture event will begin shortly.
Everyone, please be seated.
- Hello. - Hello.
A cultural event for the citizens of Hyecheon,
An Afternoon in Hyecheon.
It's an honor to host "A Meeting With Writer Shin Yeong Chun".
Nice to meet you all.
All right.
Writer Shin Yeong Chun is famous for never showing her face in public.
You're all curious to see Shin Yeong Chun's face, right?
- Yes. - Yes!
It sounds like you're an audience for a TV show.
That being said,
if you would kindly allow us to hold onto your phones...
for a short moment,
Ms. Shin said she would be more than happy to show her face.
That's why we've prepared this surprise event.
There are so many people here.
I know.
- Wait. - What?
- All right. Let's bring out... - My aunt...
Writer Shin Yeong Chun to the stage.
Please give her a big round of applause.
(A Meeting With Writer Shin Yeong Chun)
When I heard the name Shin Yeong Chun,
I imagined it would be an old man.
- Me too. - Right?
By the way,
Mr. Cha, why didn't you...
introduce yourself?
Hello, I'm Cha Yun Taek, the chief editor of Dain Publishing.
- He's sexier than I thought. - He is?
Hello, were you all dying to see me?
- Yes! - Yes!
I can't hear you guys.
I'm the Shin Yeong Chun...
that you all wanted to see. It's nice to meet you.
(A Meeting With Writer Shin Yeong Chun)
Ms. Shim,
you went to the same university with Editor Cha Yun Taek, right?
Yes. Why do you ask?
It's nothing much.
By the time your book is published,
we heard he is publishing a book too.
Is he?
Every time he publishes a book,
he sells more than 50,000 copies. So we were wondering...
if you could tell us anything about it beforehand.
Oh, that publishing company...
published Shin Yeong Chun's novel lately, right?
Yes. It's only been two weeks, and it's a best seller.
Already?
I'm sure we'll sell even more copies.
Anyhow,
is it true Shin Yeong Chun and Cha Yun Taek are going out?
What? Shin Yeong Chun is a woman?
Yes, she's a woman.
And she's even young.
Shim Myeong Yeo.
Hey.
Oh. Hi, Min Jeong. Look at this.
Look at how much they left.
Isn't it such a waste? I told you we shouldn't have ordered these.
- What a waste. - I think I saw your friend.
My friend?
Oh, you mean Eun Seop? He came today.
- I wanted to say hi to him. - Right.
Well, why didn't you?
Did you see Eun Seop today?
- Yes. - Did you see who he came with?
Yes, he came with a really pretty girl.
Yes, Hae Won is pretty. She was really dressed up today.
It seemed like they were going out.
I guess it would be inappropriate to ask him to dinner.
They're going out?
No, no way.
They're not going out.
No, you can have dinner with him. They're not going out. No way.
Hold on.
Why do people always call me when I'm with you?
Who is it?
Yes, sir.
Oh, that noodle restaurant?
Yes, I know the place.
I'll be there right away.
Gosh, you seem like a new person.
Me?
You've aged quite a bit, Myeong Yeo.
Do you still cry often?
Do you still curse in public?
I heard you got divorced.
Yes, three times.
I envy your reckless life.
Reckless?
I loved all of my exes. What are you talking about?
What do you want? You're getting on my nerves already.
You visited Seoul recently, right?
I think I saw you in front of my house. Am I wrong?
Do you have eyes on the back of your head or what?
Haven't you ever thought your clothes are a bit unusual?
I just stopped by.
I heard so many rumors about how rich and successful you were,
so I just wanted to go see...
how big your house was.
It was really big. Do you pay rent?
No, I own the place.
Good for you, jerk. Tell me what you want.
Who will ask me
Are you going out now?
Yes. I'll see you later.
- Hold on. - What?
Wear a muffler.
- A muffler? - It's cold.
No, there's no need. It's fine.
It's not even cold. I'll be fine.
You're meeting the people from the mall, right?
Yes, I am.
Then you should tell them.
When...
someone goes missing in the mountains,
tell them to stop asking for Eun Seop.
Oh, that... That's...
Tell them.
You have to tell them...
so others won't ask for Eun Seop from now on.
But, still...
We already have the police and paramedics.
What do they need Eun Seop for?
Well, that is true, but...
Last time, when he suddenly disappeared,
do you know why he went to the mountain?
He said he saw that woman.
That woman?
Yes.
He saw an illusion of her and followed her.
He had no choice but to follow her.
How could that...
She's dead.
I know.
I was worried our son...
might be possessed by the mountain.
I felt scared.
Okay. I'll go tell them.
Really?
Yes, I'll go tell them today.
Thank you, Honey.
Don't worry about it.
You should wear a muffler.
There's no need. I might lose it.
I heard you're publishing a book.
So?
I'm publishing one too.
So what?
Your publishing company was trying so hard...
to find out the publishing date of my book. Did you know?
Since I'm here and all, I meant to ask you.
When are you publishing your book?
When you publish yours.
I've already finished writing the manuscript,
so I can publish it whenever I want.
Isn't that nice?
I'm going to publish it on the same date...
your book comes out.
Is this revenge?
What a cheap move.
You weren't as good as me at writing...
and no one acknowledged you during college.
I never imagined you'd get back at me like this.
You shouldn't be doing this...
when you own a house in the middle of Seoul.
How pathetic.
You were pathetic back then,
and you're still pathetic.
Then why don't you publish your book through our company?
What?
Your book. Let our company publish it.
I'll make sure it happens.
In return,
how about you write a novel based on your life...
since college?
How about it?
Okay?
There's an old saying that wise men...
relieved their hangovers by eating noodles.
Is that what that sign on the wall means?
It's nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you, but it's the first time we get to meet.
Me too. It's nice to meet you.
You take after your mother.
I do?
- We have different personalities. - I don't think so.
It seems similar to me.
Really?
- Watch out. - Oh, gosh. I'm sorry.
- Are you okay? - I'm okay.
- Hae Won has her charms and flaws. - Is that so?
Although I haven't met her mother...
Hey, look who it is. Aren't you Jang Woo?
Sir, hello.
Oh, boy.
- It's nice to see you. - Hello, sir.
- Hello. - It smells like alcohol.
It smells like I drank a lot of soju.
I haven't met Hae Won's mother...
By the way, how's your dad doing?
Oh, my dad? He's doing well.
Yes. Have a good time.
- Good to see you. - Me too.
What do I do? I'll reek of alcohol.
Guys, I guess I wasn't mistaken earlier, was I?
I mean, you two... What is going on here?
Gosh, must you ask?
Even this old man can tell...
that they'll probably get married soon.
My gosh, sir. Please.
Sorry?
Hey, man. What is going on?
What?
I can't believe you. You're really something.
Hey, just drink.
Don't mind them, okay?
Hey, so this is how that story ends?
"That story"? What story?
What do you think? The story of him falling in love with you.
Really?
Why? Do you want to hear it?
Oh, I'm curious too.
Don't be. He's just talking nonsense.
- Tell us. I want to hear it. - Hae Won.
I think the story begins with the Mugunghwa train.
Hey!
- Don't. - "Don't."
(Be Careful When Crossing)
(To Jecheon, Cheongnyangni)
(Stop)
The Mugunghwa train and the maple trees.
But to be honest, I don't remember exactly when that was.
Back then, I went to the train station very often.
I think...
it was the day when you ran away from home.
Hey, hurry up. Mr. Park is waiting.
Let's go.
Then is that when you first fell for me?
No.
Then when was it?
I had a crush on you a few times before that.
It was just one of those moments.
Hey, you scared me.
Hey.
Do you want this?
Give me your hand.
- I don't want this. - What?
I don't want this. Take it back. Now.
Hey.
Wait, hey!
(Bus Stop)
It's so cold.
What? Why?
Just because.
What do you mean?
I was just thinking...
What if you vanish all of a sudden?
There you are, Eun Seop.
There's a big commotion going on in the market.
What's going on?
- What? - Why are you two being like this?
- They're too loud. I can't drink! - What is the matter with you two?
- Enough, please. - What? Hey!
What's wrong with that?
Then what? Let her die?
Should we have let her die?
What's wrong with sending someone who could save her?
My son isn't invincible. He can get hurt too.
I told him to go up there because I knew he wouldn't get hurt.
And let's be honest. He's done it many times.
Why didn't you say anything in the past?
What's the problem now?
Okay, fine. When it's a person, I get it.
But last time, you called my son over and made him...
go into the mountains at night because you lost your dog.
That's just wrong!
What's wrong with asking him to help me find my dog?
- Gosh. - And he found my dog!
He got back safe and sound, so it's all good!
Okay, but what will you do if he gets hurt?
- If Eun Seop gets injured, - Goodness.
- who will save him? - Please don't fight.
You don't care because he's not your son.
Is my son the town servant or what?
- My son is also... - Goodness.
"My son"? Seriously?
Gosh, people will think that he's actually your son.
Break them up.
- Hey, please. - Don't say that.
What? It's true!
- Stop. - Everyone will think he's your son.
Goodness, even I had totally forgotten about it.
The fact that he's not your child.
Hey, enough.
Gosh, where did you even find that street urchin?
- Enough, seriously. - You...
- Father! - Gosh.
- Break them up. - Father!
My goodness.
- Hey, you're here. - Father, don't do this.
Let's go.
- Let's get out of here. I'm sorry. - Hae Won.
- Let's go. - Take your dad home.
- Let's get out of here. - Let's go.
Hey, we've known each other for 30 years.
- And you treat me like this? - You piece of...
- Gosh, Jong Pil. - Just get in the car.
- Go home, Jong Pil. - Get home safely.
I'm sorry, Hae Won.
All right.
Sorry.
What a disaster.
I feel like this happens once every few months.
How's Eun Seop's dad?
Is he okay?
Jang Woo, did you...
Don't say anything to your dad.
When he told me he was heading out to meet up with those friends,
I egged him on...
to tell them not to make you climb the mountains again.
I won't say anything.
Thanks.
Was it when I was in 2nd or 3rd grade?
One day, out of the blue,
an aggressive kid appeared at school.
That was Eun Seop.
What are you doing? Let's go play soccer.
Oh, right.
Apparently, that kid was brought to town by a wolf.
People were saying...
he used to live in the mountains and was raised by animals.
Let's go. Hurry up!
- Hey! - Why did they say those things?
- There's a fight going on. - Let's check it out.
Break them up! Hey, we should break them up!
- What are you talking about? - Break them up!
- What should we do? - That must hurt.
My mom said...
- your dad is a hobo. - No, he isn't.
She said you were abandoned by animals.
You're a street urchin!
No, that's not true!
Eun Seop's real father was...
a vagrant living in the mountains.
A vagrant living in the mountains?
Yes.
So that's why...
Yes, that's why.
What happened to Eun Seop's real father?
Well... I guess he died.
I don't know exactly.
As you know, Eun Seop never talks about those things.
I've never seen a wooden headstone.
Do you know whose grave is this?
"Kim Gil..."
The story about the wolf's silver eyelash...
This grave belongs to the person who told me that story.
Dad!
I want a new bike that can speed up to 80km per hour.
I need to ride real fast.
Or please at least change my saddle.
My bottom hurts so much these days. Dad!
What are you staring at?
Oh, right.
You had it with you?
I've been taking other people's wallets for the past 18 years,
but I've never seen anyone like you.
You don't even look for your wallet.
Next time, tell me beforehand.
Gosh.
Is that...
your dad?
I mean, he looks a bit like you.
Eun Seop.
Why don't you throw that picture away?
What?
You're carrying around a picture of someone I don't know.
It makes me jealous.
You're jealous?
Hey.
I'm serious.
Okay.
What's with you? Have you lost your mind? Gosh.
Dad, there's something wrong with Eun Seop!
He laughs to himself these days.
What's with him? That ugly fool.
Did I ever tell you?
That I...
used to be really happy.
Daddy, hurry up!
Kid, you're way too fast.
I can't keep up with you anymore.
Hey, a boar appeared.
Where?
Just kidding.
Daddy.
Today, I'll teach you how to chop wood. Let's go.
- Really? - Yes. Today,
you're finally going to become a man.
It's cold. Put on your jacket.
Let's go. Let's do this.
Daddy!
I caught a beetle.
Daddy?
And then one day,
all my happiness...
suddenly disappeared.
This moment
Now that you're getting washed up,
you look so handsome.
What's your name? What do you want to eat?
What should I make for you?
- Do you want some tteokbokki? - Gosh, it's cold.
- Almost all the stores were closed. - My goodness.
Close the door. The boy will catch a cold.
I hope they fit him.
- Goodness. - My gosh.
I should have come with you.
They will do for tonight.
We can go to bigger stores tomorrow.
I would have expected to become unhappy right away,
but I didn't, which made me even more anxious.
So...
I ended up fearing...
all the happiness in the world.
How come you're not afraid to go into the woods at night?
Do you see all the trails or something?
I know the place like the back of my hand.
I know it very well.
Never come up here again.
Even if I...
never come back.
You can't come up here.
Where did you even find that street urchin?
- Enough, seriously. - Hey, come on.
- Enough, seriously. - You...
Father!
- Father! - My goodness.
"The boy who used to get hurt by people all the time..."
"started watching people..."
"through the wolf's silver eyelash."
(Bukhyeon-ri, Downtown Hyecheon, Seohyeon Village)
"To find real people..."
"in this world filled with fake people."
"But the boy saw no real people..."
"in this world."
"The boy was lonely."
"He couldn't trust anyone."
People will...
always try to deceive you.
So we have to read their faces...
and find out what's really on...
their minds.
Why will...
people try to deceive us?
In this world,
there is no such thing...
as real people.
No.
You were wrong, Eun Seop.
Hi, Hae Won. I'm Lim Hwi.
I look nothing like him, but I'm his sister.
Why did you call Eun Seop here?
- You know how he is. - Calm down.
Honey, calm down.
(Good Night Bookstore)
(Books)
You were wrong, Eun Seop.
That story about the boy with the wolf's silver eyelash.
You said...
that boy...
eventually fails to find the village with real people.
But you were wrong.
The boy finds that village in the end.
And he lives...
happily ever after in that village.
Just like you right now.
You were...
that boy.
that boy too.
You were as cold as me.
Then you know what?
I'll hug you from now on.
Can you hug me as tightly as you can too?
So what we have won't suddenly disappear.
So it won't melt away in a short moment.
Can you come to me...
and hug me...
so I can hug you too?
So we can stay warm like this forever.
Can you hug me, Eun Seop?
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(If I think about it,)
(the Mugunghwa train was where it all started.)
(It was an early autumn morning, and there were maple trees.)
(She was standing there.)
(Where the morning train had come to a stop.)
(How could I not fall in love?)
(Actually, my history with Irene goes way back.)
(When I was about ten, I bumped into her once.)
(I thought Irene was a boy back then.)
(That's right.)
(We might've been together in many more pages than we thought.)
(When the Weather is Fine)
Why is he looking for you?
He's probably asking where Eun Seop is.
He may have already been to the bookstore.
You better come to your senses.
I'm your real family.
Are you going to sign the contract or not?
Winter will be over soon.
Didn't you say you'd go back in spring?
Still, I can't send him away.
Hwi told me you're leaving this place soon.
Mom, Eun Seop ran away!
Eun Seop will be leaving.
To somewhere very far away.