(All characters, places, companies,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
Wow.
- Goal! - Goal!
Good job.
Honey.
Isn't it heavy? Give it to me.
I told you to bring me with you.
Let's go home and make something nice.
Myeong Ju.
Hey, you're here.
Dad!
Yes, Hae Won.
- Are you having fun? - Yes.
Auntie, come on.
Honey, come on.
Darn you.
How dare you? How dare you do that to me?
You wench.
How dare you?
Say something. How dare you do that?
Let go. I said let go.
Let go!
Let go of me! How dare you?
How dare you?
Hey! How dare you?
Who are you to hit my sister?
- Move! - How dare you? Hey!
What do you know?
- No. No! - Come here!
- Let go! - No! Myeong Yeo.
- Stop it. - How dare you?
- Please, don't. - Let go of me.
You wench!
Darn!
Get a divorce!
Get a divorce.
You don't deserve to live with a scumbag like that!
Myeong Ju.
Get a divorce. You don't deserve...
No, no!
Let go of her!
- What did you just say? - No!
I'll teach you a lesson...
No!
- Oh, no. - Hurry.
Get out now!
- Myeong Ju. - I said get out!
Get out! Darn it!
Shim Myeong Ju, get out of the car!
Don't open the door!
- Myeong Ju. - Don't let him in!
Get out!
I told you to get out!
Hey!
- You darned... - No!
Have you lost your mind?
No!
Myeong Ju.
Hello?
911, right?
There's been an accident.
Yes, that address is correct.
Yes, just now.
Right.
Gosh.
Yes.
No...
Hey.
Gosh.
Listen carefully.
Ju Hong is dead.
No.
He is dead. I checked.
I killed him.
No! No, you didn't.
What?
Myeong Yeo.
Do you have cash on you?
No, I don't. I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
Then,
get out of here and take the bus.
We're on the outskirts, so there are no security cameras.
But I'm sure there are some in your area.
Your neighborhood is by the main road, you know?
Walk home and make sure...
you're not caught on any of the cameras.
Okay?
Myeong Yeo!
Shim Myeong Yeo, snap out of it!
Myeong Yeo.
You should hurry. Right, your shoes.
Myeong Yeo, here.
Hey, wear my shoes.
Wear my shoes, Myeong Yeo!
Myeong Yeo.
- Myeong Ju. - Yes.
It's okay, Myeong Yeo.
When you get home, take a shower.
Nothing happened.
It's okay. Everything will be okay.
You're okay.
- It's okay. Nothing happened. - Myeong Ju...
- Go on. - Myeong Ju, he's...
- Hurry! Come on. - Myeong Ju.
Just go home.
Hurry home, Myeong Yeo.
Myeong Yeo.
I told you to hurry. Go.
- Hurry, go. - Myeong Ju.
Take a shower and a nap.
By the time you wake up, you'll get a call.
Hello?
Yes, hello.
This is Investigator Gu Hyeon Tae at Paju Police Station.
Is this Ms. Shim Myeong Yeo?
Yes.
I see. I'm calling because...
Ms. Shim Myeong Ju is your sister, right?
Yes.
Well, her husband, Mr. Mok Ju Hong,
passed away.
The police will call you and tell you that Ju Hong is dead...
and that they're investigating me as a suspect.
The thing is, your sister...
Defendant Shim Myeong Ju...
is sentenced to seven years in prison.
- What? - Just seven years?
She killed her husband.
If I get arrested now,
I'll say I was running away from my abusive husband,
so I can be released quickly.
But in your case, it'll be different.
You'll have to spend...
the rest of your life in prison.
So you should...
just leave.
Look after Hae Won, who will be left all alone.
(Episode 12: A Confession)
I'm in trouble.
Why?
This sight.
I don't think I can forget it for the rest of my life.
I'm sleepy.
But I want to keep looking at you.
Hey, Eun Seop.
Yes, I'm sleepy.
Really?
Then sleep.
What were you going to say?
Nothing.
Come on. What?
Nothing. I'll tell you another time.
Mom. Mom!
Mom.
Mom...
- Mom... - Why didn't you come sooner?
Your mom kept waiting for you.
Mom...
I pity her daughter the most.
What did you say?
I said...
I'll live here from now on and look after Hae Won.
You know,
writing novels...
is so lame.
Mom.
I'm not as talented as I thought.
You're not talented?
No.
I'm not.
I'm not talented at all.
So...
I think I'll spend the rest of my life here...
with you and Hae Won...
Hang in there.
I told you it's not your fault.
Myeong Ju.
If it weren't for me,
none of this would've happened.
Don't cry.
Go home now.
Start writing novels again.
Go on dates too.
And...
Hae Won.
Spend...
a lot of time with Hae Won.
She must be...
lonely.
Myeong Ju.
Myeong Yeo.
I'm...
really...
(From Shim Myeong Ju)
(I'm fine.)
Hey.
(My first love letter to you)
(Good Night Bookstore)
Why are you coming out of there?
Gosh, you startled me.
This early in the morning?
Well...
You're a grown-up,
so I guess it's none of my business.
Where were you?
A friend of mine died.
I see.
I'm tired.
Can we skip breakfast today?
Of course.
I could make you something too.
Don't bother.
Hey, I hear...
they...
loved your cello performance.
Who said that?
Su Jeong did.
She says it was phenomenal.
She's exaggerating.
I wonder who has taken away all our hedgehog's spines.
What? What does that mean?
A hedgehog? What?
It's a poetic expression.
Go inside.
Okay.
It's cold. Don't be too long.
("Traveling After a Breakup")
Hae Won!
Hae Won, come on!
Okay.
Come on. Hurry up.
Hey.
What are you so happy about?
What's that? Dried seaweed?
It's a picture of stars.
- Stars? - S-T-A-R-S.
I know that. Do you know who I am?
I'm an AN.
What does that even mean?
You don't know?
It means an "astronomy nerd". I love astronomy.
Okay.
Stars make me so excited.
- They're amazing. - You're crazy.
What about you?
What were you so happy about?
Hey, look at this.
It means a lot to me.
I guess she means a lot to you.
What?
- She's pretty. - No.
It's not her.
She's not the one I'm talking about.
Then?
- Have another look. - Okay.
You have to look closely.
That's her.
I see.
- She's pretty too. - Right? She really is.
But the thing is...
She looks even prettier when she eats.
- I love her bangs. - Right? They're pretty.
She has a good sense of style.
By the way, what's the big deal about stars?
- Do you know all the names too? - Yes.
Do you look at these all day?
Yes.
Mr. Cha.
Just leave it here.
The person you are trying to reach is unavailable.
(Hey. Who do you think is the one who killed my brother-in-law?)
(Crybaby)
(19 missed calls from Crybaby)
What do you mean by that?
It's nothing.
Okay, whatever.
By the way,
you look pretty good in plain clothes.
I wear these all the time.
You look nice. Is it because of your broad shoulders?
I've never heard that before. I have broad shoulders?
Yes, wide as the Pacific Ocean.
Didn't you say you don't like me?
I don't. That's all in the past.
But did you just say that I look nice?
Young Soo.
Just because I don't like roses,
does it change the fact that they're beautiful?
No. Roses will always be beautiful.
Whether I like them or not.
This is the same thing.
You have broad shoulders and look good in plain clothes.
What can I do when you're that charming?
Although I liked you in the past,
you still look good in the present.
What can I do?
Is the bookstore far from here?
Yes, so you better keep up with me.
An afternoon book club gathering? It feels unusual.
It does.
Su Jeong, are you feeling sick?
Your face looks pale.
No, I'm fine.
I guess we're all here.
- Yes, shall we begin then? - Yes.
Guys, I'm a member too.
- Right, I forgot about Hwi. - Excuse me.
Oh, my gosh. Hwi, this is unbelievable.
You brought him? Did you hunt him down or what?
What are you talking about? What do you take me for?
Hey, I mean Young Soo. Come on in.
You came here voluntarily, right?
- Who are you? - Oh...
He's a new member of our book club. Let's give him a big hand!
- Give him a big hand! - Welcome.
Say hi to Mr. Jeong behind you. Hello, sir.
Do you have a chair he can use?
- Eun Seop, a chair. - I think it's over there.
I'll go bring it.
- You can leave your bag there. - Okay.
Who are you?
Here.
- Thank you. - Eun Seop, why are you mad?
- What? - You look really mad.
I'm not mad.
"When we sat face to face..."
"smiling and talking in front of that tree,"
"our breaths,"
"our laughter,"
"and our stories were permeated in that tree."
"They were permeated so deeply."
"And even after we forget..."
"the fact that we smiled and talked..."
"below that tree,"
"every year in spring,"
"that tree..."
"will remember our laughter,"
"our breaths,"
"and our voices..."
"to produce fresh and green..."
"new leaves."
("When We Sit Face to Face")
"When We Sit Face to Face".
That poem really made my heart race.
Right.
My heart feels like that too, guys.
You do?
- Can't I feel that way too? - Seung Ho.
Eat this.
So what brought you here, Young Soo?
Oh, I heard he loves reading books.
He's the top student at our school...
and the unicorn of our school who even has a girlfriend.
He probably came here since he likes reading.
- Unicorn? - And also,
Hwi has a huge crush on him.
- But he's not interested at all. - Hey, but...
Can you speak in the past tense?
That's all in the past for me.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Unicorn Lee Jang Woo, a graduate of the 42nd class...
of Hyecheon High School. You really look...
smart like me. Is that why Hwi likes you?
No, wait. I said it's all in the past.
Do you not know the meaning of that?
But do you think...
Hwi really likes Young Soo because of his looks?
I'm not sure.
We do live in a world where looks count.
Wait, guys.
I said it's all in the past! The past.
Do you not know the meaning of "past"?
What are you talking about?
I really mean it.
Okay, if Hwi insists it's in the past...
It seems like she still likes him in the present.
No, no! It's in the past.
- It's past tense. - Is that so?
Do you mean you like him now?
- No, Jang Woo. - Or you liked him before?
- No... - So you like him now?
- No! - Eun Seop.
- I said, no. - Can I...
- borrow that book? - Is he your ideal type?
- What do you mean? - Sure.
I said that's not true, Jang Woo.
Goodness.
Eun Seop, what's with your face?
- Me? - Eun Seop, is something wrong?
- Eun Seop has a fever. - No, I don't.
- You're even sweating. - You look mad.
- He looks furious. - It's because he's hot.
He's hot?
So, as a unicorn of Hyecheon, what did you think...
of participating in today's book club gathering?
Right. Thanks to me, because of me, due to me, and because I allowed it,
how do you feel about participating in this amazing book club?
Well? Tell us. Why aren't you saying anything?
You guys can go first.
- Hello? - Hi, Jang Woo.
- Ji Eun Sil? - Yes.
Hey, it's so hard to talk to you on the phone.
Talk about some bad timing.
What do you mean?
Jang Woo.
If it's that bad, just hang up and go to a hospital.
- I'll hang up then. - No.
No, no. Why did you call?
The thing is, I want to ask you something.
Can I?
Yes, sure. Ask away.
I'm ready to listen. Ask me anything.
(Gyungpo Coffee Festival)
So you're holding a coffee festival in Gangneung...
Can you recommend a barista?
A famous barista?
Did you call me to ask me that?
Yes. Why?
Can't I ask you stuff like this?
Then I'll just ask someone else...
No! No, no. I'll find someone for you.
I can do it.
I knew it, Jang Woo.
Thanks, Jang Woo.
I promise to repay you one day.
- Hey, wait. - What?
You don't have anything else to say?
I don't.
But... Okay, enjoy your lunch.
What do you mean? It's 4pm.
Enjoy your lunch then.
Oh, all right. I'll have lunch.
I'll have... I'll have lunch now.
- Bye. - Bye.
Gosh, that was the first time talking to Eun Sil on the phone.
The weather is lovely.
"Eun Sil".
By the way, Young Soo...
(Bukhyeon Three-way Intersection)
Are you really, I mean currently...
first place in your school? For real?
Oh, me?
Well, I guess I am.
Oh, so there really are people who are the top of the whole school.
What shall I say? All this time, I thought...
You know, like the fox from the desert in "The Little Prince".
Like something that exists but is hard to believe.
Shall I say it's unrealistic?
Mr. Bae, he's really the top of our school.
- He's really smart. - By the way, Hwi.
Aren't you younger than him?
Yes, I am.
- But why... - Is she talking down to him?
It's probably because she likes talking down to people.
Bingo.
But why do you use honorifics to me?
Think about it carefully.
If I really used honorifics...
when I talked to you all this time.
Whether it's just a feeling or not.
If you think about it carefully,
maybe I was talking down to you all this time.
What are you talking about?
Young Soo, why do you smile whenever she says something?
Is it because you actually like Hwi?
I'm smiling because I'm dumbfounded.
Do you think what she says makes sense?
No, it doesn't.
Right.
Hold on. Guys.
You guys are already...
lost in my irresistible charm.
You got it?
Goodness, you guys are really...
- addicted to my charm. - Why isn't Jang Woo coming?
This is driving me nuts.
What?
Hey. Shim Myeong Yeo.
What...
What is this? Explain.
- Explain what? - The fax you sent yesterday!
You wanted to read the opening sentence.
What? That's why I sent it to you. What's your problem?
So is that it?
Yes, that's it. What, then?
Don't tell me you thought it was real.
Is that why you called me 34 times?
Like a crazy person?
"I will never ask you which parts are based on facts..."
"and which parts are fictitious." You said that yourself.
You said you won't ask which parts are fiction...
Hey.
It's not dark at all, right?
Yes.
Someone fixed this.
I wonder who did it.
Let's go.
When my aunt falls asleep,
I'll sneak out and come over.
Can you actually pull that off?
Yes, I sure can.
My aunt is actually dull-witted.
I'm serious.
She can't hear a thing when she has her blanket pulled over her head.
("Traveling After a Breakup")
You came to return that book?
You didn't have to come all the way here just to return it.
You should've just called so that I...
This is just an excuse.
Is everything well with Hae Won?
Yes.
You see,
I actually had a crush on you.
What?
For a very long time.
For...
a really long time.
I didn't know.
What if you knew, Eun Seop?
Nothing...
would've changed.
Really?
That's okay.
I knew you'd say that.
Thanks for the coffee. I should go.
(Good Night Bookstore)
(Books)
Hey, do you want to know something?
You know what?
I have a crush on someone.
Who is it?
The loner in our class who likes reading books.
I like him so much!
I liked you first.
Right, the fact that I had feelings for you for longer doesn't matter.
Hae Won.
- What? - What's going on?
- My gosh! - Good for her!
I want to get flowers too.
Hae Won was always the star.
Come on!
- My gosh. - How romantic!
- Hey. - Oh, my goodness.
- I'm so jealous. - Me too.
Even you, who was always at the edge of the frame,
had your eyes fixated on Hae Won.
You see,
I'm here too.
I exist too.
(Good Night Bookstore)
Like this.
Just like this, I also...
(Good Night Bookstore)
Hi, Jang Woo.
- Ji Eun Sil? - Yes.
Hey, it's so hard to talk to you on the phone.
Talk about some bad timing.
(Eun Sil)
Su Yeon in Class Two has a crush on you.
Gosh, cut it out. I have no interest in girls.
If you guys are going to keep dating girls...
and gossip like this, you won't get into college.
You get bad grades to begin with.
Sorry!
Hey!
Nice. It's mine!
- What's up? Checking out girls? - What?
- Me? - You said you had no interest.
That's right. I have no interest in girls whatsoever.
Hey.
I'm home.
It's cold outside.
Why are you still up? Go to bed.
(My first love letter to you, the 133rd post)
(Tonight, I want to take you to the cottage.)
"This is my first love letter to you."
(That day, through the window...)
"That day,"
"through the window,"
"I saw you looking as hurt as I was."
"I want to leave. But no."
"I shouldn't."
"I'd feel sorry."
"Forgetting all of that,"
"I ended up following you."
We will soon be arriving at Cheongdo Station.
Make sure you take all your belongings with you. Thank you.
"You got off the train at Cheongdo Station."
"Cheongdo is famous for its persimmon trees."
"The Nakdong River that runs across the city looked clear."
"I was scared..."
"you'd jump into the river."
Hello, Ms. Shim. This is Eun Seop, Lim Jong Pil's son.
Okay,
Myeong Yeo.
The thing is, I am out of town right now...
and was wondering if you had a moment.
No, the thing is...
(Campsite)
I'm almost there.
Sir, please speed up.
I'm driving as fast as I can.
What is she doing out here anyway?
"Even after calling your aunt,"
"I was still scared..."
"that you'd die."
"I was scared that you'd die."
Hey, Mok Hae Won!
Mok Hae Won! Come here!
- Hey! - It hurts!
Have you lost your mind?
What were you thinking?
"And that was..."
"probably our very first..."
"autumn trip together."
I managed to escape.
- Good job. - It was hard.
Auntie wouldn't go to bed.
I had to wait until she became quiet.
- What were you up to? - Nothing.
What is it?
- What were you doing? - Wait.
Why are you doing this?
- What is it? - It's nothing.
I feel hurt.
Well, I was ordering something online.
It's true.
Well...
I was ordering something.
- Then show me. - Wait.
Gosh.
- The thing is... - You hurt me.
I'm already hurt.
Hae Won, it's not what you think.
I get jealous easily.
When you chop wood,
your whole body should be relaxed, including your arms.
First, check the grain of the wood.
You want to cut the wood along the grain.
Look.
- Step back a little. - Okay.
That's not how you do it.
- I wanted to show you. - Okay.
- You're funny. - All right.
This is how you do it.
Like I said, check the grain of the wood first.
Here we go.
Well...
This is not sharp enough.
It's not sharp enough.
- Do you want to give it a try? - Me? Can I?
- Of course. - Are you sure?
It won't be easy.
I guess not. Even you failed.
I've tried it a few times at home for fun.
Just to vent my anger.
- This hand should go here. - Okay.
With your other hand, hold it closer to the bottom.
Aim it...
and hit.
But you swung it with a lot more force, didn't you?
- Do that once you get good at this. - Okay.
- Is this what beginners should do? - Yes, start just about this high.
All right.
Try.
- Like this... - Yes.
Was that okay?
How did you do that?
I just did what you told me to do.
- Really? - Yes.
Was this your first time?
But...
my shoulder hurts.
I think I used up all my energy. You do it for me.
Okay.
I showed you what you shouldn't do just now.
Now, I'll show you how it's really done.
I'm looking forward to it.
Go ahead.
- Watch. - Okay.
- You need to hold it up like this. - Okay.
I quit.
Eun Seop.
Eun Seop!
Hey!
(Rice Cake Mill)
It's an emergency!
Why are you already here?
Your order isn't ready yet.
Hey, did you hear?
Min Jeong went missing.
You know her, right?
You know, the girl who passed the civil service exam.
The third daughter from the house with the red roof?
Yes. Their daughter went missing.
I'm here, Mom.
- What do we do? - It's a total mess right now.
Jong Pil's son Eun Seop went there too.
Why did he go there?
You don't know? He used to...
live in the mountains.
So I guess they asked him to go and look for Min Jeong.
Gosh, I hope they find her.
I know, I'm so worried.
It's freezing outside.
Let's go over there and see if we can help.
- Let's go. - Shall we?
Why did you come here instead of going home?
- What? - Hang on.
Let's bring some coffee in a Thermos bottle.
Do you have any rice cakes we can bring?
How about some injeolmi?
(Good Night Bookstore)
What should I do?
What do you mean?
I like you so much.
What should I do?
What about you?
Me too.
(Good Night Bookstore)
It's true, Eun Seop.
Even people who seem small and insignificant have feelings too.
What do you want to drink?
- I'm going to get... - What's the matter?
- Well... - Is it something urgent?
Did something happen?
("Traveling After a Breakup")
Here.
Go on and take a look at it.
(Contacts)
(Lim Eun Seop)
I just...
want you to know.
I'll do anything...
by all means...
so you can...
- Let's do it. - I don't want to.
- Come on, just once. - No.
You really don't want to do it with me?
You said you're sick of that now.
No, I was lying.
You believed that?
- I don't want to. Move. - Come on, let's do it.
Come on!
(Kim Bo Yeong)
know how I feel.
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(This is my first love letter to you.)
(That day, through the window,)
(I saw you looking as hurt as I was.)
(I want to leave. But no.)
(I shouldn't. I'd feel too sorry.)
(Forgetting all of that, I ended up following you.)
(Cheongdo is famous for its persimmon trees.)
(The Nakdong River that runs across the city looked clear.)
(I was scared you'd jump into the river.)
(Even after calling your aunt, I was still scared that you'd die.)
(And that was probably our very first autumn trip together.)
(When the Weather is Fine)
Come and save me.
I'll be waiting.
- Is that you, Eun Sil? - What?
I heard you're going somewhere fun.
- What? - I'm going to go there too.
Irene was me?
Can you tell me how much you read?
Can you tell me that it's all a lie?
I lost hope.
I have nothing left now.
Goodbye.
I understand that you will leave this place someday.
I just hope you don't leave with a heavy heart.
I'm bracing myself for anything that can happen.